<Blog>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would be able to say that my night was a blast, but it was the afternoon that really intrigued me. I only went to 3rd hour today. Joce and I went to Starbuck's and talked awhile. We headed to Old Navy, and discovered that I'm now a size 6 not a 12. I told Max (ah... Max) that now that I've stopped eating I should stop sleeping. Not too worried about all this becoming a habit. It grows old, I get stoned, then end up eating everything in sight. I went to work, and work was work. Doing the look up on all these hosting sites is making me eager to learn code again. But I don't think I have enough patience to do it on my own ;-) One of Nick's hottttt friends stopped by. I thought they'd already left for Kettering today, oh well. This kid is a substitute teacher... hilarious.   And lyrics to end the night with a *sigh* I hear relief but I don't feel it.  ----Edited----  *deletes lyrics*  That would have been taken the wrong way....
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I realized why I can't remember half of my day. Because half of it was spent doing nothing.  I woke up and then headed to the store to try and get some homework done. Yeah... right. I printed off all my info on Masochist Artforms and Masochist performance Art. I still have to finish transferring notes to note cards, and the writing of my outline must be completed aswell.   Sebastian and I went to Riverside after I put a hold on the whole homework situation. I was great to chill at our old hang out and talk. Talking does a lot when you feel like shit. We made a new Blair Witch friend, Sebastian named him Billy. (Oww!! Carpal Tunnel Syndrome setting in... not fun) Billy is an alien who likes soccer and dancing, he has a dick growing out of his mouth. We left Billy at Frog Island though. And that was the highlight of my day.  I came home to my parking spot finally open and my brother pulling in beside me. Nick (a Kettering friend), Sara, and Eric cooked a dinner for Eric's girlfriend, which I contributed my wonderful meat sauce to, because apparently Eric and Nicole's family are on bad terms. I hope they enjoyed dinner.  At about 5:15 I dropped Sebastian off at his dad's house and then headed to A2 for some moping around the city. I made it a point to not waste the remaining money I had. I ended up driving back to the east side of A2 to get gas then headed back into the downtown area to chill at a coffee house and do homework. I had plans to hang out with Max but those fell through... not surprised. At 9pm I headed back to the parking structure and died halfway up the stairs to the 5th floor, cigarette in hand. I'm such a dumb bitch.   I did have a very unhealthy conversation... no... note that I left Max. I wouldn't be surprised if he never talked to me again. I just hope he's not like most of my old petty friends, by hiding behind a mask and never telling me until the end that he's using me or that I'm naive and dumb and need a life. Which would be the absolute truth. He's going through a lot, so I do understand how quiet moments are sometimes needed. Again, I'm a dumb bitch.   SomethingAshley: hey you SomethingAshley: you there? SomethingAshley: If you don't want to talk/hang-out/etc. with me ever again you can tell me you know? I may be imagining things but I'm pessimistic like that so you get the idea... SomethingAshley: but on the other hand by weird turn of events I do enjoy just hanging out with you. I enjoy more than just hanging out with you, but if you don't particularly feel that way for me (anymore?) that's alright. I just need to get out of the house and into some sort of a normal social life I guess...  SomethingAshley: and I'm really sick and tired of hanging around ignorant idiots that go to my school... Okay, I think I'm just trying to convey to you that you're a extremely great guy, and I care about you and all. But, in the past, I've usually been the girl that gets ditched or whatever, that's why I'm half expecting it this time.  SomethingAshley: At any rate... I guess I'll hopefully talk w/ you later. If not, I'm always here... :-)  I'M A DUMB BITCH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will sit here forever... and I do mean it. Or at least until I pass out from mental exhaustion.   And today was yet another day for happy moments to be catalogued in chronological order. Since it went by so fast I'll explain in incomplete thoughts.  Woke up. Sat on ass. Got off of ass. Listened to my mom bitch about break up. Dad walked in. Expected him to bitch about break up. Turned stereo down to talk to Dad. Dad turned stereo back up. Dad danced to Sunshine Underground. Looked at Dad weird. Dad does what Joce and I call, "Big Man Bounce." Dad does what Joce and I call, "Everybody Was Kung-Fu Fighting." Slammed head on keyboard a few times. Burned Dad CD w/ Sunshine Underground on it so he could dance somewhere other than my room. Dad left before receiving "Dad Mix." Threw on some Zero 7 because Dad hates it. Laughed. Went to work. Made sure Sebastian's shift was covered. Sebastian's shift was covered. Joce calls during "Gay Alex" conversation with 'Wrench.' Joce and I go to A2. Joce and I walk. Joce and I shop. Joce and I get coffee at Espresso Royale. Have expect Max to stumble in. Wonder if Max is dead. Assume Max is dead. Hope Max is dead. Wipe the dry-erase board in my head clean. Walk to parking structure. Get in car. Pinball Pete's. Have a blast. Talk herb. Head to Henrietta Fahrenheit. Buy nothing. Go to Mother Flechers. Haggle over price. Get what I want. LIKE A RHINESTONE COWBOY! Play taxi. Go to B's. B is perma-stoned. People passed out all over B's house. Leave "Dad Mix" at B's. Mom's walking the dog. Go to schooner Cove to meet up with Mom. Get a call. Mom says dog is in car. Mom is stoned. I am stoned. Sebastian's stoned. B is stoned. Girls on B's couch are stoned. Everyone is stoned. Go home. Change. Sebastian shouldn't work for a florist. Refuse to put horrendously ugly flower arrangement in my room. Leave it on dining room table. I LOOK HOT! Damn, I'm a sexy bitch. Purposely smuge the ?-mark on cheek. Drive to A2. Drive seems to take forever. Walk out of parking structure and into someone's student film. Walk to get coffee. Walk to get books. Walk to get music. Walk to walk. Diag is fun. Blisters mysteriously appear on toes. Walk to car. Sit on the roof for awhile. Wanted my poetry book. Get in car. Wait in traffic jam. Hit S. University. B-line to Sabastian's house. Get major headache. Drive seems to take forever, again. Finally get home. Jason is in my basement. Walk up stairs as pissed off as possible. Wonder why Jason is spending time with Mom. Wonder why Jason is spending time with my brother. Slam door shut. Shut off all recollection that Jason is still in my house. Blast music. Make it sound like I'm having fun. Really drowning in a sea of thoughts. And I'm here. I'm annoyed. I'm pissed. I'm over-reacting. I'm wondering who's going to read this. I'm aching. I'm slamming my head on my keyboard (for the second time today). I'm broke. I'm stupid. This is lame.  So there's my entire day... congratulations.... to me.... I've bored you to sleep. Congratulations... to you... you've now wasted you life reading this. I'm beginning to realize why I'd stopped blogging.  I'm going to check my e-mail, like that's going to give me hope.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If it's one thing I really want, I want my heart to stop pounding, it's overwhelming and heartbreaking. I need something to do before I spaz out. HTML here I come!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight has been great, once again. I skipped class, came into work early, left work early. I hung out with B twice today and saw him at Starbucks when I was heading into A2 to get tickets to Rocky Horror Picture Show. Joce and I went together... We're lesbian, virgin, video sluts.   While in A2, by myself (because I'm anti-social like that), I headed straight to the theatre to pick up tickets, then went to borders and ran into Meg, my poetry club director, on my way to the parking structure. I need to start writing more.  I'm still waiting to hear from you. Do you usually fuck people over and then never talk to them ever again? Because I hate mind games and if you try to pull something with me (which I've been beginning to doubt less and less) I will make something hell for you... I promise. And at the same time that I'm thinking about all of that I just remember everyone who's basically done that to me and realize how many people I've been fake to or haven't contacted for the longest time. I can be a bitch sometimes, I'm sorry. :-/  MOVING ON: So tonight was definately great. Didn't want to have to go back to State Street to see the place I fucked up and should have turned around from the first time my insincts came into play. I don't regret what I've done, I meerly regret the surrounding influences.   AGAIN, MOVING ON: Made it from B's to my house and then Michelle showed up and we left for Rocky Horror. It was better than I expected to tell you the truth. I would have paid more to get into the place but for a night of good "clean" fun it was great. What does a cub scout have to do to become a boy scout? I don't know, maybe you can answer that one for my Joce. ;-)  You and your twinkies. "I bit it because he said he was going to vote for Bush, what a tool." The guy left anyway... pussy.  Looks like Saturday will be spent cleaning the garage in the early morning, heading to B's house for some home cookin' (mmm... brownies), and then I'll probably end up on Joce's doorstep pleeing for a friend to talk to and a place to smoke my cigarettes. I'm going to die.   Shit... it's almost 4am. I need to get some rest, I think I'm starting to pass out.  I'm such a pussy. I can handle this... I think.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does it ever hit you like a bullet or a speeding train? That there is, no....  are  girls that want to grab your belt, tug, then rub your stomach. Does it worry or excite you that there are girls that want to undress you to find out if they are boxers, or briefs, or boxer-briefs; praying it's nothing, easy to make you feel naked even if you're still wearing a t-shirt and jeans. Does it comfort you, or uncomfort you (for that matter), to know that the more you cover up the more I want to bare you, exposing items that can be used for the most taboo acts. But you can tie my up or dress me down, nude or clothed, with goosebumps unconditional. To reach inside, to divide time and space, to mesh feelings as well as chemicals. And if you want to grab me and hold me down like the weak, meek girl I am, I would only be able to find such similar and contradictory actions in dreams, frivolous yet again. But like Moses parting the Red Sea, you would be able to separate, segregate words from thoughts, and comic from truth. As they say, "actions speak louder than words," and the words that can roll off the tip of your tounge, can whip around, stabbing, darting, not willing to come out with the squeek most attribute to butterflies. Butterflies are too beautiful to describe the feeling ever time you smack me with your words, I'm left speechless as always. Moths, worms, roaches, and grubs are thrown up with anxiety, like when Cisco held my hair back, I'm always so shy. Atleast we agree on one thing. Eager eyes peer into your fish bowl but only privately disguised behind a pathetic excuse for a smile and a pair of binoculars. I'm scared to release information that could potentially interrupt or create a tremor underneath you Earth and my skin. I'd love to crawl through you mind or take a bite out of your emotions. I salivate in anticipation ready for the meat, ready for the kill. All I must do is wait, but as the minutes turn to hours, hours to days, weeks, months, and years, I am impatient. I'm dying, I realize I am as quiet as a firefly but just as efficient at lighting that space in between a dark heart and crying eyes. I feel as if I am in the palm of your hand but ready for both truth and lies to serenade my presence. But just as those words could drive me to the edge I know how to take a step back and look at the surroundings that seem larger than life. A hand, a back, a face... all with a flick or whip of wind can sent careening off cliffs and diving into an ocean of blue... you.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And now the heart break.   I knew this was going to happen.  He never called...   As B would say, "Wam, bam, thank you ma'am." (my friends are such dorks)  The next post is for you... just so you know where I'm coming from.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was reading through my old blogger (the one on diaryland.com) and I now realize how much of a bitch I was/am. I used to complain a lot, but at the same time I guess that's what bloggers are used for in the teenage world.   So maybe I should go on tell you about recent events. Last night was great... I mean really great and not what I expected at all. After hanging out with Max in downtown A2 I went back to Ypsi and called the most random people. I ended up hanging out with Joce and we talked for it seemed like minutes but in all reality it was about 2 hours. It was wonderful. Just reminds me of the old times with her and James in her old room, smoking out, listening to great music, spinning in her chair, and thinking that life couldn't get any better. And unfortunately it didn't, after our trip to Mackinaw Island a couple of years ago we lost touch because we basically got annoyed with eachother. We were only freshman... So last night she invited me to Rocky Horror with her at midnight tonight, I'm excited. I might have to ditch B though, I love you B.  I really can't wait until summer, or spring break for that matter. Being able to stay out later will definately be a plus.  *Sigh* I'm getting sort of lazy so I'll continue my entry about good times later... love you all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I've been hopping around blogger to blogger. I'm going to see how long I can go without telling anyone about this one. It will be interesting. I gave up blogging quite a few months ago but I think I've hit rock bottom so I should write. What else is there to do?   So, if you care to read on, this is the boring life of a shy girl. Mainly consisting of my travels through the world, and possibly my bumps along the way.  3 days ago, I think it was, I met him. And I think it was him that triggered this longing inside me. A gap that Jason could never fill. Meet Max... Sexed up, crazy, dirty most of the time (which sort of turns me off), but he's so well spoken that you could give this man an hour of your time and you'd be begging on your knees to fuck. Interesting isn't it? I thought so...  So I broke up from my 2 year relationship with Jason last night. I'm crushed but handling it quiet well considering the circumstances. I hope he doesn't do anything stupid. Angie told me to put everything aside for a month and then see if it's worth getting back together... I think it will be. I just need time to find my independence again, perhaps find someone who can refresh me from this ongoing quarrel with Jason.  James is talking to me again, I don't know if it was the pirate hat or what that helped him forgive and initiate me into the percussion section. I'm feeling more at home now that the guys have started talking to me. Not really fun being the only down-to-earth girl in the section. Nadia and Michelle annoy me so. I'm not even going to get started there.  One more hour of school... I just want this hell to end... I need a cigarrette.   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I just met with Mr. Riccobono (my councilor). He's calling home to complain about my absences. I think I'm going to kill someone. I'm royally pissed that just because Keith, Gareth, and I skipped the talent show assembly and went to Starbucks, where we saw Ms. Peet, she had to go and bitch to administration about it. If I don't intercept that call my weekend is going to be screwed. Grr... he also wants to talk with me about my grades. This is definitely the worst week of my life. I just hope he left a message and my parents are home to listen to it. Argh. Pleas just let this all work out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From Ashley's Everything Book:   FRIDAY! FRIDAY! AHHHH! IT'S FRIDAY! (I'm way too excited about that...) The last day of April. Opa comes into town at 3-something-or-other today. I'm buying flowers for my mom's b-day on Sunday. I might even take her to church. Oh no, did I just offer to go to church. It's a miracle. Ouchies, my wrists hurt. At any rate... I'm leave school after 3rd hour.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From Ashley's Everything Book:   Why am I writing in here either at Starbuck's or Kellman's class? Oh I remember now... because I'm bored out of my mind at either location. I'm usually alone too...  So I went to downtown Ann Arbor and parked at the Washington Street parking structure. Wrote poetry from the top of the building. When it was about a quarter after 9am I decided to head to class. So I drove down about 5 stories and paid 50 cents for parking. Not too bad for an hour of inspirational thinking at high heights.  Have you ever noticed how most foreign people, particularly Middle Eastern, are extremely friendly? I mean, the guys at the BP station are really nice, always complementing me (they want to get in  my pants). But the Indian guy that works for Republic Parking was super friendly. I did my usual "Thank you." Then smiled, then he said something like, "Have a great day," then,"You have a wonderful smile." But I drove off too quickly to reply. People can be wonderfully nice sometimes and I think that's great, especially if someone tries their best to make you smile. And for me that's been an easy task lately.  There's the bell. I'm out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From Ashley's Everything Book:   Back at Starbucks. I've decided not to go to 1st or 2nd hours. I took a nap in my car before entering. I'm so unbelieveably tired. I'm thinking about going to bed early tonight. Nah... sleep is for the weak.  My hair appointment is for tonight at 7pm with Mike at Heidi's Hair Salon at Briarwood Mall. I'm excited. Change is good.  So yesterday turned out to be pretty fucking bad aswell. Well, sort of. When I got out of work I was taking Brentt home and as I was backing up my back-up sensors went off, but I thought it was the curb. WRONG. Turned out to be Big Rog's car, and I hit it then spead off after check for no damage. I was in a hurry to take Brentt home and then make it to the mall for some pre-weekend shopping. I got an e-mail when I returned home. He was pissed. I know his car is already fucked up, but I feel horrible for fucking it up even worse. I should have checked my e-mail before leaving for "school." Nick and Tiki convinced me it'll all blow over but I'm the biggest screw up in the world this week.  (I'm leaving out our events at Kinkos Copy Shop for obvious reasons)  I got the best feeling in the world last night. Michelle and I were driving East on I-94, on our way back from Kinkos and I said something like, "We're partners in crime... some kind of modern day Thelma and Louise." And she replied with something like, "That's awesome. I've never had a partner. It'll be cool." I got that warm fuzzy feeling deep down inside.   I think I'm actually waking up now.  Tomorrow is Friday!!! Ahhh! I'm not going to be able to sleep tonight. Kettering here I come!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From Ashley's Everything Book:   Back at Starbucks. I've decided not to go to 1st or 2nd hours. I took a nap in my car before entering. I'm so unbelievably tired. I'm thinking about going to bed early tonight. Nah... sleep is for the weak.  My hair appointment is for tonight at 7pm with Mike at Heidi's Hair Salon at Briarwood Mall. I'm excited. Change is good.  So yesterday turned out to be pretty fucking bad aswell. Well, sort of. When I got out of work I was taking Brentt home and as I was backing up my back-up sensors went off, but I thought it was the curb. WRONG. Turned out to be Big Rog's car, and I hit it then sped off after check for no damage. I was in a hurry to take Brentt home and then make it to the mall for some pre-weekend shopping. I got an e-mail when I returned home. He was pissed. I know his car is already fucked up, but I feel horrible for fucking it up even worse. I should have checked my e-mail before leaving for "school." Nick and Tiki convinced me it'll all blow over but I'm the biggest screw up in the world this week.  (I'm leaving out our events at Kinkos Copy Shop for obvious reasons)  I got the best feeling in the world last night. Michelle and I were driving East on I-94, on our way back from Kinkos and I said something like, "We're partners in crime... some kind of modern day Thelma and Louise." And she replied with something like, "That's awesome. I've never had a partner. It'll be cool." I got that warm fuzzy feeling deep down inside.   I think I'm actually waking up now.  Tomorrow is Friday!!! Ahhh! I'm not going to be able to sleep tonight. Kettering here I come!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From Ashley's Everything Book:   Kellman, Kellman, Kellman. New seating arrangement. Now I can be antisocial again! Aaron Corpal is a riot.  So yesterday was the ultimately worst day of my life. Beside my computer being for shit, my dad heard the whole, "Ashley does Ectasy" story and we talked. Madeline's mom saw me smoking on my way to the Secretary of State. Ran a red light in front of her too. I worked about 2 hours. Donald and Mark bitched me out about how I'm not a "Product of the 80s" as my t-shirt proclaimed. So I was hyped up on caffine all day, and so when I got home I spent about an hour cleaning my car. I didn't realize until afterward how impulsive the Overkleeft family is. Paranoid that my parents were going to find out that I smoke, the interior of my Escape is now spotless. I looked like I was cleaning a murder crime scene or something. Blasting classical music while on top of my car, scrubbing the shit out of my moon/sun roof.  I've gotta do homework tonight. Get my hair done tomorrow and start my pill again so I can have some wild and crazy sex. Pah... yeah... riiiight.  Kellman reminds me of Red Green only without the crazy suspenders.  I started the Alize painting for Nick. I'm insane. It looks good though. I hope it's the right kind. If not, I'll drink it. ;-)  Tiki is feeling upset and empty. I bought her a card and I've been having everyone sign it. I hope it cheers her up.  Michelle and I are going up to Flint together this Friday. We'll get drunk and stoned the  party and whore it up. It'll be a blast.  My brother is off the hook with the whole dog fire situation. The Dean came back and was pissed at the Assistant Dean for suspending the pledges. It's all good, but the frat is punishing them with community service and possibly chores. Merry X-mas Henk.  I'm done writing for now... more to come later.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       From Ashley's Everything Book:   Welcome to Starbucks, the obessed hand out of lovers of the coffee flavored crack, with a side of caffine. Mmm... my carmel machiato is super strong today, but this is the second time I've been here in the past 12 hours, and the second time I've orders a double carmel machiato, along with sitting in the same  seat.   And I'm not staring at some (probably 20-something) guy with a leather jacket, blue work shirt with white grid lines, jeals and black chuck taylor all-stars (hi-tops of course. I take that back, they're navy blue. I think he's gay. Oh well.  A geeky-looking man with khakis and a wind breaker just set his calculus book and calculator down next to me. So many guys, and I'm not even wearing make-up today, for christ's sake.  And on to other topics... Nick, he wants me to talk all the time but when I'm prepared to release information that I'm not too comfortable talking about, he usually leaves or is too busy with others. I wonder how this weekend's trip to Kettering will fair for (what feels like) the inexistant friendship of us. Lots of alcohol I'd assume.  Geeky-guy is writing on white computer paper to get his homework done. Very delicate hand writing compaired to the violent jolts of my hand flying up and down. I think 20-something-year-old has the exact same shirt that I've entitled "like a rhinestone cowboy." I don't know why, but watching people follow through with daily tasks can be interesting, sometimes depressing because it reminds me I have no life.  I've strangely lost track of my writing. I'm ready for the weekend to be here, and it's only Tuesday. Tomorrow's events include suffering through band, going to a counciling appointment during Art (second hour) to fix my course selection sheet, suffering through the rest of school and then hopefully going to get my hair done. My computer is at the store for repairs, prolly a virus or something, and then the information gets tossed onto my laptop, the parts are going to Nick up at Kettering in Flint. Well, back to work for me. For now, I'm out. As Paul would say, "Peace Out." 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The next few entries will be copied from my tangable journal....
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Digital poetry for the clinically depressed:   One Night Fall  - Write these feelings down An alternative to giving it up Body on complete lock down Accenting a heart on it's way up This intercourse is so overrated Blatantly in love with you To the point of illusion And I'll wait either way I'm not prepared for the fight This cover-up has gone wrong I can be there only for so long My ideals bottled up And tossed out to sea It's too late to take things back This waiting room is lonely And slowly grows padding Because I was insane to believe That you'd stay or I'd go Please make this blindness pass Or rid yourself of self control I can save myself One night is just as right 5 years old Happy Birthday, I Love You Happy Birthday To You But this cake doesn't have it's icing I will stumble to escape I'm ready to say goodbye All you need to do is leave
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back to my old bouncy self... for now.  *Ten Minutes Later*  Ok, why the hell did he have to call back? Jesus, Keith...  *Ten Minutes Later*  Desperate, desperate girl. With a large mark on her boob. Silly, selfish girl.  Haiku time...  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be the grapes fermented, Bottled and served with the table set in my finest suit Like a perfect gentlemen I'll be the fire escape that's bolted to the ancient brick Where you will sit and contemplate your day  I'll be the waterwings that save you if you start drowning In an open tab when your judgement's on the brink I'll be the phonograph that plays your favorite Albums back as your lying there drifting off to sleep... I'll be the platform shoes and undo what heredity's done to you... You won't have to strain to look into my eyes I'll be your winter coat buttoned and zippedstraight to the throat With the collar up so you won't catch a cold  I want to take you far from the cynics int his town And kiss you on the mouth We'll cut out bodies free from the tethers of this scene, Start a brand new colony Where everything will change, We'll give ourselves new  names (identities erased) The sun will hear the grounds Under our bare feet in this brand new colony Everything will change
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I go on to petty issues that aren't worth anyone's time...  Henk's suspended from school. I'm not going that far into details but he tried to set the bull dog on fire and instead got gas on a couple of the Pikes and some Fiji pledges. The school is trying to keep it under wraps I guess, and they're doing some stupid shit to the people that were involved. I hope the best for my brother, and even though he was never there for me when my whole thing in court went down, I'm going to be there for him.  Here's the petty shit... Don't get a twist in your panties...  I'm sick of being everyone's little thing. I don't know what to even call myself. You come, you go, you come, you go. JUST FUCKING GO ALREADY!!! STAY GONE! I'm a fucking puppet to everyone. Aren't I? Mr. Sex, Mr. La-De-Da-Fuck-You-When-I-Please, and Mr. You-Need-To-Talk. I have something for each of you...  Mr. Sex - You're an asshole, you need to leave me the hell alone. I'm not going to fuck you EVER. You have too many problems and I don't need to be one of those and I don't want to be included in anyone's sex-scapades or end up as just another tick on the bed post. So go try and give yourself a god-damn blow job already.  Mr. Fuck-You-When-I-Please - Though I was actually considered fucking around again, I'm almost too sick of you. I get this feeling inside me whenever you say something, or plan for something to occur. I feel this pit of dispair but I also feel this discust that just makes me want to fully vomit all over you. So bring it on... and I'll show you the bile left in my stomach. Oh yes, I forgot to tell you. I'm not small enough? Cute enough? Sexy enough? So I was almost willing to starve myself to be the perfect something that you'd enjoy, but I already blew that out of the water. What did you expect? Pah... fuck love...  Mr. You-Need-To-Talk - I don't. I can't. And whenever I remotely come to a point where I'm willing to say the tiniest fragment of a sentence it seems that I'm completely cut off or put on hold. I really don't need to waste my time getting my point across to anyone, seeing as no one's willing to listen. I don't need to talk, so I won't.  And I'm SO IN LOVE it just drives this nail straight into something that wasn't there to begin with. I'm saying good bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The minutes that were wasted...  I woke up late for school today. Missed my sectional in band. Oh fucking well. Went to 3rd hour and bombed my test (we'll get to what my mom said later) I'm a failure. Cut 4th hour to hang out with Michelle and Gareth. We went to Borders to pick up a copy of Wuthering Heights for English, and then went to Starbucks for coffee. Made it back to school a tad bit late. 5th hour was pretty funny. Mr. McClure was talking with the class about our course selection sheets when we walked into Ms. Otwell's class. Everyone laughed and made smart remarks about our coffee and my piece of crumble cake as we walked in. I laughed hysterically, Ms. Otwell asked where her coffee was, Michelle turned bright red, Cassie rolled her eyes, I laughed some more. David got on our ass about being late to class, and then having our Starbucks in hand. He drank the rest of Michelle's. Forensics was a bunch of bullshit, as usual. Got out of school and Rex had put a illegal parking/towing notice sticker on my car. I got pissed and drove home to waste my time taking the stupid thing off with Skin-So-Soft and window cleaner. Now the oil won't come off my window... bastard. Oh well.  Let's talk grades... They have drastically improved since the beginning of this week. I called my mom when I got to work and she and I worked out a deal that I'd go to tutoring before school (at 6 in the god damn morning), but I get to keep my car. It's fair in my opinion, but did she really expect me to bring that grade in Advanced Algebra up to a B or C from a D-? Hopefully it will come out to a D+ or C-. This Honor Roll crap is driving me crazy. I just need a 3.0 and I'll be fine.  Things are going in the right direction for me. I have great friends, my grades are going up, my tank is full of gas, I have a full pack of cigarettes, I have a job and am getting paid quite a lot (compared to Pinter's), and there might be a new love interest around the corner. *COUGH COUGH* you lost your bet Michelle *COUGH*  I got out of work at 5 to go and see the baseball game with her. "And I'd fuck him. And I'd fuck him. And, oh what the hell, I'd fuck him too..." Desperate. And Joel, and Cole, and Steve, and Michelle you're so screwed. No wait,  I'm  so screwed. lol.  We left the game at 6:30 and went to get gas, then headed to Ann Arbor to chill. "You have to make me sexy." So we went shopping and I bought new shirts. Got a new cigarette holder too. Went to Pinball Pete's and she lost her bet at pool. So I'm getting laid, and she's getting gothed out on Monday. I'm bringing a camera, for both events. I figure if I take a picture maybe it'll last longer.  How many laws have we broken today? I count 16. Michelle has hers up to 16 as well. Let's see if I can figure them all out again.  1. Smoking Under Age 2. Driving with Illegal Substances 3. Cutting School 4. Parking in the Upper Lot 5. Stealing (I got me some new sunglasses... they're purdy. Thank you Michelle) 6. Buying Cigarette's Under Age 7. Buying a Cigarette Holder Under Age 8. Gambling 9. Indecent Exposure 10. Sex with Over Age Guys (Michelle. I'm obviously not getting laid) 11. Drinking 12. Smoking on School Grounds 13. Speeding 14. Smoking in Public Buildings 15. Jay Walking 16. Littering 17. Using Illegal Substances And that's a typical day... Hmm...  Well, I could go up to Kettering this weekend... but I'm not going to. I have my reasons. Paul asked me to today, but I refused. I'm not going to be happy for multiple reasons so I might as well leave it alone. Q is going to have Friday through Sunday off so I'll probably just chill with him ("Hey Cole. Are you thinking about sex?"). Michelle and I are having random movie marathon with Kill Bill 2 and Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind. We might see a few other flick but I'm going to need a lot of pot and a ton of time in between to chain smoke. But all will be fine. It will be lovely.  I just ate the biggest bowl of cereal in the world. I think that's the only thing besides crumble cake that I've had all day. Ugh... dairy products... now my tummy aches.  Okay... I will leave you on this note because I was listening to this today and it really reminded me of what Allen and I's relationship was...  Will someone please call a surgeon Who can crack my ribs and repair this broken heart That your're deserting for better company? I can't accept that it's over...  I will block the door like a goalie tending the net In the third quarter of a tied-game rivalry  So just say how to make it right And i swear i'll do my best to comply  Tell me am i right to think that there could be nothing better Than making you my bride and slowly growing old together  I feel must interject here you're getting carried away feeling sorry for yourself With these revisions and gaps in history So let me help  you remember. I've made charts and graphs that should finally make it clear. I've prepared a lecture on why i have to leave  So please back away and let me go I can't my darling i love you so...  Tell me am i right to think that there could be nothing better Than making you my bride and slowly growing old together Don't you feed me lines about some idealistic future Your heart won't heal right if you keep tearing out the sutures  I admit that i have made mistakes and i swear I'll never wrong you again You've got a lure i can't deny,  But you've had your chance so say goodbye Say goodbye  I've gotta stop posting lyrics... it's driving me insane.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because I don't want to write everything out... I'm just not in the mood....  I'm full of regret For all things that I've done and said And I don't know if it'll ever be ok to show My face 'round here Sometimes I wonder if I disappear  Would you ever turn your head and look See if I'm gone Cause I fear  There is nothing left to say to you That you wanna hear That you wanna know I think I should go The things I've done are way too shameful  Your just innocent A helpless victim of a spider's web And I'm an insect Goin after anything that I can get  So you better turn your head and run And don't look back  Cause I fear  There is nothing left to say To you That you wanna hear That you wanna know I think I should go The things I've done are way too shameful  And I've done you so wrong Treated you bad Strung you along Oh shame on myself I don't know how I got so tangled up  My cheesiness is scaring me... 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ash was right... I wish I had someone to call...  I wish I would have just stayed quiet....  Why the hell is it always like this? I'm so sick of everything.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm ready to talk... for once in my life.  Ready or not here I come.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back to School.  Slept through 3rd hour, dreamt of advanced algebra. Left before 5th hour to get coffee with Gareth and Michelle. Talked about hacking into the admin computers and changing our grades. I think the attendance office is our best bet. ;-) We returned for 6th hour, but as I walked into the room Mr. Ball was our substitute so I left, headed to the art room to talk grades with Ms. Evans. Apparently I'm failing because I don't have my fucking watercolor in. I started painting. Figured she was being such a bitch and decided to steal the watercolor paints and a few paint brushes (even though I've pilfered so much stuff from the art stock room already). Oh well...  So I had an interesting feeling today. I was walking to the band hall after second lunch and everyone that was walking the opposite direction was familiar to me. I knew everyone's name. Just knowing people is like some exciting experience for me. I was painting the announcements on the window in the media center 4th hour and as some kid came by and slammed his fist against the window (trying to screw up my Seniors Last Day annoucement) the entire humanities class (which was in the media center at the time) wanted to get up and kill the kid, I thought it was hilarious. PEOPLE CARE. It's so odd. Andrea complemented my skills of painting backwards. I blushed and thanked her.   Ash has been a little strange lately. I guess she slept with someone while down in Key West and only remembers waking up with the person. She got a pregnancy test and she's alright. We both talked about Keith. She's still not over him. I told her of how I at once contemplated if I wanted to be with Keith or Allen after high school. She said I worry too much. The story of my life. She also told me to try and be happy, but agreed that I'm happier since the break up. I told her about the unimportance of my happiness, she wanted to strangle me.    Nick and I talked last night. It was scary on my part. I'm just not used to things like this.  And yes, I flipped out. I promised myself I wouldn't. I just don't want to deal with things so I push them aside. He told me not to run from things. I'm so acquainted with running, sometimes just seems like the best thing. No one usually sees me run away though, and that's why it's so natural. No one really cares that much to look in my direction. With exception of Tiki, but she usually follows me back to my corner and sits with me until things feel a little better. This isn't going to go away is it?   On to other things I guess. Leah and Wyatt are dating or something. "Here's your gift..." *randomly make out* I was drop jawed... Kayleigh looked at me as if she'd known about this for awhile. I guess, oh what's his name.... that Davey guy is out of the picture. Go back to Gabriel Richard to which you came from. Asshole...  I have too much homework. Wind Symphony is going to the East and West middle school's tomorrow. No 2nd-4th hours for me... I just realized something, what are we going to play? Both Plato's Cave and Pirates of the Caribbean suck. Thanks for making us look like retarded band fags Snydee. I confessed to her that band isn't on my course selection sheet for next year. I think she was going to cry.  Band - B Art - D (this will change due to water color painting submitting) Advanced Algebra - C (I need to study for that test on Wednesday) Media Aide - Satisfactory English - ? Forensics - ?  I need a 3.5 by the end of this week. Hey Gareth, can I take you up on that offer? I'm getting no sleep tonight. Homework. Homework. Homework.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Run for cover...   and she goes back into her shell
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The denouement to my spring break of wonders...  I'm definitely feeling a lot better. I'm not liking how I randomly spaz out. Ignore all complaints from the previous entry PLEASE. I love warm nights. I wish I could spend them with someone once in awhile. *searches for music to excite her* oh hell yes, Raized in Black. Fo shizzle. After I last wrote in here Mom called me to come home and do yard work. I got paid for it though. The backyard is almost as immaculate as my room. Michelle and I have plans for an all movie day. I guess we're going to see Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (which I've already seen and IT IS THE BEST DRAMATIC MOVIE OUT THERE!!! GO SEE IT!!!!) and Kill Bill 2 (which she's already seen, and highly recommends). Michelle and I went out to Starbucks and played catch-up on our spring breaks, we then headed out the Pinball Petes for some good clean pool fun. Went to U of M North Campus and hung out at the most random places, chilling out and enjoying the view.   Nick and I talked today... yeeeeah. I'm going to try and be more open. If I talk with him tonight I'm going to give him the URL to this blogger. I just have to get really drunk before I do so just so that I won't remember and won't hesitate so much to write my feelings out.   How do I feel (this is for you Keehn): Okay, at the moment I'm sort of chill. I'm really tired for raking the entire backyard (which still looks like shit) with Michelle and playing DDR (the new Michelle and Ashley work out program). As for my emotions. I'm fine right now. I do feel sort of stalker-ish for calling Nick more than once today, but at the moment I thought he wanted to talk... and I was willing to talk. I don't really think I'm open about my feelings, but I'm just trying to make people happy... I really don't want to complicate anyone's life more than it already is; especially Nick's because he has enough relationship shit to deal with from what I've heard from the people up at Fiji, and he doesn't need some little 17-year-old fucking his future up... That's how I feel... Honesty. I'm in love with this illusion, a fucked up image in my head of what things could be, or what my heart thinks it should be, and I need to push myself far away from that because otherwise shit like that *points to last entry* will happen again, and I don't enjoy crying anymore. Welcome back to reality.  And as for other people... I don't think I'll be seeing Him anymore, just because I'm sick of being a toy. I'm sick of being used and then ignored the following day when I come into the building and he just sits there, never talks to me... Michelle agreed that everything is over, I think I'll leave it that way. Then again, I'm naive and stupid for ever starting this shit. I was being selfish and dumb and unrealistic. Because I almost fell for him but I then realized the open relationship and the fact that there was NO future, just coffee houses and HTML, and shit that I'm too scared to admit to. It never occurred, it never will (again). I just need to keep telling myself that and hopefully it will just go away. Kilts and mopeds. Don't you just want to die sometimes?  I need to get my shit together. I need to get a life.  There's Keehn.... oh how I want to delete this entry...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drunk... that was the extent of my night.  My mom eventually gave in and I decided to stay the night. I'm convincing like that.  I need coffee, I need to talk with Michelle, this shit on my mind is no good. Or atleast no good will come of it.   Last night was the most depressing night of my life. In some respects, I should have gone home. My mom was right. I had fun, I guess. A whole slew of the guys at Fiji, Mike, April, Nick, Henk, Melissa, Josephine, Todd, the list goes on... we went to the park and got drunk off our asses. Henk and Jeff got stoned. I took two hits and I was through. Nick was trying to convince me to get stoned. Maybe that state would have made things with April and Nick seem insignificant. I know he'd never do anything with her but her on his lap was enough for me to go into Jeff's room and strip down to my tank top and jeans and dance on his coffee table. Remotely trying to have a good night. Desperately trying to have a good night. I sometimes don't understand the actions of others. I really don't understand why Mike didn't take control of his god damn girlfriend. And I sat in a corner for what seemed like too long waiting for Tiki or someone to care and come to find me. Desperate. I'm SO FUCKING DESPERATE!!! Blah... I don't know how many times I fell down. Nick tried to get me to kiss him on his cheek. I said no. I'm done. So then I'm hanging out in the hallway. And Nick and Jeff go into Jeff's room to talk. On their way out all I hear is, "If I was 17 it'd be great... but I'm not." I don't know who that was directed toward, but I'm going to assume it was directed toward me considering the fact that Jeff and I sat outside smoking a cigarette and talking about who we wanted to kill that night. I didn't release the information that I really wanted to stab Nick in his fucking heart so he could feel what it's like to care about someone and then be completely let down. I did hint at the fact that I was upset at Nick, but I didn't explain. Tiki understood and that was enough for me. Maybe if I wasn't so closed off or shy I'd be able to do the same as April does. But Nick has nothing to worry about with her... I think. I'm not pissed, I'm just really upset, or disappointed? I unfortunately cried myself to sleep on Nick's recliner after he passed out while I was mid-sentence into my whole family problem situation. AHH. I wrote lame poetry and stared at the ceiling. Finally got to sleep around 3:30-4am and woke up at 7:30-8am. Sleep is for the weak. Hahah... weak. To tell you the truth, I should have slept with Paul. Where's my punching bag? He woke up around 9 and I went out to smoke, he shortly followed me out but left after his feet got cold. I tried my best to play everything off as okay. I don't think I'm going back up there next weekend. I don't thing I'm going back up there ever.   Time for fun lyrics....  I'm not in love, so don't forget it. It's just a silly phase I'm going through. And just because I call you up, Don't get me wrong, don't think you've got it made. I'm not in love, no no, it's because... I like to see you, but then again, That doesn't mean you mean that much to me. So if I call you, don't make a fuss; Don't tell your friends about the two of us. I'm not in love, no no, it's because... I keep your picture upon the wall. It hides a nasty stain that's lying there. So don't you ask me to give it back. I know you know it doesn't mean that much to me. I'm not in love, no no, it's because... Ooh, you'll wait a long time for me. Ooh, you'll wait a long time. I'm not in love, I'm not in love... - Tori Amos "I'm Not In Love"  You'll never see -- the courage I know  Its colors' richness won't appear within your view  I'll never glow -- the way that you glow Your presence dominates the judgements made on you But as the scenery grows, I see in different lights  The shades and shadows undulate in my perception  My feelings swell and stretch, I see from greater heights  I understand what I am still too proud to mention -- to you You'll say you understand, but you don't understand You'll say you'd never give up seeing eye to eye But never is a promise, and you can't afford to lie You'll never touch -- these things that I hold  The skin of my emotions lies beneath my own You'll never feel the heat of this soul  My fever burns me deeper than I've ever shown -- to you You'll say, Don't fear your dreams, its easier than it seems You'll say you'd never let me fall from hopes so high But never is a promise and you can't afford to lie You'll never live the life that I live I'll never live the life that wakes me in the night You'll never hear the message I give You'll say it looks as though I might give up this fight But as the scenery grows, I see in different lights The shades and shadows undulate in my perception My feelings swell and stretch, I see from greater heights  I realize what I am now too smart to mention -- to you You'll say you understand, you'll never understand I'll say I'll never wake up knowing how or why I don't know what to believe in, you don't know who I am You'll say I need appeasing when I start to cry But never is a promise and I'll never need a lie - Fiona Apple "Never is a Promise"  Can I become more pathetic than this? I think not.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday was a... I don't know, interesting day.  Woke up super early to have coffee in A2 with Keith. We talked about why we were pissed at eachother for the past few months. Something about backpacks and Allen and stuff that we've both just put in the past. I guess my old relationship didn't help much. We went to Middle Earth and I got a new poetry book, headed back to the parking structure and hung out at my house for a few before I took him home and headed to work to do shit that was utterly boring. I don't think I got all three hours in, but oh well... it's spring break what do you expect?  After work I hung out with Keith at Pennisular Park and talked some more, seems to be doing some good. Read poetry. Went to my house.  Printed some stuff off for his Geometry (pah... Geometry) project. Dropped him off and went back home to chill and finish the layout on the Tasteful Lemon. Charlie came over before heading out to the Necto, did his make-up, made a Margaret Cho desktop background. Ate apples. Went to pick up Tiki and drove around EMU screaming at decent looking guys before dropping Charlie off at his car, fixing his hair, and then heading to A2 and Espresso Royale Cafe with Tiki for some live music, writing, and wonderful beverages. At 10:45pm we went back to my place and chilled for a few. Talked with my drunken brother and Nick.   Blah... I called my mom about head up here (Fiji) today, she bitched me out, I hung up the phone and rested my head on my keyboard before deciding to head out early this  morning (against my parent's best interests). Whatever, they'll get over it. Probably won't spend the night but I'm almost eager to get back home and get coffee. Not really. It's something to do, and I really don't have that many friends available to hang today. Michelle is probably passed out on her bed from the long drive back from Myrtle Beach. Did you whore it up? lol.   Not much else. Yesterday was a long day and I'm hoping the final days of my break will be just as long... beautiful, as usual.  Check out the Lemon, tell me how you like the site... I think the main iframe is busted.... *goes to check the source* the background is fucked and I need to center the smaller iframe... I'll fix it when I get back to Ypsi.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MtDewGirl87: I'm thinking about going somewhere at 9 MtDewGirl87: any ideas? ShindaHotaru: da club  ShindaHotaru: lol iono MtDewGirl87: drop it like it's hot ShindaHotaru: um how about that one place with the stuff and things MtDewGirl87: damn, for real?! I was thinking the same thing!!! ShindaHotaru: OMG!!! ShindaHotaru: we're like kindred souls or something! MtDewGirl87: LET'S START A COVEN!!!!! ShindaHotaru: GREAT IDEA!!! MtDewGirl87: OMG! Then I can bring my guitar by and we can jam to Strawberry Gashes together... I SO love Jack Off Jill!!!! MtDewGirl87: we can start a band too! MtDewGirl87: But we'll kick out percussionist out for no reason ShindaHotaru: and we'll be like famous and stuff MtDewGirl87: I'll buy all the goth clothes in the world and rip them up so I look, like, so GOTH!!! ShindaHotaru: and don't forget to say you're depressed all the time MtDewGirl87: OMG, my boyfriend broke up with me... he said that if he fucked me I'd break ShindaHotaru: omg that's like so not right yet so true MtDewGirl87: plus he didn't like my boney ass bones jabbing into his hips ShindaHotaru: he must not know that anoreix looking chicks are the new rage MtDewGirl87: I ate a pea today... I'm going to be SO FAT!!! MtDewGirl87: hold on a sec... MtDewGirl87: nevermind, I just threw it up... I'll be okay ShindaHotaru: you scared me for a second there MtDewGirl87: I know... wait, am I spooky?! I'm SPOOKY!!! I SCARED YOU! OMG OMG I'm SO goth ShindaHotaru: omg you are MtDewGirl87: So are you fagging it out or what? OMG it's so trendy to be gay ShindaHotaru: oh it's even trendier to be bi MtDewGirl87: really? You're right! I just read the new Cosmo-Girl MtDewGirl87: I am SO going to Denny's tonight to hang out with the Christain goths
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think Paul thinks the more he's an asshole to me the more I'm going to want his "dead sexy" body. I think not.  Reading a lot of Basho, Buson, and Issa. I'm getting all descriptive. Idiots w/ Pens is dead... I mean, DEAD. Like how Ms. Seigel is going to be when I bitch her out on Monday for not forcing the U of M students to come back.   The carpet cleaners come today, oh yay... Nick, Jeff, and some others are coming down to Ypsi to watch Kill Bill Vol 2 tonight (or tomorrow morning, depends on how you look at it). You know it's going to be canceled. No one is going to want to make the 45 minute drive to watch 1 1/2 hours of a movie. Maybe Nick... I would too. God, Kill Bill was awesome.   The piano turner is here. Turns her stereo to full blast. Oh yeah, eat Chemical Brothers you bitch!!!! Just kidding....
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And I'm still up here. I'm leaving around 11am to 12pm. I'm driving Nick to his class and then taking off down 23 so I can clean the rest of my room and feel absolutely content with myself.   Henk passed out on his couch last night. Though I didn't really want to invade, I ended up on Nick's couch for the second time in the past week. We had some pretty good conversation. Here's a scary fact, middle name is Andrew... sound familiar to anyone? He's Leah's sign, Libra. I'll have to do some research. I'll ask him if he was serious about the spell casting he seemingly jokingly asked for. I don't know what to say or do anymore. In some respects I just feel I should shut up, turn around, and move on. I'll get over it. I've just have to keep a little Mike in the back of my head to give me reality checks when need be.   AHHH! I hate this keyboard....  I off to the land of Nick, Fiji, and nothingness in between. I really wish Michelle would come home...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm... so I'm up at Fiji. Nothing too exciting today. I didn't expect the arm around the neck, hand on my shoulder.... I just get the wrong impression sometimes, but that's alright... I think. He wants me to be happy but that's really not what I'm interested in. I'm not the one that needs happiness. That or give me a bottle of alcohol and I'll be fine for the moment.  In other news, I think Paul has accepted the fact that I'm not going to have sex with him. That's a good thing. He's still not off my crotch. Jeff, Zinc, Henk, Nick and I went to a tool store today (I forget the name) but I was going to buy a hammer taker to keep Paul's dick in his pants. You think it'd work?  Michelle's phone got disconnected. Keith and I have plans for Friday afternoon coffee. I'm anticipating his call back this evening.   All this shit running through my head just pisses me off. Chain smoker and all... not attractive. But who the hell should I be attractive for? What the hell is attractive? I've lost my path in life... sometimes you just need to cut across the field.   Maybe Mike is right. I need to stop wearing my heart out on my sleeve. Zero 7 and the Virgin Suicides sound track, please put me to sleep. I need something... 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We both know this is a bad idea. I should just stay home tomorrow....  I'd throttle myself to death if I could...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in the never ending state of panic...   Digital poetry for the blind:  Sex is a sinister something Poured into a vat of confusion Sex is a surreal socialization Beautifully contributed to a realization That when he lays me down I dream of someone or something A situation that can be contrived From a fantasy, Romance, you see, A controversy that involves you Sex is a brutal mistake Where lovers make way To an ocean of remorse Sex is a regretful misgiving Where living is just as it seems The breeze flying in through the window My hair whipping and tumbling for self Rules are meant to be broken And take this gift as a token Of the sex we'll never have My mistake is one worth self loathing And I'd scream one thousand "I love you's" to the sky Kiss reality goodbye And just as fast as I'd take off my clothing You'd push me away Faster than the day That laps were couches and thighs chairs A mess of hair, whipping, tumbling for self Sex is a misguided misunderstanding Where demanding for me A sick way to believe That you'd have another To be under covers And this would electrically enhance certain surroundings Turning blue eyes red, and brown hair black Sex is nothing but touching If you want it to be more I'd be willing But if certain people, certain places Are keeping virgin lips sacred I'm interested in making you happy You talk like life isn't thrilling These worshippers of untouched features are needed for killing Perhaps it won't undo or untie her From dragging the noose around your neck Higher and higher For her to kick you down from responsibility But if reponsibility Is for you to make me see That my fantasy Of you and me Would only die quickly Then I'd gladly back off Mixed feelings And checkerboard ceilings And a daylight-savings-time recliner Colonial Coney Island Diner And all the substances in between Sex is a riot of Nazis Conforming to one night stands And boys who are sons of a man Entitled D.O.G. reversed I've conversed And rehearsed And have waited for moments For me to grasp That this won't last Conversations of past Holidays spent here Sex is an exemption Redemption From day dreams of heartache And hair, whipping, tumbling for self Will forever forget me When sex is put on lay away  And he said no... *sigh* Looking for love in all the wrong places
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was awesome but it left me feeling sort of worthless.  In a tizzy I went up to Kettering to hang out with my brother and all his frat buddies. I was so pissed off at you... argh! I still am in a way. Jeff and I got stoned out on the balcony then headed back inside to play Mario Kart. I am the all ruling gamer of the GameCube. Go me... boo... Nick got back from class at 4:30. I stumbled out of Paul's room to see him screaming at the phone, I'm assuming it was his girlfriend. Easy. That's all I have to say.   I gave Nick his 80s Mix CDs. I guess he liked him, not much of a reaction came from his face. Oh well... I cooked dinner then played mind games with Nick and ink blots. Paul, Henk and myself then headed out to Sean and Ethan's place to drink. Oh yes, they got me drunk and then some. I won at poker though. I gave the $60 to my poor brother. He owes me. Nick showed up and I told him to make sure I made it home okay. I also told him to make sure I didn't end up in Paul's bed because that would have been a big problem. I then headed outside for a cigarette and then passed out on the couch that's on the deck. I heard everyone talking about me and I smelled the scent of a book being lit on fire. I couldn't cough, I wanted to but I was just too tired. "Is she out?" "Yeah" "She told me to make sure she got home okay. I don't know why she trusts me so much" "She's going to have a serious hang over" "We'll make her walk back" "Nah... Todd's coming to pick her up in a few" "Is she going to yak?" "I don't know" "Probably" *poke poke* "If you've gotta yak, yak. C'mon it'll make you feel better" ---black out--- 'God I hope I don't die tonight' "What'd you say Ash?" "She won't die" ---black out--- "Pick her up" "C'mon, lets go, your ride is here" "Hey Ash, everything's going to be okay" 'Okay, I'll be fine' *stumbled down the stairs and falls in the grass* *the puking begins* That's the first time that anything besides snot has come out of my nose "Now you've got the college experience" "I'm here to take you home. You can puke out the window if you need to" I was led into Todd's car and we slowly drove back to Fiji. "I'll take it nice and slow for you okay?" 'Thank you' I thanked the guys so much that night. Todd got me a glass of water as I fell down on Nick's couch. He then grabbed me a pillow, the trash can, and a blanket. "This is what a frat is all about, taking care of each other" Looking back on it now I want to cry because they were so considerate. I was so trashed. I was so glad I didn't go home with Paul. I woke up in the middle of the night to see where everyone was. I walked back into Nick's room and closed the door rather loudly. I didn't know he was even sleeping in the room at the time. I apologized for waking him up and then passed out for a few more hours on the couch. One foot on the ground, as Allen has always taught me. "Don't worry, you won't die" Nick said, sure of himself, and we both went to sleep.   It was good and bad at the same time. I felt like such a jackass for puking, and we won't even talk about how unattractive it was. Well, life goes on I guess. I'm glad I don't have a hang over.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm obsessed with you...  -> CrazyGirl
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *faints to Down Under*
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning heartache....  So it's been awhile. A long while  My weekend: .Saturday. Oh my god it was a blast! Well with the exception of Danny and Paul. Stalkers. But I liked it, I have to admit. (Oh yeah, my white russian still has ice in it *sip sip* Anyway...) Henk convinced Mom and Dad to let me spend the night (because he's the god of sympathy trips). Paul took Mike and I to go get Malibu and Pucker, we spent about 20 minutes just looking for a liquor store in Flint. Headed to this bon fire, hung out and got drunk off my ass. And as for my expecting there to be hot guys there, I was right. And I was all over them like the whore I planned on being. After the crowd died off, we headed back to the frat house in Henk's van. VAN SURFING IS FUN! And who said you have to be gay to listen to Men at Work? *goes to download "Down Under"* God I love you Nick. Meanwhile, I'm drunk and trying to keep my balance, Nick is chucking condoms from Ohio in my general direction "You'll need these later!!!" and then Henk flies over the hill to the frat house. Everyone exits the car besides Mike, Rick, and myself. I sit there and day dream for a few. Exit. I let the guys examine my car. Smoke a cigarette while Danny puts his arm around me. Watch a frat guy get drenched in ice cold water, take pictures, and laugh. Then he comes after me. Mike grabs me and picks me up, and here come icy-cold wet guy running to give me a hug. My ass gets wet and I laugh some more. We head up stairs and I pass out on Nick's bunk. I lose my camera and lighter in Nick's bed (I wish I could lose myself in Nick's bunk). Henk, two of the guys (one being Stalker Danny), and myself head out to the deck to smoke out. We get sufficiently stoned and head back in to collect ourselves and head to the 8:55pm showing of Hell Boy. Move sucks. I get a nap in. I feel back because my brother paid for my ticket. So I try my best to stay awake. We get back to the house and I drink Red Bull and take caffeine pills. Hang out with everyone for a few. Paul invites me to sleep in his bed instead of the guest quarters. Go out to dinner at the Colonial Coney Island at 2am (but it's daylight savings so it's really 3am) and chat with Stalker-Danny and Oh-My-God-I-Want-To-Fuck-You-Nick. Talk to Rick about my parents. I convince everyone that my parents are assholes. We get back to the house and talk for a bit. I read poetry. I write poetry. I pass out on Nick's recliner. I sleep for two hours and head back at 8am (but it's really 9am due to daylight savings). .Sunday. Well, yesterday was spent working, shopping, and crying. I'm not going into details. I'm sick of everything and ready for things to be over... I was ready 10 days ago. .Monday. Wake up with something that feels like a hang over but is really just a really bad headache. Walk to the bathroom. Realized that I cried myself to sleep and then almost shit myself (yes, Paul, shit myself) when I see how puffy my eyes are. I get to school late. Play shitty on my down-the-line. Talk to Snydee about my Sunday. She sympathizes. I walk to art. I walk to advanced algebra. Kellman bitches at me about my sunglasses. I cry. He caves in and allows the glasses. I finish two quizzes and a section in class. He feels better about things. I feel better about things. I leave school. I hung out with Joce after work. We had the most random day. We got coffee and then I took her to her therapy appointment. I then picked her up an hour later and we came to my house, went through my mom's old jewelry she's getting rid of. We take some of it before it gets trashed, sold, or given away. We then dye our hair. Blonde for Joce. Red roots for me. She drinks her white russian, I'm driving so I put mine in the fridge. I take her home. Come back and now I'm here. Getting an ear-full from my dad about being up so late. I guess that's my cue to leave.  Tomorrow is going to be spent at a party getting drunk with Can-too, his chica-amiga Katlyn, and Joce; over at Jared's apartment. It will be great. I get to stay after school to practice my part with Snydee... oh yay! Not. Alright I'm getting obsessively tired, and really don't want my mom to bitch me out more than my dad has already.   Do you come from the land down under? Do you want to?  Yes Paul.... I miss you... lmao. I miss Nick more... now I just need to figure out how to get him to ditch his girlfriend. Like he'd leave her for me... I need to get real...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to my first hangover... ever. It's not really a hangover, though I do feel a headache coming on. Maybe I'm still drunk. Lightweight.  So last night was spent in A2 with Mike. We went to get coffee and then headed to Pinball Pete's for some pool and CRACK. Hahaha. Went to Outback Steakhouse for dinner with Mom, Brother, Brother's girlfriend, Brother's girlfriend's sister, Nick (yeeeeaah.... we won't go there, will we Mike?), and Mike. Came home and got so drunk I couldn't see straight. YAY! And now I'm ready to throw up whatever bile has accumulated in my stomach, maybe last night's JACKAROO AND CHEEEEEEESE. BOO! Nick takes public humiliation very well.   Today...  I think I'll be spending 11am-2pm with B in downtown A2 at Hash Bash, hopefully won't see my parent's there. My mom invited me. I really think she desperately wants me to smoke pot. If anything, just so we have something in common. I really wonder sometimes, how mother and daughter can be so completely different, don't even get my started on my dad. Then I pick up Mike from Jake's house and take him to Kettering with me where I get wasted out of my gourd and hang out with a bunch of engineering students / fraternity guys. Tonight will be spent being the easy whore I am... because I'm easy, and a whore. Oh, tonight will be great. One problem, I need to make it back before midnight. Drinking and driving will not occur, but it's Hash Bash so you just know I'm going to be stoned all fucking day. Today will be good. Today will be great. Today will be stoner-riffic.  I sometimes wish I could do this stuff with you... *sigh* But I'll forget and everything will be okay, at least for that short period of time. I just have to keep repeating that in my mind. Everything will be okay. Everything will be okay. Everything will be okay. I don't believe myself sometimes. Bet you won't read this... but that's okay. Everything will be okay.  Mornings.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Considering the time it was created, I'm judging my ratings off of that for some of the answers but most of them apply to my current knowledge.  MIKE'S GEEK CODE ("I'm not a geek, I'm a brother of a geek" - M. Custer):  GE/GFA/GMU dpu s+:+ a--- C++ UL- P@ L+ E? N+  W++                   ASHLEY'S GEEK CODE (don't laugh at me please... *hears snickering in the distance*):  GU d--@ s: a----- C++ !U P>+ L+ E? W++ N+ !o@ K- w !O M V? PS+++ PE Y+ PGP- t+++ 5 X+ R tv+ b+ DI++> D++ !G e- h!>h+ r--->r- z+>++  Fuck geek code block, I'm too drunk... blah! If Mike is not a geek, I am the queen of computer illiteracy. THE MUTHAFUCKINQUEEEEEEEEEN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm posting two entries, one's about seniors last day, and the other is about more serious matters.   I woke up later than usual. Didn't go to class, obviously. Instead I took a bag and placed a spare change of clothes, two boxes of water balloons, my make-up bag, and two cans of red bull into it. I took and shower and put on some scrubby clothes, grabbed my purse and scrambled out the door after putting my bag of supplies into two tubs.  I drove to Michelle's house to wake her up, I passed by the pre-dismissal high school with 5 police cars parked outside, every spare teacher / administrative being were standing, guarding. I got to Michelle's house and woke up her up, she got dressed, we filled water balloons, and then headed out to begin the war.   We drove by the high school again, everyone had been let out I'd assume at 10:18 or something. So we cruised Wallace neighborhood and eventually spotted a white mini-van (belonging to Billy Firn) with SENIORS 'O4!!! plastered on the back. So we stalked him, he tried to get us to pull around to "talk" to us, but we knew better. They met up with a silver station wagon belonging to Alonzo and Alan and all those shits. We said "fuck it" to Billy's hoard of people, and started stalking the wagon. Then drove all the way back to my neighborhood then stopped at the stop sign on the corner of Edison and Burns after we threw a couple balloons at their car. Here come the jackasses with eggs and silly string, I fortunately peeled out fast enough to dodge the egg, they weren't quick enough prepping the string. We took them on a cat and mouse chase all through the suburb, getting trapped once behind Billy's car, and some white Grand-Am that tried to race me earlier. They busted out with more eggs, and we called it quits with the water balloons. I was so pissed off. Michelle and I went to Walgreens and picked up a carton of eggs and some shaving cream (which we never actually used), and came back to fuck with the seniors. It was payback time. We hit them three times, all across the senior bullshit on the back of the mini-van. Alonzo got hit with a ricochet water balloon that hit the side of his car first, but splashed all over him. We had gone by Jeanette, Patrick, Brian, and all those fuckers and gotten egged so we drove by their place and threw a nice little sticky egg to the back of their freshly cleaned car. We camped outside Ned's house after getting a car wash ourselves, and cleaned the remnants of egg off my car. We waited for him to arrive so we could chuck the last three balloons at either him or his car. He was a no show. Oh well.  Michelle and I headed to Pinball Pete's for some after-war celebrations, but we were both whipped. Got our usual Starbucks, and played some pool, DDR, driving games, blah blah blah. We were thinking about heading to the Detroit Electronic Music Festival, but it's Sat, Sun, Mon; not Fri, Sat, Sun. Oh well... we're going Sunday instead.   I'll post my little emotional break down sometime later... I'd end up throwing something breakable at my wall (probably the laptop) if I do it now. I'm too pissed off.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not trying to tell anyone anything but could people please leave some type of signature on the comments. I'm not scared to talk about my opinions, and you should feel just as open. It'd just be nice and respectful.  As for today, I don't really know. I woke up really late, I was going to attend 5th hour, but then Gareth and Michelle appeared from the East Wing doors of the school and we went to Starbucks. I came to 6th hour, and watched senior speeches. I'm going to miss Stephen like no other. Ever since 10th grade, when I met him, he was a cool guy.... only I had a crush on his scrawny ass back then. lol.   So I was sort of inspired to write my own little senior message thing... Give me a break, I have a year to go. My round up of the years past...  One year left, yup. One year until this hell is over. But to tell you the truth I don't know why I call it hell, because I've grown attached to high school. It's really where most of my life has taken place... and that's probably because I'm there 10 months a year, 5 days a week, 6 hours a day. That, or everything relates somehow to my high school life.    Freshman Year:  I was young and alone, and getting into this huge school of too many people that were too old to hang around some little freshman girl. I associated myself with friends that I'd known from years past. Returning to my former schools only once to talk of childhood with my old teachers. I can't believe that Mrs. Williams still remembered me from 1st, 3rd, and 4th grades; or how Mrs. Rust is now gone, or even how Mrs. Johnston still has those old Garfield posters still up on the wall. My freshman classes consisted of Computer Aided Drafting, College Preparatory Biology, Algebra, Varsity Band, Honors English 9, and US History. In my CAD class I usually slept, or talked with those who I'd known from the robotics team. I was booted off of inventor to work with Jeremy Knox on 3D Studio Max. Mr. Meyer was the coolest teacher in the world, and I will never forget that one eye-brow hair that I just wanted pluck off his god damn face. lol. In CP Bio, I met Nick (Marc's nephew) and played GameBoy, as they toyed with their stupid Tech Decks. I met this girl, Sarah French, and tried to help her through her tough time as a sophomore. We didn't really spend a lot of time together until my sophomore year. In Algebra, I goofed off with the other Nick, met Michelle Colon's sister Nikki (who was doing announcements at the time). She suggested for me to read Swimming Sweet Arrow, so I did and that's actually where the thought of sex began... sadly. I had my petty fights with Sally, befriended her for the sake of Cassie and I's relationship, but that slowly went down the tubes too. To band I would go, before lunch, and Leach was the best director on the face of this planet. We were the suckiest band in the school, but his lectures and stories only made me try harder to be the best performer in the class, and that got me into Symphonic Band the following year. Unfortunately, the teacher that I loved got the job of his dreams at another school. Shortly after his departure I went to visit him at Pioneer High in Ann Arbor during my sophomore year. After befriending Michelle in my US History class, she introduced me to Keith, and we all became friends. In Honors English, I met Zakk and Isaac, I originally thought that Zakk was gay and Isaac was sorta cute... but I had my eyes set on the 19-year-old Allen Vasher at the time. Zakk turned out to be quite a character, and an acquaintance. While Isaac didn't get to really know me until Marching Band this past year. In 6th hour, US History, I met this chick, Michelle. I didn't, at first, realize that she was the sister to Nikki (in my Algebra class). We dicked around, and Mr. Burnett was the coolest, never took an exam... ever. Got all A's for sitting and talking about history, it was the best class in the world. After school I was sent into my professional life as a member of the YHS robotics team. Learning everything I could I dedicated my life to that team for the longest time. Who would have known that my second year, as a high school freshman, would be my last. As I broke away my ties from a group I had originally proclaimed as my family brought me to loneliness, but Keith and Michelle slowly filled the void that had been created from heartbreak, as my naive little mind believed that my disfuctional family had betrayed me. Fortunate for me, the guy I fell for, Allen Richard Vasher, decided to date my immature little ass... and so things began there. My freshman year ended with a bang, plans for summer events were brought up, being hit with water balloons filled with detergent during seniors last day, and smoking too much pot over the summer... yet never getting stoned.   Sophomore Year:  Michelle and I's falling out over the summer reintroduced me to Cassie and with that came Tamika, Sarah, and Leah. The class line up? Honors English 10, Symphonic Band, Advanced Algebra, College Preparatory Chemistry, Geometry, and Government / Forensics. Waking up, and seeing Mrs. Griffin (SHE'S A BIRD!!!) was not the most interesting of mornings in my entire life, but I slowly lived through the agony that was English. The only English class I almost failed, it just sucked... there was nothing interesting or amusing about that class... well, with the exception of playing jokes on the Mrs. Griffin / Griffelkin / SHE'S A BIRD!!!. Symphonic Band, a new director, who I learned to hate. We still sucked, just more. And this time there was little motivation to stay in the class. Some how by the end of the school year, Rudi, Amelia, Katie, and others had conveniently convinced me to sign the papers for Marching Band my junior year. Chemistry was exciting, I met a new best friend, Tamika, in the process. Tie-Dye, Mr. Krause explaining how polystyrene bursts into flames, memorizing the table of elements (which I just realized was on Henk and I's place-mats as children), barely passing the class, Honda motorcycles, Tiki and I hoarding all the chemistry equipment in our storage drawer, and Happy HONIFBRCL (hon-if-brick-el, pronounced properly. My brother at least knows what I'm talking about). Geometry was a bore, slept through most of it, had Tamika again, and people wonder why we're friends now... jeeze. I couldn't get away from the girl! jk jk I    Junior Year:  The first semester passed by so fast, mainly thanks to Marching Band. I got buff from lifting equipment. My van was constantly packed full of instruments, parked up on the sidewalk, and blasting music. The speakers are now ripped. Damn stock speakers. I switched class schedules just about as much as I switched hair colors. I never really had time to adjust to the teachers or get really involved with them, well at least not until second semester... Where I learn that Mrs. Otwell is awesome, and Kellman takes too much shit from us. This was the year of change. I made amends with Michelle, started hanging out with my brother, and became a real party girl. Near the beginning of the year, I was so certain nothing was to change, but now I'm just waiting for things to lead me in different directions, for things to change and for me to take the flow of the current.. I'm excited for senior year, but dreading it. This is going to be my last year to possibly get my shit together before going off into the real world. But hanging around a bunch of college kids makes the transition seem less daunting.  One more year. This is it. I'm excited. Bring it on...  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No more book work in Kellman's class. All worksheets for the rest of the school year. No tests from here on out either... with the exception of the final.   Today: School was good. Ms. Rowley and Ms. Matis weren't in the media center today so I decided to steal two honor society roses (even though I didn't make national honor society) and some hall passes. Might need those later. Michelle, Gareth, and I left after 4th hour. Went to Pinball Pete's, had some fun. "Well, that's not half as bad as when he tried to fit his dick in the bottle." "No, I think deep throating the bottle was worse." lmfao. "He was pretty good at that." Damn, Ned's so fucked up.  I want to throw my towel in on this life, move away and just start over. I know I'd miss a lot of people but maybe that would give me a chance to start again. Get all this shit out of my head. Back when James and I were still messing around (yeah, I know you remember this, Josh and Mike both know what I'm talking about... perhaps Michelle and Tiki) he told me that I can't run from my problems. lol. I just said, "I just did." And hung up. I haven't talked with him since. I ran away, back to my middle school / high school life and he ran away to the ROTC, he's in South Korea now. And the cursor just blinks... not much to say...  Don't rescue me When I play with with fire Don't need to know Is this desire We hold back words Our eyes are giving away Deny the past We've come to radiate In need of some substance In need of some substance A little's less than nothing In need of some substance The sun might set Tonight could be the night And if that's the case You'll get on all right But there's no point In spoiling for a fight Because we're blinded by The darkest ray of light  I look at my life. Just high school in general, and I realize I'll never stand up to what my brother has accomplished. I'm such a family fuck up.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The concert was great.  The turn out was awesome. And the band fucking ROCKED. I was so happy. So blissfully happy.  MtDewGirl87: I had some kind of attack at the concert junknerd: ? MtDewGirl87: yeah MtDewGirl87: that's what I said junknerd: attack like what? MtDewGirl87: I was dancing and taking pictures, smoking a cigarette when I felt the need to sit down. So I asked Michelle if she wanted to sit, she said she was okay with standing but if I wanted to I could go. MtDewGirl87: So I nodded and walked to two open chairs MtDewGirl87: I sat down for not even a minute when I told her I had to go to the rest room MtDewGirl87: she said she wanted to come along too MtDewGirl87: so I walked in and two of the stalls were free of doors, and the others were occupied MtDewGirl87: so when the next stall opened up (the handicapped one) I went in then blacked out MtDewGirl87: I woke up apparently a few minutes later, and broke out in a cold sweat MtDewGirl87: she thinks it was an anxiety attack junknerd: sounds possible to me junknerd: hope you're ok MtDewGirl87: I'm fine now MtDewGirl87: but it was weird MtDewGirl87: how was your night?  LMAO. Besides the random attack, the concert was beyond my expectations.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know it was a short departure from my last entry but here...   urlLink LosT   It's worth the time. And I didn't see that coming from a fucking mile away.  I owed you, your hug and I got much more than I even bargained for in return. Thanks, I think it's all dissipating. Plus, "I think you're cute." LMAO. The time spent with friends... and no, I no longer feel alone. Don't ask me why I'm finally accepting things so openly. I'm just crazy like that, and you know it.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need someone who's 18 or older, lives in southeast Michigan, and wants to go to a Zero 7 concert. Call / IM / e-mail me by 7pm or meet me at the Majestic Theatre in Detroit. I don't care who... I just don't want to have any parental unit there...  Skipped 2-6th hours and went to Josh's house. Did homework. Slept. Woke up. My battery is almost dead on my cell. Dammit. ZERO 7! TONIGHT! AHHH!!!   Remember Michelle: "Damn, if Zero 7 was coming into town I think I'd be the most retarded about it." So what happens? Zero 7 comes into town...   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AHH!! Andrea is the fucking BEST! I'm just bouncing off the walls! How does she do it? How the hell do you just reach inside me and pull me out of such a shitty day? OH OH! Here...  Ash: I talked with him... (Nick) Andee: I wondered why someone (aka you) was in a good mood... how was it? Ash: Better. A lot better.. I guess. ARE YOU STONED OR SOMETHING?! Andee: Well... it's definately good things are better. That makes life a little easier, no? I 'm not stoned, persay. I forgot how to spell. Ash: lol.  p.s. Dan is hotttt!!! But yeah, we didn't talk much but he sounded like he had something on his mind. So I'm beyond curious now. But I did tell you about the whole instant messenger ordeal.. (I go on to explain the instant messenger ordeal). I think he's hiding something. Andee: Yeah, no kidding... now I'm super curious! I wonder what it is... Was he all nervous about it? Hmm... I have to know now. Ash: Me too. It's driving me insane! I can't spell either. What do you think he's hiding (if anything)? Andee: I have no idea. Maybe he's a hermaphrodite or maybe he thinks Snydee is hott... lol. Ash: Well, I've narrowed down to a couple possibilities. A) He's SOOOOO in love with me he can barely stand keeping it a secret (lol, what a joke) or B) He thinks me liking / loving him is fucking rediculous. (more than likely) Andee: Maybe he just wants to talk to you about liking him, neither bad nor good, you know? I decided you and I are going to have wild passionate sex right now, k? Ash: Sounds good to me! Perhaps. Then there's selection C. C) He doesn't want to lose our great GREAT  GREAT  friendship over this. Which is almost a joke because we do talk but I'm always too scared to say anything. I'm shy like that sometimes. Damn, Amazing Graze  Andee: Grace.. Grace can make me all warm baby! Ahh! Never again will I take that shit. I was excited that Michelle IM'd me online. She can join the wild passion sex too. Ash: Seriously. I've had some wild dreams about her! o.O lol. Andee: Damn, I'm jelious. Is she 1/2? Wow, that's all rude of me to ask. Ash: I don't know. We made out to give the druken frat guys hard-ons up at Kettering. But we were just joking around. But about the 1/2 thing, I dunno.  Andee: Hmm.. curious. Don't worry that makeout thing is never going to leave my lips.  We went on to plot out a part in the movie where a 3-some takes place between Jordan, Jocelyn, and Jamie.  More to come later... I've got to go and sort some stuff out. Damn, Coldplay is making me really happy for some reason.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "For a shitty day, today's going pretty good..." "Isn't that an oxymoron or something?"  Why is there a party bus all up in my ass? lol.  I was trying to find a use for a fifth wheel. Steering? Because that's what Michelle and I decided I'd be... well, if I would have stayed the obliviously happy girl I was a week ago.  But with last night's killer low I'm surprised I'm still alive. Or something. The music line up for today? Dashboard Confessional, Something Corporate, and Maroon 5. Depressing, I know. I couldn't get to sleep last night. I woke up late for school. Forgot my flute. Said that I lost it. She bought it. I was half conscious up until 3rd hour. I saw Nick online when I was in Kellman's room, but it felt wrong of me to say anything. I don't know, it was just weird. I took my quiz. "Just let the little things make you happy." I was just happy that I could get my mind off of this emotional chaos and onto something that seemed to matter less... but it distracted me, so I guess that's a good thing. I got my first A on a math quiz... ever. 12/13. Kellman thought that I cheated. I need to give Josh a hug for helping me out last night. I would have never passed that quiz. So as he told me, to have the little things make me happy, to smile even if you're drowning in tears, I smiled. It was the fakest smile in the world, but I felt better... and I fucking smiled. I then left for Starbucks at lunch with Michelle and Gareth, they made me laugh and all was fine. Came back for 5th hour. Made my schedule for the week. Congratulations to me, I have two days of complete freedom. Saturday and Monday. Then 6th hour was alright. I performed my monologue, and everyone loved it. I smiled... again. I snuck out of class 20 minutes early, went to my car to be alone. I apologize Tiki for not taking you home.  I'm bottoming out, but it will eventually go back up. It took awhile last time, but I'll be alright. I almost forgot what it's like to be this way, I'm getting used to it again. Plus I'm on a roll, I haven't cried yet today.  It's like this Nick, I hate to love you but can't bare the thought of loving to hate you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night.  I'm going to be honest. Take it or leave it... just don't leave me.  First of all, Josh, all bets are off. If I'm going to do this, I'm doing it on my terms. Fuck money and fuck proving people wrong. I'm going to prove myself wrong. No one else matters except the people involved. I'm so fucking scared.  I've forgotten who I am. And I know I've been saying this for awhile, but I feel so blank and empty. Care not, everyone. Care not. Because it wouldn't be a change from my current situation. You can say you care all you'd like but no one has done ANYTHING to prove that. Two people, Michelle and Tiki. Josh has been a weight on either shoulder, letting me down and pushing me up at the same time. That's the reason I left last night, if you're ever so curious. But everyone seemed to stay sitting, speechless, careless. So I will be alone, and I will not be fine. I'm not okay, so if you want to fix things don't just push me up to let me down.   Hey Josh, painless way to commit suicide? But I'm not a quitter, I'm just... invisible or something.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There you go Josh...       THIS WAY UP         SomethingAshley has fragile contents which may break!     Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After about 15 minutes of trying to get off the phone with him while Nick was here, even saying "goodnight, talk to you in the morning." And explaining that if they wanted to hang out they'd have to come over at 11:00pm-12:00, Mike calls me when I'm ready to fall asleep. I ask to talk with Josh (big mistake) and then I get hung up on. Josh calls back, and I get hung up on. Josh calls back, and I get hung up on. Josh calls back.... and gives me a lecture. "I was thinking about saying it, but I didn't because I knew it'd hurt you." or something to that extent. Well, sorry to say Josh, but that was the wrong fucking sentence to use. It hurt even more for you to agree with what I said then to just play it off. And you KNEW it would hurt me. You fucking knew it. I know we said we'd be brutally honest but you knew that I wasn't feeling that great and for anything of the sort to be brought up was just... Aggravating.   "Let me guess... You think this time it's the same as Allen." "You just want men until they give themselves up to you." "No, I think it's different this time." "Well, I wasn't going to say I agreed with that, but I was thinking it. Maybe it's just like how Allen was..."  I'm not wearing the dress tonight. I don't even know if I want to go out anywhere today. And the last person I want to see is Nick... because that was all about him...     I'm going to climb back into bed and listen to depressing music while curled in a ball under my covers. Hopefully I'll just shrivel up and die.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nick randomly drove down. I got a call at about 9:30.  "Hey, I'm in Ypsi." "Dammit, Nick..." "What?" "I just woke up and my room's a fucking mess."  I did a quick clean up before he arrived. Josh and Mike were suppose to come over too, but the second wave of storms hit and they stayed at Angie's place. I took Nick out for Starbucks and then we went for a drive in the RX7. After hanging out at my house for a bit, he decided to leave and stay the night at Kettering (even though he's going to end up down here in the morning anyway, oh well). The weather is bad, I hope he makes it back safely. I don't know if he didn't stay because his shit's in Kettering or because Mike and Josh didn't show up. Which ever reason, I don't mind. My dad got pissed that he was in my room anyway. I helped him clean out the car and then he drove off, and I ran back inside.   I'm now trying on my "prom dress" for tomorrow night. I don't know if I want to wear a dress anymore. Maybe if we come back to my house I'll dress up but I don't want to wear this all tomorrow night. They can deal with it...  I also hope my asshole of a brother shows up tomorrow. Maybe we'll make amends over a couple beers and some shots.  Contemplation.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... or else they might eat you.  It feels like 4 days rolled into one.  Day One: DDR Madness. Michelle and I went to Pinball Petes and played DDR and pool before getting out usual Starbucks and heading out.  Day Two: The Picnic. Senior Skip Day was today, the seniors had a picnic down at Loonfeather Park. Met up with Andrea and Chloe. Talked a shitload before getting a page from Q. We went out to Q's house but he wasn't home and Ryan wouldn't answer the door, so we left.  Day Three: The Tornado. We came back to my neighborhood and chilled at the park at about 2:10, so I could smoke a cigarette before heading to the mall.  "Damn, those clouds look menacing." "Yeah... It's like a sunset or something. All dark over there but bright as hell in that direction." "Hey look, it's turning green." *Ashley's Cell Phone Rings* "Hello." "Hey, it's Josh, you might want to go home and stay there for awhile. I don't know where you're at right now, but you might want to find some shelter." "Okay, bye." We quickly drove to my house as the wind picked up. I wasn't too scared up until the clouds starting passing by as fast as the cars that passed us down the street. We sat in my car for awhile, and then decided to head inside when the wind got worse. I didn't think my mother was home, so I went looking for my grandfather. I was screaming his name and then I heard the dog barking from what seemed like outside. I ran to the back door and almost got blown away yelling for my dog to come inside. My mom finally yelled my name and then told us to come down into the basement. I stayed there for awhile, but then decided to go and find my cat. Sonya was sitting pretty chill in my room, so Michelle and I got the cat carrier, but as soon as I picked the cat up she pissed all over me. It was hilarious but pissed me off. I ran into the basement just as my mom yell, "forget the cat!" But I ended up taking her anyway. I think she's still angry about the whole thing (my cat of course). After everything pretty much blew over, I went back upstairs to change and called a few people. Josh was driving back from Arby's, examining the damage done to our little town. I invited him over so he'd have a place to hang in case another wave was to hit. Apparently the next wave is coming tonight.  Day Four: The Mall. I took my mom to her alergist to get her injection. Michelle and I chain smoked a cigarette in my car like little 15-year-olds or something, before my mom came back out to the car. "I need to put something in my mouth." lol. I'm such a dork sometimes. We then went to the mall for our little shopping spree. My mom's car isn't fixed yet, so she's not leaving for WI until Tuesday. That sucks. I bought a lot of clothing and two new pairs of shoes. Fun shit. Michelle and I the headed to Makara for dinner after dropping my mom off at Louis Cafe. We had the biggest dinner in the world. I still feel like I'm going to puke from eating so much.  And now I shall make a fifth day out of my 24 hours by hanging out with someone, anyone, tonight.  Tomorrow's events will hopefully go smoothly. Nick's coming down for sushi and Starbucks. Then we're having the party at Mike's. Hopefully. That or things will be moved to my house.  Mom, Dad, don't ask questions....
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot that it was a bad time to drive... I should have taken Packard.  I'm in a horrible mood. Being shot down on the spot was like hell. Hell.  Well, we'll discuss the upside to my day before going into the depressing shit. Woke up late again, I headed to Espresso Royale and picked up some coffee for Donald and I. I dropped that off at work and chatted up a storm... well, at least until Maria got there. (depressing point #1). So I left and went to school. I got to 4th hour and restocked the printer cartridges in the media storage closet. (depressing point #2). I finished my painting on the window late into 5th hour, then got a pass to Otwell's class. I did nothing for an hour, well with the exception of arguing semantics with Mrs. Otwell. And before I wasted another hour of my life, I decided to leave. I walked down to the lower lot with Madeline. Thank god Rex seemed to have the day off or something. So I went to Starbucks with the intention of doing homework, I instead wrote more to the movie script. I think I have ADD or something. (depressing point #3). I got pissed after writing the scene with Jocelyn, Natilie, and Bret... it was so sad. It's just one of things that you can see playing out in real life, but it just pissed me off. (depressing point #4). Some bitchy, loud girls showed up and spoiled my mood even more. So I left. I was going to go to work, or home, just somewhere. Then I decided that DDR would change my mood for the better. I played the quarter machine only to be kicked off my some asian guys that broke the Extreme DDR machine. (depressing point #5). So I put the remaining change in my pocket, assuming that parking payment was going to be a bitch. Meanwhile, on my way up the stairs to Forest Street parking structure, some guy, that had been stalking me on the DDR machine yells, "Hey DDR Girl! You're really cute!" In a state of confusion, I looked around assuming he was talking to someone else, but yelled "thanks" when I realized he was speaking to me. I ran... RAN to the parking structure and got in my car. I didn't mean to run. I just ran. I paid for parking then headed to work. Worked, then left early to have dinner with my parents. Dinner was okay. We came back to the house and I played my amusing voice messages for my mom and Tom. I called Andrea and we talked for awhile. We're going to the Senior Skip Day Picnic together tomorrow. (which made me extremely happy) I then decided to go for a drive, realizing that the choir concert was tonight I went to the high school in hopes to see people that I knew. I talked to a few people, then left. Nick understands what happened. (depressing point #6). I came home in a pissy mood and explained my situation to Nick. Now we're trying to find him a nickname... I need sleep. I'm going to die. I need a Red Bull.  *passes out*
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If my scale is correct, I just lost 20 pounds in the past month.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morning: Woke up late. Went to 4th and 5th hours.   Afternoon: Doctors appointment. I'm okay right now, but they're sending me in for more useless testing. Work was aggravating. Terrible customer issues.  Evening: Got out of work. Went to Michelle's and we went out to South University to play DDR and get Starbucks. Talked with her co-worker Steve(?) for a few. Headed home after playing some pool. DDR kicked my ass tonight. lol. I can't believe I'm writing about DDR.   Night: I dropped Michelle off at home. Then headed back here. Josh called and we talked for a few before Reanda showed up. He told me that I have this way of turning a man mentally ill after dating them. I called Allen. Yes, you read that right. I called Allen. He's doing alright. Damn, I miss him. Did I just type that? Well... I do... He said I should join the Robotics team in the fall again. I'm considering.  I need to get homework finished. I've slacked off enough for this semester. I'm going to a full day of school tomorrow, but participating in Senior Skip Day on Friday. Mother / Daughter shopping extravaganza on Friday afternoon. Ah.. well off to homework and sleep.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a dream I sold my soul to the devil. I knew I should have set my alarm to wake me up, because I couldn't wake myself up for the life of me.  Mike and April broke up or are one a "break." I talked with Mike last night, he's alright. I need to talk with April, I'm worried about her. To tell you the truth I thought she broke up with him. Oops...  And as for the remnants of yesterday, I went to the mall and bought a dress (I know you're proud Michelle) after getting my car back from the Ford Service Department. I knew I wanted to by something, I just didn't know what. I changed my work hours. Monday, Wednesday, Thursday, and Sunday. Now only 4 days of work instead of 5. I don't know how I'll live with 6 hours on Sunday but we'll see. I need to find a new job.  I'm too lazy to go into detail of what's pissed me off the last couple days, but I should probably turn in my applications to colleges and companies.   8:00, I think I actually might go to class today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hate me. Please do it.  I'm off to go stalk Mike down and solve his relationship problems for him. Exciting, isn't it?  Tamika, I know you're pissed at me. I was going to talk to you at school today but you weren't in 6th hour. Watch out... I might stalk you down as well.  I was driving to Varsity Ford to put my car in for service and I realized that I no longer know who I am... I have too many problems to figure out for other people, I'll find myself later.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today... hm...  Woke up late. Escaped the wrath of Rex and skipped band for Starbucks. Went on the art pillar field trip extravaganza. Not much excitement there. A lot of writing though, the script is coming a long very nicely.  Went to Michelle's house during 6th hour with Gareth to find her half naked and passed out on her bed. Gareth was happy.  I got to work and planned out a new schedule. Left at 6 to talk with my dad for an hour. I'm officially grounded from Kettering, after talking with my mom while going clubbing with her last night. Father agrees. Dad, Opa, and I went out to dinner and then to see my art project. My dad has turned into more of a dad recently. I like the change. I've never really had a real dad before... *sigh*  Hung out with Josh, went out for a drive and talked about the shit going on in our lives.  I'm so sick of this broken feeling. It's forever lingering in my rib cage. And it's turned from painful to annoying. I just need to get my aggressions out some how. I'm so pissed...  --- EDITED ---  I had to delete that, I'd ruin so many things going for me. I'm too weak for this.   ... and the crying begins. I wonder how long it's going to be this time...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that I'm not in a bitchy mood...  Okay, I must apologize for the last few entries. Somehow my emotions got the best of me. It's called being a teenage girl, I guess. This is going to be really long, but do please, read on. It will explain a lot of the shit that went on in the past few entries...  Friday, I was obviously a raging lunatic. I got to the school late and bitched out everyone in my path. When I got to my locker, it wouldn't open (because I always get the ghetto locker) so I kicked the shit out of it then slammed my fist only to have it bounce back and open before my eyes. I should get pissed more often, seeing as it opens lockers on command (because I always get the ghetto locker). I flicked a few people off, Keith observed my presence by yelling "Hey, slut!" as I retorted with "FUCK OFF!!" Andrea listen to my ranting spree, and I felt a little better. I decided that I'd change in the hall in front of everyone because they don't care and I couldn't give a flying fuck. Cole walked by and started making weird noised then said, "Strip!!" As I told him, "GO TO HELL!" I then decided that I was going to do every drug in the world that night. "I'm getting SO fucked up tonight. E, Coke, Pot, Alcohol, hell... heroin too. Does anyone have any Oxy-Contin? How about Crack?" Isaac was even scared. He's like, "As long as I'm not the one you're pissed at... all is good, because I'd hate to see what you're going to do to the dude that's to blame." I laughed. At least someone made me smile. Keith's new girlfriend followed him around like a lost puppy, I laughed some more. The concert was fucking great, in my opinion. It was hilarious to see Brian singing. Jeanette was awesome. We won't talk about Sally's "solo." And the fuzzy amp. But Symphonic band was great, and Wind Symphony (this sounds cocky but) we were the SHIT. Plato's was just... Indescribable. It was just sweet. Someone (I can't really remember) told me that I looked upset the entire time. I was actually on the verge of tears. But I got my mind off of the people that were too busy (COUGH henk COUGH COUGH) to show up. He would have fallen asleep anyway.  Friday night was spent being a drunken fool. Josh and I did a shot of vodka, and I shared some Cranberry Vodka cocktail with Mike, I also had a beer or two or three. Woke up Saturday around 5 or 6am with Josh laying on me, decided I should go to my room because I didn't want to make people worried that we did anything.. which we didn't. And the rest is described in previous entries.  After yesterday's events had past I slept, a lot. I sat on my ass for around 16 hours or so. Maybe more. Watching VH1's top 50 worst songs ever. My mom was probably stoned when she stumbled into my room and decided to sleep in my "warm and soft bed." I tried not to kick her when I had my terrible dreams but I didn't really care. I woke up and she was gone... then I got an instant message from Donald about my weekend and how I needed to get him coffee. I decided a few more hours of ass-sitting laziness would be good. But then I got an instant message from Keehn. He basically apologized for the things said and done on Friday. No apology yet from my brother. I can't get a hold of him to know when Mike and April are coming home (her car is still outside my house). After the conversation I became active enough to stop being a depressed, lazy bastard; so I got off my ass and went for a drive. I couldn't stop smiling. I almost went to church, but they don't have a service at noon-thirty. Plus, I thought it would be best if I didn't listen to sermons for an hour or so. I drove to Penisular Park and wrote more to the script. I can't think of a name for it, but it's all good. It will come with time.  I randomly went to Michelle's house afterward, to see if she wanted to have some Starbucks for coffee talk of our evenings / mornings. She went to William's last night for a bit then went over to Chloe and Kevin's place for fun with alcohol. We went to Old Navy for shopping and then to Pinball Pete's for our DDR workout program. I think we played 14 games or something. Went to Middle Earth and Starbucks to finish off the "Nick Sushi & Starbucks Raincheck Project." Then went back to PP for pool. Lots of fun. Now I'm exhausted tho. I've got homework to do, and cleaning of room. I have to go through all of my clothing and figure out what I'm getting rid of and where everything needs to be.   Tomorrow I've got school and work as usual. I have to talk to my mom about changing my hours around. This summer is going to be strange. I think I might work two jobs, that or quit Provide.Net to work somewhere else. We'll see...  All is well, and I'm alright.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i feel stupid - but i know it won't last for long i've been guessing - i could of been guessing wrong you don't know me now i kind of thought that you should somehow does that whole mad season got you down  i feel stupid but it's something that comes and goes i've been changing - think it's funny how no one knows we don't talk about - the little things that we do without when that whole mad season comes around  so why you got to stand there looking like the answer now it seems to me - you'd come around i need you now do you think you can cope you figured me out - i'm lost and i'm hopeless bleeding and broken - though i've never spoken i come undone - in this mad season  i feel stupid - but i think i been catching on i feel ugly - but i know i still turn you on you seem colder now, torn apart, angry, turned around will that whole mad season knock you down  so are you going to stand there are you going to help me out you need to be together now - i need you now  now i'm crying - isn't that what you want i'm trying to live my life on my own but i won't at times - i do believe i am strong so someone tell me why, why, why do i feel stupid and i came undone 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Enough of that. I hate having to do that.  I went to bed around 5am after talking with Josh for a long while. I think I'll take a nap in a bit.  I woke up at around 9:30am. Brother and Co. were gone to Canada by then.  *door bell, looks out the window*  LMAO. Some door-to-door solicitor holding a box that says FRESH on the front. Vanna White wannabe.  Anyway. I went downstairs to wake Josh up, and we went out for Starbucks. Talked about last night and why I wasn't invited to Canada. I told him I no longer care. I figure it's the whole "little sis tagging along" situation. Went back to my house to chill, we were going to watch Kill Bill before he had to go to work, but Michelle called. She came over and we hung out for awhile. Went back to Starbucks. She asked why I wasn't in Canada. Discussed that situation, yet again. I must of said or done something wrong. And damn... does it hurt to be left out, or even worse, having your friend invited but not you. Josh turned them down because of work and what not. Well, I don't know what Henk and Nick's intentions were, but if it was to hurt me they've succeeded. :-/  Michelle and I talked about her and Ned as well. I haven't really taken thing to heart, well at least not until this morning. I put myself in her shoes and Ned did a lot of things to break her heart. Looking at it now, I don't know how she deals with it, because if that shit were to happen to me I'd be a complete mess. We went to Pinball Pete's for some DDR stress relief, I lost at pool but I felt really good after playing. I don't know why, I mean I fucking lost, but I'm in such a better mood.   I really appreciate Josh and Michelle for being the upper to my down time. I don't really know how I'd survive without some people... much love.  >>-- 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a ranting spree to go on. Not really a rant, though it may turn out that way, it's really just to explain why I'm not hanging out with Sarah anymore. Immaturity... fucking squared. Yesterday in the media center was enough to want make me want to hurl. First off, the downloading of the video of the U.S. soldier being decapitated... that's too much right there. Okay, what kind of sick fuck do you need to be to search the net for that footage? Then watch it not once, but twice. If that was, say, your brother would you want that video put out on the net? Would you want the world looking in disgust at one of your closest friends or family members being publicly humiliated in a foreign country? I think not. So why did you do it? Curiosity killed the god damn cat... do you have a death wish? Because I can grant you clearance to an afterlife if that's what you please. Or perhaps you'd like your head chopped off in front of a camera only to have the footage posted in the internet. Secondly, poking fun at the rape situation at the school in the media center was not even cool. Not in the slightest. Please, for the sake of those around you, put your morals higher and grow up a bit... at least to the point where everything isn't a fucking joke. No one is laughing anymore.  Yeah, that sounded bitchy but that needs to be out there. And she wonders why the hell I don't want to talk with her. Just because we both apologized for the falling out doesn't mean I want you to run up and converse with me every time you see me. I don't want to talk to you. So leave me the hell alone. Please. I have enough shit to deal with... I don't need any of this.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I think it's over. Finally.  Today's events have been strangely smashed together and then stepped on by the ones I care about. I can understand how I may be annoying but a lot of this shit is ridiculous. I think Nick's in a bad mood, maybe that would explain why I headed up to Kettering for nothing. Yes, I wasted 3 hours and a half a tank of gas to sit and play Rummy and Speed Solitaire with Colin for 30 minutes. Excitement. I was supposedly suppose to pick Nick up and head back down for sushi and Starbucks before heading to my concert. But he ended up coming down with my brother to fill vending machines and watch TV I guess. I have no clue. I really don't care. Henk missed the last performance in band that I'll have in the US. And I just wanted to say thank you...  Thank you for showing how much I mean to you. And thank you Nick for adding to the fact. Thank you all for almost ruining the night that was suppose to be perfect.   On a serious note, I'd like to thank Andee, David, Michelle, and Leah for actually being there for me. It means to world to me to know that there are people that actually care. I love you all.  Tomorrow. No Canada. No hanging out with Henk and Crew. Nothing. Everything will be nothing. Congratulations to me.  Nothing fails like success. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know how typing with nails will fare for the next few days. I'll learn...  I cut out of work at 4pm to go to Mervyn's with my mom. Bra Shopping! I got two tube tops because I must "show my belly" as Michelle so blatantly puts it. I purchased some other things but it was mainly underwear... for the most part.  I then headed to the mall to get my nails done for tomorrow night's performance. There are going to be a bunch of random people there. A really weird mix of people I know, but it'll be fun. My camera is still broken so Michelle is just taking pictures for me. We're going to print out a Press Pass for her... fraud is so much fun. Too much fun. I don't know how tomorrow will be, but it seems to be a load of spontaneity if you were to ask me at the moment.  Seems like I'll be waking up super early to take a shower and get caffeine. Then it's off to sound checks. Back to school for about 2 hours. I don't know if I'll be going to 6th, but I need to call Sue to tell her that I won't be making it into work due to pre-concert preparations.  Lately I've had this urge to build more bridges than I've burned in the past. I'm giving Michelle (Evanoff) a note basically describing what went on in the past. I hope our beef will be sorted out so everyone can get on with their lives. I don't mind if we're just mere acquaintances but I hope a friendship will blossom out of the pile of shit I created in the past. I was such a bitch. And for whoever thinks I still am, damn, you should have seen me 2-5 years ago... it was pretty bad.  I'm off to homework and bed. I'll probably just pass out in front of the TV, but all is good.  Must write note.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Going back over whatever stoned logic I was trying to convince myself of last night...  Nick started talking about Allen. Like I'm suppose to care or something. Well, I started that process where impulses are sent to synaptic nerves in my head... I believe it's called thinking. Let me light some candles before I start writing about this. Ok. So I starting thinking about why we broke up, and I do believe a lot of convincing of the need to be alone was done by Donald. Not to make excuses because  I  was the one that broke up with him. But Donald played a part in it. And that tears a chunk out of me because I love Donald to death but I also just feel sort of... really fucking lonely. "I'll take you out and make sure you're not alone." I actually got that from two people, but at least Nick was telling the truth. I look back on the relationship that Allen and I had, and I realize how many problems we had, but I also realize that during about the first year or so I was completely in love. I just don't understand how things faded. And don't get me wrong, I'm not going to deny that I get jealous when I hear shit from people about him. Such as the night that Chris went to the Comedy Club and saw him there with his cousin. Ironic, my cousin sees Allen hanging out with his cousin... whatever. At any rate. I'm constantly looking for excitement now. I'm addicted to a wicked cocktail of adrenaline and caffeine. *takes a sip of her red bull* lol. Perhaps it's that addiction that fuels the reason that I go to Flint so often, or why I'm always everywhere, always with someone. But then again, I'm scared of being alone and that's why I'm always with some, or why I've been socializing so much more.  As for today, you may ask why I'm not in class. I decided to fake some abdominal pains so I could come home... and be alone. I got stopped by Rex this morning, walking down to the lower lot with Tiki and Gareth (I think I'm going to make a nickname for him... G-Dog? Captain Inexperienced? something...). Rex threatened me. He asked for passes, said we didn't have any. Said we were getting out of RCTC, said we had Dual Enrollment. None of that shit worked. So then he said something along the lines of, "You know I'm going to check, right?" then under his breath mumbled, to me, "If you take these students off campus you won't be driving any longer." Empty threat, considering the fact he has no judicial authority. He may be school security, but he's not police enforcement. I unfortunately didn't see him when I actually left. I wanted to paper cut him to death with my out of building pass.  So I've got medication now. Go me. I have an appointment on Wednesday. My test results get back on Friday? Saturday? They said 3 days. Then I go in for more testing and radiology. Getting my blood drawn... blah blah blah. They act like I'm going to die or something. If I die, it will be by my own will and sword.  I don't know what this weekend holds. April wants me to come to Kettering with her and Mike. I might drive up on my own. I have the band concert tomorrow. Sound check from 7:30am to 11-something am. Then I get to load equipment for percussion and skip more class. Fuck you Rex.  Damn... I write too much. I love to write though, so it's all good.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... In The Waiting Line  Wednesday in the mirror. I feel like I'm forever switching sides. Might as well pluck a flower's petals to determine my mood for the day, or the hour. My sentences sometimes even confuse myself.   God, that message just killed me.. and finding--oh fuck it.  I look at some of the reasons we broke up, and I remember how easy it was to get a kiss. And now I struggle for a remote amount of attention.  And this: "She's flirting with Keith again. I think it's funny." I think it's lame. Sarah knows me no longer. Oh god... the things I could forget. Do I all of a sudden have regrets?   "I only make jokes to distract myself from the truth...."  Stoned and Alone. And sitting thinking about everyone, everything.   "Is there anything worth waiting for? Is there anything worth living for?"  I hate hospitals.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Man, do I feel like Winonna Ryder right now or what?"  Michelle and I hung out today, as planned. I had a wonderful time. We first went out to STD testing centers but we can't find one that's free, because she's poor and I'm just not willing to pay. I'm going along more for support than for anything else, since Nikki is being a bitch and won't go with her. Both the Corner Health Center and Planned Parenthood charge up the ass. It pisses me off... and people wonder why others won't get tested, because they CAN'T FUCKING AFFORD IT!!!  Blah.   At any rate. We then went to the mall to shop....  lift . Two new tops, new earrings, a suit jacket, some cute little brief-like panties, a toe ring, and a new purse. Want to guess what I stole? Our clepto-total was around $75, but the mall is over priced anyway. She had $5 to begin with, and ended with the $5 as well. ;-)  Headed to Media Play to buy Lost in Translation and some CDs. Bought some chill out music, some Fat Boy Slim Live in Brighton Beach, and (randomly) some Kill Bill memorabilia. A lunch box for Nick and a Flask for myself. Media Play is so over priced. lol.  We chilled at my house for awhile to listen to some mashography, too bad Windows Media Player blows. Too bad I downloaded WinAmp to replace it. Fucker.  I started writing a script for a movie. Nick want to read it... beggars can't be choosers biatch. JK JK. I don't know, it's a little personal but he can watch it when all is either A) written and published or B) filmed. I'm excited. I like secrets... they're fun.  I think I need a new layout for my blogger, though I'm lazy and no one reads it so it really doesn't matter in my opinion.    DOES ANYONE READ THIS?!!! THAT'S WHAT THE COMMENTS ARE FOR!!!!!   Oh well..
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, that pissed me off... I just wrote my entire day, and would you like to see what's left of the post?  Here...              
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today wasnt that great, with the exception of hanging out with Nick, April, Mike, and Josephine; then going shopping with Michelle. Mothers Day is a bunch of bullshit in my opinion. Just another Hallmark Holiday to instill guilt upon those who dont contact their mothers during the 24 hour period that was created to piss people off. In my personal opinion, Mothers Day is celebrated every day. Or at least in my mind. Every time I wake up and look in the mirror, or see a relative its a lasting reminder of the hell this earth was subjected to when the zygote, turned fetus, properly entitled Ashley was brought to life. Ah pessimism, got to love my cynical pessimism.   And my day? Half spent at Yotsuba with the list of people above, my parents, and my grandfather. Stuffed myself with sushi and miso soup. Then went to Starbucks after contemplating the fact with my parents, who wanted to go to Cold Stone Creamery which just happens to be in Saline. I wasnt going to Saline. And what the hell? Who was going to wait in line 30 minutes (if not more) to see people scoop your ice cream, put it on a cold stone, do a little song and dance, put chocolate chips or cookie dough or whatever additive youd like into the ice cream after putting the cheesiest smile upon their face? Not I. So instead we went to Starbucks, the coffee flavored crack with a side of caffeine (as aforementioned) which was overloaded with calories or so my father says.   So now Im sitting on a ottoman, staring at the crowd of people that have congregated in my living room from random places. Theres Chris (my cousin) and Ernie (his room mate) which came from the back roads of Ypsi to sit and eat cook out buffet. Theres Henk fresh out of Flint, probably hung over from a cocktail of homework and hard, Canadian alcohol. Theres my Aunt Henny, who drove, All the way from Pennsylvania, and oh is her garden SO beautiful. Oh so just MUST show me the pictures on her computer of the beautiful flowers she planted. But yet, shes never home, shes a fucking flight attendant. What is this world coming to? Her boyfriend, I forget his name, Ill surely remember when I actually post this entry. He flew all the way from the Netherlands, oh boy. Barely speaks English, oh well. He makes fun of my sarcasm and takes my attitude toward life seriously which is anything but serious. My parents, recently returned from the Arboretum, where they sweated their Starbucks, calorie inflated treats away while walking up and down hills ridiculously obsessed with weight loss. Hmm maybe thats why theyre eating right now and Im not, so they can lose weight.  Watching boxing. Excitement. Oh sorry, Kick Boxing. Mmm I think Ill have a salad and then go puke on the chicken (as previously planned with Michelle). I almost forgot grilling in the pouring rain, perhaps a thunderstorm, its a bad idea. A really bad fucking idea.  On the brighter side of things, I get to look forward to a nice night of homework (finally time to be alone) and school tomorrow. Plans for Tuesday Testing with Michelle might fall through due to planting flowers with my mom I will escape, I will do whatever it takes to get out of this place on Tuesday. Time for salad 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stare into the mirror, and sometimes I understand why I'm alone. Maybe I'm crazy.  I had a dream last night. It was sort of relative to the whole Cassie situation. I just remember a lot of crying and running. The halls were those of my high school, yet the people that lined them were those who, I had thought, cared about me. I was tripping over my own feet as I passed by Leah and Keith, Michelle, Jessi, Q, B, a few of my co-workers, Todd, Nick, Jeff, Paul, Henk, Mike, teachers and parents, family friends. Just everyone staring at me, all slightly blurred due to my fast pace, standing in silence. A myriad of people lining a hallway with doors at the end. I never got to the doors.  It was then, that I'd been jolted from my nightmare, if you should call it that. It was 2-something in the morning. I flipped out because I had passed out with Tiki at my side, I was suppose to take her home at midnight. I ran downstairs and talked with my parents (who were drunk off their asses and didn't particularly care about the tears that I just realized were on my face). My mom had taken her home earlier. I feel like such a bitch for passing out. I guess I got what I deserved, a horrible dream.  Earlier in the day, Michelle and I hung out. We went to Mother Fletcher's and I bought a black shirt and a strip of purple satin cloth (possibly a head band in a previous life), it's my new belt.  Tiki and I got stoned at Q's house, Q fell asleep. We left before he woke up, but B and Ryan kept us company during the time previous to that.  Today is Mother's Day. I have no clue what I'm going to do. Michelle and I have to return bottles, pick up our pictures, and we were planning on making a trip to Anthology (Anthologee? I think the store may spell it funky or something). After that, I do believe my mother and I are planting flowers and cooking dinner. Henk's not home yet... he's going to get his ass beat when he finally arrives.  As you can see, I do have shit to get done today... I'll write more later or something.... or something....
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to Saturday.  So I'm in some strange void of a hangover today. Henk, Zink, Mike, Nick... blah blah blah... the list goes on, went to Canada today. Henk's coming down tomorrow for Mothers Day.   I called Michelle just as I'd realized that the feelings haven't gone away. But they've faded. Maybe they'll be gone soon. I was completely retarded for him last night, I bet he doesn't read this. lol. I had a very vague conversation with her in front of Nick and Danny, because I was too lazy to leave the room.   We got drunk and it was fun, but the side effects are near killing me today. Did my drunken coffee table dance and what not. Leaving random messages on the voicemail of others. Nick jamming Melissa in her tit. Me making the Mike's Hard Lemonade 6-pack carton into a hat. Tackling people as they came across the field. And watching a drug / prostitution deal in action... I need to take a shower but again, I'm really fucking lazy. I don't understand how people can be motivated after a night like that, but I was trashed. At least I didn't puke.  I don't really know what happened with April but it would have been fun to party with her last night. We have a lot in common in regards to how we feel about each other... completely oblivious to what the other thinks. Ah.. it will be sorted out. I'm not worried about it.   I'm going to give Nick (Cantu) a call and chill with him this afternoon, more than likely. See what Michelle is up to. See what Tiki is up to. Possibly chill with Q. Seems like it'll be a pretty social day. I just need to "get my homework finished" so I can leave without my mom getting all pissy. I'm planting flowers tomorrow, but I'm too tired to do anything but sit on my ass and possibly drive today. I need to conserve money.   More to come later tonight or tomorrow or something.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Social Butterfly. Uh huh.  I slept in, as planned. I went to Starbucks instead of art, 2nd hour. Fuck Dali. So when I returned with all my Advanced Algebra homework done I came to find Mr. Kellman's absence. I walked into the room. Michelle violently jolts her hand into a pointing motion for me to leave. Mouthing the words, "GO GO GO!!!" So I press the rewind button and walk backwards out of the room. Laura gives me an evil look. I want to give her the finger because I painted the rest of the brown on the art pillar. We went shopping after talking with Michelle's now psychotic unemployed dad. Value World is fun! Got a Hard Rock t-shirt from Niagara Falls. She got a pair of Old Navy pants to which the tag and stickers were still attached. Went back to class...   I'm heading up to Flint tomorrow. I don't care if I'm a party girl or not anymore. I'm going to enjoy shit to the fullest. I'll figure everything else out in the morning. I've got daisies to make me happy. Daisies everywhere. And no, I'm not stoned.  I'm ready for tomorrow's day of school... C'mon bitch. I'm taking that shit head on.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Short Phrase Day Description Time:  Woke up late. Went to Band late. They had down the lines. Plato's Cave movement 2. I don't play movement 2. I sat. Painted Dali in art. Have to get painting done in less than 10 school days. Left for 3rd hour. Finished research paper. Ate chicken wrap thingy. Drank coffee. Smoked cigarette. Returned for 4th hour. Got little pencil box from China from Ms. Matis. As if there aren't enough things already made in china. Thanked Ms. Matis. Finished Works Cited for research paper. Ran to English. Sat on my ass. Finished reading portion of MEAP testing. Done with MEAP testing. Went to Forensics. Sat of my ass. Gareth asked if I have a "floppable swappy drive." I said no. I told him I also didn't have a swappable floppy drive. Gareth is a chode. I laughed. Hooked my laptop to the speakers in the monitors. Jammed to Flogging Molly. Got yelled at. Plugged speakers back into the desktop. Bell rang. Went to work. Worked. Not really. Made little signs for the recycling bins. Went to buy flowers. Decorated my entire room in flowers. Wrapped daisies in ribbon for Michelle. Went to Michelle's house. Talked with Michelle. Went to get sushi with Michelle. Went to Crazy Wisdom with Michelle. Got little pentagram charm for Nicole's (my band sister) b-day. Bought new purse (finally). Bought some Mantra meditation beads. Went back to my house. Chilled with Michelle for a few. Took her home.   Michelle and I seem to be on a better understanding with one another. It's great to have someone great to talk to. I'm going to highlight this so that I can get my point across.  I WISH OTHER PEOPLE WOULD BE AS CONSIDERATE AS MICHELLE.   I'm going to bed. I can barely stay awake. I need to finish math homework. Snydee is in St. Louis with Symphonic Band. I'm sleeping in tomorrow and Friday. I'm excited.  Damn... my dog just ate all of my cat's food. I hate that dog.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drowning.  I'm thinking... if you can't beat 'em, join 'em. But I love beening an angsty bitch.   I was going to cast a spell. But instead I asked for the happiness of others. If Cassie only knew... damn, people really care about her. Even the girl that bitched you out in the first place prayed for you. No spite. What do you have to say now? We may not love you but we can share what love we do have...  And as for other people. Andrea and Tamika, possibly Jessi, would understand the second request. Two candles. Gently move them together. Rose Quartz. Rose petals. Rose incense.  I am so scared.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Campbell's tomato soup feels like warm, bloody death sliding down the back of my throat.  So a few things were weirding me out today. Maybe it's the full moon. Maybe I'm too superstitious. Jessi and I hung out for the first time if forever. That was sort of weird. More random than weird since we dyed her hair during 4th-6th hours at her place. I don't understand how I'm passing high school. The door to her bathroom mysteriously wanted to open... we even put the hamper and the rug in front of it and it still wanted to open. I thought that wind usually shut doors, not forced them open.   And now... why is it that every time I REMOTELY think about you. Such as, "Damn, my day is going just GRAND I wish I had someone to talk with..." You just randomly come online? Maybe I'm too superstitious.  Cassie is at Mott's Psych Ward. They want to put her on meds. She think she should be on meds. Jessi thinks I should be on meds. Jessi thinks that Cassie has situational depression.   Jessi thinks I have bi-polar disorder or maniac depression... whatever they call it now-a-days. I think my days of therapy are over.  I want to go back to therapy  Shh... My mom won't pay for it. I don't think it'd do any good. I don't have situational depression. I don't have depression, I just have really bad mood swings. But Shh... no one knows about that... they're not suppose to. I'm perfectly fine. Really. REALLY.  Cameron is in a psych ward some where too. I think Charlie is going to end up in one by the end of the night. I had to save Andrea from a mental break down last night as well. I love her so. Keith, Andrea, and I are going to have our morning cigarettes and coffee while in Italy this summer. It'll be grand.... and legal. All of these problems with my friends is starting to weird me out. I now believe that spring is the epitome of mental problem random explosions.   AHH!!! Will anyone fucking listen to me?! argh... whatever.  I'm off to Q's house. Gotta pick Tiki up first.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And another day of boredom.  Woke up late. Cried a lot. Sorted shit out. Went to the new Espresso Royale. Smiled. Went to 5th hour. Almost finished my English MEAP test. Went to 6th hour. Went back to Ms. Otwell's class. Finished my English MEAP test. Got out of school. Went to work. Worked overtime (hell yeah...). Went to Espresso Royale in Ann Arbor. Saw Mr. Fuck-You-Whenever-I-Please. Talked. Got my peach iced tea. Left. Was forced to go to dinner with my dad. Blah. Went home.   I have to finish my research paper for Otwell tomorrow. It's due Wednesday... or one of those days that end in Y. Q, Tiki, and I have plans to hang out tomorrow. I'm sorry for blowing you off today, Tiki. I love you. I hate you Dad.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      P.S. The sun came out...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh of relief*  I think I've finally been tossed back into reality. Kicked off my little cloud... but that's alright. Next time I'll wait for the feelings to be mutual.   I feel so much better but I still want to cry... damn whore-moans.   Ah... "I'm over it." lol. I love you Mike.   Well, off to class I go. You just know Mr. Riccobono is going to find me and bitch me out even more about my attendance. Oh well. I still can't believe I got that wrapped up into emotions. Jeeze... I've got to stop listening to Emo music. I get myself into the weirdest situations. In the words of Michelle Colon... "That was fucking clown shoes."
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not in the mood... blah. But I will anyway.  Today. What a weird day for everything. I don't remember going to sleep in my bed. I didn't go to work. I hope I get fired.  So it was my mom's b-day. I went out this afternoon, after having coffee with Dad, Opa, and Mom at Espresso Royale, and bought her some flowers after picking Mike up. Mike and I hung out and he got a hold of Nick. We picked Nick up from Kettering. Got lost on I-75, don't ask. They talked about cars, I sat there... and sat there... and sat there.   And sat there... you thought it was over didn't you?  Got back around 7-something. Picked April up and went to my house. My mom got pissed at me for dumb shit, but I'm too tired to explain.  Went to Pub 13 at 9pm to celebrate her b-day. I think I came across as a whinny bitch tonight. Oh well...   I've decided that my week doesn't suck, but my life just sucks in general. Hey Tiki, at least we have something in common. I'm just feeling worthless right now.  Ok, true feelings of the night: I don't really think anyone cares really. Not at all. I could just fall off the face of the earth and it really wouldn't matter. How long would it take to get over it? Really... Well, maybe Mike is right, I'm just a sadistic pessimist.   I dropped April off at her place at 10pm and then didn't really feel like being alone. I gave Q a call, headed over to hang with him for a few. Saw him but didn't stay that long. Went home... ended up alone anyway.   It's really too bad that I care so much about you but you don't give a flying fuck about me. Maybe it's a show... at this moment, I think not.  Maybe things will be better in the morning. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Him: what would YOU like? Me: why does that matter? Him: because it does...  No it doesn't.  It obviously doesn't.  What the hell have I done with my life?  After I'm done pouring my heart out to you, you always leave. Don't ask me if you don't want to care...  I want the sun to come out. I really want to stop crying for a just a few minutes. No one cares about that though.  How can you talk to me about sex at a time like this? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I hope that tonight is a display of what is to come for next week.   I randomly got an instant message from Mike and we decided to hang out. We went to Jimmy John's, Pinball Pete's, and the Diag while we were in Ann Arbor. Fun stuff. I DDRed my ass off. "It's the solution to anyone's problems... Just dance until you pass out." I told Mike about my subtle ways of making myself completely fucked up without people noticing. I think he's worried... ah, oh well.  We visited Josh at McDonalds after we got back to Ypsi. We were headed toward Penisular Park and saw his car so we went through the drive-thru for milkshakes and said 'hi.'   Both Mike and I hadn't seen the second Kill Bill so we called for showtimes and headed to the 6:15 showing. "My loins are quivering in anticipation." lol. Great movie, and that's a lot coming from the girl that hates sequels.  Q gave me a call afterward so we ended up smoking out at his place. Good times. But Q was being really weird, well in my opinion. The random feeling up of foot behind a pillow and sitting on lap was really ... um... interesting? B was there and we chilled for awhile. Played some Soul Caliber, watched some funny shit. Both guys gave me hugs on the way out. Q has plans to hang with me tomorrow. I'm excited.  Speaking of tomorrow. Apparently... Henk and Nick are heading down tomorrow. Riiiight... Mike knows where I'm coming from here. Hmm...  I do have 3 hours of work tomorrow. That'll be hell. If I go in I'll just finish the filing and call it a day. I don't even care about getting my salary this week. I'm a lazy bitch.  DAMN! Kill Bill Vol 2 was sweet. Q and B were crazy about it too so it was great to discuss with people.   Anyway... I'm off to bed. G'night all.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have 3 hours of work to make up in the next two days.  Kettering was okay. Last night was definitely an experience. Well, at least I came clean to a couple people. Danny and I had an actual conversation, but I think I was too drunk to understand how much of an idiot he actually is. He can be okay sometimes. My brother came up and slapped Danny on his shoulder and said, "I thought I told you no, Danny." I laughed and walked off, no, stumbled off. Speaking of stumbling drunks, Nick was just about as wasted as I.   I want to write so much about last night but then again, I just don't. Not because I'm shy about the whole thing but I just don't want it to come across the wrong way. Ah, what the hell? In my opinion, I've already screwed things up, so what do I have to lose.  I tried almost too hard to keep my mind (and hands) off of him. Yeah, didn't work in the slightest. The whole Michelle and Paul thing sort of weirded me out, but that was only when I was sent to save her from statutory rape. I got this whole over-protective, mother-like image in my head and I was trying to just do something to save her from regret. I don't know if she regrets it, but she told me about how she thought it was a desperate move on her part. She spent the night in his room.  And as for me. I had no plan. Michelle and Paul had a plan for me... but sometimes I don't know. Yes I do. I know that it hurts me more that it helps, and I just try to stay away from that. I don't know why I'm crying about it. Paul told me he'd pay me if I broke Nick and Julie up. Fuck that. I'm not a fricken fate sealer. Sure, I'm in the same boat as Michelle is with Ned... desperately in love. And Ned is just like Nick in the sense that they both think that the friendship will still go smoothly even if love is in the picture. But I screwed up big time. This morning when the drunken, outgoing, stupid side of me showed up I was almost able to put that personality back into the box it came from. It made me think way to hard about what I'm doing and where I'm going in life, and if I'm just going to be some slut or party-crazy girl for the rest of my life. And driving back with the 80s Mix in put this feeling of complete white across my face. My mind was just completely blank. Not really because I didn't want to think, I just didn't know  what to  think. For everything that has happened over the past two months... I sometimes wonder where all of this is taking me. I'm sort of scared.  I'm sorry Nick.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need help... seriously. Okay... this next entry is sort of... weird. Maybe I shouldn't drink anymore.   From Ashley's Everything Book:   I have the choice of going up into his bed and at a sorry attempt to make him feel uncomfortable, or I can sit here and write. C'mon Ash, no regrets... Plus I think I'm still drunk. *Sigh* This is so hard for me. Go for it. (my heart is pounding)  Where are you Michelle?
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was going to explain my fears, but I think I'll take some time in Italy to think and figure things out before jumping into situations only for them to go unsolved for ten days.  Ten days. I've grown to love Ypsilanti to tell you the truth. I've grown to love everything and everyone here. I'm going to be so torn when summer ends and everyone heads into their own little corners of life. But at the same time, it's selfish of me to believe that I'd be the reason for someone to stay.  My bags are just about fully packed, and Mr. LaRue sits beside me, sketching as usual. My head is prepared to leave, but my heart wants to stay. If I wasn't so happy with life this would be so much easier.   So the obvious would be to put these lyrics in here... so here we go.  I hate to wake you up to say goodbye. But the dawn is breaking, it's early morn. The taxi's waiting, he's blowing his horn, Already I'm so lonesome I could cry.  [Chorus] So kiss me and smile for me, Tell me that you'll wait for me, Hold me like you'll never let me go. 'Cause I'm leaving on a jet plane Don't know when I'll be back again - Oh Babe, I hate to go.  There's so many times I've let you down, So many times I've played around, I tell you now, they don't mean a thing. Every place I go, I'll think of you, Every song I sing, I'll sing for you, When I come back, I'll wear your wedding ring.  [Chorus]  Now the time has come to leave you, One more time let me kiss you, Then close your eyes, I'll be on my way. Dream about the days to come. When I won't have to leave alone, About the times I won't have to say ...  [Chorus]  I love you all and I'll be thinking about each and every one of you... even if you think I hate you, life couldn't be as beautiful as it is without your presence. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it seems like forever since my last entry. but since i'm heading to italy in a couple days i figured i should write. btw: if anyone wants a postcard from italy call me, instant message me, or leave a private comment with your addy.   the past couple days have been a blur. yesterday was spent with ned going to a water balloon fight at 8 ballard, and then mongolian bbq with michelle, ned, and the guys from ballard. after dinner we came back to my place and downed a fifth of jager with some red bull. relived kettering. and talked for awhile. good times.  michelle headed home but ned was tired and i didn't want to subject him to my brother's talk of cars and drugs. so we slept in my room with the door locked. i didn't get any sleep, but he passed out for a few. we went to denny's at about 5am, then went to his place to crash.   i headed to band at about 9:45-ish, and found out last minute that i'm in the percussion section again. for pirates of the caribbean this time. i have about... oh... four and a half hours to learn my part for the concert this evening. that's at the ypsi high auditorium at 7:30pm... be there and listen to us suck.   i wouldn't say i'm ready for italy, but i think i'm as ready as i'll ever be. i'm going shopping and packing tomorrow, then we leave wednesday morning. two more nights in ypsi. i want to party but my mom's being a bitch. a little sleep will do me good. plus i have a few things i need to make, buy, and pack. ten days of hell in a beautiful country... sounds like fun doesn't it? damn i don't want to leave...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was debating on writing, seeing as it's 4 in the morning. But I will. Forgive me if I pass out. Everything was great. Emphasis on was... but now I'm just confused, and half of that is my fault. I knew I should have never said anything, and the truth doesn't hurt, but realizing what I felt was not the truth, that hurt. And now I sit here... at 4 in the morning. When just about 7 hours ago I was scared I didn't feel the same way... I didn't know what to feel. I was hoping that much of my first idea was not true, but everyone knows how I am with hopes.   Last night I got drunk as shit at William's. Ned and I dropped Michelle off a little late, and headed back to William's to talk. The talk was complicated and involved too much thinking. But the thinking I did last night was not a result of a sober girl... which scares me because I remember some important points I made, and the responses given... but I don't really remember the full picture. Maybe I'll find out some day. Maybe not. I don't know... yeah I do.   I'm going to sleep. More later... if time allows.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .... it's still stuck in my head.  I want to.. no. I'm not saying it. No matter how shy I am, no matter how much I promised to be honest... I must NOT say it. Certain words destroy things so quickly, and I'm not about to let that happen.  Maybe subliminal messages. Maybe blunt honesty. Maybe maybe maybe... everything is a maybe right now. And it's sort of disturbing but fun. I go to sleep thinking, 'I'll figure it out in the morning.' But then I wake up and everything just sort of stays where it was earlier. Until new subjects are brought up and new information is released. After that, it just gets a tad more confusing but I just let it go like everything else. I've become so carefree to situations like this, it's delightful.   I don't know the ending to the story, but I will leave you all with these philosophical (hardly philosophical) words:  "MtDewGirl87: I didn't think it was my style; but hey, there's a chance for everything... life is made up of new experiences, and I'm ready for it all... bring it on."  I think I can handle this. If not, I hide things very well from myself.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't even know what to write.  I fucked up and it was completely dumb of me to think like anything and everything wouldn't effect me as it has. Things have gotten better since two nights ago, but I was so selfish... I don't know.  I'm happier but nothing's going to change things with the exception of time. Things will get better... I promise. And I promise this to everyone who's in the same boat as I am.  Today is father's day. I just went on a coffee run for him. we're possibly going out on the sailboat today. It'll be a nice escape from reality, I'll probably listen to music and write. Even if we may never film it, I want to finish the script. I need to finish the script. I just have this really weird feeling the ending is going to be really really depressing. We'll see. I really don't want it to be, because it's already sort of a knock off of Rule of Attraction. I don't need to feed that impulse to my viewers... or readers... or whatever. I'll post it in my blog when I'm done. Everyone can read it. Like that asshole that left the unsigned comment. Seriously, if you can't leave a name don't even pretend like you have balls. Don't even act like it. Either leave a name or say it to my face... it's called respect, it's called HAVING A FUCKING HEART. :-) Thank you.  At any rate. I'm going to see what's up with my household. Too many people are randomly crashing at my place... it's starting to freak me out. Since when did my house become a homeless shelter? Ah, oh well. I was homeless a couple nights ago, so I don't have much room to talk. So off to the fabulous fathers day fun... riiight.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning!  Yesterday was weird, but I'm living. Went to p.net around 1:30-ish. Got to JJ's by 5. Work at Jimmy Johns seemed to last forever... and I have to go back today... dammit. I get out of work rather early though. 3pm. I don't know what I'm going to do with my spare time. Probably finish cleaning those stupid fish tanks.  Last night after work I called Michelle before calling Ned. She told me something was going down, but wouldn't give me details. I called Ned then headed over to his place to get up to speed on the nights occurrences. Apparently, this is going off of what both of them told me, so I might get screwed up, but this is from my own understanding / opinion. So Michelle went out to get gas (because she now has enough cigarettes, right? buy one get one free. fourteen holes for fourteen dollars) and then stopped by Ned's place. Ned told me she was super pissed and slammed on the breaks... blah blah blah. And Michelle admitted to being angry but she said he was exaggerating a bit. She chewed him out and told him not to hurt me, she did a very fine job of standing up for me. She didn't want our friendship to get weird or be disturbed by any of Ned and I's actions... and personally, I was thinking the same thing. I love Michelle to death, and care about her so that I would never want to do anything to hurt her or the friendship we share. Now, granted, I do want to get to know Ned and perhaps be intimate with him, and that's something that Michelle would more than likely have a problem with. In that respect, I'm torn to make this oddly hard decision... or lack there of. To put a wonderful friendship on the line, or to cut off relations with someone I'm getting to know. And as for Ned, he's a great guy. With some of the things I've heard from Michelle I sometimes wonder if it's all an act. He seems, I wouldn't say it pure, but honest in his actions... at least for the moment. I really don't know what to think. I try so hard not to judge off of what others have told me, and in this case it's been alright. I haven't had that many problems in this situation... but it's always in the back of your mind. You know? Damn, this is really hard for me to write about. We're all victims of our own decisions and actions.  A forbidden smile is so inviting Humans try so hard to grasp what is out of reach We are the immortal toddlers And the cookie jar is allowed to those tall enough to reach  Other than that, Reanda found out about Josh and I. Oh well, it was going to happen sooner or later. I know this world is some kind of giant game of telephone, and no one can ever keep their fucking mouths shut. So much for trust. Such a thing is fought over, fawned after, and lost too easily. And Reanda can't stay pissed for too long. She can hate me, hold a grudge or whatever, and I can blow it off like a feather of weight on my shoulders. But as for Josh, he is her life line and I don't believe she would be so easy to turn down love or sex. Although, I don't doubt that she would do the opposite either.  Last night was spent getting stoned with Ned. We smoked out on the back porch, then headed in. And yes, I'm still going to edit my profile just for you, Ned. "Look at that asshole of a dog." "How can you say that the dog's an asshole when you were just complaining about being a gentile?" Grand, it was. We headed up to his room and 'broadened my horizons in music for a half-an-hour.' Got a call from Michelle, it was 1am by then, so I decided to go home before talking with her about anything. We're hanging out tonight at William's. CANTU NEEDS TO CALL ME DAMMIT!! *yawn* How am I going to last the day as sleepy as I am? We'll see.  Your heart is a star And I am a child with dreams of rockets and astronauts If these dreams are true I will continue to smile For the fight is the best part To gain a part of you To fill a part of me.  More to come later... damn, this entry was way too long.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because you're desperate for me to write an entry... ;-) not.  Today. Working 7 hours sucked. Period. There was one high point to my day at work... the guy that came in stoned and asked to trade a sub for either pot, cigarettes, or cash. We accepted both the cash and the cigarettes.  Tonight. Ah... tonight. I got home to shower off the Jimmy Johns smell. Maybe they should make their own line of perfume or something. Jimque, the new fragrance from Jimmy Johns. Dork.  Michelle and I hung out for a few. I took her out of her house, she was stressed out because her car got fucked up by a drunk driver last night, plus Nikki and her father were being complete assholes. We drove around then ended up at my place. We sat and talked for a few then I drove her back to her house to pick up her work attire, met her at William's. No one was there so she sort of, not really, forced me to call Ned, then she went to work.  I sat in my car staring at my phone for a few minutes. Contemplating. Weighing consequences. Deliberating. Then I pressed the send button. I went over to his house and chilled for a few. Could he tell that I was nervous? Could he be more courteous? Could I blush anymore? We watched Jackie Brown. And yes, I made out with him. Woo. That's for all those assholes out there that I know read this for "dirt" on me. Well, a kiss is as dirty as it's getting for tonight's entry. Congratulations to you. The contemplation of if I "was going to take advantage" of him sorta raced through my mind a little too much, but I'm alright. Self control is a good thing... yes it is. Anyway. We took a break from the movie, smoked a cigarette (we did this twice). Then I dropped him off and was very lady-like as I walked him to the door. Goodnight kiss. Then the realization that rain was completely drenching me. But I was alright. I was fine. We made plans for tomorrow night. I guess I'm hanging out at his place for a few after work tomorrow. We'll see how that goes. I am so completely tired. I'm falling asleep at my computer and that's sad.  Yawn. Speaking of sleep. I keep having this recurring dream where I'm on band tour and get really sick. Maybe it's all in my head.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      titled off of april's entry... i became inspired  and as for today...  went to work at p.net... wow. yeeeah... nothing special there.  after work, michelle, gareth and I hung out. we went to starbucks and chilled then headed back to michelle's for my phone. got a call from andee and got our vicodin. talked with her in the ypsi high parking lot for a few and then headed to william's for the game.   hanging at williams is fun as shit. michelle was a little stress with ned being there and everything. the vicodin wore off pretty fast but when i did take it i was so numb it was wonderful. michelle and i played some one on one beer pong. julian played michelle and i after that. i flashed julian because he won the game... fucking promises. julian apparently called michelle some dirty comment when she did it last so she didn't agree to the whole thing. but oh well... i can understand her feelings about the whole thing.   michelle and i chilled for the rest of the night. she left early and i chatted it up with ned for the remainder of the time. he's a cool guy, i can now understand michelle's attraction to him during their time together... and to be honest i would go for him, but the things michelle has told me are enough to make me want to slap him.   i headed out to show ned my self portrait (which has been in the back of my car for way too long). he showed me some of his sketches and then julian came out to talk with us. julian was hitting on me the entire time, i really didn't mind but his whole girlfriend situation is too shaky for stuff to happen there. i really don't need some chick on my ass for anything to do with him. jamie's really pretty too, he's better off with her. i gave them kisses on their cheeks and then decided to head out (seeing as it was 1am and I was suppose to be home at 11pm). I was backing up out of the land mine of cars sporadically parked throughout the driveway when I hit ned's car. yes... the benz. go me. i really shouldn't drive anymore. i wasn't even that drunk. maybe it was the vicodin fucking with my perception. but ned told me, "chicks can hit my car and i'll still be on my knees kissing their feet." how odd. at any rate, he moved his car (because he's an asshole of a gentleman) and guided me as i backed up, safely this time.   julian and ned put up a fit for me to stay for awhile longer. i said, 'no.' they were worried that i'd get a DUI. oh fucking well. i gave ned my cell number, and he gave me william's number. i got home safely and called ned to 'check in.' because ned has all of a sudden turned into my father or something... whatever.   my dad talked with me for a few. he didn't seem pissed that i got home so late. but i have work in the morning so i'm outta here. g'night. i'm so numb.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe I was that dumb. But it's hilarious. I laugh at my own stupidity. Steve is gay. I wouldn't have known! He kept talking about ex-girlfriends and shit and I stood there like, damn, I want a chance. Like some kind of carnival ride or something. Ah oh well.   And I started at the State / William Street Jimmy Johns yesterday from 11am-2pm. The guys are cool. Joe's (my boss) is really laid back. I don't know if that's because it was my first day or because he's always like that. I felt lazy for not doing anything, but when I asked if there was anything I should be doing he just said, 'nope,' and went back to work. Ok... I guess. The whole parking thing is a problem. I'm not paying $3-$9 for parking... not going to happen. I'll figure it out in the morning or something. Maybe I should start riding my bike to work from Mike's house or something. Like I said, I'll figure it out.  I worked at Provide.Net for a few. Didn't get much accomplished, but then again, I really don't care about that job. I went over to Michelle's afterward. We hung out for a few before I realized I was suppose to be at Monday Night Band Rehearsal. So I floored it to my house and talked with my mom for a few, got her to sign my tour papers and everything. Now I'm all set to go to Italy. I just need money for the trip (though my tour payments are completed).   I got out of that bullshit at 9pm and talked with Andee for a few minutes before heading back over to Michelle's house. Michelle and I headed over to William's house and I got completely plastered in front of Ned. I thought it was pretty hilarious if you ask me. We played a game of beer pong but I got so fucked up because he had 5 redemption. 5!! I think we scored a record or something. But when I went down stairs to call my dad, Michelle didn't make another redemption so we just decided to quit and go smoke a cigarette. Michelle drove my car back to my place and Josh said that he'd give her a ride home, so I gratefully accepted. When I got home I felt the inevitable, I was going to puke. So I headed to the upstairs bathroom to complete my task but Mike knocked on the front door, so I ran downstairs and let him in. Ran back upstairs, told him to chill in my room and tried to puke in the bathroom. No go. My mom came home, Mike and I ran into the basement. Tried to puke in the bathroom down there. No go. I came out and Josh was back by then. We walked back up a flight, and I ran into the bathroom by the kitchen, and all hell broke loose. I think I actually threw up part of my stomach or something. Bile is the most disgusting thing I've ever seen. I walked slowly back up to my room, Josh and Mike followed to make sure I got to bed okay. Josh said something to me, I can't really remember... but they left and I fell asleep.  I feel like such a bitch for getting that drunk. For making Michelle drive my car and get a ride from Josh. Making Josh drive Michelle home. Making Mike wait around for no apparent reason. Puking. Having the guys leave while I passed out on my bed. It was just all so fucked up. I'm not getting that drunk again any time soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things have gotten better since my last entry. I got out of the house for the majority of the time too, today. I'm going to make this quick because I'm stoned and lazy.  Went shoe shopping with mom. Got new shoes. Went to Andrea's open house with Michelle. Got Madeline's number. I got the hook up on certain places I can buy certain things ;-P. Dropped Michelle off. Came home. Did laundry. Took a shower. Went to hang with Q and crew at the TI building at WCC. Came home. Ate and watched TV. Danced around like a geek. Went to Jimmy Johns for the first day of work. Stared at Steve too much. Work was alright. I wish I was actually and interesting person. Oh well. Jimmy Johns is going to be weird... but I think I'm going to like it. But I just never pictured myself as being the girl behind the counter at the register; smock, hat and all. It was alright. I wish it were busier but oh well to that too. I'm going to bed now because I have work in the morning.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Heal these broken wings. I need to fly again." - Zero 7  I got into a fight with my parents. Now, people may say yelling is better than being grounded.. but that is the first time in over a year we yelled at each other. I don't even remember why they originally got pissed at me, but I complained and said that everyone in the house was pissed off. Then my mom and I started yelling at each other, she took a shower, and my dad came up to start his bitching spree. He screamed at me. Meanwhile, Henk and Nick sit contently downstairs. I was surprised he didn't hit me, but he lunged at me a couple of times. After I'm terrified and crying, he drags me into their room and continues his rant. I try to explain things, he doesn't want excuses. I'm meek and crying, so scared that I start hyper-ventilating. He's still pissed, but hugs me as I'm this emotion wreck. And everything just hits the fan... Grades, finals, work, friendships, Josh, money, substance abuse, starvation, alcohol... just everything. It all comes crashing down, and I can't stop crying which makes my breathing situation even worse. By the time I told my dad I needed to leave to be alone for a few minutes, my heart was racing so fast I felt as if I was going to die. I was satisfied with my oxygen supply but couldn't stop gulping down air. The pain killers were wearing thin after that. My chest aches and I'm really tired. It feels like something inside of me is broken, I think my ribs might be bruised or something. Before going out to dinner, my dad took me aside again. Fearing the worst was yet to come I braced myself, and started taking deep breaths. Fortunately, he only apologized. He broke down into tears. I've never seen my dad cry before. I accepted his apology (what else was I going to do?), and he sat at the dinner table with a guilt-free conscious. We ate at Smoke House Blues. I left early, after dinner was over but before everyone was done packing up, and went to the park to puke up my food. My stomach hurts so much. My dad told me something strange... he said, "Don't do anything for your mother or I, do it for yourself." But yet this hypocritical statement lead me to ask myself why he wanted me to lose weight, or why they wanted my grades to be at honor roll status. The majority of my work is not for myself. I do like to indulge in many things, but I don't really do much for myself as far as practicality goes. But we need not get into that shit now. I think I'm going to bed. G'night all.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went out to William's last night with the two Michelles (Colon and Evanoff). Evanoff and I got plastered. Played some beer pong and then just chilled for the remainder of the time. We went out to Abe's afterward, so we could sober up before dropping Evanoff at home. I met a shitload of people while there... hope that Ashley and I's conversation struck some sort of friendship, though I'm way too hopeful about some things. Michelle (Colon) and I headed back to her house and chilled for awhile. Mike and Josh came over to talk and hang out. I dozed off, but Michelle, Josh, and Mike woke me up. Apparently Ryan was coming over or something (I really don't remember, I was half drunk and half asleep) and she wanted me to stay the night at Josh's place. So in my half drunken, half asleep stupor I pulled out my keys and drove to Josh's place. Passed out when I got there, and didn't wake up in time for the ACTs this morning. Oh well. Next year I guess.  Today was spent cleaning my bathroom, going to Liz's open house, shopping, and dying my hair. Nick and Henk came down for the afternoon to work on the car, Nick wanted to get sushi but Henk's being an asshole. Asshole. Anyway. I think I might go out for dinner or something. Maybe my parents will take me out.... mmm.... sushi. Yotsuba, here I come. Blond hair, here I come. Ugh, 10 more minutes of this shit settling into my scalp. Yuck. I need a hair cut.  In other news (since I have 10 minutes), hot guys infested William's place last night. Most of them taken, and plus I'm not as pretty as the other girls that were there so it was obvious that I wasn't going to meet up with anyone. But Michelle (Evanoff) and I talked about her father, Kenny, and sex... a lot. The entire night actually. It was sort of annoying, but I was drunk off my ass so it didn't matter. Plus she was drunk off her ass so it's not like she would have noticed. Oh, and I was being very courteous about the whole thing. I really didn't mind that much. We made amends near the end of the night. I apologized for being a bitch back in the day. I guess that time changes things, so do official apologies sometimes. I just wish that official apologies would heal all wounds.   As far as Josh, I don't know what to think. I don't know whether I'm in love, or in denial. I care about him so much, but it seems that nothing in the world can change his mind... or solve his problem. My disposition is just that though, I am his problem so therefore, I can solve it, but only by extreme measure that neither of us would want. He showed his concern yesterday by sitting me down and talking with me. Sometimes it just feels so good to be asked questions and answer them so honestly. Sometimes I want to leave, just disappear from his radar; and other times, I want to be there with him for hours on end. I don't know which one is worse. Leaving all together, hurting myself by my departure. Or, over-staying my welcome, make him sick of the sight of me. Any advice?
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Junior year is over... 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's to my 100th entry...        "I took the 405 and drilled a stake down into your center, And stated that it's never ever been better than this. I hung my favorite shirt on the floorbaord, wrinkled up from pulling pushing tasting. You keep twisting the truth that keeps me thrown askew. Misguided by the 405 'cause it lead me to an alcoholic summer. I missed the exit to your parents' house hours ago. Red wine and the cigarettes... hide your bad habits underneath the patio."                          "She had a history of killing herself  I had a habit of dying  I think she gave me something to live for  I guess I helped her pass the time   And I had a vision of seeing things straight  She had the heart of a liar  I never saw her leave me once  She never felt me beside her "         
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think Josh is avoiding me. I may just be thinking too hard about the whole thing. I hope you're happy... where ever you are.  I look back upon today and the things I accomplished and the things I fucked up and I realize that I was so alone. True I did see David after school, and we talked for awhile. I gave him a ride home. But as for work and the p.net party hour, that was sorta fun. I hadn't been in a chat room for years up until today. Oh! And I'm a 22-year-old, Swedish model with a hermaphroditic twin sister. Forgot to tell you that. Riiight.  At any rate. I got out of work, and Donald helped me out on my English final. Yes, he actually did something besides feel me up! It's AMAZING! jk jk. He never reads this anyway. And if he does... HI! Oh well. Tomorrow is the last day of school. My grades are up, my English take home is not even half way completed, but I'm doing alright. I'm going to pass out at my computer. But I'm doing just fine.  My emotional state has been put on hold. I've had WAY too much caffeine to care right now. But it's not like it's gone away completely... I can feel it lingering in the background, waiting for a time when I'm not busy so it can sneak up behind me and terrify me with some kind of mental breakdown. Like after I got done talking with Mrs. Otwell at school today. That was so completely random. Donald called me and asked for coffee so I was driving out of the parking lot, and I'd just gotten off the phone when I just started crying. I stopped myself though. I don't have time to cry. I don't have time to care. I just have time for other people... I don't need time for myself. I'll be okay. God, I don't need this when I still need to finish my stupid final exam... okay, I'm leaving now.  G'night... hopefully I'll get some sleep. I'm going to go raid refrigerators for more caffeinated beverages.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My parents just got home.  The stress is building and I really just want to go to sleep, wake up at 4am, and study for that fucking Advanced Algebra final. I probably will, because I'm getting really anxious and ADD. Ahhh!!! I can't even concentrate on this fucking entry. What a waste of my time.  I'm stoned, depressed, and angry; all at the same time. It's no fun. I'm not going to do this ever again. And I'm putting my heart under lock and key, and then throwing the key in the river. I guess this is the end of love, and relationships, for awhile.  "Traveling some where, could be anywhere. We drift deeper, and life goes on. We drift deeper, into the sun." - Motorcycle
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First off, thank you Tamika and April for the comments.  Secondly, I'm going crazy. I am crazy.  So here we go...  If not on the Honor Roll, I'm fucked this summer. Royally. No car. No late curfew. No raise. I'll be fucked. They've taken my entire life and put it to the fate of a piece of paper that will come in about a week or so. I'm not anticipating it's arrival, but I am anticipating it's interception. I will be the first to see those letters, the little formations on the sheet that will determine my life for the next 2 1/2 months. I hope it goes well.  And if that's not enough to be crazy about. I don't think anyone has died of confusion before, but there's a first for everything. Right? My heart says one thing, my head says another; and if two voices aren't enough, he says yet another thing. Every time I see him I feel like someone's throwing rocks at this glass house I've built, camouflaging it to appear as brick. I build my walls so high, but it's so easy to make them crumble. Too easy. So when he's away I feel empty. I know I probably shouldn't see him anymore, but these feelings lift me to my feet, walk me down the stairs, place me in my car, put the key into the ignition, and drive me to him. And this unwelcome visitor, this guilt and unhappiness, pain and hopelessness, it's all overwhelming. I begin to just sit alone and think and I'm disgusted with myself, but it also seems so right. It seems like there is/was something... or should have been. So many unanswered questions... and it's only Tuesday... well, now it's Wednesday, but you get my point.   "You shouldn't think what you're feeling."
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is going to be a long entry, deal with it. And leave me some advice or something... I don't care who you are, just leave a fucking message of some sort.  Right after I wrote that entry at work I was called into my dad's office. I thought I was being fired or some shit so at first I was a little nervous, but excited... lol. Turns out I'm going to be the project manager of the new Provide.Net site layout. Though, on the down side, I get to work 4 hours a day 5 days a week... plus the Jimmy Johns shifts. Just after I get a new job because they aren't giving me enough hours at Provide.Net, they give me a major project. Damn Considerate Assholes.  At any rate. Now, on to the part that will piss people off. Don't read it if you're going to get pissed off. I'm serious. It's just been pissing me off all day, so now it's my chance to spread the hate.  No, I won't say anything about this morning, don't you worry. I'm seriously pissed at you Josh. You're such a hypocrite it drives me crazy... and not in a good way. It's like this: "You make me so happy, and she pisses me off, so I'm going back to her!" Sound familiar? Oh yes. And don't get me wrong, you have said kind things about her, it's just that you mainly complain. You must have gotten me wrong. I know you're not one to chase women, so how come you chased me when I ran upstairs crying that night in the basement? And don't say it's because you cared. Don't even give me that shit, because if you cared you have chased me when I said "I'm giving you, your out." You knew that I didn't want it to be like that. You fucking knew it. Do you know how hard it was for me to say "I love you," for me to pour my heart out to people, and for you to ignore it or toss it off to the side? You should, because you were the one who listened to me when all that shit with Nick went down. All I needed was for someone to listen. I lent my ear, my shoulder, my innocents to you and my repayment is a sad ending and emotional scars. You knew you were hurting me, that's why I always talk about leaving. That's why I run. Maybe I deserve all of this, this is what I get for everything I've ever done to hurt anyone. But that still doesn't explain how you could have taken me, placed me in a bottle with all the times we spent together, and sent me out to treacherous seas with all the words that ever mattered. I'll forever be known as Henk's sister. Congratulations to me. I love you so much I hate you. I hate you. I hate you. I hate you. I love you. I love you. I hate you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I hate you. I love you.   Please don't tell me this is the end. I don't know if I'm going to be able to deal with this.   Finals, Two Jobs, and a Broken Heart... the Experimental Single Sonic Summer of 2004, has turned into the Trashed Stupid Single Sad Summer of 2004. I think I need a nap or something, crying about it is just wearing me out.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No. It's not a death threat so just shut up already.  I woke up at 5am. I couldn't sleep. Went to school so careless, it was wondrous. But I left after 1st hour because I started to feel like shit. Plus there was no reason for me to stay. I picked Michelle up and we went job hunting together. She got me a job at Jimmy Johns. I think things are changing for the better. And I'm not saying that because things are actually getting better, I'm saying that because keeping myself busy will make things seem better. I start at Jimmy Johns on Monday. I've got a great shift schedule, I'm really excited. This summer is going to be hell though. I work 5 days a week. Oh well. Keeping myself busy. I've got the evenings and nights off as well as the weekends. It will be just like school, but not; because now I get to sleep in. Oh hell yes.  I headed back for 6th hour. I swear if I'm ignored by one more guy (with the exception of David and Anil, because they're sweeties) I'm just going to blow my fucking head off. Bring it. Ignore me. I've been reclaiming the suicidal thoughts that used to overwhelm me months ago... it's no fun. I just feel so useless. I'll write more later. Maybe I'll feel like coming out about my problems then.  Back to work...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's funny how feelings can change at such a rapid pace. How your entire world is torn apart by a sentence. How everyone wants to start, but doesn't know how to finish.. so we're stuck now aren't we? I'm stuck and I put myself here. I'm so dumb. This always happens to me because I let it. I'm done with love. Give me a world without feelings. I'm just finished. I don't think I can take anymore.   I thought I made you so happy. I'm sent running away again. I hate when I do this... 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got completely plastered and stoned last night. Allen came over along with two of his cousins. Henk, Nick, Seth, Will, Mike, and Allen all worked on the car. Allen, his cousins, and I went out for a beer run. We came back to the house and got drrrrrunk. Seth and I had a nice little conversation out on the back deck while smoking out. He's a great guy. Came back in, Henk, Seth, and Nick decided to head out; as with Allen and his cousins. Mike and I chilled out in the basement for a few. I passed out. But woke up to most beautiful sight in the world. Baise. And the rest is a drunken interpretation of love and history.  I picked Josh up from his place and we went over to Mike's this morning after breakfast at Denny's. Mike's dad is such a dork.  Michelle and I went to Tim's open house. We bought him Position of the Day postcards and a little mini book on sex (which makes a distinct moaning noise when you grab it the wrong way, which Michelle and I found out quickly at the register) The open house was pretty fun. Random ass kareoke machine blasting the Beach Boys. Yeah, it was cheesey. But David, Pete, Elizabeth, Ayana (sp?) and Gale hung out with Michelle and I. It was grand. I had to head out and get gas and drop Michelle off before going to work.   Work was a blast. Riiight. I was busy the entire time. It was ridiculous. Then the tech meeting was an ongoing travesty in itself. I don't really know why I was even there. We filled out these little worksheets about how we want things to be, and how things are. It really pissed me off because there was a question that asked something like, "My boss gives me extra training when I request it." Or something like that. I was so pissed off! I wrote 'no.' I'm not scared to get fired, and it's not like I wasn't going to be honest. I was just ticked that she would ask such a question, knowing that I requested to be trained for tech support. So what did I do once I got out of the meeting? Dropped off my application at Starbucks. Go me.  I have more room cleaning to do. I have more waiting to do.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      '...Do you believe In what you see Motionless wheel Nothing is real Wasting my time In the waiting line Do you believe In what you see..." -Zero7  "...I don't need you anymore I'm okay and I am sure I don't need you anymore Yeah I'm ok, I'm reassured..." -Zero7  "I'm on fire And the day is feeling hopeless You'd see me burning but the burning's turning smokeless Soon I won't feel at all No  It's electric the neon hurt inside your phone call The layered sadness and the madness it revolves Bringing down the walls where you found her  No  Well, I'm willing to break myself To shake this hell from everything I touch I'm willing to bleed for days my... reds and grays So you don't hurt so much  And now I'm static As your sky is turning purple and gray I'm learning that the further that I crawl The farther that I fall, is that ok?  No  And you're in pieces  As your world becomes a rainstorm You've got no shelter I'm a thousand miles away If you survive the day  You say your leaving You say your leaving  Well, I'm willing to break myself To shake this hell from everything I touch I'm willing to bleed for days my... reds and grays So you don't hurt so much  So you don't hurt so much  Never again will we fire this gun No never again your the only one No never again but you're already gone.  I'm willing to break myself I'm not afraid..." -Something Corporate 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm just pissed now. As if I'm not making it apparent that I'm pissed/upset/dying over you. Over everything that ever was or wasn't. And I'm going to speak in confusing little phrases because that's what I do best. I'm tired of just loving and this is why I want to leave. I'm tired of being tossed from guy to guy, some little rag doll of some sort. I'm just tired of everything. And I want to live in my little fantasy world and tell you so much. Tell you everything. I want to pour my heart and soul into you to make up for what has happened over the past couple weeks. I want to take care of you so badly, whether that involves a steady relationship or not. I want to hold you when you're upset, and kiss you in hopes that everything will go away and all will be better when we wake up together. I want all of this so badly, but I can barely stand being placed in a corner with no expiration date. In my opinion, I've already expired... I'm gone and I lost you or what I thought was you for so very long. I've been placed in the proverbial trash can that has now consumed not only my heart but my life as well. I let the feelings get the best of me, and I don't know how to change that. I don't know if I'm able to change that. I don't know if I want to change that. I'm not scared to say this anymore. I'm not scared to fall off bridges or careen into placid seas. I'm not scared to say that I've utterly and fully fallen for you. And I'm a sucker for love. I love you.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Should I explain the events of last night? Yeah... it's worth it.  Thursday night I was hanging out at Michelle's place when Ashley gives me a call and tells me how her date canceled on her for prom and that she tried calling other people, but they were too busy. And then, out of the blue, she asks me to go with Peter, Leah, and herself. I gratefully accepted. It was the best and worst of times all in one night. Grazi was awesome. We were serenaded at dinner, and the food was excellent.  Prom itself sucked. The music was mainly sucky, but everyone looked fabulous. Just hanging out with a bunch of people you may see once or twice more before they head off to college, taking a shitload of pictures, I should have spiked the punch.  Afterward, I was suppose to go the Harry Potter with Ashley and Peter, but I had to be home before the movie let out, so I went with Michelle to Elizabeth Cornish's place and chilled out in back, by the bonfire. Chloe made her Chloe Specialty (essentially a Jager Bomb, just mixed differently). Got drunk before I got stoned, but either way I was so tired. I headed home. I was terrified to drive but I concentrated on it, and all went smoothly. I took back roads back to my place, because it seemed like the best idea. I don't think I'm going to do that again.  Today I have Ashley's open house and I need to find Josh, we've been playing telephone/AIM tag. Must take shower... Eww.. I smell like a YHS prom and alcohol. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm drunk.  I'm stoned.  Prom sucked.  But the afterparties made up for it.  Much praise to Ashley for taking me in.  Much thanks to Michelle for finding me a dress last minute.  Much thanks to Clohe and her Clohe Specialty.   Ah....... bed. Must sleep.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... yes, that would be me. I've been dubbed the girl that is sent to fix everyone's relationship problems. Yet the funny part is, I have no one to fix mine. Greeeat...  I'm not in the mood to write. So I leave you with these bits of wisdom from the Colon and Overkleeft Relationship Consulting Group:  victoriainthesky: lol this is also true MtDewGirl87: ah fuck him MtDewGirl87: I'll never get through to that boy victoriainthesky: i don't think so either. penis on forehead MtDewGirl87: it's never going away dude MtDewGirl87: it's always going to be there victoriainthesky: yes it will MtDewGirl87: like a fucking chode victoriainthesky: lol eeeeeewwwwwwwww  "yes. sex. now. I can't live underneath these circumstances. how is a woman suppose to function without sex for so long? I hate my cycle.  I'm going to go and die of unfed, pent-up, sexual anxiety now"  So random. Think of it as what you will. Laugh when necessary.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "So I'm in a room after a D&D game and I'm rolling my D-20 when a scantily clad elfin chick breaks into my room and realizes I have an enormously large penis and we then commence to fuck, HARD." - Dave E.   Okay, okay... I'm writing now. Sum up of the weekend...  Friday: Seniors last day. Explained in past entries. Pissed at Nick for something, I don't remember.   Saturday: Pinball Pete's. Michelle. DDR. Pool. Driving Game. Starbucks. Left. Job hunting. Michelle = home.  Sunday: Electronic Music Fest. Michelle. Sleep. Feel up Seth, who I think is Josh.  Monday: Wake up. Realize Josh is actually Seth, or Seth is actually Josh, or something. (?) Hang out with April and Nick at the park. Take them to the wave field. More Pinball Pete's. Talked with Mike. Delivered car to April at Mike's. Install key pad on car door. Eventually get drunk as fuck after learning that Josh is still fucking Reanda. I'm feeling used. Polish off the Tequila Rose. Have a couple beers. Have school in the morning. Josh shows up (not with Reanda, as originally planned). I'm happier. We talk. Shit hits the fan. I go to bed. He talks with me on AIM. I finally get to bed. I'm not sober... at all.  Tuesday: Wake up late for school. Drive Mike to class. Get Starbucks. Get to school. 3rd hour sucks balls. Leave with Michelle for Starbucks (yet again). See Mike's dad. Talk = guys. Get back to school. English sucks. Post up VOTE FOR DAVID posters around school for senior cabinet. I hope he wins. After school. Go shopping with Michelle. Have a bottle of wine and a movie afterward. Get stoned. Go home late. Oh well.  Today: Late to school once again. Get Starbucks. See Mike's dad, again. Make it to 3rd hour. Meet up with Michelle in the lower lot. We get a shitload of work done in Kellman's class. Get Gareth and head back to Starbucks. I'm broke. They get iced coffee for me. Write more to the movie script. Get back to class. 5th hour sucks. I hate movies. Instead I sketch. Forensics fucking sucks too... thanks to the bastards that don't do their work. Tiki's monologue was awesome. Michelle's (Evanoff) was good too. Get out of school. Go to work. Work blows. Drive Sue's daughter to pick up Sue's Daughter's Daughter from school. I get back to work and clock out after running credit cards. Head to Michelle's (Colon) house after work. Watch dumb Anne of the Thousand Days movie. David, Michelle, and I have a nice little conversation about sex and drugs. I have to leave to make the curfew that my mom put in place. Drive home. Mom's not home. I'm pissed.   And now I'm here.  Tomorrow, Michelle and I are leaving for 3rd hour. I should probably go to all my classes but I don't know anymore. I'll probably give into her, but I really need to stay on track with my homework and shit. Tomorrow isn't going to be that great, but I do need to figure out what all of my grades are looking like for the end of the year. I  NEED  to make honor roll or I'm so completely screwed. I've got dinner with the family too. Then Michelle and I go and work out.  G'night all... or whoever still read this.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I need to take a day to be by myself.  &nbsp;  I had you listen to my cheesy poem. You passed out... you were too stoned. And the sad part is you probably never read this anymore. That's alright... I would say so much more but it doesn't really matter.  &nbsp;  Other than that the past few days have been weird but I'm alive. (alone... *back space*... alive). This is the first time I've had trouble typing. I'm too drunk to care right now.  &nbsp;  One is the loneliest number... especially when you've just lost all hope.  &nbsp;  Ned, if you actually read this, call me please....  &nbsp;  And as for everyone else, I'm placing the blame on me. I'm glad I'm too drunk to drive. I'd probably be in New Jersey by now, if otherwise.  &nbsp;  Blue-eyed, brown-haired girl.  A youth to each their own  And unmarked graves for the undead  Though these ghosts walk among us  We never divert to such a lifestyle  Beauty's face and Purity's scent  This crowd of beloved ones  Nothing can change the position matter has taken  Self and the state of "one"  A worship of an addictive feeling  Clearance to sleep though I will never partake  Fear that life will pass us by  17 and scared  I never want to miss the good times  Or the lust of pleasure  Thunder rolled over my heart  And all was wondrous  Intoxicated by Euphoria herself  Kiss my lips and let me experience the culinary genius  Taste the majesty that is happiness&nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would write about tour but the people that actually care about my time in Europe have already read the diary that I kept (which is unfortunate on many levels). It's good to be back...  I got back on Friday. I missed everyone to death. Though there's been more controversy than I've ever desired, I'm trying to deal with things. I really hate waking up in the morning to my heart pounding, to me panicking, but then realizing it was all a dream... or so I hoped. Hopes are useless on many levels. And recently I've been going though my old journals and bloggers and poetry to not only realize how immature and petty, but that I got my hopes up too often... I trusted too many people. And I'll say this now but this may not be true by the end of the day: I don't think I trust anyone anymore. It scares me because I've never held this many secrets from anyone, not even myself. I'm sorry I feel this way. There are so many people I want to trust or put my faith into (again?) but I don't know. I'd hate to say I learn from my mistakes because that's not the truth. Past situations have changed me... and this is what happens. Like I said, I'm trying to deal with things. I hate these feelings as much as the next guy. I'm sorry if I hurt either of you...  Besides the sad stuff Michelle and I dyed my hair red yesterday. We went to Ballard. I had a whip-it but flipped out (long story) and got drunk or something close to drunk. Ned came by my house after I stormed out and said "fuck you." He called Michelle in the car... but again, this is all a really long story that, personally, I'm not willing to talk about (yeah, going back to the trust thing). But we sorted things out and I made sushi, we were going to watch Train Spotting, but something happened there. We all camped out in the study when my dad came home, both Michelle and Ned were falling asleep so I showed them to the door and went to bed myself.   I'm going to write about you all I want. Fuck you Donald. Kill me if you'd like, I know you'd have intercourse with my dead body, but it makes me want to hurl to know, to understand, to comprehend that every time you IM me it's only about sex. What the fuck is your problem?? Don't talk to me for the most selfish reasons in the world, and don't complement me ever again... because we both know their fake.   Damn that felt so good. I think I'm ready to take on the unpacking of my suitcase.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello from Pisa, Italy. Tour is going great and but I am still ever so excited to get home in two days. I hope everything at home is going okay. I'll probably type up my entire tour journal and post it up here for people to read. I've been hanging out with Zakk, Cara, Andrea, Mallory, Kenny, and Keith for the majority of my trip. Everyone seems to be pretty cool with everyone else... that's the great thing about tour. I played my last concert of my high school band career last night. I shed a tear, but I'm a pussy like that. At any rate, I better let Sally have the computer. Yeah, we're actually being rational. Ah... to Milan tomorrow and then home on Friday. I miss you all... :-/   I love you. :-)   
    
</post>


</Blog>