<Blog>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Mom woke me  up with a phone call at 10am! I didn't know I sound absolutely ridiculous in the mornings as I was slurring away as though in another language that even my mother couldn't understand. funny, recalled a dream just before she called. i was somewhere in outspace. perhaps it was the IMAX after-effects. Chatted for a good 37 minutes and I realized it was time to return to the car. I got down and boy it was so bright and glaring from the snow. slushy too... yuk! shot some pictures of the damage...  Here are the pictures of the what actually happened to 'my car' that was rented.    That's the unfortunate Cavalier.             I may be liable for up to the value of the car but since I am not at fault. However, I am extremely thankful for the honest people who were involved. thank God it's not a hit and run scenario. i heard a lot of stories about last night that the driving conditions were so terrible! There were many accidents just from last night's freezing rain and snowing!  I might be getting a haircut of my life today! I'm going hairless! I know i will definitely look alien but that's what I decided for now. it's a committment and I do this to remind me of something. silly as it sounds... but that's what it's going to be. hope it grows back just in time for my convocation. i dont' think i can get used to a different look i never had for the past twenty over years of my life. that'd be something to look forward too, eh? 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After watching Bruce Almighty at Kirk Backstrom's place with Yanbing, it was time to go back to catch some sleep when I saw a yellow wooden barrier placed beside the rented Cavalier that I parked along Cumberland Avenue (closest to Walloston Hall) was hit and there is a deeeeep dent in the driver's door towards the front left wheel. "oh shit!" as i advanced closer to inspect what actually happened and this time it wasn't my imagination; nothing could be more real that realizing that "that's a fucking huge dent!" And I was like "what am I going to do?!  urlLink Hertz !! they're going to screw me! Insurance! oh damm! i should have purchased it!!" Then I noticed a note wedged in between the wiper and windshield. I thought that had better not be a summon ticket for illegal parking! But I know I  did NOT  break the law because that is a legal parking space at that time. A sign is just before where I parked reads,  "1 hour parking: Mon-Fri 0800 - 1700"  I parked there at 22:40 so I could have parked till Monday! "That couldn't be a ticket", I convinced myself! Took it off and unfold it. Under the incandescent light I could hard make out any words and besides, it was snowing heavily! On top of the paper reads,   There was a 5 car accident last night just after 11:00pm. We will all be reporting to SGI   The content of it was a list of those involved in the accident.      Danielle R.  Mercury (Grey)  NZH 888    955-****  4 people  31702491       Tiffany M.  Ford Escort  450 CTS    242-****  2 people  3014436       Kristen D.  Saturn  300 CSZ    343-****  1 person  30391031       Jae H.  Mitsubishi (White)  335 DTB    717-****  4 people  n/a       Farshid T.  Neon  692 DSW    372-****  1 person  31661580      Drove back and called up the first person on the top of the list, Danielle. After talking to a lady (apparently learned that that is her mom) she said that it was Danielle who hit a parked car. That is the Cavalier. oh my god! But very politely her mom explained how the accident happened despite the fact that I might have awoke her coz I think she was surprised as well the driver of the parked car called up looking for information "this late". All went well. Kirk was on the other line waiting to be answered. Asked me if I had called up the city police. Yeah, I did and the officer told me the what Danielle's mom told me. So I figured that is what I must do then. The best part is all the numbers and names provided in the note was all genuine. This has made it so much easier!  Lets just hope that I will not be liable for the damages incurred in that accident. I learn one thing here, no matter what your chances are, that infinitestimal probability can always show up and boom! you're hit! If you're insured, then you can be rest assured everything will be fine! If you're not, you don't call the shot! It can burn a huge hole in your pocket! Take the inverse of an infinitestimal number and you'll see it's a huge number! that's a simulation of how big the impact can be.  to be continued...   signed out: 02:07 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The interview this noon went through well but I suspected something was amissed. Whatever that could be, I am really hoping it'd be a successful one! I left Ridelle's Center, where the interview was, right after. Stopped by IMAX theater to watch the Space Station. It was awesome! Wished it has lasted longer than 45 mins for a 7$ pass. Sneaked into the Science center via the back door... nobody noticed and yes, I got a free entrace inside. I've been here 5 times (including this time) so I thought there won't be anything new here and I won't be planning to stay for long. Walked around and noticed quite a few exhibits that are new. Stayed for a total of 3 hours! ha! I also had a chance to get on the  weightlessness simulation machine .   Me, experiencing the weightlessness simulation machine    The weightlessness simulation machine    Making a bubble sheet    Double image of myself  Nothing much after that; just drove back to Saskatoon. It was raining. But about 60km before S'toon, it was hails and little ice. Road was extremely slippery. There was an accident about 40km before S'toon. I almost skidded when I slowed down but thank God nothing serious happened. I don't know what it was... it doesn't looked like an accident but there were several other cars and trucks that stopped by. but that's it.   urlLink Jason Strauss  asked me for a huge favor -- to take a picture of him... with a pose! said it will be for " someone " tonight. but i just got back and read his email and I guess it's too late. At least somebody out there do recognized me as ahem... "the people's photographer". hey, t'is a professional job and I take it seriously.   I should study and get some times done especially Comm301's project. geez! I haven't done anything yet and the due date is just a week away!  signed off: 22:07 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Glad I got this up and running for the first tiem. Never really have written any thing for the public to read so I'm not sure how this is going to turn out to be like.  Right now, I'm in the main library of University of Regina. These are some pictures of the place. I'm here for an interview. It was heck of a day today.   A view of the main library of the University of Regina   Got picked up by Hertz to collect the car I rented at 10:51 and left for Regina by 11:45. Arrived the city at 13:45 (i was speeding a little; just checking out the top speed and apparently it won't go any further than 170 clicks.) On average, i was running at 120 clicks.  Anyway, I found the Education building and I just realized I don't know where the session was suppose to be held. Before i panicked and thought that all my efforts made for this trip could be futile, I found myself asking around and it was a 1 hour search. Gone through 3 people (2 and half actually) but I have to thank Kristina Lee (from her accent, I could tell she's from Singapore) for helping me big time. She called and called so many people asking if they knew anything about Peppy Kidz Club. None of them knew anything! On the verge of giving up, she made one last call to this guy and she said and I quote, "Hello [name]! How was your day? ... Listen, I'm calling up to ask you if you have any information regarding Peppy Kidz Club because I'm helping out a gentleman here who is... " "YOU DO!?!!" That is such a relieve!! I was just about *this much (pressing thumb and last finger together) to giving up and heading home feeling useless! The one hour battle to know where the heck the room is is finally resolved! I KNOW it is somewhere in the Education bldg. of U o R. and also the first name of the person who is recruiting... David. Later I learn that his name is David McNeil! Good thing I can still trust my short term memory! So the place is at Audio Visual Services: Screen Room C.  Been there, Done that! Now I need to find a place to stay. It's now such a relief! After all that I've been through this afternoon, it's now all good. Tomorrow is the interview session. Today was just the information session where I caught a glimpse of what Japan is like and how is it like to live in Japan.  Signing out: Terminal: Main library (U of Regina) archerly38 Time: : 21:17 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The weather these past few days have been awesome! Believe me, it's not cold at 6 celsius. Soooo comfortable! well, we've gone through the worst winter ever ... minus 57 celsius! that's why it's not cold for us.  the visa is still useable though, I THINK!!?. lol! shitty! cleaned it up! yuck! hope i doesn't give me shit when its magnetic tape is being read. e.g.  Transaction Aborted! Full of shit!"   Ran into Ai Yoshida in tunnels. can't feel my legs. damm! i don't even know why i began bowing... whenever I see Japanese. I must stop this behavior! they're not in Japan and I'm not even Japanese... I learned from them: when somebody offers you a piece of food with their chopstick ("Do you want this meat? It's cooked"), you can't pick up it up with your chopstick from him/her. A Japanese taboo. The act of passing an item from person to person using chopstick is practiced in Japanese funerals. Don't do this when you're dining with Japanese. It's easy to forget because there is no such taboo in the Chinese culture; Chinese people just  take  it.  Spoke to Samantha Leong (*Sam) in Commerce Reading Room. her exam schedules aren't as bad as mine. i have a confession to make. i really admire her. l liked her. but not my type... i don't know. maybe? however, I am not going to make any moves to her or whatever. I'm not desperate for a young well-endowed lass like her. pretty face, her eyes (the way she looks at people/me??) and her voice just sweeps my feet off the floor . ooh! haha! i'm in love! nah! this is what everybody else feels too. i'm pretty sure! I think I should consider going after who I think is my compatible as oppose to potential partner. A pretty face can fail in compatibility & potentially end very messy. Maybe not. It's hard to tell. But as observed and I believe, men have levels of ego so high they lose track of who they are... whatever. I hate generalizations. But anyway, who wouldn't want to go for such sizzling hot 18/19yr old girl?  19 eh? sigh! Eelynn asked me about my new 19-28mm Tokina lens. As I explain to her, maybe half of her mind was thinking about Kuni (Kuni Niina) whom she was once 'in love' with. She's 19, he's 28 yrs old. It was an impossible relationship. He's not into her in "that" way. She interrupted me, "I was thinking about Kuni when I saw you turned it from 19 to 28." We were on the railway bridge. Adam (met frm AIESEC) was taking a walk.  Returned Jessie's digital camera (Casio make). Probably from here there won't be as many pictures as before. :( 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I dropped my Visa credit card into the potty! yuk!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ha! I'm so drained out! I have been in school from 9am till 10:30pm. We have been working on our project since morning. I needed a break and a new scenery, so I headed on to main library at 5pm to tutor Trent in Econ277 for an hour. After that, Sakura invited me to for a hotpot dinner (a.k.a steam boat) where I also met a very cute Japanese girl, Ai Yoshida. ;)  Benson Or, man.. I haven't seen this guy for so long and we sat down and chatted a little in artsbuff right after econometrics! I remember he said he will go skin-head with me. not sure if it was a dare-you kind of thing, you know what I'm saying? Looks like he doesnt have as much guts as me. Very nice person! always wanting to play chess although he doesn't mind losing most of the time, if not already always. i recalled a [normal] game of chess with him that lasted 2 hours! I dont think when playing chess... lol!  13 days to freedom! feels like i'm maximizing my utilities by consuming the feelings of freedom and/or vacation moods right now. I'm just so rational! This might most probably just lead to my failure to graduate! Rational?? guess not!  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Managerial Accounting project deadline: Monday April 5. Stressed out. Driving me up the walls.  Exams schedules are horrible!! Monday Apr 12, 7pm Tuesday Apr 13, 9am Wednesday, Apr 14, 2pm Thursday, Apr 15, 2pm. Friday, Apr 19, 2pm.  This is what I deserve to graduate? damm! That's horrible! There will be sleepless nights! 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tutored a student from Econ277 (Economics of Natural Resources) for an hour this evening. Felt a little nervous when I stumbled upon the things I'd go "huh? what's that!?! waaait a minute! let me figure that out first". ;-)  Having said that and I thought it was not a good session, I declined her offer to pay me because I think it's a fair game. The only time I will accept payment is from second sessions forward because then s/he thinks that I'm good enough to be his/her tutor. ;)  I got a message from Eelynn through Michelle Tan who rang me up. How nice of her to think about me as she didn't want to go for her dinner in Marquis Hall. Well, she still refuses to talk to me for some unknown reasons. Probably by now everybody would have knew that I was rude to her. I dont know what she said but I don't think it's appropriate. Her habitual sarcasms were well recieved when we chatted before she swore that she would not talk to me for the next 24 hour. Quite simply I put forward my sarcasms but didn't think it was stinging or sharp enough or let alone offensive or even rude to her in our conversation (over MSN Messenger!!! how silly can this get?). We have tolerated one another's remarks in the past and it was just one of our usual chat-away time then but somehow things just went wrong. with me? or with her?!  Received a call from Hertz! Good thing it's good news! I was thinking I am going to pay up to over a thousand dollars! Not even close. $414 including the 2 day rental, a difference of 299$ if nothing had happened to that car!  Scouting for tree-planting jobs across Canada with silviculture co.'s right after convocation. Seiferling (Mike) is going to help me out. hopefully things will go as I wish.  Daniel Cheung, my coke/drinks supplier! and stalker! wtf! he so quasi-gay when comes to political matters! lol! Since he's the only person consuming his over supplied drinks, it would be rational (people are assumed to be generous) to share it all out. meeh! at the end of exams, we'll bug him! 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMG! I tried to make Szechuan's Eggplant and it turned out ab-sooooo-lute-leeeee superb!! I was missing 2 essential ingredients though -- Worchester sauce and hot paste sauce. I did without them anyway and it turn out unbelievably deeeeeeeeeeee-leeeeeeeeeeee-cious!!excited!! all done in one hour including preparation time. want the recipe? check out  urlLink here at RecipeZaar  You won't regret this! Here it is the dish!    Waiting for my steam rice to be cook... it's 23:40 now. I made that eggplant dish for tomorrow but now that I discovered it is absolutely irresistable!! Ah, finally, My most awaited late dinner here! I am not hungry actually but this is just irresistable because it's still hot and fresh. Microwave  heated food are left for the following days.   Arial view of my creation. Silly! *sniggers!*    You just can't imagine how much of steam rice I eat everyday! Yet I look don't look like Jay Leno. *lol!  K! Those are the pictures! Everyone has their own ways of describing things and mine happens to be very, very visual. I love to cook and this dish has just made my day! I did alter it a bit and it turned out to be a little way to spicy than I thought. I wonder why everytime when I cook I tend to trigger off the smoke dectector; having to fan off smokes away from it's 'nose' so it'd shut up. it's beeping is deaftening high pic alarm! the good thing is that it's not connected centrally to the local fire station. ;)  Did a whole bunch of studying today at the main library. I haven't seen those Malaysian people around these few days. hmm... 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was looking up for some news back home and when my eyes caught the headline printed in bold that reads  urlLink "Student beaten to death by seniors"  just fucking brought my moods down! I hate to read the details of it but I just have to know what has happened to that poor 16 yr old victim, Mohamad Faris Ibrahim, who apparently is new in the school and is intelligent and is liked by teachers.  What is the goddam problem of being smart and liked by teachers that Ibrahim deserved to be beaten up in the first place?! To hell with jealousy!! Everybody can be liked by teachers, parents, elders if they are smart and intelligent and wise and kind and generous and all those positive attributes that societies embrace close to [her] bosoms. Is Malaysia (certain parts) a really screwed up place? The 14 perpetrators are arrested and personally I think they are society's pest and should be banished until they learn the essence of life. In fact, to beat up somebody who is smarter than them to death is animalistic! Humans are not animals! And because these people manifest such anamolies, rightfully the entire group should not even be given a chance to live because they have not given Ibrahim a chance at all!! What kind of people are they!? Where can our society start to pin-down terrible ills like this?! Everybody has a familiy; Ibrahim belongs to somebody where love and care is given to him! To take somebody's life is NEVER anybody's rights! To fucking RAPE a girl (a female, not to be politically incorrect) is outright fuck-up, screwed and have brainless and should not live! I am so sick with sighting news like these!   I'm so mad at people like this! Do these people want to have a less-educated society to live in?! hell no!! there should be more educated and smart people and are liked by teachers in the future! I wish these smart people will be able to protect themselves from harm. It's sad and I'm terribly sorry for Ibrahim's death. But one man's mistake is another man's learning.  The hostel lack of security systems! If only hostels have surveillances for the safety of students are implemented, then chances of such tragic incident would have been minimized. Something must be done to rectify this sickenning social ills! Start with our schooling children first! When sex education is passed on or educated appropriately, society as a whole should be better off. I am concern for the safety of the female populations back home specifically limited to the area of sexual assaults.  My fury for dickheads out there in Malaysia (as well as the rest of the world) is burning like never before! If only I am omnipotent and omnipresence, (haha!) I rrreally want to crunch  these dimwits, shallow-minded, hollow brained, sex maniacs in my hands until none of these wasted sperms exists on the surface of earth! Such animal behaviors are done only by lowly people who would just degrade and humuliate the human race! And we DON'T need to be humuliated by these people! Something MUST be done! pathetic dickheads! a bunch of retards! give them a dozen of tranquillizers and put them to sleep forever! if only law enforcers are equipped with such measures! Caught criminals on sexual assaults should and IS RECOMMENDED to be castrated without trial and such punishments must be made public! Since no men has ever donated penises, no man will EVER want to face such a shortage at the peak of high demand! At least I have put my economics knowledge into good use here! And woman who are threathened to perform oral sex to fucking dickhead should just chew away their dicks! They don't and cannot respect women, women should not suck up to men who cannot respect them as individuals! CASTRATE SEX-MANIACS! CASTRATE DICKHEADS! CASTRATE! CASTRATE!! CASTRATE!!! Castrate in the name of women's safety... aw shit! then women won't be happy no more, eh? Still, CASTRATE DICKHEADS! CASTRATE SEX OFFENDERS! Every women in Malaysia should arm themselves with a razor sharp knife! Hmm... how do I get this message to the Parliament of Malaysia?! 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today, I visited a hairdresser @ Da Bomb (Upper Place) to get a few tweaks on my head. She had me asked four times just to make sure that this is really what I wanted. "This" meaning a skin-head. I didn't look when she was in the process of cutting it all off but somehow her reconfirmations made me look and I'd gasp at every look. It's funny. She enjoyed doing the service for me too... seems like it! Above all, to NOT to forget her, I told her to carve out  APR '04  behind my head. All done by 11:05am.  Went to SGI to get claim insurance for the damaged rented car. Jae Ho went with me. Thank God we didn't have to wait long (we were told to but were helped ASAP). Apparently, I learned that Hertz is one of those rental company that charges their customers 'downtime costs' for as long as the car is in service/repairs. So, that'd mean that I am still renting the car and they're charging me for it. totally not fair but I guess it's on my head as I did not agree to purchase their insurance at the day I rented the car so all these 'unnecessary' costs could be waived. I hope I'm able to get a claim from those involved in the accident on the basis that IF there were no accident, then there is no downtime cost on my behalf. It's beween me and the renter. I know, but assuming all's good ... no accident, I could have returned the car without any damages the next day. As for the damaged insurance, I am 100% entitled. Jae Ho hit my car first and he is liable to whatever damages that might have incurred that night. During the discussion with our adjustor (Jeff), Jae Ho does not have a valid driver's plate at the night he hit my car. Too bad for him. Danielle R. was the person who slipped and rammed into the driver's door of my car (Picture below). things just gets better and better!  Alex Ng, my roommate, left and artistic work on my head too. He wrote  "4HiM"  on top of my head on my request. Good job! lol! Now I feel like my head has a potential to exhibit people's artistic works. You can't do these when you have hairs! Why I do it? Well, why not? This is not something that you'd look forward to doing especially when you have kept your hair with a certain style almost all your life. Right now, I have done something very different I have never even imagined before and perhaps, since my memory has served me right, I will never forget this event. I make history for myself. haha! Get a tattoo? Nah! not myself and not my type. I have thought about it but didn't like the idea. True, it's something that I never had but tattoo is not my game. This is my souvenir from Canada.          Back view; Notice &quot;APR'04&quot;         Reflection of a mirror. A silly self-portrait; kinda cool.       ;-)         I'm like, &quot;What do you think, huh? Like it or hate it?&quot;         A Chinese thug look-alike.          4HiM  here has religious connotations. It's up to you  to interpret; I like it! Got it from a Christian band called 4-Him.         A better back view [again].     This has better serve me good! at least for this short period of time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just came back from a bar with my two other friends, Xiaohai and his friend. Xiaohai wanted to experiment with a digital video camera so he came to me and asked if he could borrow it. I didn't mind though so I passed him everything except the most vital part -- firewire card -- that's afixed in the mobo. Too much hassle to remove and put it back i explained even after many of his pleas. sigh, why can't some people understand that? said that i will never remove that but told him to do whatever experiments he wants with it and when it's time for post-production works, just ring me up. i've got exams to write so i don't want to even though I have no use of it now.  Went out for dinner with my brother, Andrew... after convincing him that I'm hungry and I have to eat right away six times before he agrees to go. I just want company. after all, he had a tiramisu dessert at Alexanders... that's something he can  always  do and I don't think "there's nothing to do" when you're with somebody. boy, felt the brotherhood there when chatting! it's good! wish he could be more  un -reserved. cool guy! Looks like we both have a common opinion on Malaysian girls, in which I think is hilarious. very seldom we discuss matters especially our counterpart girls.  I just know that [most, if not all] women are complex creatures. some men are too simple beyond comprehension too. ahh! that's just the perfect world, eh?  Ee Lynn, my adopted sister as well as a great friend, "promised to herself not to talk to me for the next 24 hours" over petty things. 24 hours is just right for her to be done with all her whinnings and get over with the fact that she can't beat me verbally.  "O... you poor kid! I'm sorry you have to put yourself in this unnecessary mess and make a biggie out". Called her immediately to clarify but her roommate, aah.... Jessie *daydreaming....*, was "instructed" to say that Lynn is sleeping. sigh! This, further substantiates my aforementioned theory. lol! Maybe I don't handle little kids too well...? thus, I foresee myself as a bad teacher. Whatever it is, that 24 hours is going to voosh by quickly.  beware of Vdan's unusual mood swings! Somebody operate my brain pleazzzzzzzzzeeeeeeeeee! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Too soon to think about convocating this May.  Too soon I have told people that May is the month.  Too hard is 2 of my courses namely Portfolio Analysis and Econometrics (316, 404 respectively)  Two days more I'm screwed and convocating this May, may still be a distant.   Applying equations are easy when you know what's going on  having to know at least more than > 100 unique equations per course is just insanity even if you know what's going on.  but more likely, the truth is you don't!   Do I really want this Business Economics degree?  Right now, I think I am doing a degree I didn't want  Not because formulas from lagged variables t-1 to infinity the summation of difference squared divided by some arbitrary number multiplied by ONE minus the summation of sigma square from t=1 to n is tearing my very soul apart... i'm parting away for an imaginary mental assylum; there will I be safe from the bombardments of "academically sound equations" so-called! Gawdd!! Am I in the wrong class or am I doing the wrong degree??? Either way, I am at close proximity to megalunaticism!   Time I do not now have  There's too much to know and too much of have-to-know  Phuck! Life were better those days in the caves  Hunt during the day and return home for good time with wife and kids, you know?  I wish life were that simple!   Ai-ching, not love, but Ai Yoshida.  Bugged her today for tea-break.  Dyed her hair to a disastrous color--dirty blonde  but politely I comment it's the best color and she looks awesome!  So, that is Pareto Improvement strategy-- set(s) of strategies that does not make any party worse off as a result of your action(s).   Economics is just so theoretical and I really wonder how I am to apply what I learned. Whenever I look at economics, all I see are just equations after equations & I'm flabergastered without fail every single time. Do I understand them? Heck no!! Why am I doing in the Department of Economics then?! Besides the department is dominated mostly by males, heck, I have NO IDEA!!   I should get off and get some sleep so when I wake up, I can continue to amaze myself of how dumb I can be for every equations I have-to-know when I don't understand them and most of all, I don't need them in real life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dined out with Kendra in Alexandre's Restaurant/Bar after studying at 22:09. Received an email from David, the person who interviewed me, and it looks like I will not be going to Japan to work. For that kind of job, I would probably have guessed that my behavior during interview was not approriate for a teaching position especially when my audiences are kids below the age of 8.  Disappointment creeps up to me in a way but it didn't last long.  I guess the rest of my days will be extremely mundane as I prepare for final exams.  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...and Eelynn spake unto I; When fullmoon begins to subside My awaited apology offered when the moon was bewitchingly bright and round and I'm her "bestest sucker friend".  Rained today it was cloudy and; winds up to 56km/h but I was in the library from 9:30am so, didnt feel a as though I would be blown away.  Somebody approached me earlier and asked enthusiastically, "You know that girl you were speaking to? Your model friend? What's her name? She's soo... super b-e-a-utiful!! Do you know her well?" Um, this person whom I hardly know is asking me about Kendra. I don't know how I should feel about that. I just noded my head affirming to his latter querry. "Oh... man, she's hot stuff!" I think it's more appropriate if he tells her that rather than reaffirming the facts (which I already know!) with me. I should understand why he's saying these to me... thinking back, I have actually done something similar too. Too heavy to carry my swelling balls to where that good looking lass is and pour our all my praises and admirations and adorations to her.  Here's Kendra. An extremely gentle lady! Unfortunately, she's seeing someone who has much more calibre than any of you undergraduates/graduates!   Please ask me for permission if you wish to have this picture. It would be more polite and not take advantage of what you have here, a privillaged information/media   Back to study.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How to make snowball - snowman... an illustrative guide without captioning. See for yourself.               Throw it!   Bang on!!  Pictures were shot on March 24, 2004. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "It is so basic. A human being is an innocent part of nature. Our civilization has distorted this universal quality that allows us to feel at home in our skin.  Other animals have coats that they accept, but the human race has yet to come to terms with being nude"  For as long as our society has not reached an eligible level to be called 'An educated society' we have NOT come to terms with nudity and/or sexuality. Immoralities and sexual plots/vices will definitely be manifested through small empty minds, like those of animals, but only worst. Therefore, censorships should and ought to preside at our assemblies.   I wish I could do something to curtail sex crimes in Malaysia. Law enforcers should consider my castration proposal to condemn filthy infidels sex offenders!! I hate them (potential/actual offenders)!! Gorge all their eyes out so they can't see sexual desires. They can't surf porn, therefore, they can't victimize an innocent woman. The internet is a good place for information but because small empty minds can't think the benefits to education, they rather fill it up with filthy information. There is nothing wrong to surf for pornographies but do it with the right mind and the right attitude. However, too much of porn is extremely unhealthy and this has been proven in a psychological study. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sakura has just passed me her picture and I was just speechless!!     Nothing much to say. Spent all day in the library today. Got intoxicated by coffee. felt a little weird in my body and couldn't concentrate from a while. then decided to grab marquis hall food... from my nice brother!! but it's just this once; and a few other times. hehe!  Exams are just 7 days away. getting pretty cornered and I have no where to run! if i had more time i'd slack off... so, maybe this is good! 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was awaken by Kendra's call at 09:30 who was just returning a call for her on Monday night at 22:30, which was me right after exam. Then I thought about my plan for today and for the rest of summer as I shower. Gone downtown with Eelynn and I had 2 rolls of films for developing prints. Cost me 29$ by Black's Photography and that is !@#%ing expensive for 2x24exposures! Initially I thought that's stupid as I could have had the same quality prints from Photolab for under 5$ (plus tax) per roll. There's something good about it though. The person printing pictures actually "criticize" your photos and if s/he likes it will adhere a little sticky that reads "Great Shot!! We'll take 2$ off when you re-print a 8"x10" I had like 3 of these. The revelation is not that I realized how good a photographer I am, but... how ambitious I can be.  So, I was suppose to be working on a website for ESS (Economics Student's Society) and is scheduled to be done by May. But I think my department's website deserves a much better revamp than creating a new website for the society I was involved in for over 2 years now. The department's website will be my biggest project and I intend to make it more presentable, if not already as presentable as, the other colleges in the University. If you'd take a look at Agriculture's website, Drama department, etc. you'll be astonished at how each vary from one to another. Then take a look again at our department's website. If shame is a forbidden feeling, then I am totally disappointed at the web-developer who made that website for us when he has made much more good-looking website for others. I took a peek in his portfolio. His work really made our department "bad" at least limited to my opinion.  I'm going to put my best and all I know in it. I'm going to teach myself XML, XHTML, and Javascript to accomplish the project too. Although I dislike Economics as much as I have studied it for at least 3 years, I think this will be some generous offering I can give to my department. Hm, maybe I should impose a fee on them and it will be called as an "incentive contributions" to working on the project. *winks*  Will begin looking for a job too. No revelation on this one yet. I got my new Canon EF 75-300mm IS USM lens today. It's totally a cool lens!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh shit!! I have no idea what is going on in this class! How can I write exam for tomorrow?? Already I wrote 3 in 3 days. i'm screwed!  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Went for a swim at the PAC. Did a few jumps from spring board but that's one a meter high. I did a 5 meters platform some 3-4 years ago so I thought I could do it for show on their highest 3 meter springboard. Went up there I boy I was freaking out didn't have the guts to go down even though I was just going to do a straight dive. Climbed back down. what a chicken I am! Now that the university has spent so much building and extending the previous Physical Edu. gym, I should be making full use of it and it's only the right thing to do and not be a potato couch... or even a book couch for goodness' sake.  I managed to put together a few pictures I shot. Below are a few nice ones.            This panoramic scene of University of Saskatchewan is shot from the Graduate Computer Lab of the Department of Economics on 8th Floor Arts and Science building/tower.    After watching Once Upon a Time in Mexico, I'm inspired to make a dish featured in the movie called "Puerco Pibil" and is translated into "Slow-cooked Pork". You can get drunk with this fine cuisine because of of its ingredient is premium tequila! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello friends,  I have made Puerco Pibil (a.k.a. chonchinita pibil) for the second time and could be the last time because the coffee grinder in which I used to grind the ground spices is broken in the hands of Eelynn. But that doesn't mean she broke it. It could have been a defective grinder and I wasn't aware of the low quality item.  This time I had the Mexican girls come over my place to have the slow-cooked pork marinaded in tequila and other spices. All of them were excited and saw their native cuisine in disbelief in Canada... not to mention Saskatoon, the place where no one really knows a lot of. My brother was invited too and he just loved it. Their compliments to my fine art cooking (hehehe... just kidding, but seriously....) were never ending. I guess I am as elated as them because I have made a whole lot of people happy.  After that, I did shoot some portraitures of them individually. Will post them here once I get them developed. It was all good today, this evening. I'm good too. They snooped through my entire photo album and just love the pictures of China. I was there with my mom and brother in 1999. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       While taking some time off the project, I finally got to play "Max Payne 2: The fall of Max Payne". It wasn't too impressive although i still find the first episode best.  It's Tim's birthday today and he got a wonderful gift from us all -- love doll. As soon as the gift was revealed while we were all waiting for our cab ride at upper Place Riel, we can all sense he was too embarrassed to accept the unexpected. I have no idea whose idea was it to get him a love doll but it was definitely a kick-ass idea simply because the joy of watching him gradually (took about 3 hours) accepting the gift was just hilarious beyond descriptions. The doll was not inflated until we went out to Denny's Restaurant (right after a stripshow, in which I got a poster autographed by the showgirl simply because I caught her attention by pointing the red laser I had onto her pu**y and her fake but voluptuous t-t's). Avoiding embarrassment was inevitable when waitresses and customers were watching us laughing our lungs out teasing each other especially on Tim. Well, hehe... I did some silly's too. All these will be illustrated in a few days when I received pictures from Vincent.  It took 3 persons to inflate the Britney Spear-look-alike doll and doing that was ridiculously funny as the teases and silly words exchange were never ending. When all the girls refuse to inflate the doll, it came to me and my friends made it as though it was my duty. Well, already feeling shy, I tried not to look around when I'm inflating it. When done, 2 cute caucasian young ladies walked over my back and pat on my right shoulders and made a comment "You've got a lovely friend there!" and continued their way to the exit. Of course, anybody would surely have thought that it is my doll I'm inflating. And I was like, "w-t-f! but it is not mine". Friends at my table went crazy lauging at me and Tim, BECAUSE it is his doll. I was framed. I was accused of possessing another man's object of desire. It was unfair. lol. It is totally funny!  That's about all I can describe. Take care, my readers! Sincerely. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have been selling a piece of information for not more than 10$ in which will allow the buyer to acquire a camera or other gadgets for only US$39.90 as oppose to paying an ugly sum of at least US$600. I was totally surprised today to know that someone has bidded up my price to $156.50! For the past month, it has never been sold more than 13$ and today i'm getting more than ten folds. It's been great!! I doubted the winning bidder would pay but after looking at his flawless feedbacks (100%) I'm sure he will pay, and he did! I was even flabergasted as this is totally out of my expectation (because I think that piece of information I'm selling is not worth a hundred over dollars; hehe).  Got a pair of rollerblades today at Sportschek. It's been nearly 10 years since I skated and back then I was a pro. I did stunts and went on ramps and did all those twists and sommersault tricks but now maybe my old bones and weak muscles won't allow that no more.  And today, I received a letter from the Dean's office and the first line went like this: "I am very pleased to congratulate you on having completed all requirements of the College of Arts and Science for your  Bachelor of Arts Four-year  degree which will be awarded at Convocation on  Wednesday, May 26, 2004. " I was so excited! Finally, I have accomplished something in my life; not that I have never though. haha! My plans after this is to probably look for something to do with my life before I start to think of going back to school. What should I do if I were to go back to school for another 4-5 years? Engineering? Mom called me this morning and I told her I wanted to do architecture and she forbided me because she said it'll be very difficult to find a job with that.  Kurt Fletcher, a friend of mine (Metis), ditched me for the camping trip we were all suppose to go. He said the rest of the 12 people who were suppose to go ditched him first and it was only his girlfriend, himself, and his dog, plus me. I was still willing to go even if it was the 4 of us but he didnt like the idea maybe because he wants to have a private time with his [new] girlfriend. Maybe it's a bad idea to go with his girl too. I don't want to be seeing or hearing things I am not suppose to. I don't know who's telling the truth; who ditched who first. it could be that because he is still going with his girl, he ditched all of us and me. whatever. i don't really care. If it's true, he's a man of disappointment and very selffish. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's 2.5 hours past midnight. There was not much to do for the entire day as I stayed home all day; which was good as I could save some money. Furthermore, it was cold today and thought it was going to snow but it didn't.  Came to school at 23:50 to watch some Cantonese comedy movies (VCD) in Arts146 alone. The good news is that it was entertaining and it was definitely way better than watching it at home on 15" TFT screen of my laptop. coz here in arts146, i used the projector and watched it on big silver screen .. theater like. *winks* I felt like a murderer, I murder time because I have to and if I don't my idle mind would just drown me in boredom. This is for survival. geez, now i have to go back and it's freaking cold now. minus 3? not suppose to be cold but hey, we just came from plus 20's. if it was the other way , minus 30's, right now i could have gone home with my shorts. i'll cut the boring story.  later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Say Goodbye (zhu fu), a song by Jacky Cheung, playing as background music as I type this. Triggered some memories about my friends in the past and was comparing with the present. Some left, others came and eventually left. Only a few stayed. The rest left with promises to keep in touch but sadly those promises are usually behind the viels of hectic schedules to come out and be fulfilled. Life's pretty much revolving around goodbye's.  Did some gardening work today at Sherry Lin's house, Renee's aunty, with Charmei and Jessie (Shanghai). At noon all works stopped for lunch and I guess all got too lazy after eating and soon we continued watching the Cantonese series about paintings (Cruelty to Oblivion?) from where we left the last time. Took a nap at 15:15 for 2 hours when the smoke detector went off. "Noo!! Who that rookie doesn't know how to cook?" The smoke found its way through my closed door from the gap below between the floor and the door and I sniffed it. Smells familiar and smells good by the way. Didn't want to get up but the alarm went off again. I guess I had to get up anyway and I did. As soon as I opened my door I saw Benson standing up on a chair trying to remove the smoke detector from the ceiling.  He asked, "You just got up??" "No, I came back for a nap" The thought of a magazine flashed in my mind because that's what everybody living upstairs with me does whenever the smoke detector goes cuckoo. We would fan as hard and as fast as we could to shut up the detector... And there he was, twisting the smoke detector off from its secured position. Now, it dangles from the ceiling and would tell anyone that it has been tampered. That's Benson's signature there! I asked him later in the evening,   "Why did you want to take off the smoke detector from the ceiling?"  "Because that's what I'd usually do when I was living in Emmanual St. Chad", he explained in a matter of fact tone. Silent after.  I was like, "Ooh, okay. But this is a house and smoke detectors actually helps to notify everybody about a potential fire hazard. Not a very good idea to remove or to tamper with it. you were here many times when the smoke detector went off and I was cooking. hm, maybe you forgot"  Back to reality, there he was still standing on the chair with his left hand on the SD and his right hand probably searching for a wire to pull. NOOoooooo!! it's funny! I told him to get down and he did. I found a magazine and fan off the smokes so that annoying high pic alarm would shut up. He went straight to the kitchen to see how his Pork Chop was doing. Looks good... with all the smoke. :P Man, this guy must be something! It's just a hilarious scene--Benson's best alarming smoked pork chop! I didn't try it, but I have confidence that it's good!  Went out to the gym and worked on chest and arms. Felt good. the pool hours really suxx! couldn't swim after 2pm Mon-Fri. And later, we caught a movie called "13 going on to 30". I thought it's a girly-girly girl movie in which I was not even interested. Hopped theatre and sneaked into another to watch "Hellboy" , which is almost similar to "The league of the Extraordinary Gentlemen". Action-packed! my type!  That's it! Will write another day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hang-out at the library and had a long chat with Snowflake (Kendra's eldest sister) about her life and her beliefs. It's odd to hang-out there because there's practically nobody at the library especially during this time of the year. People are tree-planting, job hunting, and painting houses earning money. Ah, good news today and I am convocating in May 26th! Maybe that's why I'm at the library trying to get back that feeling of "studying"; weird.  Char Mei, a very cute girl and super nice came to our house for a black pepper T-bone steak in which Benson and I made. Sooo good! Didn't realize how easy it was to make steaks. When we're done working on our delicious steaks, we then remembered something was amissed--potatoes!! T'was too late as they're sitting and relaxing in a hot bath. A waste? Not really.  Then hangout at Yanbing's place for a while because Kirk Backstrom started talking with Benson about stuffs. Believe me, this guy can go on forever.      The looks of our first attempt at the steak; comparable to ones served at The Keg        Charmei and Benson posing before their dinner. I thought I noticed the drips of saliva from the mouth of these two people?        Meeh, the so-called iron chef taking a pose with Charmei after Benson insisted.        The woman with big long nasty knife gone wild with her food. Beware! report to your local authorities if you see this woman galavanting in your neighborhood. She'll devour your meal like there's no tomorrow!    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's full moon tonight Gazing at the moon light gives me a shiver The glow from it consumes my imagination wild Somehow it's weird coz I felt hungry while gazing at it  My friends left for home Home for them is Malaysia My roommate left for home Home for him is Guangzhou, China, Asia. A friend of my came in to occupy his room This friend is Benson.  Have not been writing for a week now already. I'm free but I don't feel that the freedom I should enjoy. Should I not know that freedom is what I am doing everyday -- boredom. Whenever my rested body awakes me in the morning, my restless mind asks where and what should be done for today. It seems there are nothing much to do compared to past months where school work is wha I get up to daily. I should really complete ESS website because Mary Jane, the secretary of the Department of Economics, told me Monday that a link was inserted to their brand new website. It's good news, and if I don't work on it, it'll be a bad news for all. Ah, pressure... this pressure I miss. The pressure of deadlines. The pressure of debts is climbing up on me too. damm!  The Mexican girls left Thursday. Found out that Daniella took with her my negatives. I'm okay with it but it'll funny if she had brought it back to Mexico. I'm just hoping I will get it back, not harping on it. I heard they are vacationing in the greater parts of Toronto and will soon travel to Montreal. Ah! Those brochures I said I will pass to them but non of us remember about it. Looks like we're all absent-minded sometimes, most of the time after pampered with a gooooood meal.  Went to gym on Friday and saw Omiyesu, a hot Metis girl. Went to her house to watch hockey; it was Calgary Flames vs. Detroit. Detroit won. Met her mom, who later revealed me her 2 precious cook book from Malaysia. She learned that I'm from Malaysia too and held me ransom for a cooking day Wednesday May 5th. I know we'll make yummies. Odd, but I think cooking is what I like to do when I have time. Photography too.  Yesterday, I ate all day. ha ha! believe me, I actually ate all day. I was with Char Mei and Jessie (Shanghai) in Sherry's home. Sherry, a person I have forgotten, is the aunty of Renee, a sweet girl whom I met about 2 years ago was here for ESL and gone back to Taiwan when her course ended. We were at her place making a Taiwanese snack called "Jiu cai He zi bao" that looks like dumplings. It was good! We started making from 12noon till 6:15pm, after which I had another appointment with Yanbing to make Chinese dumplings at her place. There were lots of people there laboring for the dumplings. Kendra was there too and she worked out her first few dumplings, which turned out to be not-a-disappointment. ;) There were just so many dumplings not many of us could finished it all.  Today, nothing much happened. waiting for tomorrow. waiting to gaze into the bewitching fullmoon again. signing off friends. I have bore many already. You'll not be the last. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am having a good life. Never have been better. I'm not worried and stressful days are a matter of the past. I miss you and you've been kind enough to tell me to have a good life. That's the least expected words from you. "I miss you too" never came out, even if I made a cute pout.   It has been 48 hours since I last ate a proper meal. How did I survived with just 3 glasses of milk and 6-10 cookies? Sugar sustained me? I'm not even too sure about this and it puzzles me even more coz I don't know why I had not felt hungry till this late evening 7pm.  Skated down downtown via University's bridge at plus 4 celsius. Fell once on my bump just before the bridge because of uneven surface and annoying pebbles were in the way. Used to know how to stop on slope but I just felt hopeless and clueless. The only way to stop I guess, right now, is to fall. That's a definite stop. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was away from May 9 (sunday) to May 11 (Tuesday). Three of us, Benson, Richard Wong, and I, headed out 2.5 hrs Northwest of Saskatoon to a place regional park called Meota. It's between North Battleford and Llyodminster but closer to the former. The car we were travelling in was packed with food, primarily meat and poultry; hoping to BBQ all of it after a long winter period of school. I was like, y'know, "hell yeah! it's about time we BBQ some stuffs" Arrived at campsite a 30mins late as we missed some turnings; we would be heading towards Llyodminster if Benson didn't turn back coz we're on the wrong highway. My bad, i was the so-called nagivator.  Arrived to the lonely campsite (we were the only people at the site) and excited and can't wait to start the fire the traditional way, not by striking 2 stones but but repetitive drilling of 2 fire wood. My hands were not made to last for this kind of mundane workout so I grabbed some dry grasses and gathered some smaller pieces of wood and lighted a fire on it (using a kitchen lighter; hehe!). We cheated but who cares? Set up tent and one of us will have to sleep in the car as the tent could only fit 2 people.  We chose to camp on this day and thought it will be nice and warm but little did we expect that night itself it was friggin' minus 15 with windchill, we were told the next day. Woke up in the morning at around 09:30 and noticed some icicles were just above my head, dripping cold water into my eyes and forehead because the day was already warming up. Now, that is a definite-wake-up call. That night, I had to have my face covered up as it was just too cold and windy outside. The bond fire we set up didn't help much to keep us warm. On the second day, I helped Richard over the fence where firewoods were kept. It's quicker to get wood that way instead of standing on two pieces of wood and pick out one by one with armpit on fence. We were planning to set up our little grand finale bond fire at night and hoping this will really keep us warm, dont want to be freezing out arse out again like the night before. It was funny when we all woke up and told each other how friggin' cold it was to sleep through. My brother's sleeping bag really helps and has kept me warm. Without it I really don't know how i would have survived. Later, we went to the lake nearby  with intention to fish and it was low tide. Didn't catch any fish to BBQ and that's unfortunate. What's more unfortunate is that we do not know how to fish. Snapped some pictures and went back to chopped more fire woods. Chopping these woods are not as easy as I thought. Those are really, really hard & dry wood. We exhausted so much energy doing this. Even the ground is pounded in and probably can be an evidence of thousands of wood been cut. Our only tool was a small cheap camping axe for that job. Some time in the afternoon, a wild hare crawled nearby our car and when noticed, it ran away so fast! Missed a photo opportunity! *sob*  We ate all 3 days and 2 nights. Mainly beef & chicken, bread, sausages, and bacon. I'm vegetarian for the next 3-5 days.  Benson "upgraded" himself from the cook to our camp's most dangerous alchemist. He wanted to make a bomb! I just wanted to throw in a battery and wait for it to explode. He wanted to make a BOMB!! haha! T'was really funny, especially to see him so involved with flammable liquids around him. Richard who is suppose to be objecting his actions, offered him (Benson) his skin lotion because on it Richard pointed out to Benson that the lotion is flammable. I was puzzled for a moment but as soon the lotion is in Benson's hand, I could see how happy and excited he was probably already thinking of all the possibilities he could do with that flammable skin-lotion! Of course, he went psycho by spraying that lotion on every flames he sees. lol!  I found out that woodpeckers (type of bird) are extremely shy OR maybe just too afraid of humans. However, after much attempt, I had a great photo shot of it. Will post up here soon.  later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Since mom's arrival things has been a little wee bit different. I gave up the comfort of my bed to my mother so I can sleep on the floor with a camping mat with 3 pieces of pillows on it for cushioning and a head pillow. Clothes hanging everywhere the hangers can hang on to.  Yesterday, Friday, lazed around in my room with practically nothing to do. Later in the afternoon, I decided to walk down to Student's Health Center to get a check up on my left arm again and be advised explicitly and learned that the rotary cuffs were torn. The beautiful blond doctor has doctored me in both ways. She was unsure whether one or more rotary muscles were torn and after many simple diagnosis our doctor-patient ordeal were concluded. What a relief! At least I know what went wrong in my arm. At Medi-clinic on Circle Drive and 8th Street, I knew nothing and thus, was uncomfortable until yesterday.  Mother was certainly on a shopping mood, not for herself, but for both my brother and I. I couldn't recount the number of times she went in a shop and mentioned what she was interested in or more like what she was looking for and told the sales girl why she was getting it. My family will be attending my convocation on May 26th. I feel proud to be around her especially these time when she has every reasons to brag about her son(s). I figured that that is what mother's do. Those many days of toil in the past has finally paid back when she can step back and look at her son, sigh a relief, and brag constructively. The way I am today is partly (or at most) molded from the long boring naggings of a failtful, loyal, patient, meek & humble, enduring, and generous mother. And I know she was gonna cry... when she would hear all these.  I bought a coat and a shirt and tie. I supported mom's idea that dad has to pay for all these because he has never bought one ever for us (my brother and I). Furthermore, I could also use it for future job interviews after wearing it to the May 26th's convocation. Sounds cunning and witty but I couldn't reject the idea mother suggested. hehe.  Dad called at last. We did not know where his whereabouts as he was suppose to arrive with his friend, Simon Ignatious, 20th. I learn that he, dad, rented a car from Vancouver and drove to Calgary. He rang me up at 21:19 (Saskatoon's time) when he was 1.5hrs away from the city. The thought of 2 old (well, not that old) men still have some sense of thrills of adventure seeking. When I asked why, "There's nothing to be seen when you fly" was the answer. I'm like, yeah right, what are you going to see during the night when the skies are already dark?! It has been 28 years since dad last stepped on this land, Canada. So, I think he was really excited to want to drive down his memory lane. My mother, on the other hand, thinks dad is out of his mind to even try that after a long haul. Well, they just arrived from Malaysia.  Went out for bubble tea with Albert P. and 3 of us. We missed out the Miss Venus Bikini model search contest at Shockwaves on 8th street. Kendra called me up this morning and I knew she won and was excited to tell me about it. I was right. She won and is going to Florida and will receive other prizes all totalling up to 10,000$ US. One lucky girl! I could hear she was almost crying her hearts out. I know, she's just overwhelmed and elated about the news that she did not even expect. I am lucky too, well, in a sense that I'm worthy to be the person to know she won and she told me personally. Expressed her feelings how she won and how she did it. It's wonderful! She's wonderful! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My left arm still hurts whenever I tried lifting forward. Its excruciating pain won't allow me to completely lift my arm forward without the help of my other arm. Thank God it's not broken or twisted but just a sprain. Dr. Eustace saw me and I was disappointed because he didn't communicate much with me so I didn't exactly know what was going on with my arm even after X-ray was taken (speaking of which, he did not even invite me over to look at my X-ray with him and explain).  My mother arrived today. Benson, who has been wanting to go back since Monday and is *still* here, drove my brother and I to the airport to pick her up. She didn't noticed I kept my arm behind the zipper of my jacket I wore until my friend mentioned about my arm in the car on the way home. Mom was shocked but she was okay soon after. The weather was rather cold, colder than yesterday and the day before. It was plus 6 and with windchill it felt like zero to one degrees celsius. My breath was visible although not as obvious as minus 20's or 30's.  I received a Fable Castel bi-way pen from mom as a graduation gift. My brother received a similar one as well. Good lord I have cleared the kitchen and my room before her arrival. The stinking pungent poop-like rotten smell just by the corner of the hall way before the kitchen has been discovered and discarded. Apparently it was me who left the rotten prawn/shrimp shells in one of the boxes chucked in that corner. Believe me, it was super stinking. Smells like dead roden with maggots creeping on and through its body. Yuck! I honestly couldn't imagine what my mother's reaction would be when she sniffed it out before me.   Jill called today and it was definitely a pleasant surprise to hear from her after many many days of trying to get hold of her. She'll be leaving for Atlanta tomorrow for 5 days. I haven't seen her for a long time and I miss her. Really fun to talk to her. Love to hear her sniggers, sound just so angelic cute girlish feminine? whatever. A turn-on for sure.  Well, I'm looking forward to days of adventures with both my parents around and my brother. Hopefully SASKATOON has "much to offer" than rumored. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This might sound crazy but a friend of mine we went out at 1 in the morning to the University's fields on Cumberland Avenue North just to star-gaze. There were not as many stars as the nights during camping last week. Alderamin is a star not too distant from Polaris, using little Bear's bottom's edge as guide. Imagining a linear line across from little bear (ursa minor), we'll see a constellation that looks like a kite. I'm short of words to describe this experience and I truly apologize. During this time my eyes gazed into the heavens, I noticed a shooting star from the corner of my left eye as I looked southeast. We were lying on the fields equipped with a constellation map, a pen-knife flash light, and a DPSS green laser pointer. Finally, I actually used this appropriately rather than distracting cyclists and pedestrians on sidewalks during the night. hehe! Could be fun, as well as dangerous to them. I sold it and shipped it off today. Im going to miss using it. Pointing a star or a constellation have never been easier with it. We saw almost 7 moving stars. It's hard to point out with your fingers but with it, its beam is so visible during the night and only realized it's an aircraft flying about 35,000 feet above us. My friend was like, hey, don't point to it. Pilots may get distracted and crash the plane down. The laser can only go up to 5000feet, hello?!  It's sucha nice day out today. Didn't want to get bored sitting at home staring at the computer screen so I decided to go out skating. Went to look for my brother who was not home so I headed on to Brunskill Junior High school for a nice gravel to skate on. Tried a trick move and I was moving fast; fell down 3 times. The first two on my bump, and the last one sent me to a clinic for an X-ray scan on my left arm. Apparently, it was a sprain and thank God it wasn't dislocated or the like. Now, I'm typing with a sling over my neck. The anti-inflammatory / pain-killer prescribed to me has some very horrifying side-effects. You don't want to hear it. So do I. Don't wanna get stomach-ulcers, burn my oesophagus, nausea, etc. sigh! I bet mom will be shocked when she arrives tomorrow at 16:38. hehe. This sling will definitely create a lot of attention.  Like Kendra said, it's not that you're ADD or LOA, but you're merely enjoying the attention you get. By the way, ADD and LOA is the abbreviation for Attention Deficit Disorder and Lack of Attention respectively.  I stumbled upon a poem posted (not written) by a blogger who is from Malaysia. I find this guy is quite articulated and quite talented in writing indeed. The poem is about smile. Enjoy!     A smile cost nothing, but gives much.      It enriches those who receive,    without making poorer those who give.     It takes but a moment,     but the memory of it sometimes lasts forever.      None is so rich or mighty that he can get along without it,    and none is so poor but that he can be made rich by it.       A smile creates happiness in the home,     fosters good will in business,     and is the countersign of friendship.     It brings rest to the weary,     cheer to the discouraged,     sunshine to the sad,     and is nature's best antidote for trouble.      Yet it cannot be bought, begged, borrowed, or stolen,     for it is something that is of no value to anyone     until it is given away.      Some people are too tired to give you a smile.     Give them one of yours,     as none needs a smile so much as he who has no more to give.  Smiles! think positively! Take care and get well soon, danny!  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Many have claimed to see unusual phenomena and/or objects in the skies and people often question their credibility. I am not a fervent believer of such stories but I do know that we are not [quite] alone.  My green laser pointer got sold in eBay and I'm going to ship it to the buyer tomorrow. I know I'm going to miss using it so I decided to go out and star-gaze using the laser pointer for one last time; well, more like star-pointing. The laser pointer has some sentimental meanings to me and so, again, i think I'm really going to miss it. When I was gazing into the night sky for a while already with the laser's beam visible, I noticed 4 objects flew over me in a parellel line heading southeast. It was moving very fast and silent. There were no wings and I really didn't think those could be big birds like goose; I could tell the shape of it from the faint lights reflected from under its body and my judgements convinced me they are not birds. I could not confirm what I saw were UFO's because i don't quite believe I'm ever so lucky to encounter one. If they were really UFOs, then have them come down and meet me. I want to say to them, "Show me the way... to your home" so their place will be a place of history when I return as a hero who have destroyed their planet. drop a nuke and run like never before. In the future, there will be no more lame stories like Alien Spaceship encountered in Tennessee farm acreage abducted farmer's daughter or an Alien's body with a husky dog's head. gross!!  There's something missing about this blog. I suspect it is missing substance. This substance is essential to every stories that will bring back readers or at least create an impression to readers. When a story lack of substance, the writer lacks that substance too. Love and relationships are not something I will love to write about because I think I'll end up complaining about a person more than I would proclaim my feeligs for her. What should this blog be on as the main theme besides my boring life? Everybody has their boring days and if I write my boring days then that makes me a boring writer. Comments are more than welcome. There is a link just right below every stories I write. Write to me.  I watched "Secret Window" by Brad Pitt today and figured that it's just another movie on schizophrenia, a multiple personalities disorder. I believe that everybody is a schizo in one way or another. When you're faced with problems or during a decision making process especially on something you've never tried before (i'm narrowing down the scope to ones that society deemed to be negative or not good), you'll often hear your 'other self' speaking in your head. We all grew up with cartoons and I'm sure Tom & Jerry, the silly witty cat and the little smart mouse, is very familiar amongst you. You've seen a little angel Tom speaking to one side of the cat's eat and a little devil Tom on the other side when he's up to no good. When you talk to yourself; when you're just over with a quarrel with your wife, your other self becomes more evident gradually. Some people don't think about it, while others do. Everybody's little schizo is not a real problem because we're all normal people, people without the severity of a real schizophrenic. Like my friend I wrote about few days back, in his email he wanted so bad to be somebody he is not. And I found out that he has been trying so hard to be "The ladies' man" just to please his female peers. Because of disappointments and also usually fueled by anger from not getting what one wants, the other part which he is not begins to manifest itself. Who is the other part of him? I'll find out, but I know that part of him is up to no good. I will have to find a way to suppress that part from emerging. It is about life & death. I, again, will become a hero upon successful suppression of schizo patient. My other self, whom i named Kevin, will help me. ;) 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Back to writing again. Received a call from Charmei 2 nights ago and learned that she was going to plan a BBQ outing on Sunday, which is today. I thought it was suppose to be an invitation, and it is by the way, but she admitted she has never actually done an event like this before. I was questioned mostly on the how-to's part. I thought since she has never done it before, shouldn't she have kept the number of invitees small so as to avoid major disappointments and probably embarrassments? Well, it kicked off today and most of us were there and it all went smoothly. She was almost thrown into the river, though. Funny.  We played soccer and frisbee together, I mean at the same time. incoming soccer ball and the frisbee plate... yikes! i'm sure we all had fun time and it's nice & warm outside today although it did get a little cooler (plus 14). lots of breezes though. Anyway, here are the pictures of our group and some activities. All pics have been resized to fit this blog. Please contact me if you wish to have the original pictures.      Met a girl who was walking this dog. Walked up to her and asked if I can play with her dog and she agreed. This dog, Roxy, is hyper-active and extremely agile. She's a swimmer too and nothing can stop her even if you threw her ball into the river. She'll bring it back to you         This picture is shot around Victoria's Bridge, the last or the first bridge in Saskatoon.         Similar shot. From left to right in order: Wayman (HK), Colin (China), Gavin(?), Leonard (Shanghai, China), Raymond (M'sia), Tim (M'sia), Sandy (Taiwan), Benson (HK), Riley (Saskatoon, Canada), Charmei (M'sia), Jessie (Shanghai, China), & myself (M'sia)        -no comments-         I've always wanted to shoot this kind of picture. It's just so beautiful. From clockwise beginning from 12 o'clock: Jessie (Shanghai), Sandy (Taiwan), myself (M'sia), Charmei (M'sia), Tim (M'sia), Wayman (HK), Benson (HK), & Colin (China).         Tim's butt was arched in a very obscene way so I decided to sit on him just so that I don't have funny ideas while posing for the camera. ;) *wink*       Another baby story about a friend of mine.  One of my good friend emailed me just a few days back and the content of the email sounds pretty scary. It seemed like he just did a review of his personal life; like how he has fared in of relationships with girls. Here is his email I never thought he'd ever write: " MAN usually dont cry, but my heart cried out loud last sunday just before midnight. I curse the world to fall with me, there were thunder and rain starts pouring in the north. I can feel it! 13 of them will lose their live before sunrise' i failed my mission again, totally lost in foreign land. There i was,i run,run and run looking for the precious someone in my mother's land where people utter in different tongue it was so close, yet i lost it without knowing what was the reason!! The cut is really deep this time, it does make me a stronger person but as an EVIL person. Once motherly, now i can only see female vex in them !! I just wanted to be a ladies man but... I fail when i was good, the world its not fair. I WANT TO BE BAD!!! I WANT TO BREAK MORE SOUL THAN ANYONE ELSE!! I dont believe in HIM, i always get what i dont want! I realise why there are angels who become devils' I will only see heaven from my daughter's eyes I want to denied the gate of heaven! I chose to be in hell "  I didn't really get what he was trying to say especially 4th line. Whatever it is, like my friends have told me I passed on the same advice to him, that whatever goes around; comes around. It doesn't really matter if one believes in HIM (God) whether or not one gets what one wants. For those of you who knows the bible, you should realize the reasons why angels turned their back from God -- they lost their focuses. They were influenced by another who deemed to be as great as God. Where ever one chooses to be is entirely up to that individual's choice but he who chooses hell has chosen unwisely and even more foolishly to proclaim that. I feel it's really difficult to explain to somebody who doesn't believe in the spiritual realms.  As a friend, certainly I do not wish to see my fellow dear friend to "go to hell" just because he chooses to. But there's a subtle mutual understanding that we can't go around pushing one's belief to another. Am I helping out this friend a great favor by just doing this much? I feel that I can do more but at the same time I'm afraid I'll be invading his life.  If things didn't work out between the two of you, why not let go and live on just as life goes on? it's no big deal to lose one person whom you think is your potential partner when you have half of the entire nation's population of females to choose from. Having said this, damm, i feel like a pathetic hypocrite. I don't think I'm over with my Jean, my exgf. My love for her is deep and... i don't know, mysterious? I really miss her. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Woke up at 6:45am, one hour earlier than scheduled because the clock on my cellphone was screwed up. It was quite chilling outside with a 6 celsius and windy (gushing up to 28 km/h) and feels like 1 celsius.  I am still mesmerized by the fact that I shall walk away from the Dean on the stage in Centennial Auditorium with a Bachelor's degree awarded to me. "You have done well, Dann!", I thought to myself.  "Mom! hurry, we gotta leave!", I shouted to my mother who's in the washroom taking her time powdering herself. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Yoshida, model for me this spring/summer  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today, like any other day, I was reading news online at  urlLink The Star  checking up on the recent severe abuse case of a 19-year old Indonesian domestic maid by a merciless and mentally retarded house-wife and a mother of 4 children. Whenever I finish reading a story I'd look else where to click on to read further. I hate to look at ads but as this ad runs it cycle again, I thought I saw somebody familiar. I was like, "Oh my god! Is that him?!" I waited for the next loop and confirmed that it is Srikanth, one of my best friend whom I grew up with. He's online for the world to see but I'm more interested if he knew the sweet girl who comes next after his picture.      Right-click on the picture & save to get the fullsize view    He could really be a model for some fashion magazines, I thought. He works in an advertising firm and I figured it would have been much difficult to get my picture out to the world when I'm not in an ad firm.  Earned 30$ for a 2 hours session of Photoshop 7 tutorial today. Scheduled for 2 more sessions next week. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have been blogging almost daily, if not frequently. So have my friends. Today, I reflected on what we, youngsters as well as adults alike, are doing on the world wide web almost literally glued to our computers for hours -- blogging. Do we have a life?  What if you told you friend that you have a blog and s/he laughed at you and told you to get a life?! Don't we bloggers have a life to write about? We are, I think, constantly engaged in deep thoughts analysing situations and things simultaneously. We keep our brain active, thus alive. We do not want  deadbrains therefore, on the contrary, we want life and we have a life! Perhaps blogging is one of our lonely desperate means to communicating with people? There are some who even do it round the clock and their names get published on the WWW and gets interviews from media agencies. Uhh... is that their pathetic life? Can you say they have no life? If so, you're telling me there are few conditions one has to fulfill before they can be labelled "No life!" by blogging?  What keeps us coming back most of the time is that rewarding feeling about the things you wrote and somebody has read and commented on it. You may have written a good article/poem, or just plainly your dead boring story, however, even so, you'd often find yourself reading and re-reading what you wrote. Feels like you have succeeded or a sense of achievement. Don't you agree?   I can't be writing email to everybody about what's happening in my daily life, can I? Can you? What do you think? 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Being single in a foreign land can be an interesting one. I have been in love, deeply in love with a woman who is 2 years my senior and I thought to myself, "This is it! She's the person! My search ends here" Too soon have I said and convinced myself of that. Too soon I began to realize a part of her that radiates discomfort to my sensitive heart. I fell out of love. She is no longer the one. Although I dread the thought of this reality, time has not healed my horrific discovery. How can I be wrong? Things were wonderful but they are so different now. Nothing I can do. I am trying to unlearn a belief that I held on so strongly that the love I have showered on a person will return eventually. Perhaps this belief has a time period in which it can be true but lapsed when her age catches on?  Meeting people on campus and on the streets is one helluva adventure. Should I be falling in love again? Or should I learn not to be afraid of falling out of love? Perhaps both clearly states to me to get on with life and not sit here deciding which path to take on. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Friendship   is a promise   spoken by the heart  It is not given by any pledge  nor written on any paper.  It is a promise   renewed everytime   when we keep in touch.   Extracted from CikguLee's blog. I am certain my readers will agree with what was written above. Our Friends from Mexico, Germany, Canada, France, remember us and we will continue to fulfill each other's promises. We will only gain a beautiful wonderful friendship bountiful of love and respect. Don't be a fool for friendship does not come easy at times.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Mom has been staying with me since her arrival and I am loving it (plz disassoaciate this quote from McDonald's latest and lamest ad campaign). We talked about many things especially on life's experiences. Despite all the warm advises and painful times in life she had been through, I have not only learned life on earth would be as easy as what our eyes perceive.  The other thing I realized is when one has too much of advises from the same person who is eager to teach/train you up, one would not be able to take it all in within a continuous period of compacted time. To illustrate, one would fall back in performance if one studies too much of a subject for prolonged time unless of course, s/he has the passion for it; but that person is considered to be part of the predisposition of the norm. Basically, you can't be studying on biology for the rest of your life 24/7. You must give yourself a break and be away to do other things so that your mind can focus on things that is not dull. When you don't, you feel stressed up, tensed up, and just feel like crinching your hand into a fist so hard you could punch a hole in the wall. It's up to your neck level and you're boiling with stress and you don't want to hear it any more, at least for the moment. However, it does not mean you have lost your interests in that subject. Smokers would religiously take 5-10 minutes break from their study desk for two reasons: 1)It's the finger-to-mouth thing for cigarrettes or in other words, they're hooked to it; 2)For the brain to rest and thus pushing in for more room to accomodate more intake of information. It's a subtle mental process only known to your body and mind. You feel bored with the subject after a while and you'll find yourself wondering around the library, chatting with people on various subjects, picking up a magazine to read (aside your textbook), going out for a walk, etc.  That is what I need right now, at least that's what I feel right now.  I'm in the process of making my own decision. I should decide on whether or not I should go to England for Law degree, China for at least a 2 months back-packing trip, or use all the monies for the backpacking trip to purchase a car here in Canada, continue staying in Saskatoon to try to get into College of Engineering, which is one of the top 20 in the school of Engineering in the entire North America.  I have been told that Engineering is not meant for me. It is not my direction. Like my friends used to tease me "Show me the way...", I thought I could really use that right now. That phrase was suppose to be a pick-up line I picked up somewhere from the internet long ago but never actually used it until last year and I get teased about it till today. Samantha, a beautiful flick-chick of Asian origin who aspires to be a dentist is a smart, intelligent, charming, gorgeous, and Liv Tyler type of personality. I was in front of Lynn's room when she came in after I helped her smashed and killed a bug on the ceiling in her room, which is opposite of Lynn's. I was 'pressing'. I knew where the washroom is but since she is right there I blurted out,  "Sam, can you show me the way?" Looking puzzled and looked back into my eyes, "Yeaaah, where do you want to go?" unconvincingly she uttered. "Show me the way to your heart", I promptly responded with a smiling grin; then laughed. "...", speechless. blushed.  I can't recall anything if she had said anything from here on. She walked away and back into her room. That day onwards, I suffered the tortures of this mental recollections with teases from Lynn especially then news spreaded and Michelle Tan, Vincent See, Ivy Hor, and the rest of the Malaysian people who lived in Rezz that year. That incident was meant to be funny and by saying "torture" I don't mean it in a negative way that warrants a stop to it all. I have used the lamest pick-up line on the weirdest situation (after killing a holiday-ing bug in her room) on the sweetest girl whom I know there's no way we're going to work together to make things happen. Just think of it as a fantasy, she's in it. I'm not getting any funny ideas about her although usually in my fantasies anything goes.  Days in Saskatoon for the past 5 days has been a gloomy one--rain clouds shrouds the entire city bringing rain and wind, and of course, bringing the temperature down to as low as 2. Because of such nice weather (to the farmers), I didn't shoot many graduation photos of myself. The best, I think, in the next twenty years to recollect my memories of a unique day like my recent convocation would be in my memory & I hope it will not be lost forever. As best as I can I hope at the best of my articulation I could paint out clearly a picture for my family and friends to see. Small achievement though but worth remembering as this has become a benchmark for my success -- that I can make all things done, at least with positive driven determinations. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's  Saturday May 29th.  It has been a long time since I wrote. Occupied with both my parents and my brother My old lady too occupied with free-cell game Days were like these during the days I did not write Today a double celebration, Mom's birthday & my convocation/graduation day, a unique Red Ice Wine brewed from British Columbia, was opened and savoured till the last drop at the Gan's family (Jullian, Josephine, Jotham, & Melissa). I had the privillage to the very last drop of the indescribable fine & sweet ice wine. It was shared among 9 other people including myself over raspberry pie on vanilla ice cream (2 scoopings).  I made Conchinita Pibil for my family and they just love it. Mom couldn't stop teasing me about the pig's butt or the pig's backside, sometimes slipped her tongue and blurted "hey, the chicken backside was reaally gud!" I'm like "chicken baaaaaackside lah!", reminds me of Michelle Tan. I will probably from this day onwards remember pig's backside whenever Michelle Tan exclaim chicken backside. I had to constantly remind mom it's rump, or pork's rump. Just because, just because it sounds so much better. I couldn't help laughing about it whenever she mentions it and tease me about how good the "chicken backside" was!   Wednesday, May 26th.  The convocation went all well. It was nothing as I expected where proud parents and family and friends would constantly applause and cheer for their son/daughter's achievement when s/he walk down the stage to recieve his/her degree and being congratulated by the Chancellor of the University. I came to realize that "Universitas Saskatchewanesis" is the actual name of this University (U of Saskatchewan) and thus the actual name of the province. It's probably in Cree? Loooks Latin, though but certain could be Metis as well. Don't you come asking me for the meaning of it because I can tell you it is actually quite self-explanatory without feeling surprise that you can actually understand that in English. There's no need to reach your nose with your arms around your head.  My parents, my brother and Simon (a family friend) were seated up on the most high balcony of the Centennial Auditorium and I'd imagine looking down it must have been extremely difficult to locate a bald-headed guy who calls himself Danny V-Li Teok who again may appear as a tiny black dot (he has black hair, remember??) from above. I was seated 5 row from the stage somewhere in the middle (about the 11th -13th person from the most right). I was quite disappointed as dad did not do a great job at video recording the event but just a mere 20 seconds of recorded time when I walked over the stage with to receive my degree after my name was announced. He missed this part where my name was announced. *sob!* It would have been nice to watch the entire thing on video or DVD but I don't that is quite possible. I will depend on how articulated I am to describe this significant event (not only limited to myself) to whoever wants to know. In fact, I have already anticipated poor media captures. Because I am trained as a photography (as a hobbyist) I will make better pictures for my brother as well as for my friends. It is at this point of time I wish my friends have the know-hows of photography and/or video recording. There are a lot of professionals out there but certainly you'd agree with me it is a waste of resources to hire them just for this event unless you are born with a platinum spoon in your mouth. But otherwise, a commoner just like my family, I have to push myself to accept what's there for me. At least I can view the video and still see blurred colors and visions. After all, the most vivid pictures for this moment of my life is and will remain in the hollows of my brain. They will never be lost. -Ran into Ayako, Ayako Saito. She was climbing up the stair from Lower Place Riel and we were going up on the escalator from Lower Place Riel. I was still in my graduation gown. Said hello to her she looked from the corner of her eyes and returned a "hi". Tried to talk to her but she kept on walking and did not even stop for a second to engage in a conversation. Oh, don't get me wrong. She might be in a hurry or whatever, but her body language spoke the loudest and it was like telling me to "back off, I'm not interested in you nor am I ever going to talk to you!" She just kept her pace and thru the doors of Upper Place Riel and out she goes. I paused for a moment, just off the treshold of the escalator, tried to recalled what did I say that could have offended her tremendously. I just know we had a lot of fun with Michelle Tan, Ee Lynn, and herself during the winter break of 2003. If she pretends she doesn't know me anymore, she has my pity. I mean, how can you  not know a person anymore??  It will either be that you're trying to be rude or you recently had amnesia. I don' know what the heck is going on.  I really love the lady boss at Ding Dong restaurant, dishing out Vietnamese style meals or rather cuisines. I wasn't there with my family as I was tutoring. The boss, I call her Auntie, was so persistent with smiles on her face about me resembling more of my dad. 3 times dad denied, 4 times Auntie rub it in. LOL! Knowing Auntie is a very amicable person whose personalities would tickle anybody's bones, I can be sure that was something to laugh at and was a wonderful and enjoyable experience, to dine out in a not-so-fine restaurant that we've been frequenting sicne the arrival of my Sponsorship Director and his Madam. Aunties' warmth is what brings us students back to her restaurant again and again.  Recently dad and I have been discussing about the possibilities about going to the U.K. for Law studies. Whenever I think about it I tend to get a little numb on my knees as I imagine the number of books and literatures I have to read and know. I-m-a-g-i-n-e, just imagine the size of a New York's public library (no, not thaaaaaaat small!) and you gotta read all books therein within 3 years. If you don't get numb knees, then you should check with your doctor if you're suffering from Sensory Retardment Syndrome. U.K is a new place and it'd be great to live there for 3 years! I'm 24, turning 25, I mean, the opportunity cost of spending another 3 years in school pursueing another degree that could be a great combination with Business Economics, my first degree, can be very rewarding in the future. The other side of the argument is work/job experiences. I'm forgoing that if I go back to school. But I had thought a few months back that I had enough of studies and exams. I should take a break. I want to waste time and be mindless about thins for a while then go back... like a prodigal child. But a prodigal child who knows what he's doing. Where is my direction? Where am I heading? Show me the way!  To be continued... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bragging can often convey positive feelings as well as negative ones. I have been dealing with this problem for a long time. Sometimes a few of my good friends and my brother would confess their heart-felt feelings to me saying that I sometimes go over-board in arrogance and often find me bragging too much about myself.  Looking back, this problem I have been fighting since my early 20s can be traced to my teen years. I craved for parental love & attention in which I lacked much. There is this vague stigma in me to seek for attention and was a very serious problem in my late teens until I realize I did not gain much from deliberate search. I have not been complimented much for the things I do when I was a teenager and today when somebody do compliment me in some ways I get so full of myself. Stop! Analyse! Everybody do crave for some attentions in one way or another. I am guilty of this act myself. Even up to today but there are many possible explanations to this social ill, at least that's what some people would categorize it to be. There is, I think, another part of me, who is innately malignant and suffers from probably minor ADD or Attention Deficiency Disorder. The things I say today would somehow subtly hurt or offen that person I am communicating with. Often it will be too late for me to realize what I have just said is offensive. The way I word things out, as a good friend of mine said, made her felt stupid. What is the psychology of all these when I can sometimes relate and understand people who are doing similar things to me?  My dear mother has always related to me about my childhood and especially my growing years as a teenage boy. There has been a lot of damages done to my brother in my pursuit of attention. Today, my family owes something to God because we, my brother and I especially, did not resort to drug abuse, become a punk in the society, turn out to be a spoil spoilt, or a really psychopath attention disorder patient. As for myself, today I seek attention in my very own way is perhaps, according to mother, the best of two evils as a mean to calm and reward myself of attention deprivations, perhaps. There is an urgent need to be humble and meek but even with God's help, it will not an over night effort; however, I do and I will try. My brother's heart has been very broken and perhaps his childhood times are as haunting as mine but with different problems altogether and for the most part, I believe I am the culprit of it all. "If you break a vase, you should patch things up" is the thought that now constantly pounds my mind. I now feel the terrible qualms of my guilts expanding day by day; the more reasons for the need to patch things up. There can be no amount of apologies, perhaps, to forgive myself and hope things will be fine. But I need to stop living in my past and from this day forward I will make things new, with the strength of the Almighty and Holy Spirit.  A brag not one more from me Spit back at my face and hug me once more when you know I tell a brag Help me to help you, and I will help you to help myself we then can live without seeing black faces. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Bienvenida a mi bitacora! Tambien se le conoce como Blogger, Weblog o Jurney. Eso te da una idea de lo que es esto? Si es asi, felicidades, mereces una galletita ^_^ Podria comenzar diciciendo que aqui yo escribo lo que me de la gana y si no te gusta te larges (espera, espera!)No es asi ^^' Ms acertadamente, este blog ha sido creado por mi mana a escriibr, por lo que no ser raro que veas ms actualizaciones en mis Escritos que en mismo blogger ^^ Como sea, por ah encuentras algo que no va contigo, en lo que no estas deacuerdo o de plano algo que te resulta ofensivo y/o denigrantemente grotesco (quiz exagero un poco) entonces observa el lema de este blogger: "Todo est aqu, y la puerta tambin. Cada quien sabe que hacer con esto" Mmm esperando no haber sonado muy agresiva, me despido :)    Traduzca por favor para m y lo anuncia en los comentarios.     A meal a day   I had the entire school year to experiment the above title for myself and here is my result: it works! Although we were often hammered in the head that breakfast *is* the most important meal of the day, you can actually skip it and get away with gastrics and/or stomach aches or feel hungry later in the day. It works for me but please remember, results will vary from person to person depending on your metabolic rate, how active you were during the day. Whenever I'd wake up for early morning classes at 8AM, I'd just have a glass of milk and 4 slices of break or just a banana (best choice). I'd go on till 6pm without anything except for juices. Of course, this is not a very healthy practice but if some of you girls are looking to cut down weight, this is probably one way you can starve yourself. Well, while I'm aware there are some other options for your dieting plans without starving, mine's the cheapest and teaches you self-discipline. I'd study at the library for a day long and when it's time for dinner, around 6pm, I'd think of my dinner as a reward. Not that I will not reward myself if I didn't study much, but that is just not a good practice habit as it would cultivate laziness. That's the last thing I'd ever want. It's more like a reward-scheme. That's my "A meal a day" plan. A meal a day keeps gastric away.  On to another thing, my old desktop has failed on me. I bought 2 HDDs to replace thinking the HDD that came with the IBM has bad sectors and rendered useless-- practically a piece of junk. I can't load any OS into it and I gave up. I had no clue what is going on with the machine. After much hessitations, I decided to call up IBM support. There were going to charge me depending on my questions and I know my warranty has expired long ago, which was why I hessitated. I lied my way through and the operator said, "... I may charge you depending on your question, sir." After relating much about my pathetic machine's condition and symptoms, I think I had his sympathies. I learned that some capacitors around the CPU were leaking. The forever reseting looping behavior now seems all so crystal clear. Because computer understands only binary language, that is ones and zeros or off and on, data cannot be continued to be passed down to another section of the mainboard. The way I understand it is quite simple actually. Imagine a superficial city with your starting point on a road that splits into 3 roads. these roads goes to a destination in a bottleneck road. You were instructed that if you can't use Road 1, you shall use an alternative route, Road 2, and Road 3. If all else fails, return to starting point. In my case, all the capacitors were leaking, all the roads were blocked. So, it's not very difficult to figure out why it's behaving that way it is behaving.  Anyway, it has been raining in Saskatoon almost 2 days now. The past 2 weekends has been a rainy one. Looks like I won't have a sunny weekend day/night for this week either. Going to the observatory during the weekend would be a nice thing to do -- on a clear day. Hate being stuck at home, with only one PC to use. My mother's staying with me in my room. It's hard to surf for sexy pictures! haha!   Ai Yoshida. Seems to me that you knew something that I don't Your behavior towards me changed as you remained not-much-to-say You didn't have to take it so seriously of what others say to you, because I have not made my move yet. I have no motives nor intentions. Beautiful! I wish you a happy vacation in Japan! See you in 3 months!  Michelle T. Everyone has a nickname as I, too, is known by many names. nothing offensive werrrrt! Gah! I had to spit out those Malaysian suffixes here to justify an amicable speech. You bejesus me sometimes. To say that it's hard to find a girl like you in China, Malaysia (esp), Taiwan, Thailand, Japan is to mean that you are a very special person. In a good sense! haha! Saskatoon owes you one for you have resurrected this ghost town. It's dead once again. shsssh!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Priscilla G. a.k.a. "Tortilla", Ee Lynn, and the Late Atomic Weight Michelle Tan. Uhh, please ignore the "Tan" ; just Michelle. Her ego is already too big to fit into my car, so I have everybody do me a favor NOT to call her fullname so Michelle can get in too.  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Portraits of some of my friends are up.    Agent Danniella    Agent Prishilla a.k.a. Tortilla    Agent Denise a.k.a Sore Throat??    The Dannie's Angels posing in Danny's kitchen after feasting on pork butt.   These were the only Mexicans that came by to my place to savoured  Conchinita Pibil , one of Mexican's most rare Slow-cooked pork powered with a 2oz of Premium Tequila. Ee Lynn was not left out and I extend my gratitude to her for making this happen. I was like "*ahem!* On behalf of all the Malaysian friends you know, I present to you a dish of your native land, Puerco Pibil, as a friendly gesture towards a friendship (between Mexico and Malaysia; kononnya play politics! haha!) that is just about to begin. It's too bad that you people had to go too soon but I'm sure all of us Malaysians, the ones you know, are very grateful and happy to have met you all. bla bla bla!"  I have been tutoring a student from HK on Adobe Photoshop 7 for the past 3 weeks. This is the coolest job I have ever done coz I get to write my blog, listen to music, and chat while I tutor her. Best thing of all is that I still get paid full amount (15$ per hour) for at least 2 hours a day for 4 days a week at least. Sometimes I end up working for 4 hours just to do her assignments for her. There is a difference between tutoring and doing assignments for student(s) and I think the latter best describes my current position. I don't think she's learning anything at all but heck, think about it, I'm getting paid that amount and I'm learning new stuffs on Photoshop-- stuffs I never knew existed. Remember about chatting and listening to music while on the job? If you say i'm robbing this girl her purse, you're wrong to such lame claim. Instead, you should feel happy for me, shake you head side ways, give me a sigh of relief then say to me, "what a job! what a job, danny!" 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Saskatoon unfamiliar to many a name frown upon usually by people out of this town twenty miles away asking "where is that?" ignorantly.  I have been here 3 years already this coming August 20. There are hardly any mountaineous landscapes around here only to learn later that I'm 'stuck' in a place called the prairies, which is a large area of level land and is one of the dry treeless plateaus east of the Rocky Mountains according the Webster dictionary. Translated to simple English, it's freaking flat land.  Anyway. Only when I'm in the mood do I churn out some awfully good thoughts not for shallow minds. Oh yeah, I'm very shallow minded now.  Chatted with Priscilla Gonzalez & Lynn today and they were both great people to talk to. I am not really sure if I have made a good friend with the Rosalva Luna look-alike because until today she's been very kind and generous with words towards me. Perhaps it could be the Mexican's customs to remain persistance with kind words? Wait a minute, what am I talking about? It's not like the rest of the world is uncivilized and uncurteous. I'll leave it be. All I meant to say was just the first sentence of this paragraph. And a good friend!  Claudia, Hong Kong hottie in her late teen, sought help with me for a problem with her computer, which I later learned was infested with 41 unique computer viruses. I supplied her with tips on how to get around the problem and called her up today and I got good news. Not that of a biggie anyway but at least I know she's capable to become a tech-savvy person ... one in a million.  There's a dire need to get out of Saskatoon broiling from within my heart. Somewhere I will go but I don't know whereof yet, however, it will definitely be a place I have not been and hopefully not too expensive in terms of currency exhange. High time for arbitraging scouting opportunities. Somewhere where I don't see a multitude of ethnic Chinese people loitering on the streets or flocking malls. A few caucasians would be ideal but definitely not too many though. Where would that be? Where would that be? Maybe I should postpone my photo-shooting session with Claudia to August. It was suppose to be in July. She's such a beauty! A real talented girl, indeed.  For the most part in this blog session are not of today but yesterday as well as 2 days back. Later readers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink      Click on image for a larger image. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here are the few banned ads that I find extremely hilarious. For more, please visit  urlLink Block Nine  and click on the video section.   urlLink Boobs Magazine   urlLink Bad idea jeans   urlLink 3 girls take off bikinis in Denmark   urlLink Blind man and Levis jeans   urlLink Erotic food   urlLink Fart   urlLink Loose panties   urlLink I need a condom now!   urlLink Kylie Minogue [Lingerie]   urlLink Yeah, but at least it takes our focus off your face   urlLink Metal detector   urlLink Nice boots   urlLink IKEA pig farmers   urlLink Fighting chimp   urlLink Football fever   urlLink Dancing penis   urlLink Sony camera    Other news:  Yahoo! Mail has just increased their free webspace quota from 4MB to 100MB, which is a positive step to take in order to keep customers from flocking to Gmail that offers 1000MB free! Did I say free? Yeah, for FREE! What makes Gmail more interesting is the keyboard short-cut keys in which I believe no webmail providers have done it before. Thus, making Gmail the pioneer in this cutting edge technology and is about to change our daily rituals of using webmails as our primary email consoles. Yahoo!'s new interface hasn't a dramatic change either. I don't think I am all that impressed with the changes except for the 25 times larger mailbox.  urlLink Check it out!     What happened  It was my turn to make dinner today and I made one of my fav Asian dish called Szechuan's Eggplant Stir-fry with ground beef. I'd g crazy over this dish and because it was  sooooo goooooooooood , I'm insanely mad... to have a late lunch and wasn't hungry at all when I dished it out. Mom has always insisted that she makes our meals but she didn't have to. I didn't hessitate even though I dislike working/playing on the computer for too long. T'was a great dinner though. We, mom brother and I, took a walk downtown along the river side up to Delta Bessborough Hotel when 2 parade horses pulling a carriage parked beside the curb. Ah! 7.50$ per person. Since we missed a horse ride in Montreal 2 years ago, we hopped on this carriage and the  urlLink Palomino horses  took us for a 15 minutes ride trotting gracefully. The sound of  cloking: clok! clok! clok! clok!  when their hoofs coherently hit the ground is not any noise/sound. Unable to explain nor describe in further details, felt like musics to my ears. These light brown parade horses are simply just amazing creatures. I had the opportunity to carress my palm on the mammal's body, neck, and head. I'm dreaming of the horse taking me away to a land far far away, with my lover behind me. We had to hurry home as it was getting dark and I felt a heavy heart to leave these beautiful beasts. I don't know how to explain how I felt but I think horses and I do have some kind of connection. My brother made a statement: "It's nice to own a horse, eh?". It's weird and yet amazing and coincidental because here I am today with real horses; 3 days ago, we were all trying to immitate the 4 singing horses Acappella style. Mom traced out the gray horse that stood on the most left. What is the connection? Is something happening?  At Mandarin restaurant having dimsum with Lavina Yuen for lunch earlier, I read my chinese horoscope for my year, 1979. The last sentence reads:  Gets along well with Horses, Boars, Sheeps, and ... (can't remember) . I'm a Sheep/Ram by the way. After lunch, I had to lugged back a 14lbs bag of rice. At least now I know how to get around town by bus, so, it's really nothing. In the bus, I noticed a young large girl at the back of the bus where she sat looking at me. Well, I wasn't sure if it was a look or a stare. I noticed her eyes shied away when I was glancing around my shoulders, then I looked back at her and she greeted me with an obliging smile. A smile makes two. Wow! That was something. If she had really been looking at me, should I freak out?! Nah, rather I should be a man and get to "sell myself" away in hopes to get, uhh..., laid? I'll just leave that to my imaginations. She got off with me at the stop close by where I live. No wonder she's somebody familiar? Perhaps I don't quite remember where I've seen her or what I've done to/for her? Oh-uh!  Finally, I watched Jackie Chan's latest remake of " urlLink Around the world in 80 days ". I am still amazed at JC because he is still able to amuse people with his absofucklutely cool stunts and moves. One big disappointment to me is that this version do not have cut-scenes at the end of the movie. I have always loved to see how things went wrong and they're always really hilarious! It's quite funny but not the best given the knowledge of his capabilities and abilities. JC can make better movie than this one even though it's a remake of the one in 1989?? 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    M&M's drunkened with weed  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Girls, pay attention! Guys, too bad.  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Next winter's project in Saskatoon  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    During winter this year, I think the sculptor came to our university and left his piece of art at The Bowl, on campus.  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Get a date, emulate her.  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Europeans vs. Americans  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    OMG! You can read chinese!  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    MILF  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Whoever designed this is definitely not a woman.  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       615! Six fifteen!! Claudia (Cheng Kayan) hinted to me it is a kind of shoe. I found out later that 615 is a type of New Balance's shoe for girls, uhh collector's items, I think. Last week, she has been changing her handle everyday and it doesn't look any different except one will definitely know that she's counting down to June 15. So, I asked her Monday what was she going to do in a few hours time over the chatline. She just said "615!!!!!!!!!!" I thought, "Oh yeah, right, the shoe. Probably it's a year's anniversary for her shoe and herself." I asked her today when is her birthday. "615!!" Ah, A belated birthday wish from me then. I thought I have just missed something... felt the emptiness in my heart.   I asked what she wished for to which she responded "I can't tell you. If I do, then it will not come true". Well, here is my wish list people:  (some are really just imaginaries/fictitious), 1. A nice home; not too big nor small like where I'm staying now 2. Vaccines to all diseases so people may live longer 3. I wish I could stop United States from nosing into another's ass 4. Happiness within myself as well as my immediate surroundings 5. Unbreak my broken limbs 6. I wish to find a loving & understanding soulmate (Yoon-Young Choi look-alike always preferred) 7. Peace in my heart as well as in everyone's! 8. Lactose tolerant! 9. Cranium has a Malaysian Edition, in English!! 10. A professional digital SLR (Nikon & Canon) 11. High end lenses to fit item 10, cheapo ones don't mind too. 12. Travel around the world. 13. Able to draw nudes better, they all look disfigured on my drawing paper. lol! gotta visit the art's studio more often and still be able to hold on to my sanity. 14. iPod 40GB!!! 15. Casio Exilim! Why the heck do I want more than a camera?! I love these little gadgets. 16. A love doll. *sob! I'm so lonely. 17. A magic wand!! granting wishes for myself. 18. a sponsored annual snowboarding trip in Canada, Whistler Mt. 19. Retire early. 20. A car 21. gas price drop!! 22. Another bachelor degree! 23. academic scholarships 24. ...  Is your list longer than mine? Are all your wish list, uhh, selfish?  What do most, if not all, men want the most in their lifetime (other than sex with all beautiful women in the world)?  given a chance, would you live either on the moon or Mars for 6 months? I wish for the red planet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Zero. Nothingness, emptiness, empty, no longer there, not existing or non existence and that's probably up to where I can think of zero. If you have other variations, please feel free to add on. Pretty much like the previous posting "Till the last drop", but the only thing is that this time I had a Finnish vodka  Evgeuni P.  got for all of us to drink from small shot glasses at  Mark Caeser's  apartment (Sutherland). Clint, Caeser's friend, I'm quite amazed at how much in similar taste in genre's of games he has with me. A big fan of Silent Hill episodes in which I did try to play the 3rd part last week and was already all freaked out. He completed the game.... whooooosh!! Jumped out of his seat twice; Caeser wasn't left out of the action too as he devotedly watched Clint fiddling his way to kill monsters and get terrified, petrified, and mortified by the game.  After much of the vodka disappeared (down in our stomaches), and after much talking, Caeser decided to show us something he finds amazing. He opened his email and there are four horses behind wooden fence like those in farms. When I saw it I knew what those horses do. They don't run or does anything like what normal horses do. Interestingly, well, you might have seen it before, they represents a type of sound in music, much like in acappella, but without music instruments. Because it was so long ago I heard & seen of such thing, as well as it was the first time for the rest, it was pretty amazing. If you want to know what I'm talking about, please visit the following link below:   urlLink Acappella Ranch horses   So, it is very difficult to try NOT to immitate the sounds of each horses especially the dark gray horse that goes "boom schee schee; boom boom... booom schee schee". So, because Mark plas the guitar and records his own musics on the computer, it was his idea to record all of us doing what the horses are doing. We each pick a horse to immitate (its voice). I picked the above, Clint the female horse with receding hair (most right), Evgeuni is the light gray horse, and Caeser is the second from left that sounds like as though he's the meditating buddist monk going "Ooouuummmmmmmmmmmmmm...." repetitively. Much like you'd click on the each horse to hear it humming its own acappellic voice, we did the same by pointing fingers. The entire scene was awesome & hilarious, it was recorded too. When we hit the playback, we can actually see the sound waves of our singing. I started first and the wave was mild; but it grew as the others took turns to join in the singing, didn't want to leave me solo all the time. Then, there was this big leap in the waves... that's Clint's. None of us could contain our laughters and as soon as I broke out in laughter, it spread!! It really spread to the rest. Almost died laughing! I will get the sound file up here for your listening.  As for the poor bottle of vodka, which has been sitting & chilling out in the fridge for 30mins already, Mark grabbed in and called for the 7th toast, was was for :( some BS i can't remember. But the 6th was for Exotic women in which we discussed quite interestingly disputing each other's point of view. Mostly a comparison between caucasian women and asian women. the 4th toast sounds like "you can do any friggin' thing you want, but just don't get caught". Perhaps the lamest toast by me. haha! the 3rd was to friendship; Mark offered upon which I agreed/seconded abruptly. The 2nd, was in Russian in which Mark's guessing translation turns out to make more sense after Evgeuni explains the need to rhyme like that of Russian. So,  " Between one and two, keep the minutes few"  but what the heck, we understood anyway. Down goes the vodka. The first shot (and the 5th), WTF?!, can't remember. Anyway, had a good time there!  My student for photoshop is really dissing me by making me do all her assignments. :( but should I complaint much as i'm getting quite a good pay for an unemployed chap like myself?? hehe! so much to learn.  I'm broke. Now, doesn't the zero up there makes more sense to you? 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After I wrote my previous posting, I didn't think anybody would find "Boozed weekend in Scott" funny. Perhaps I have found my true talent, and that would be a talent of not knowing how to describe something funny when they're suppose to be funny. So, do you say to me I have dry humor? So, What is dry humor (or humour as the British's would spell it)? Do I have it?! "Is it humor minus the  saliva ?"  I have always thought that Eelynn has dry humor either in some ways or in all ways. If that is true, because I do see a little of myself in her, perhaps it is true for me too. Michelle used to say to us to give Lynn charity laughters whenever she  tries  to tell a joke or two because we know Lynn (and perhaps myself) can't really make a joke a joke! A joke that make us laugh crazy & and wild & perhaps remembered and worth to tell to another.  Hmm, there are people whom I know who are really, really funny. They tickle your funny bones with their stories about their life. How do they do that?! Are funny people borned to be humorous? If they are, then I can accept the fact that my humors are a little dry. Just like drinking dry wine, there's this tangy taste in your throat when you gulp in as oppose to smooth wines.  What do you think?   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Scott and I have been planning on doing things for the weekend of 12th and the 13th since last week. He came up with 2 plans and both of the plans flopped because things either came up that required immediate attention or time just wasn't right. So, he called again Thursday and suggested that his friend who is from Scott has invited them for a camping trip at her place. Her name is Sylvia. Scott was quite excited with the idea of going to Scott and Scott's friends. I thought this might probably work out because it wasn't Scott's idea to go to Scott. And it all worked out!  Pause. Scott is a place approx. 1h 40mins west of Saskatoon and about an 40 mins south of North Battlefords. Scott is also a person. From a certain angle, he somehow appears to me to resembles Owen Wilson. So, I hopped into Ben's (Benjamin Eng) car, and headed west with a piece of a what-appears-to-be-a-horribly written-directions.  We arrived nevertheless. But when we left Scott, we were all asking each other how to go back. That piece a paper with directions is, however, apparently a one-way-ticket to Scott. It was funny as we drove aimlessly but were heading east. ;)  Anyway, the weather has been butt ugly so the initial camping plan didn't quite carry through. All six of us stayed-in Sylvia's. Went out to the town's only bar at around 9:30pm. Apparently, Sylvia has invited a 28 year old huge beer-bellied guy who is desperate and is going to hit on any girls he meets. We are 3 guys and 3 girls. Ben, Scott, Myself Danny; Sylvia, Chelsea (Scott's girl), and Leah. When Sylvia told us about him (Conrad), we were quite worried for Chelsea and Leah. Uh-oh! I didn't sense any harm from Conrad though, quite a nice chap. Probably he was hammered, with beer!!! omg! what a drinker! And perhaps we, or maybe our girls, were quite lucky as a blonde came in the bar and walked up and chatted with him. Maybe somebody familiar? At least he is kept at bay.  Those 3 girls are totally craaaazy fun and hilarious!! Leah, speaks with a unique accent, is a calm, down to earth, amicable, and perhaps sensible girl so full of energy. When I entered, I noticed somebody familar who took Beginning French II with me last summer -- Leah! Learned that she grew up in Malaysia, lived in Penang and went to an International School over there. She came back to Canada when she was 15 yrs old. Been nine years ago and she doesn't speak any Malay. That is just unfortunate.  Sunday morning, to kick things off, we chugged in our last 6 bottles of beer for breakfast. Scott and Chelsea were pushed to down in all in while still in bed. We joined however. Pancakes to eat and then later, played a very interesting board game called  Cranium.  I enjoyed it very much and thought that everyone who is visiting Canada should at least play this game once before going back to wherever you come from. Since it's a Canadian edition, it is packed with quintessentially Canadian content and it-is-a-definite roof-raiser!! We raised and brought down the roof and the ceiling with our laughters and jokes on each other when making a funny move or looking at a stupid picture drawn with the eyes closed. Know what a fartknocker is? How about a jumart? There's another game called Slanger where you would, very much similar to Balderdash, guess out the meaning of a slang. Oh yeah, we did laugh our asses out reading aloud the creative definitions of others. Leah, apparently was known as the Hussie in green! coined by Chels when Leah wrote "I suck!" for slang she knew nothing off. This would be a timestamp so I will not forget how much fun I had.  "Soup and fish" is a slang for "A tuxedo". Imagine what kind of glares you'd get when you demand for your tux using this slang. Wouldn't you just snap when your butler who didn't understand that slang actually brings you what you specifically asked? It would have been hilarious!  Pot luck... I was late.  Where shall I go? Nobody has invited me to their homes. Have I been a bad boy? I'm sorry if I have. Cool down, because I think people are cool, I'm cool as well, no?  That is about all I would write for tonight. I'll postpone my other thoughts for another day.   -Ps: Blogger's server was down a night or two ago, I think. Because we do not always know when website servers go down for maintenance or malfunctioned, always make a habit to COPY ALL of the content you wrote to NOTEPAD before you push the button that reads "PUBLISH POST". Simply "SELECT ALL" (Ctrl + A) in the box where have typed, and COPY (Ctrl + C; or right click on highlighted areas, select COPY). Open NOTEPAD (optional) and paste your blog in. Then switch back to your blog to PUBLISH POST. There you go! I really hate to rewrite my entire blog. This is the precautionary step I practice even in writing emails, especially when they are long ones. Have fun.  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ..., I have made several decisions: (Bold sentence denotes true)   01. When I was younger, I made some bad decisions    02. I don't watch much TV these days    03. I love broccoli  04. I love sleeping  05. I have loads of books   06. I once slept in a toilet (don't ask) 07. I love playing video games 08. I adore marijuana (juss never smoked it before..) 09. I watch porn movies 10. I watch "One Tree Hill" 11. I like sharks  12. I love spiders, I think they're adorable, especially the ones with bright colors on their backs  13. I was born without hair and I still have no hair  14. I like George W. Bush   15. People are cool   16. I have changed a lot mentally over the last year  17. I have a Toyota and a pool   18. I have a lot to learn   19. I carry my knife everywhere with myself 20. I'm really, really smart   21. I've never broken someone's bones    22. I have a secret    23. I hate rain  24. I drink health juice (JAMBA JUICE)  25. Punk rock rules 26. I hate Bill Gates   27. I love Vietnamese  28. I would hate to be famous  29. I am not a morning person  30. I have long hair  31. I have short hair   32. I have potentials  33. I'm pure Afghan  34. My legs are two different sizes I refuse to believe my legs are identical 35. I have a long lost twin  36. I wear those long ass socks   37. I can roll my tongue  38. I like the way that I look 39. I'm obsessed with Italian food 40. I know how to French braid   41. I can be pessimistic or optimistic whenever I want    42. I have a lot of mood swings    43. I skateboard/snowboard   -->SnowBoard!!!! yey! 44. I think that skateboarders are HOT  45. I'm in a band  46. I have talents   47. I'm always hyper no matter how much sugar I have  48. I think that I'm popular  49. I am currently single   50. I can't swim   51. My favorite color is either blue, red, or white   52. I practically live in sweatshirts  53. I love to shop  54. I would classify myself as either punk or goth  55. I would classify myself as ghetto 56. I'm a prep, shop at abercrombie&AE&FCUK, and ADMIT IT  57. I'm obsessed with my xanga (blog)  58. I don't hate anyone   59. I know how to square dance   60. I have a unibrow  61. I'm completely embarrassed to be seen with my mom  62. I have a cell phone    63. I believe in BUDDHA (yes, he existed)  64. I watch MTV on a daily basis  65. I know how to play the tuba   66. I need coffee to live  -->only during study sessions & exam periods 67. I have had a boyfriend before 68. I've rejected someone before  69. I currently like someone and they have no idea that I like them   70. I have no idea what I want to do for the rest of my life   71. I want to have kids when i'm older    72. I have changed a diaper before   73. I've called the cops on a friend before   74. I bite my nails   75. I am a member of the Hilary Duff club  76. I'm not allergic to anything  77. I love Broadway plays, and have been to at least 3  78. I have no idea who the 38th president was  79. I plan on seeing Mary Kate and Ashley's new movie  80. I am completely shy around the opposite sex  81. I'm online 24/7  82. I have at least 25 away messages saved  83. I have tried alcohol or drugs at a party   84. I loved Rush Hour  85. I've read all of the Harry Potter trilogy 86. If I were a dwarf, I would be dopey 87. When I was a kid I played with G.I. Joe  88. I don't mind country music   89. I would die for my friends 90. I think that Juicy Fruit is the best type of gum   91. I watch soap operas whenever I can    92. I'm obsessive and paranoid and extremely jumpy  93. I would love to be Demi Moore because Ashton Kutcher is a major hottie  94. I love the Beatles.. they're classic  95. I know all the words to 'I'm a barbie girl'(by whom?)  96. Halloween is awesome because you get free candy..  97. I watch Spongebob Squarepants and I like it   98. I have to fart    99. I want this damned thing to be over    100. I'm happy    41 true out of 100 items   Verdict: I am not so much of bullshits in life. Thank heavens I failed this "Life's a Bullshit" quenstionnaire. *chuckles!*  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My dental appointment was tentatively scheduled for July 13 but I received a call yesterday and Michelle, the nurse (why are there so many Michelle species around?! One big one who teases me as though Arnold Schwarzennegar has a little dong is already enough to handle), informed me there is one today -- in the morning. I promptly agreed without much thought that these days I not really  the morning type of person   I got up at 08:45 to make a phone call to the clinic explaining to the nurse, I suppose it's Michelle's sweet voice, why I couldn't go. I don't have any other excuses except lame ones. Felt too lazy to get up anyway. Still in bed and felt like I could get drowsy and hit back to dreamland again, 2 things woke me up. Mom was already up earlier and was working in the kitchen making some goodies for dinner later. It was the smell of chinese mushroom that ponged my senses up--too strong a smell. The other, Michelle said: "Oh? Did you know that there's a 50$ charge for last minute change or 'no show'?"   I'm like, "50 fucking dollars just for no show?!! That's ridiculous!" Then after much hessitations I felt like I was cornered and there was no other way out unless I am willing to fork out 50 bucks for nothing.  Whew! Fresh air finally! I'm out of the house and the smell of mushroom no longer cause uncomfortness to my nose. It's not stinky or the like but they were just too strong too aromatic that I couldn't take it anymore.  Dr Simon Wong is his name. He is the dentist. I didn't wait long outside and when I got in, I gagged and went like gagaga!! Woah!! 6 TV's, 6 inclining chairs, 2 beautiful nurses (pls ignore this), clean as white and bright. I was invited to lie down and the other nurse slided down something on my head in which I learned that it's a headphone so I don't watch mute TV! Totally cool! Then she pulled out something from the cabinet on my left side and inform me that she was going to take some x-rays. Later, I saw my 10 x-ray pictures and Dr Wong explained everything, including the most terrifying thing I've ever heard: I've got 9 cavities; 10 including my dysfunctional wisdom tooth.  Dr. Wong took some colored digital images of my teeth with a tiny little steel rod. I was watching TV and he grabbed the RC from me (*sobs!*) and switched to "Video 1" mode and  Viola!  all my decayed teeth in color media! *embarrassed!*  But above all that, that dental clinic is one that has impressed me so far.  Quote from Dr. Wong:  ...brushing your teeth is only 60% complete. Flossing give you the other 40%   But, on the contrary, even if you floss your teeth daily, you will still get decays. What happens is that flossings only reduces the chances of tartar build ups (which I had, omg! but they're history now) thus minimizes cavities and decays. They're still going to be there. But you're helping your dentist a lot such that s/he doesn't have to spend too much time cleaning.  Met Leah Knox. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink A new item  to add on to my wish list. I fell in love with it when immediately after reading all it has to offer me. *drools!* 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Lonely?  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Jessica's [high school] graduation pic  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Jessica while sunbathing  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just chatted with  (double grass) and she mentioned a phrase that I thought I would meditate upon:    And that would mean that  For every problems that happened, there [also] exist a reason, an explanation for it all.   The translated meaning, I must admit, does not sound or does not look as good or authentic as it should be. Maybe I am just not too good a translator ; or perhaps the English language is somehow limited or inadequate to unleash its full capacities to be able to convey the exact meaning as it is written in the Chinese language.  "Learn to let go" flashed in my mind after reading that phrase. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today officially marks the beginning of  the  most awaited day or perhaps season of the entire year by at least everyone, but me. *sobs!* I miss winter! Summer kicks in today; there better be warmer days ahead but the hope of warmer days didn't seem so promising with rainy clouds to start with today. The earth must have been crazy. Perhaps Saskatoon itself, eh?  It looks like I have acquired this habit of sleeping at ungodly hours and waking up at noon time for the past month already. I got up just in time to walk over to the  urlLink Royal University Hospital (RUH)  for a scheduled Ultrasound scan appointment at 12:30noon. I was all dressed up and ready to go by 12:20 when I flipped my Sony Clie SJ-22 to check which floor am I suppose to be. Heavens strucked my oblivious state off when my organizer showed me the place I was suppose to go was not the RUH but Saskatoon's Imaging Center on Bedford's Square. Now, where is Bedford's Square? I didn't want to be late to try to remember where Bedford's Sqr. is. Immediately I rang up for a cab and arrived to Bedford's Sqr., a very familiar place I've frequented for some  urlLink bubble/pearl tea . It is on 8th Street!  When I was at the clinic's reception desk to register myself, I was asked to produce the note Dr. Ansell gave me.  Oh fuck!  I must have forgotten as I left in a hurry. I got in anyway. The nurse who is a blonde chic named Michelle, told me to take off my shirt and sit beside her.  Oh wow! *wild thoughts running around; but within the confines of the room.  She closed the door behind us and dimmed off the lights.  I'm like, this is sooo.... not happening!! Stop it, Danny!! What are you thinking?!  Okay. She squirted some gooey Ultrasound gel on my naked left shoulder and picked up the scanning device and motioned on my shoulder bone-arm. I could see a baby!! It is a girl!!!! Nah! I mean, I will not be normal if there was really another being growing in my hurting shoulder! It was just amazing how these Ultrasound scans work! Michelle picked up some gel onto the scanning device and pressed lightly on the front of my shoulder and while rubbing in circular motion she's observing the monitor with me. The images are, unfortunately, not colored. Of course, I expected that. The entire session lasted for about 10 minutes. Now, behind the chair I seated is a bed. It didn't take me long enough to realize that it's primarily for expecting mothers. duhh!!  My brother and mom were doing some groceries at Superstore. I met up with them. Collected some photos of my graduation as well as my recent "camping weekend" in Scott. As I looked through the 35 prints, I was kinda disappointed when I saw the picture 'Jillian Morgan' and I posed in the Arts tunnel on the 26th of May. Not very nice and I had the most ackward pose of all. Then I thought about it for a while and wondered if she was offended. Maybe we were physically too close to one another? Felt shitty and embarrassed and couldn't bare to take another look. The convocation pictuers didn't turn out all that good either. The auditorium was dim, the film's speed was a ISO 100, and the distance from the photographer to the stage where I received my degree was as far back and high as the auditorium could get. Although my family and I did go to campus for some more photo shooting, the weather then wasn't all that pleasing either. I could just heave a heavy sigh of giving up right now to realize I have lost an opportunity of a lifetime. It should be temporal though. It's just that things on that day did not go as I wished them to be. However, I should just pat myself on my back and convince myself that I am at least fortunate enough to have my parents over to celebrate this late convocation with me. My other friends whose parents couldn't afford to come to celebrate with their only daughter/son. Worst yet, one even had to borrow a camera from her friend to commemorate her convocating day.  So Dann, you're fine. It's okay when things didn't go the way you want them to be sometimes. It's not that your expectation levels were too high, but this is the time when you learn how to tolerate with others, things, and especially  yourself! So, be cool!   When my brother graduate next year, he's gonna be my center of attention! I hope he allows my glamour shots! hehe!  Bought a book from McNally's Robinson on Photoshop and found out it's kind of not worth up to its value (25.99$). It came with a CD and I'm not quite certain if I should return it... is it returnable?  Chatted and video-conferrenced with  urlLink Priscilla G.  today. Feelings of guilt lingered in and around me when she first messaged me in  urlLink MSN messenger  because I haven't finished reading it and I did slacked off for a few days. As soon as I knew it was her messaging me, I'm like  oh-uh! is she going to ask me about the paper that I'm suppose to proof-read and I'm like only three-quarter done?  The conversation went kinda cute though and I thought I was snaking my way out of it. But no, it was funny! Then mom came to the rescue by yelling "dinner is ready!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Come and eat your Egg pocket!!"  Egg Pocket, mom's new creative creation. T'was good. I'm gonna steal the recipe from my mother and make it for my own (well, later I'll make it for friends) till perfection. Like the Americans, they steal ideas and make it better and claim ownership on it. Thankfully Im only quasi-American.  Felt like someone was insinuating me. Maybe I am just overly sensitive. I should just put up with a Alex-type A behavior--don't give a fuxk about anything. It'd be different for me, change the "anything" to  certain things   Happy Summer holidays! Enjoy your summer, dear readers! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    My first digital art published!! Spent an hour creating this cool feather pen using Photoshop CS. Feather pens have always been associated with knowledge, intelligence, articulacy (if ever there's such an adjective), and literacy, hence, the "Knowledge is Power". Quite a common adage I must say but it simply adds more to the composition. I thought splattering some ink carelessly would make it more believing. Do you have time to critic on this picture?  H!  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just played  urlLink this game  and was horrified, petrified, and mortified! Little did I know that vagina bears an uncanny resemblance to raw meat.   urlLink     Was at school early in the morning for a forgotten appointment with Lavina Yuen but she waited for me anyway. So, I ran into Connor, a beautiful 6ft Caucasian hockey player girl (36D-34-38) in the Arts buffeteria right after I dropped off the Adobe Photoshop 7 textbook to LY. She was having her egg sandwich lunch I suppose, alone! I couldn't help myself but to approach her for a conversation because we have never really had a real conversation in 3 years we've known each other. It was pretty wild 3 years ago when we met in Rez in a person's room and she was sitting in there and I noticed her tattoo on her back that reads "beautiful" in a Chinese Character (). Trying to impress her  then  I went on to explain the character's etymology while we sat in the UV illuminated room. Today, she's dressed in a white sleeveless top wrapped around a colorful sarong sporting a high cut slit on the left side. Mm-mmmh!  So, last night was quite intense with Scott, Ben, Silvia, and Chelsea. We finally had dinner at Moxie's on Circle and 8th just right by  urlLink McNally's Robinson bookstore  because the 2 other restarants we planned on going initially were closed for Canada's Day; Sushiro and East Mario's. The latter restaurant was just too long a wait so we end up in Moxie's, where i had a 10 lbs New York steak. We were all planning on going to the Diefenbaker's Park to watch the fireworks in conjunction with Canada's Day. Only Ben, Scott and I ended up going there while the girls could not be found anywhere-- the place was insanely packed. There were so many people. Every boom that went off lits up the night skies and I'd just look down the hill and be dumbfounded at the amount of people that were present. The fireworks can also be seen from the Broadway bridge, according to Connor who was there with her friends. The grand finale of the pyrotecnics showcase was, as it was mentioned, grand! Awesome! There exploded about 10 colorful blooms and the last couple were the biggest and the grandest of the colors of the flag of Canada -- red and white! The entire showcase lasted 10 minutes from 22:40. To get out after the grand finale was a pain in the ass considering the size of the crowd there. It was a good thing Ben did not park 5 minutes away from where we sat to watch, but a good 20 minutes walk.  We stayed over at Ben's place because it was already too late (and it rained!!) for me to walk back after watching " urlLink Stuck on you ". I thristed for cold beer for the entire night but sonofagun there is none to be found and i then settled for the second worse beverage -- coke! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This afternoon, about 13 hours ago, I've got  urlLink my arm  treated at Daniels Kimberley Physiotherapy and this time the therapist (not the rapist!) is a guy! Ookay, although out of my expectation, I walked in to his treatment room with him anyway. Had my t-shirt off and laid down and he started pressing on my shoulder where the pain is massaging there. Soothing! I saw his 2 degrees that were hanging on the walls to my right and noticed his name. I asked if he was a "Hokkien" or equivalently a  to which he was surprised and said yes. His last name is "Ong", which is to mean  A king  (). Session lasted only 30minutes... my last session was an hour long. Probably I don't need further diagnostics on my arm.  Waited for 3 hours to catch  urlLink "Spiderman 2"  at 15:50 with my brother. Never would I have thought this movie is also a sequel like that of "The Lord of the Rings" that comes in  urlLink Part 1 ,  urlLink Part 2 , and  urlLink Part 3 . Unlike the ubiquitous advertisments for LOTR sequels annually (or more like monthly), Spiderman sequels were never advertised and for the most part of it, we will always be guessing if Part 2 is the end of the sequel. I guess with 99% confidence there will be a Part 3 next year. At least now I know after the end of the LOTR's sequel, it's not the end of my cinema-going habits. There's another exciting movie to be anticipated next year, much like we have for all the LoTR's. Perhaps the producers were not heavily funded in adverts as its counterpart did. It's worth a watch; be sure to know where the story left off in  urlLink Part 1  before you watch  urlLink this next sequel .  I have been watching too many movies in these 2 days. Tomorrow I might be catching " urlLink White Chicks ". Why so many so soon? It's boring to be sitting at home  urlLink building cities .  Received a call from Marzi and she insisted to pick me up at 21:00, so I waited but she did not show up until 22:00. Changed venue from Winstons (between Bessborough Hotel and Midtown Plaza) to McGuire's on 8th. On the way back in Heba's car, we saw a white couple making out in their living room of their apartment on the 2nd floor, along  urlLink Cumberland Ave and Main Street  (just before the Stop sign at the 4 way junction OR click on the link and look out for the red star). No curtains whatsoever on the wide window and it was brightly lited by the ambient floor lamp. From where we were, Frank noticed them first and he exclaimed "stop stop stop! they are people making out up there. back up! back up!" Heba was surprised and I supposed curious too. haha! she backed up the car in the middle of the road just weeeeeee before the Stop Line and turned right into the front door of the apartment where we watched the entire show. Like in one of  urlLink Craig David's song , "... Why do I see two shadows moving [back and forth] in your bedroom... can you fill me in?" We actually saw 2 person, guy behind (looking down; at his dong, i suppose) and the head of a blonde girl looking at him (his dong, perhaps). The guy was only visible up to his middle torso from where we were looking. We honked twice and drove away. Back up the car and passed by their window again, lights were off and they were not doing what we saw seconds ago... guessed they knew they were being watched. hahaha! A great way to celebrate Canada Day... for them!   Other news  Waskasiu pictures from Hindra's digital camera  urlLink available here . 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Pretty hot day today. 28C by noon. Nothing much to do on this hot day after giving a last session of Adobe Photoshop to my student. Went to Centre Mall on Circle & 8th and practically spent the entire evening over there watching 2 movies:  urlLink Shrek 2 , and  urlLink The Two Brothers.   I could help thinking what it would be like if really, my brother and I were separated like the latter movie. Even I have a share of joy watching how the two tiger brothers reunited and later with their mother at the end. The story has simply dazed me; I mean, it's wonderful! In a scene of the movie conveys a very strong message to boycott poaching by-products, which in my opinion, is an excellent way to create and disseminate awareness of endangered animals. I'd recommend one to watch this NOT just to take note of the anti-poaching movement but also the wonderful love story of  urlLink The Two Brother  in their journey to survive among humans.  As for Shrek 2, I could not believe I can be entertained by a mere green ugly (but cute) ogre especially donkey's deviant talkative behavior. The the cat, when it befriended Shrek with its drop-dead-innocently-cute look with wide eyes open gazing into Shrek's eyes, everyone in the cinema went "awwwwwwwwwwwwwwww...............!!" An undeniably heart-melting look! If you're looking to be entertained, watch this!  Currently listening to  urlLink DJ Tiesto's Just Be . You don't know who is this DJ?? Then you might want to check out the following link  urlLink here  and read a little about his achievements. I'm taken away by his musics most of the time and it always feel anew everytime I listen to his numbers. I must say, great musics! Instruments and trance genre are probably my all time fav! 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just got back from  urlLink Waskesiu  approximately 2.5 hours north from Saskatoon. It is situated in Prince Albert's region.  The trip was generally a good one and will consider of heading back there if I ever get a chance again with one condition-- that I know for certain mosquitoes will not party in the woods during our presence. The best part of the entire retreat is not one but many and that includes close encounter of a mother brown bear with her 2 cute cubs...  So, as soon as we arrived at our camp site, tents were set up. There were 6 tents all together and mine was the most mini of them all. Cute though. Since mosquitoes were already out by sunset, I was already overly annoyed by these blood thirsty peskies that I couldn't wait to spark off a camp fire. However, we did not aleady have a permit to do so but Rianto got them after dinner. It cost 2$ for the camp fire permit. Together we gathered some fire woods that were already halved to a suitable place. Initially it was under some branches and I didn't think it was a good idea because I was going to make a huge fire. Having a permit doesn't give me the right to burn down a tree now, does it? Anyway, the woods were relocated so that the rising flames dance freely and not consuming anything in the air. That night was friggin' cold too; that fire helped a bit. We gathered around the fire and Eddy brought in his small packet of marshmallows and wooden skewers (satay sticks).  Albert P. started to make noise at 4am waking me up. My tent was just beside theirs. Most of us froze our ass out by dawn. I didn't think this was worst than my last camp with Benson and Richard Wong in  urlLink Meota -- -15 celsius with  urlLink windchill  on our first night. Insanity! But this time it felt like 4 celsius with  urlLink windchill .  Day Two: After breakfast (simple bread and jam), we headed out to the beach by 10am and stayed to 2.30pm. Went back to camp site for a quick lunch and we left for a nearby lake for canoeing and  urlLink kayaking . I did the kayak. Little have I realized it could be so much fun! Best story of the day was Albert P. ran into the canoe (my brother and Edwin were paddling it) and he flipped downside up. We all knew the water is cold. As we laughed and watched him struggle to climb back on his kayak (10 of us kayak and 2 went on a canoe) only to see his kayak gave up on him and flipped again; there he went down the cold water. Poor saint. We guys paddled to his rescue and he climbed onto the canoe and they brought him back onto ground. All went with him and only Rianto and I stayed back to hold on to his kayak and his paddle. I was the last to struggle against the waves and wind before I reach the pier. On the way back, we stopped along the road side and watch a mother bear with her two cute cubs feeding. The mother bear would probably stand to 5.5 feet. I got a picture and will put it up here soon.  On the last day, Sunday, all of us went back to the beach and this time we went into the waters. Cold! That's all I can say about the water. There were a lot of people this day compared to yesterday. Lots of people sunbathing and frolicking with one another on the water, especially the indonesian people we're with. I went around with my camera wielded in my hands hoping they'll notice that I do not want to get wet. A neat excuse to avoid getting bashed on beach.  Trip is over.  Arrived Saskatoon and mom got busy packing stuffs and preparing to go back. I did not stay in my room for long. Went to school and ran into Marzi, Navjot Kaur, and Heba. We went out for a drink but Heba did not join us. Matthew did; and we hanged around and chatted till 2am at Olympia downtown. Came back and mom chatted with me till 6am. I lay down and fell asleep immediately. 7 am we were suppose to send mom to the airport but I got too comfortable sleeping and really hate myself for hessitating to go just because of sleep. I don't think this is the way to pay my respect to my mother. I'm really sorry.  Got up at 12noon and headed down to Daniel's Kimberly Physiotherapy for my left arm. It's so much better now compared to last month as I now have full arm movement. I will need to do some home exercises to strengthen and hasten the healing process of the partially torn tendon. Since I have full movement, the tear could range from 20% - 40% tear, which is not too serious.   Other news  I got a confirmed placing at the  urlLink University of Leeds , UK. Karla got sunburn on both her arms. Mother left for Vancouver and onwards to KL on Wednesday. I'll be heading back to Malaysia at the end of July or in the first week of August. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ... with Claudia. She's a very quiet, sweet and undoubtedly innocent looking girl. She calls herself "", which means "The [chaotic] cold blooded person"; as the name would suggest a serious [but down to earth] person, to see a smile from her is to see flowers blossoming to maturity during the end of winter. I am certainly one person who was taken away from her mesmerizing smiles-- the elixir of love. Unfortnately, I could have failed to capture every of that moment as far as I can remember. She doesn't reproduce her expressions on demand or on request. From what she dresses today, I can probably tell that she's quite shy with her god-endowed looks but at the same time, bold enough to try out various posing positions as I request. Ackward feelings invoked within me as I explored into new areas posing of glamour photography but with casual outfits. We all had fun... under the hot afternoon's sun from 14:10 to right now, 18:00. My, my my, am I getting dark already. Once again, she has been fun to work with and I look forward for another opportunity.   First roll of film is on slide film and it is my first time shooting slides. It is the best out there and there are, of course, many many advantages over 35mm negative films. The second 36 exposures is on B&W, which will give out a more artistic value as oppose to color. I am about to find out which of these two will stand out best. Wayman was there to helped me out and I must admit that he has been very useful to today's success photo-shooting. Although a mere reflector guy, if all the photos turned out to be excellent then I will have to buy him a house as a big thank you. hmm, a cup of Blizzard from the house of diary products, DQ. I'm pretty sure the 3 of us enjoyed our time out there today. All photos were shot on campus; the slide film was used mostly for outdoor photos while the other, indoor. We'll have to wait for at least a week to see the results.  As I was shooting for hours earlier, I cannot deny the fact the job of a photographer (especially when he is starting fresh) can be quite taxing. I don't consider myself as one, yet, although I would like to. Right now I'm just enjoying my hobby and this could probably be the reason why I found today's " work " is demanding. Where does all these lead to? Well, lets see. At the moment, I have no intentions of getting noticed professionally so I'll just do what I do best in giving and making good pictures. Communications, humbleness or was it meekness, generousity, understanding of the line of work, patience, and along with other positive morals are some of the few values to be observed even more thoroughly as a photographer, as a person?? Anyway, I don't really know waht I am saying here so I'll just leave at it.   Once again, a big hug to Claudia and Wayman. You guys have been great! More pictures to be posted up here soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Tuesday, July 6, 2004  Cheap movies on Tuesdays for new releases. Too bad nobody can bring in their  finger licking good  Toonies Tuesday's KFC into the theaters. My brother and I watched  urlLink White Chicks  at the Odean cineplex, Circle Mall. Nobody actually thinks comedies from Hollywood like this breed are ever good.  urlLink IMDb 's ratings on movies are quite credible as far as movies are concerned and the people who rated them are movie buffs. Anyway, silly movies like this one doesn't deserve to be at the top 90% quantile in the category it's in (Crime/Comedy). When it is in its own category and people who would rate are aware of such categorical ratings, then I would say this movie is worth at least an average of 5.4/10 as oppose to its current 3.7/10. It's not that bad, really. Movie-goers who watched this movie went in with too high of an expectations that includes laughing their arses out.   Later that evenning, there was nothing much on my agenda for the day already. So, I pigged out in front of the computer playing my mayor's role in Simcity 4. Everything in there is so methodical and perhaps ritualistic. Mundane. Being is mayor is the only reason for me to kill plenty of time. Time Killing sprees.   Wednesday, July 7, 2004  Marzi came over to my place to look at the desktop I am selling. My almost 3 years old IBM P3 machine is going off. Gave her a good back massage for like 10 minutes as she complained about the soreness around her neck area and her back. So, I remedied her with my sweet careress and... things happen you know?   Went to the movies with Ben Eng, Scott, Chelsea, and her two other friends. At long last,  urlLink Fahrenheit 9/11  is out to reveal the little secrets of America's late president, George Wussy Bush. It is not exactly a movie that most movie-goers have been watching at cinemas but it is more of a documentary-type showing GWB's backdoor life and how is he related to the collapse of the World Trade Centre that happened on September 11, 2001, and what is his stance. Also, how the war in Afganistan shifted focus to Iraq, which means to say that how the search for Al-Qaida/Taliban members went to hunt down Prime Minister of Iraq Saddam Hussein, which means to say that the focus actually shifted from apprehending criminals that attacked United States' business center and military center to a person who never attacked United States in his lifetime. As to me, it has already been apparent that pursueing the attackers of United States is not U.S's top priority but disarming Iraq and bringing down Mr. Hussein is. Oil is blatantly the reason and this reason is denied by the US government. My opinion is not influenced by this documentary I just watched but it has merely substantiated what I believe in even more strongly--that GWB is the terrorist.  There has been some theories regarding the 9-11 tragedy and one of it is that it was a commercial jet aircraft that hit the Pentagon building but a mock aircraft that looked like one but in reality it could be a remotely guided missle like that of a cruise or a tomahawk missle. I can't believe that the GWB could sit through reading stories to elementary school kids when he was informed that aircraft hit one of the WTC's towers. His expressions remained the way it has been for the past 30 mins or so... no dramatic change like "omg!! wtf! who could fucking do that! lets go lets go lets fucking go!!" But, his face looked kind of troubled but could not do anything. maybe he was consciuos of his crime--Selling America!  Worth a watch! Kudos to Michael Moores!    Thursday, July 8, 2004  Stopped by Economics Department to see Prof. Bruneau and Howe. Had a nice chat with them. I asked them to write a reference letter for me to which they both agreed to write a good one. Quite happy to hear that.  Later in the evening, we (Ben, Scott) headed out to Lydia's to see  urlLink cutie Theresa Sokyrka  perform live. She's one of the top 10 competitors in Canadian Idol and she's from Saskatchewan! OMG, she has this husky voice that I happen to find it extremely attractive, sexy, and relaxing.. like a piece of chocolate melting in the warmth of your mouth, ooh!! She jazzed from 8pm till midnight and she's a natural scatting jazzy jazzer. What a talent & a an extremely nice person too! Ever heard of Scatman's World? Received a hug from her (an Idol?!! woot!!)... well, if it wasn't for Ben who intended to go up to her and congratulate and wish her best, I would go home feeling empty. Thanks to him!       We stayed over at Ben's place after that. They, Ben and Scott, were going to watch "The Last Samurai" but those wussies fell asleep leaving me watching the movie alone until 6am. Only had 2 hours of sleep when Scott had to get up and go to work. I didn't sleep until Saturday's morning at 3am.  Hasta de la vista, baby! Later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Saturday, July 3 2004  Friggin' cold today but I hanged out at my brother's playing a role of a city-building mayor in  urlLink SimCity 4  for an unfathomable 32 hours with an accumulated 8 hours of break. There will arrive a day when I just get so sick of playing that game that I "would" devote my free time to do something more constructive. Gawd! I hate doing nothing during holidays. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'd like to share a secret to success with women that I've been thinking about and using for awhile now.   The interesting part of this particular secret that I'm going to share with you is that it involves CONFLICT.   And it involves conflict on more than one level.&nbsp;  Because this particular issue involves such a touchy and emotional topic (conflict), one which most people like to AVOID rather than talk about, I have to ask you to read this email ALL THE WAY THROUGH before making any judgments or decisions about how you're going to use what I'm going to share...  &nbsp;&nbsp; Fair enough?  &nbsp;&nbsp; OK, so here's the concept in a nutshell:    WHEN IT COMES TO ATTRACTION, SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO DO THINGS THAT SEEM "MEAN" OR "INCONSIDERATE" ON THESURFACE IN ORDER TO GIVE A WOMAN WHAT SHE "REALLY"WANTS. IF YOU DON'T DO THESE THINGS, YOU WILL FAILTHE TEST, AND ULTIMATELY FAIL WITH THE WOMAN. &nbsp;      By the way, I really struggled with the idea of writing this particular newsletter. It's not always easy to explain things like this particular idea, and I know that I will lose subscribers, have some women get upset with me, and cause a little bit of commotion. But ultimately I do believe in what I'm sharing, so I feel that I have to say it.  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Onward.  As I've mentioned many times in these newsletters and in my products, women aren't attracted to men who have lower STATUS than themselves.  &nbsp;&nbsp;  This is one of the reasons why there is a lot oftension around the ideas of:    A taller woman with a shorter guy   A woman making more money than her spouse   A man being "led around" by his female partner ...etc. etc. etc.&nbsp;&nbsp;   These are " naturally " sensitive issues, because these issues hint that the man is " lower status ", and somehow we all know that this is somehow " not right ".&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp; Now I'd like to give you a situation that you may even have personally experienced (in fact, there's a pretty good chance that you have), and use it as an example to explain the principle I'm explaining.   Here's the situation:   You're going out on a date with a woman. You ask her where  SHE'D  like to go for dinner. She doesn't give you an answer, and seems to be indifferent.  So you ask her what her FAVORITE restaurant is.  She says "Well, I really like this one particular place, but it's up to you".  You say "But I really want to take you wherever YOU want to go... you decide".  You can hear in her voice that she's actually beginning to get annoyed. This confuses you, since you're just trying to find out what she wants so you can give it to her.  &nbsp;&nbsp; You finally decide to just take her to her favoriteplace, since... well... DUH, it's her favorite place, so she's obviously going to enjoy it.  &nbsp;&nbsp; As the evening goes on, you can sense that she's in a bad mood, but you can't understand why or how this could be. The evening ends on a bad note, even though you went out of your way to make it nice for her. &nbsp;  OK, sound familiar?   &nbsp;&nbsp; Let's try another one:  &nbsp;&nbsp; You meet a woman, get her number, and meet her for a cup of tea. She's unusually attractive and beautiful, and at the first meeting you realize that she's also intelligent and successful. This woman is obviously exceptional.   After the meeting you go home and think about her.  A LOT. You decide that it would be good to call her to tell her that you had a great time, and ask her out again.   You pick up the phone and call her. You tell her what a great time you had with her, and ask her if you can see her again the next night. She agrees.   The next night, you have a wonderful dinner, and great conversation. At the end of the evening, you start talking to her, and you tell her that you can't believe how beautiful, intelligent, and sweet she is, and that you are already beginning to have feelings for her.   She smiles and says "thank you", but doesn't offer any comments in return.   The next day, you decide to call her and ask her out again. She doesn't answer her phone, and doesn't return your call.   You get an email from her three days later saying "I'm sorry, I just need some time alone right now. I really like you, but I think we should just be friends."   Even though it was obvious that you were both havinga great time and enjoying each other's company... something went wrong. You somehow suspect that it had to do with the fact that you shared how you felt with her, but you have no way of knowing.   And how about a third scenario:  You meet a nice girl, get her email and number, and call her to make plans to get together.  She flakes out on you, and doesn't show up for your first meeting.  You call her later that day and ask her what happened.  She explains that she got busy and wound up having to help her best friend who was going through a crisis.   You say "Oh, that's OK. No problem. Can we meettomorrow instead?"  She says "Sure, give me a call then and we'll talkabout it".  The next day when you call, she's not home, and she doesn't return your call.  You call her the following day, and she has anotherexcuse for why she wasn't around and why she didn't return your phone call.  You keep calling to ask her out, but she keeps being busy, and eventually stops talking to you altogether.   Ever had THAT happen? HERE'S THE KICKER...   In the first situation, the best thing to do would have been to just decide where YOU wanted to go for dinner, then take her there.   In the second situation, the best thing to do would have been to NOT call her right after you met for coffee, NOT go out the next night, NOT share how you "feel" so quickly, and actually LEAN BACK a little and give her space and time to miss you and pursue YOU a bit.   In the third situation, the best thing to do would have been to NOT TOLERATE the fact that she flaked out, and to actually CONFRONT her with her poor behavior, then to NOT call her for awhile (if at all), and to make sure she understood that it isn't acceptable to waste your time ever again.    SO WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE?    And why is it that sometimes, when you're trying your very damn best to be nice, considerate, honest, open, and respectful, women DIS you and run? Why is it that doing things that seem inconsiderate are best in some situations?   Well, part of the answer is that ATTRACTION isn't like other areas of life.  Attraction isn't a CHOICE, for one thing. We don't go through a logical decision-making process and carefullyconsider who we're going to be attracted to.  NO WAY.  It just HAPPENS.  POW!  And attraction isn't triggered by being NICE.   In fact, as ironic as this sounds, some of thecharacters in movies and romance novels that are considered to be the SEXIEST are mean, nasty, and horrible!   Go watch Marlon Brando in "A Streetcar Named Desire".Women will tell you that he is a SEXY BITCH in that movie.   Oh, by the way, he also beats his wife and rapes his wife's sister in that movie.   Attraction is NOT triggered by being nice and considerate.   Often, ATTRACTION is triggered by things that make no sense at all, and it's destroyed by things that SHOULD make it stronger.   Now, I'm not saying that you should treat women badly. Of course that's not a good idea.   I believe that you can take what I'm sharing and actually treat women  VERY  well. But if you don't understand the psychology of the situation and the  psychology of ATTRACTION , and know how to handle situations like the ones I've just mentioned, you will fail the tests, and ultimately not succeed with women and dating most of the time.   To put this in plain, simple words, women aren't attracted to WUSSIES.   Women are ATTRACTED to men who  DECIDE , who  LEAD , who are in  CONTROL . Women feel that gut-level emotional attraction for men who have DIRECTION... men who make decisions and then take action on those decisions... NO MATTER WHAT ANYONE ELSE THINKS.   This is why you can ask a woman what she wants, take her to her favorite restaurant, tell her how you feel about her, and have get ANNOYED at you.   It's because you made a BIGGER mistake while you were trying to be "nice". When you asked her what SHE wanted to do, you put HER in CONTROL. This is annoying to women. When you couldn't make up your mind where to take her, and wound up taking her to her favorite restaurant, you demonstrated that you can't LEAD. Again, by being "nice and considerate"in one way, you were making a HUGE mistake on another level.   The reason why it's hard for me to express this thought and explain this concept is because this isn't exactly great news about life.   It means that you have to deal with and accept the fact that you might have to do something in a situation that seems "inconsiderate" in order to actually "do the right thing".   I have one friend who is VERY good with women who says that if you can get into an argument when you first meet a woman, she'll be far more likely to sleep with you.   This really shook me up when I first heard it, because this isn't something I wanted to hear. But then I thought about it and realized that "jerks" often have the most beautiful women around them... and these hot women will often endure all kinds of abuse just to be with the jerk. So there it is.   Sometimes you have to do things that don't seem to "make sense" or be "considerate" in order to make and keep a woman attracted to you... and ultimately give a woman what she REALLY wants.   I've spent the last few years taking what I've learned about how to be successful with women and dating, and distilled the process of ATTRACTION down to a few keys. I've also done something that I'm very excited about... I've figured out how to do the things that make women feel that powerful GUT LEVEL ATTRACTION... but without any of the ABUSE that jerks use.   I now honestly believe that it's possible to treat women well, while being interesting, challenging, ATTRACTIVE, and sexy at the same time.   But you have to know how.  It all starts with understanding the basic principleslike the one I've just discussed, the origin and evolutionof ATTRACTION, the beliefs and values of "naturally"successful guys, and, of course, the specific techniquesand strategies to use in different situations to do things like approach women, get numbers, get dates, and take things to a physical level...&nbsp;  And I'll talk to you again soon.    Your Friend,&nbsp;  &nbsp;  P.S. If you'd like to send me a Success Story, Question, or Comment, follow these guidelines:  1) Keep it short and to the point. Two paragraphs max.  2) Tell me what's working for you before you ask your question. I appreciate all of the "Your stuff is great" and "I don't need to tell you how well your stuff works" comments, but the fact is that I DO need to hear all of the specifics... because this helps other guys to see what's working in different situations.  3) If you have a Success Story, write "Success Story" in the subject line of the email. I read these first.  4) At the end of the email, give me your initials and tell me where you're from.  5) Send it to me at:  d a n t v l i [ a t ] h o t m a i l . c o m  ...don't just hit "reply" to this email. Thanks!   Notice: The article above is authored by David D. and you can find more information on what he writes about at  urlLink his website .    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sold my digital camera that was a gift from dad 3 years ago to a Nigerian guy for 10$. It is a Fujifilm FinePix 2100 and it was acquired for 299$ then and I believe it has been discontinued. Besides, the SmartMedia storage that it uses is no longer popular and perhaps discontinued as well. For 10$ perhaps it's a little too cheap for a digital camera that is still fully functional. It should have been 30$ to justify the price that was paid for but for a person who stepped into&nbsp;my room and imagined himself as though he just entered a Dollar Store or Dollarama Store where most merchandises are under 5$, I didn't think 30$ would be as attractive to 10$, or even 1$ (might as well be a give-away). I haven't been using the FinePix for a very long time ever since  urlLink Canon Rebel Ti  has been my possession last summer. &nbsp; My fan died on me yesterday and it's hell to sleep in my room now that it is so hot and stiffling! Anyway, I'm glad that I have finally found a store that carry Jelly Beans, the original Jelly Belly's. It is just right after Famous Player's Capitol. Had a great time shopping for jelly beans there. She commented on the weather and yeah, I agreed with her that it's a nice and hot weather out there. I told her about my fan out of the blues and her jaws just dropped and eyes was about to popped out and she gasped. She thought I said "My friend died [on me] yesterday" and she was surprised how I can still shop for jelly beans happily. Pretty funny. Got to know her during my 45 minutes stay there. She's in her mid thirties and of Ukraine origin. Dressed in a simple low-cut spotted brown blouse knee level. Maybe she wanted people to notice that she has a nice cleavage and she's naked under her blouse. Her B-cup&nbsp;quasi-sagging boobs hangs down wobbling a little and stretched in freedom when she bends down to reach for a jelly bean that dropped from the counter. hehe! I don't know... not that I am a bloody pervy but hey, maybe I was there at the right time and the right place. She's single and have no kids by the way. *winks!* &nbsp; I just got a Canon EF 50mm F/1.8 prime lens and a tripod, which is a monopod also. Both of these cool&nbsp;items can be striked off my wish list now. Darn, the rate of depletion just gets steeper as I spend more... burning a bigger hole in my pocket. &nbsp; That's all for today. later! &nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am turning 25 this September.  Am I ready for a new relationship? Should I still be on the look out even though I already have one by my side?  But that couldn't be cheating, no? Maybe it is because my heart is not devoted entirely to my current girl. Am I afraid to commit? I don't think I am afraid to commit myself into a relationship as long as we are both attracted to each other.   In my opinion, there is nothing wrong with commitment in a relationship but if this is so, then why are there some people out there are afraid to commit? They are not ready to 'settle down' I'd suppose and that being said, perhaps they are still looking for more fun before tying a deadend knot (assuming divorce is not an option)? I call it  diversification .    Diversification  is healthy in a relationship, I mean, if you are in a relationship and you'd like to know if he/she is really the one for you, then you should diversify! I know it sounds crazy but it's not like I am "for" Temptation Island's idea but, somehow I do believe that every relationships should be tested for its threshold tension; that is to say how far or how strong the relationship is before the ropes that ties the couples together in love snaps. Not the kind of test where you take her (and not only her) for a "test drive" where she'll "ride" on you happy.  While I am not suggesting that is the right thing to do, when you do "test" out your relationship at the of the day you'll reap out the benefits by multiple folds.  gone for beer. brb.  Back. My previous romantic relationship was more of a lesson to me given the condition of "now that I know". I did test out our relationship in many ways that now I thought were all misleading and headed to no where. To make matters worse, I had placed a lot of high expectations on her to which she did not respond sufficiently and appropriately leaving me feeling flustered and frustrated most of the time. There was no "Temptation Island" on TV then ;) hehe! I love her too much. But things just didn't go the way I wanted. Am I being selfish? Both of us were selfish in our own ways so I guess we're even, but on the wrong grounds. To be even on a balancing scale ( [gang2gan3]) our relationship would have a higher probability of survival. However, it seemed like there were more than one balancing scales and instead of being in equilibrium for all the scales, they are unequally weighted on either sides.  That was what Ben and I discussed --the BGR (Boy-girl Relationship) problem-- when we went out to catch some breezes on our blades along the Mewasin Trail (River side). We sat on the last bench closest to Circle Drive bridge for a good 20 minutes and chatted. His girl is afraid to commit but simply because I think she's still immature towards BGR. Scott made a huge mistake on giving up on Chelsea but he realized soon enough to mend back his relationship and right now, what can I say? Lucky chap!  What's going to happen this weekend? I thought of going back up to Waskasiu Lake for a weekend camping getaway. But I want to see  urlLink Theresa Sokyrka  the cutie at Lydia's too. The opportunity cost of forgoing a last camping trip to the wilds and be in and around natural habitat "is" I think, greater in some number than going to see Theresa serenading my heart soft on Sunday when I know she plays at the Lydia's most Sundays. If I can have both, then it is suffice for me to say that I am even better off thus happier?! Yeah! So, camping that is!  Oh yeah, I watched  urlLink King Arthur  with my brother earlier... Not that good even though I did enjoy the medieval settings or backdrops in the film?   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I spent the entire evening and night over at Yanbing's place watching  urlLink Cool Running  and " urlLink The Journey of Natty Gann " and chatted till sunrise and watched funny video clips at  urlLink Joked.com  (Be warned! Some medias are not suitable for persons under the age of 23!). Went to sleep at an ungodly hour: 7:45am and got up at 2:00 when my phone rang. It was a person looking for some items I put up for sale because I'm moving out of this place pretty soon. I thought I have put up notices to have people call me after 8pm to enquire? Tried to snooze a little bit but couldn't because a few minutes later came in another call, from the Royal University Hospital. Thank god Dr. Ansel rushed my case to the hospital otherwise I wouldn't be able to use my left arm ever again! That sounds like kind of cruel to my own arm, but anyway, it is not that serious. I'm quite happy as it is healing fast!  I stepped on a weighing scale and there was no good news! Horrors were scribbled on my face as I read out loud my weight in disgust! Kirk Backstrom, Yanbing's other half, tried to be nice by saying that the scale is off by 5kg (~11 lbs) but I know that is not a possibility. I am eight-fucking-ty kg (~176 lbs). 2 weeks ago, as far as I can recalled I was merely 76kg! Heck, what did I do to myself?! I didn't want to continue facing my horrors by not doing anything so I decided to put on my blades and go skating. Hmm, felt kinda heavy downward... more gravity thus more stability (don't they call it center of gravity?). fuck! aahh!! im fat!! heck no! but look at my tummy ... or has it become a belly?! omg!! omg! Danny! Cut this out! You're not fat! You just need to do more ab-crunches! Oh, that is so reassuring! So, my brother decided to come along. We skated south on Clarence Ave and I noticed 2 young look blonde girls taking a stroll ahead of us. One of them was wearing a particularly short skirt, tight on the hips but lose around the hem lines. It's funny the way she walks , or maybe it was just her skirt that was flapping back and forth each step she takes. If you have eyes, then her bare naked ass is impossible to miss when her skirt flaps up. There was a puddle of water and she lept! Oh-oh oh no!!! I tripped and fell when the thong revelation befell on me! hehe! Nah, I didn't fall. Couldn't afford to lose another arm now, could I? Anyway, they continued walking down on Clarence and we turned left on 12th street and we had dinner at East Mario's. Good meal but the Kung Pao's chicken pasta is not that fantastic. It's funny how they westernized a chinese/asian (Kung Pao chicken) menu item... anyway, I did flirt a bit with our server/waitress. hehe! I played dumb and later I admit I was just kidding with her and she hit me. hey, that was something! My brother who sat on my right tried to stop my obnoxious behaviors towards the dirty blonde server maybe because I am embarrassing him? hhehee! Fun though!  Somebody called me and she sounded too distant to be audible so I asked her to speak up. She hessitated for a bit and threw in some interjections which I didn't understand. From the voice, I can tell she's a Chinese, Mandarin speaking person. So, I told her to speak in her mother tongue and my, my... the next thing she said totally blew me away! It was Xiaoyu! We laughed silly at ourselves because we didn't recognize each other's voices and number (I have caller's id). So, yeah, we'll meet tomorrow for a date. ;) hehe! But it'll be more like... uhh, well, she's coming over to my place... to buy things! Cool! 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       School girl got suspended for showing off her assets in a sexually suggestive manner. For complete story,  urlLink click here.    urlLink Click here to read more.                 Hint: Right-click and "SAVE AS" for larger picture.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Shot by Keeane: Well, needless to say further. If you are seeking for the "virgin" picture, contact me.  Photoblogged!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Soon after stepping out of the theater I realized that "Bourne Supremacy" is the second part continuing "Bourne Identity". It was the former that I watched with my brother. Good movie! The story line wasn't that bad and the special FXs are quite decent too; and the car-chase scenes or maybe you'd like to term it as high-speed pursuits are jaw-droppings aftermath. Sit put in your seat... lest you be swayed away.   There's something about how the movie was shot that I am attracted to; perhaps the positioning of cameras and methods used to capture several out-of-the-ordinary scenes. hmm... I might put that on my wishlist-- be a film-maker by first owning a video camera?   Bah!   Anyway, enough said about movies.  This time I walked to Danville's resident for a scheduled appointment to take some pictures of the stepping stone I made with a big leaf on Wednesday. The concrete is not dry yet but he suggested that we lay it down on his garden for photos. And we did just that!. Embossed on it are the copper wires that I twisted and bended to form alphabets that would apparently spell out my name with a date stamp. Cool!   Here are some pictures of it.    urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: There lay my stepping stone on a bed of lilies; ever so strong and steadfast. I feel indebt somehow.   Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: Stan Danville laying down the second stone. Mine will be on the third.   Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: Stan posing a backache stance. Just kidding. He's picking up something and mind you, he is ever so healthy!   Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: A closer view of the finished product.   Photoblogged!!     There it shall lay in garden for eternity(?)  I have left behind quasi-time-capsule souvenir  They have left behind beaconing memory for me  that would raise reasons for yearning to return to Canada   I mean, come on, I don't suppose that any host families make their own garden's stepping stones, right? Let alone your name on one of it. Frankly speaking, Stan Danville and his wife, Nelly Danville, are not even part of the International Friendship Program that the International Students Office of my University runs.   We met last summer after I return from Malaysia for a month's of holiday. Jean (Jingfang) and I went outfor our daily strolls around the place we stayed, which was Soji's 1428 14th street East. Now, on January 30th it was the  urlLink  coldest day of the year with a temperature of 57 degrees celsius below zero , 1428 got burnt down. Jean moved out of 1428 to live in BC at the end of August 2003. So did I. So, we came upon this beautiful fenced garden full of lilies. We decided to walk into the garden to have a chat with the person whom I know today as Stan. He showed me this water fountain that he made from nothing and continued to surprise me by revealing to me that most of the stuffs I see in his garden are not bought but made with the two hands endowed to him. I am already convinced that this man is not only amazing but as creative as I would like to be. To raise one more brow, over many conversations within that period I just could not believe that we do share some common interests and I would suppose that that is the probably the reason that has kept this friendship. I don't really think that age has largely to do with this although I cannot deny that it could be a contributing factor as a senior citizen in the community spends his/her day trimming the garden, read a book outside, invent something, etc. in other words, they are just too nice and meeting people has always been part of their life in their retirement years.   Onwards to another item.  We sat and chatted about Canadian history, Malaysia (pronounced as Ma-lay-sia and not Ma-lay-zhuh) on most part. Then he took me down to his 'dungeon' where he works at polishing stones and jewelries during the winter. The entire base is just full of tools and motors that I suppose would assist in his polishing work. So, I had the opportunity to polish a stone for myself and so I did! I got a rounded  Snowflake Obsidian  1 inch in diameter and about a quart of an inch in thickness. He showed me how to do the job and I polished the stone from its coarse surface to a glossy shinning stone. It's the kind of stone where kids would find on the beach or by a river and keep as souvenirs. Their borders or corners would usually be rounded and blunt (not sharp) and a variety of mineral deposits in layers are visible. Here are the pictures:     urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: The Snowflake Obsidian stone is waxed onto a stick so that I don't get my hands grinded by the machine. I am polishing the stone here until it glitters! It's mica not gold!   Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: The polished stone in my hand. From pointy edges to polished dome. My  Precious !! My precious jewel from Canada!   Photoblogged!!     So, at 23:00, we drove out of town (about 10 minutes) to pick up  urlLink Amanda  (who is now engaged to Tony, the two person behind my head) and headed to The Hose. Most of the people whom we played Ultimate Game together were there drinking and yakking away. As usual, we were late because Scott was driving. He needs to have a talking wrist watch that would annoy the daylights out of him by reciting every quarters of the time and probably yell   "Scott! Scooot now!! Scooot!!"   That would be horrendous if it were to be true for him. I get too IMpunctual sometimes too and because I am a (Canadian??) Malaysian, we have coined a name for such impunctuality --  Malaysian Timing  -- as though we're dumb in telling time and meeting appointments on time.  Why am I having so much fun now? Like, what happened to the days before tonight? These people are people of substance and I'm just about to learn about them getting to know them and right now to even think about not being able to party with these people again would probably cause some tears rolling down ones cheeks. But one has to move on in life, eh? It's good to get comfortable with what you have and your surroundings but it's never too good when you get too comfortable that laziness pops up and you're not motivated to do something else. If you don't know what I'm talking about, try looking up for a book called " urlLink Who moved My Cheese " authored by Dr. Spencer. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I am glad that Claudia finally got her chance to look at her own glamour shots. While looking at her analyzing each slides that she picks up and held out at arms length, my heart just beats faster and you know I think I also feel a little panicky as I am afraid of her being very critical of how I have made her look like in the shots. Anyway, there are 37 slides and she's gone through each and every one of them and now comes the verdict:  "So, how are they? Do like like them?", I querried in deep trembling voice. "So-so lor... there are some good ones", she replied with a smile probably feeling a little embarrassed too. "Well, you can probably go through all of them again because I am going to have ask you to pick out the ones you want for print", I explained. She nods her head.  From #37, she filpped through the slides until 25 and called out "number twenty-five" as her first slide of choice to print.  In my head I questioned myself about the last 12 slides. Perhaps they are no good. Oh well, at least from #25 and below, there are more good ones (the ones she likes) as she called the slide numbers out. 15 slides out of 37 she picked out for print. I dont know about myself but I think that is quite an achievement for me. However, I should also give myself the benefit of doubts that "what if" she chooses out of obligations or sympathy...? Anyway, the whole thing didn't turn out bad... it was a good scene. I guess we're both glad with the results... although we're not taking into consideration of&nbsp;the bad shots.  Gotta go... might go and watch "Bourne's Identity".  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I  have been a member of  urlLink SMS.AC  for a long time now. You would probably know they are free-service providers when you sign up. However, behind the attractive word "Free" that consumers like me are always looking for on the WWW, there is a price to pay.   When you DO sign up, I learned (just now even though I was already a member for over 2 years) that you have several credits per day in which will allow you to send text messages via their website for free. Those credits will be replenished at midnight Pacific Time. However, your membership with SMS.AC will warrant an automatic sign up to their other "pay per use" services. You will be charged for every text messages received. I have gone through their  urlLink Terms and Condition  and assuming I have not overlooked any clauses, there is no where it mentioned that users like you and me will be bounded to such situation, which does actually opens up a door for them (SMS.AC) to milk us out.   You might probably be asking yourself how would they charge you. Well, SMS.AC is predominantly a text-messaging provider company and when you signed up you have provided them your cellphone number. That is where you are vunerable.   My cellphone bills have been regular and I am quite familiar with the iteneries within in until I received my last bill. Take a look and I shall draw your attention to the highlighted item that reads "Total Pay Per Use Service Charges". urlLink      I just got off the phone with  urlLink Rogers  operator/customer service assistance. Been on the phone for like 33minutes! They have been trying to resolve what seems to be my problem as well as Roger's. Because it appeared on my bill, therefore, it does mean that Rogers know about it and was charged thus I am responsible for the charges. But  How did I not know about it?!"  This is what I'd call it hidden charges.   I don't exactly know how it (SMS.AC) works out. They may have changed their policies, terms and conditions without notifying or highlighting key points that could and/or would change or influence consumer's choice on whether or not to continue to stay as their members. For most cases, silence construes acceptance or agreement, which I think is totally unjust.   Recently I have been receiving a lot of text-messages from them and I haven't actually question myself as to why and how seriously... until today.   So, the purpose of me writing this to you so that you be aware of SMS.AC's cunningness or wittyness in their business conduct. Alhthough I do not and am not a member of any pornography websites, I know how they work-- you sign up for XXX's 3 days trial at NO COST and failing to withdraw your membership within 72 hours gives XXX the right to bill you their full membership rates as well as you are automatically signed up to XYZ, AXX, ABC, XZZ trial porn sites for free... but you'll be billed. Before you know it, you've been billed by 10 sites behind your back when you are only aware of ONE porn site that you signed up for at the end of the month when you look at your credit card invoice.   Another point I am making:  ALWAYS (EXTRA EMPHASIS!!) READ AND SCRUTINIZE "TERMS AND CONDITIONS" and "PRIVACY POLICY"  whenever you sign up to a web service site that requires your financial information (e.g. credit card).  There's another reference to this testimony and is found at  urlLink Abysm Of Time . Who ever needs a translation, I am more than willing be at your service. All you have to do is to let me know... using the comment link available at the bottom of this posting.    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Using the same pictures used to make the previous panoramic photo, we have rearranged the scenes in an attempt to get a different look. We didn't think the one looking like an island was all that good.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot collaboratively by LF and me: 360 degrees panoramic view of the beach and around us. The beach is in facing in front of us while the hibachi is behind us in shadows. Looks like an island, doesn't it? Using multiple shots, we have combined these using Photoshop CS  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by LF: Spy at work... on bended knees. One of my fav shots.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wasn't going to miss another bus as I was late for a scheduled physical therapy appointment. It was already 13:54 and I was still in my room; I have 1 minute. I dashed out of my house half naked and the 6A bus passed me and stopped at the bus stand which was just next block. There wasn't even a chance for me to slide in my shirt (buttoned) as I did the fastest sprint as I could... on my almost torn sandals. Just a few more steps away from the stand, the bus left.   "No!!!", I exclaimed!!   Already panting and grasping for air, I walked at ease and realized that the bus was slowing down at the ambering lights ahead on College Drive and Wiggins Ave. Determined not to miss my ride, again I did the 100 meters sprint. As I approached the junction of Wiggins I was sure I could get the driver's attention. It stopped at the next stand on Wiggins. A couple of people got down and doors were closed. I was only 3-4 leaps away and the bus had to step on it.   "Nooooooooo......!! Not again!!", I shouted in frustration. Who wouldn't be frustrated after attempting twice or more to flag down the bus after a few sprints? I gave up and guilt almost ate me up for leaving my door late... but, alas, I heard screeching noises from the bus and that's a good sign--the driver had lifted up his leg on the gas pedal and stepped on the brakes! Woohooo!! I jogged there to make my entrance... still half naked! Stepped up the stairs and dug up for coins in my pocket, still topless! Passengers by the windows who noticed me running after the bus applauded me and one of them made a comment:   "You must be ready for the Olympic games!".   I was panting like mad. I offered a generous smile to the person who made that comment as I walked down the aisle passed him looking for a seat to put on my shirt. gee!   After receiving treatment, I paid and left for Walmart to get my photos. When it's my turn to pay I gasped and panicked digging all the 6 pockets of the cargo pants I wore.   "Heck! where is my wallet!?"   Apparently, I left it at Daniel Kimbers Physical Therapy clinic. The panic attack subsided after I made a call to the clinic and so I strolled down 8th street when my sandals torn into two pieces.   "Give me a break!! It has not been a good day to start with since I stepped out of my door at 13:54!"   Limping my way to the clinic and took back what belonged to me and limped back to Walmart to pay for the merchandise.   Limped all the way to Sportschek and the first thing I did when I stood before the shoe shelves was to kicked off the rotten sandals I was wearing and pick them up to dump it in my trash bin behind me.   The sales assistance grins. I bet he thinks that "this" guy is certainly going to buy something from here. hehe! Of course I am! Don't wanna be walking on bare foot now do I?   Great!  Headed to Black's photography to pick up slides I shot for Claudia. Some turned out so-so but most of them are okay and there are a few exceptional ones. Felt excited as it is my first time shooting on slide films. Color saturations are top quality and they were all super vivid! I have to keep in mind to underexpose by either  or 1 stops next time I shoot slides, and overexpose by the said amount when I shoot negatives. I'm quite satisfied with the quality of slide films has to offer!   Later in the evening, I was at Stanley Dansville's to make another impression of stepping stones that he lays down in his magnificient lily garden. This time it'll be a different stepping stone -- it has my name printed on it. Not that I don't already mind people stepping on my name, but how many international students (I'm from Malaysia) would have their names on a concrete stepping stone in somebody else's garden in Saskatoon, let alone Canada?! *sniggers!* I thought of it as a time capsule and offered that idea to Stan, a retired mchanical engineer who will be 83 years old in a month, and he pretty much liked the idea and adopted it. Best of all, he taught me how to do it and I did everything on my own.   After that, I joined Scott, Andrea, Andrew, Jordan, and a few other friends for a game of Ultimate -- the ultimate frisbee game!   Whew! What a day! :)  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dear Guys,&nbsp; Please update how true is this if you've been there.&nbsp; Please forward to all your girl friends out there!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; FW: Aware of the RUSH club washroom!  To every ladies out there,&nbsp; Please be aware that there is a new club which used to be calledViva located in Eastin hotel called RUSH Club.Inside the ladies washroom there is a blue water flowing glass with a mirror next to it, it's a one directional mirror from the guys washroom.   So ladies be aware because we can't see the guys from the oppositebut the guys can watch every single move and things that we are doing in the washroom except when u're in the cubicle.&nbsp;  I've been to the club and my bf told me about it.He said he sees every gal in the washroom clearly and the otherguys are like watching a show in their washroom. Please pass this messageto all of ur gal frens to aware them about this humiliating action that isgoing on at RUSH Club.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by LF: You will see the shot I was trying to create here... little did I know that there's a papaprazi eye around the beach. The naked truth is... I think I might have discovered that I have boobs!! I'm a 36AA. Do also check out the pic with me lying on the beach sand.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : Lovely shot! Finally I get to see myself... looking away into the horizon perhaps trying to get a glimpse of bikinied-humans?!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by LF: Group photo... how about a lift of my leg for kudos!? Had good time!  Photoblogged!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : Dancing Flames. A Flame dancer puked a whole lot of fiery goo after the drunken dance while the other still dancing away into oblivion.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : Paint with fire. Ambers and flames from our hibachi just before we headed up to the pier. This was around 00:30.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The Aurora Borealis Showdown we witness-- Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : For an hour we sat on the pier just to see these formless green lights as though they have a message for us. Another great shot by LF! Kudos!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The Aurora Borealis Showdown we witness-- Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : To witness this is to be in second heaven. Words are beyond description to describe just how at awe we were. This is one of the best shots LF has.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The Aurora Borealis Showdown we witness-- Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : As you can notice, brighter on the right side. These thing actually moves like when you'd run your finger across the ivories on a piano. Just magical!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The Aurora Borealis Showdown we witness-- Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : The auroras gathering up and taking formation for intensity. Generally this one we saw were all green in color.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The Aurora Borealis Showdown we witness-- Shot by Leonard Fang (LF) : A little too dim but as spectacular!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ... about the motion picture of the sexy lass in white on the right side bar of this page, you might have asked yourself why is it there and perhaps wonder about the degrees of a social deviant I am that would equate to a sick pervert. &nbsp; Before you allow your mind to lead you thinking in that direction,&nbsp;you&nbsp;must first allow me to clear up the stench in the air then you make your judgement. &nbsp; I, too, have never heard why would anybody want to hack into personal blogsites like mine and put up stuffs that the hackers thought was funny or just for the heck fun of it.  &nbsp; Doesnt' it look cool? Okay. That picture is situated on the "About" [this blog] part and not "About Me" part so it doesn't speak of my sickly fetishes or that I'm sick. Whatever I do to that picture it will still come back. So, for now I'll just leave it as it is until it's time is up. Right now I"m too lazy... &nbsp; Cheers!  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Come back to keep up...  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Saturday, July 17, 2004   Got up at 06:15 and started packing up before&nbsp;my ride arrived at&nbsp;07:10. Threw in a sleeping bag, a pillow, a tripod, a camera, and some clothings into&nbsp;Julian's truck.  &nbsp;  After a&nbsp;two and a half hours&nbsp;on the road we arrived&nbsp;Waskesiu. We were&nbsp;on one of the beaches&nbsp;to start off with lunch at around noon time. Played and relaxed on the beach till&nbsp;17:00 when&nbsp;rain clouds were already setting in. Some of our guys said that there was going to be a thunder storm in this place&nbsp;earlier but nobody seemed to&nbsp;be bothered by it too much because&nbsp;the sun was scorching our skins earlier and at this time it would be been deemed&nbsp;to be an impossible phenomena.&nbsp;Skies were clear&nbsp;and cotten-candy clouds painted the blue skies pretty. Man, I even got a mild sun-burn.  &nbsp;  A group of people went to town for a shower while&nbsp;a few more stayed back. I stayed back for some sun and photo-shootings (scantily clad girls in bikinis perhaps?). At around 16:45, Leonard, Raymond,&nbsp;and Jotham Gan have all gone to the campsite to pitch up our tents leaving behind Josephine (Jotham's mother), Melissa Gan, and myself at the beach side. They came back 20 minutes later and I must say their timing were excellent. We would be under water had they not. All of a sudden, winds up to probably 56 km/h were constantly blowing for more than 5 minutes. It's not like a gush of wind for a second or two but a constant flow of air so strong that it would have perhaps moved the lid of the hibachi sideways. Waves on the waters became violent. The six of us pack up stuffs in haste and headed out to our campsite. No rains yet but we were already expecting one.  &nbsp;  It started rainning already when we arrived at our campsite and since there were 11 of us in total, we had to pitch up another tent. Four of us got out leaving behind Josephine and Melissa in the van to do just that. Each of us held a corner of the tent and stretched it out to lay it on the ground. As soon it the tent was on the ground, something dropped from above&nbsp; and hit on the tent right in front of me and I thought the tree bore some kind of interesting seed or fruit as it was white in color. The second I picked it up it didn't take me long enough to know that that is an ice ball. About an inch in diameter and half and inch in height and looks like an UFO's flying saucer (oval).  &nbsp;  "Hey guys! It's a hail!!&nbsp;This is ice!", I exclaimed.  &nbsp;  Already [half] drenched in the rain, we must have unanimously agreed in our minds to get into the tent that was already pitched because somehow we believed that that one piece of hail that fell off the sky had a purpose.  &nbsp;  Those 3 guys quickly crumble-folded the tent and walked towards the tent. They were confused as they did not know where to put the tent -- back into the van or bring it into the tent that was dry on the inside. I shouted to get them into the tent and they did. As we hurried in, the rain just got heavier. We opened the 'window' of our tent and we can see Josephine and her daughter stucked in the van on about 10 feet away to our front left side. A minute later (17:40) there wasn't much rain but this time little hails poured down.  &nbsp;  We sat/knelt in the tent and stared at each other in consternation just watching one of mother nature's powerful force unveiling her wraths. The&nbsp; grounds were beginning to look like a floor of white sago seeds rolling in all directions as water droplets hit them. The hail got worse. 5 minutes later, the sound of hails that hit out tent grew harder and louder. We looked outside once again and we were telling each other to look how the size of the hail changed. They were no longer&nbsp;the size of&nbsp;sago seed but now the size as big as foosball and golf balls.&nbsp;It size of it all were just mind-boggling.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Josephine later on relate&nbsp;to us her experience to be inside&nbsp;the van during the hail. It's like somebody playing&nbsp;a drum kit's snare&nbsp;and you're trapped inside it. She&nbsp;got so worried that those hails would crack her windshield so&nbsp;without much hessitation she&nbsp;switched on the wipers at&nbsp;max speed hoping the pair of wiper blades&nbsp;can bat the thousands of hails&nbsp;pouring down on her van and on us. We thought the movie we watched a few weeks ago-- urlLink The Day After Tomorrow -- is not simply just a movie but some kind of manifestation as prophesied in that movie.  &nbsp;  The hail storm lasted about&nbsp;20 minutes and it is the first hail storm I have experienced to date. Alas! That first hail that dropped on the tent we were&nbsp;going to set up has served as a warning to us all -- "GET IN!! Or else you'll be hurt!!".&nbsp; If that's the work of God, He must have been gracious to&nbsp;have warned us! Glory to be Him!! &nbsp;  The rest of the people finally arrived at the campsite at around 18:10 when it&nbsp;the hails were already over. I bet they have had&nbsp;hell of a ride to here. One by one came into our tent. We&nbsp;sang and played the guitar. Jean, from&nbsp;Taiwan, is apparently quite talented&nbsp;at strumming the strings and singings&nbsp;as well.  &nbsp;  The storm subsided&nbsp;20 minutes&nbsp;later, 18:35-ish. Mosquitoes came out! Great!! Why didn't we have a break from mother nature? I have seen&nbsp;those mosquitoes the size of a&nbsp;twoonie coin (2$&nbsp;Canadian coins). Here is a pic of that coin:  . When one of those blood-sucking pest lands on your back, you had better slap on it fast and hard when its stomach is still empty or you're gonna get your own blood splattered all over its land site. God knows what kind of viruses/bacteria it carries. I learned that mosquitoes only detects carbon dioxides that our skin pores&nbsp;and breath emits. They don't have those super high tech heat sensors or was it called a thermal goggles, no, no shiats like that. Products like insect/mossies repellents sprayed onto the skins prevents CO2 from emitting into the air. really effective! I've seen a wandering mossie buzzing close by my left arm confused whether or not to land on its land of milk and honey.. but hessitated and landed on my shirt (where I didn't spray anything on it) to meet its death.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Great! Now that rain has&nbsp;subsided,&nbsp;firewoods were wet and&nbsp;we can't start a fire! How can we&nbsp;have dinner? Soon I realized that the woods were wet on the outside&nbsp;but dry on the inside so I began splitting them&nbsp;using a 20" axe and viol, we made  FIRE!!   &nbsp;  Kevin drove Josephine, Mariata, and I to&nbsp;Waskesiu's town for shower. We left at 20:40. Just 3 minutes before we arrived town&nbsp;four of us got the opportunity to catch the breath-taking sunset on the&nbsp;horizon of Waskesiu's lake.&nbsp;I asked Kevin to pull over so that I could capture that rare moment. It reminds me of&nbsp;some arts we&nbsp;used to draw&nbsp;during our elementary years&nbsp;in schools where the bright orangy-red sun sinking down into the sea&nbsp;or behind some mountaineous humps or both. The reflections of the sun on the water is not missed too.&nbsp;The sensation was so... oh, so wonderful! Magical if I can say?  Anyway, the shower facilities&nbsp;in town were closed. We arrived 20 minutes late. So, I suggested that we sneaked into another campsite that has shower facilities.&nbsp;That campsite is electrified, but ours&nbsp;are not. Mission accomplised! Feel&nbsp;so refreshing!  &nbsp;  It was already dark&nbsp;then. It was 22:00.&nbsp;When we were back at the campsite, all were already gathered around the hibachi warming up, singing and having fun.  &nbsp;  By midnight, most&nbsp;have gone to bed. Those&nbsp;who were still up were:  Jotham, Leonard, Jean, Char Mei, and I.  Leonard, weilding his digital camera, and I decided to&nbsp;head&nbsp;out to the lake nearby (~2 minutes walk) to be away from the trees and to get a better view of stars.  urlLink The Big Dipper (Ursa Majora)  was really, really big&nbsp;in the clear dark skies.&nbsp;&nbsp;   We&nbsp;walked down several steps in half a circle before&nbsp;we came to a landing. It was low tide then and it was 01:40. The second we landed on the platform and looked up the skies (that's what we were there for anyway), we&nbsp;beheld&nbsp;something else we never would have thought we'd see. Jotham, Leonard, and I were&nbsp;" urlLink Taken away " in spirit just by looking&nbsp;ahead of us. We were facing north&nbsp;as Polaris was just right above and in front of us. For 30 minutes,&nbsp;Leonard and I rushed each other for the one tripod we brought with us taking turns shooting at the amazing showdown on earth --  urlLink Aurora Borealis &nbsp;or commonly known as the Northern Lights.  &nbsp;  Not wanting&nbsp;the other 2&nbsp;lass to miss the show, we decided to call them, who&nbsp;I believe&nbsp;are still playing the&nbsp;guitar and singing around the hibachi, over to join us to watch the show.  &nbsp;  We stayed up till 03:15 before hitting the&nbsp;sacks.  &nbsp;   Sunday, July 18, 2004 &nbsp;  More meat for breakfast. They have, I think, done quite a good job in taking care of the food part. We were all fed quite well and energized for the day's activities. So, kudos to those who have prepared and thought out for the meals.  &nbsp;  Packed and headed out to town by 12:30noon. Most of us went into the water. The sun was at its peak heat and I could literally feel it scorching on my skins as though I have my arms just over the electric stove set on max temperature. Well, guess what? For the first time in Canada, I got sun burn. I had one yesterday but this time I thought I could really want to burn myself. Frolicking under the heat of the sun at the beach and later sun bath for 40 mins did a lot of burning. I'm now... an African Chinese!  &nbsp;  Left Waskesiu at 16:10. Still hot! To be in the van with only a window that opens a crack is stifling and perhaps a torture!  &nbsp;  Had good dinner at the Mandarin Restaurant when we arrived Saskatoon.  &nbsp;  That's that!  The pictures of this trip are up next. They are photoblogged!             
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Co-worker or Scott's colleague for Spring/Summer 2004 That wasn't nice of me that I didn't look into your eyes and initiated conversation This is not the usual gesture I'd offer but I was busy You seemed too familiar as though I have known you for a long time, a connection I was busy and time was my constraint but I couldn't steal some off it to be with you... and Scott.  We have not really got to know each other although that idea would have been a blast If this scares you, know that I am frigthened as much as you because I dont wanna believe there is an attraction between us. Let it something that I can think of as a precursor of my higher self-esteem; live and let love, let love be liberator -- that which liberates me from my insanity to even write this out.  Ah! The power of atractions and love! they both never cease to amaze me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by ... the table?? : At Chelsea's place after stuffing ourselves with pizza and watched an independant movie... kinda silly. From left to right by head queues: Me Myself, Ben, Sylvia, Canaan, Scott, and Chelsea. Look!! All of us have clean feets!! Except... lots of shiats going around here. beware, don't step on one. hehe  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: This was the look I got when I asked her "I want you to be my nude model". That look is her knock-out look for a "yes!".  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan: We're in the pub crawl bus. Right behind me is Ben. And right behind the Scary Movie ghost (Scott) is Chelsea. The bus is rocking!! The party ambience in the bus is, however, surprisingly even greater than in pubs.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Ben: Dont steal shots, Ben! Ask and you shall receive! Tango for Ben .. mm-mmh!! Hey, is that a two-headed guy?! Oh my god!! It is!! It is!! The world has evolved! Aaahhhh!! Bio-mutations have begun! Flee your lives! Save yourself!!!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Ben: Doing the 2-steps dancing with Rochelle, Ben stole a shot of us having fun. I couldn't keep up with her, man, she's good!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by ...the table? : From 7 o'clock, Lindsy, Canaan, Keane, Andrew, Myself, and Sylvia at the Longbench (?) pub; plays mostly country musics.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Keane: Karen and drunken Jordan being silly on stage. I believe Jordan was kneeling down on one knee while the other bended on a right angle like stretching your hamstring muscle before working out.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Andrew: Sexy lass Lindsy, myself looking good, and infantry Keane Ooo-ooh (keey-ann Oooo-oh) at The Pat.  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Lindsy: Woahh!! This is Lindsy's self-portrait. She did it again -- took the camera away from from Keane's possession and "showed" him how to use the camera in the most proper way. It does look proper though!! That would mean that all guys sucks at using camera! Heyyy, I remember I TOO have cleavege! but without the laces like she does... *winks!*  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Lindsy: Rochelle and I at The Pat on 1st Ave, the place where we began our Pub Crawl. Such a sweet girl she is! Strong and atheletic build... beware!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Shot by Keane: Myself & Chealsea, inclined towards Sylvia for a trio shot. Sylvia wanted a small pop but she got a mini jug of coke and rum. Don't I just have that  urlLink "Chow Yunfatt"  look?? hehe!  Photoblogged!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan on Tv Mode for 15 seconds (Canon PowerShot A70): I lay down on the grass of the park just opposite Brunskill High School (illustrated) along Wiggins Avenue gazing into the azure skies full of random activities. Notice the different color streaks.  Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan on Tv Mode for 15 seconds (Canon PowerShot A70): The camera was tilted at >120 degrees on a concrete block. I believe most pictures are shaky, therefore, would appear to be blurry but at an acceptable level.  Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Over looking the aurora beyond Saskatoon's tallest building--old folks home.  Photoblogged!!       urlLink    This one was totally brutal and is a killer! It almost killed me by running and dancing its streaks in multicolor and at speed of light in swivel for a few seconds and then disappears into thin air. This is the best of the best show!  Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Laid on my back and shot this picture! Sometimes flashes work better!  Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan on Tv Mode for 15 seconds (Canon PowerShot A70).  Photoblogged!!       urlLink    Shot by Shutterdan on Tv Mode for 15 seconds (Canon PowerShot A70)  Photoblogged!!    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
             Gee, there "is" a time limit to record your message, which I good to keep you from floating and blabbling away till sunrise.
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Arrived Kuala Lumpur International Airport on Friday 13:30 local time. My three "Heavy Load" tagged baggages did not come out until most passengers from the same flight as me has claimed theirs and went home. I must be really heavy for those weaklings down there in the baggage areas of the airport.  Anyway, I gave Eelynn and Michelle a surprise visit on Sunday and they almost had their pants down. There are a few more people waiting for their goodies.  Malaysia is nice and hot. There have been changes since I left. New roads, highways and freeways, climate changes (not too much of a difference) and technology!! I got myself a  urlLink Nokia 6600  and it is totally cool and complicated; so complicated that I realize how tech unsavvy I am or perhaps I've fallen too far back... by living in Canada. To have a cellphone in canada is like a curse so they say. I'm not sure for what apparent reasons though so I'll just leave it be.  Right now I am already missing the wintery days. My nose seems to be letting me know a lot of things it didn't tell me back in Canada. It's a little more runny now than before and the humidity here is to be blamed. I miss the clear blue skies in Canada, the clean air, Jill, Ben, Scott, Kate, Sally Zhao, Charmei (fried noodles),  urlLink my university , and mostly My Brother.  Looking forward to colder days ahead of me. How I wish I'm going through days (or nights) of 30 degrees below zero!! Fantasizing of snowboarding down the Alps, it used tobe be the Rockies.  Oh, I got laid in Hong Kong while waiting for my connecting flight. It was a blast! 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>