<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gentle, fragile, and silky to the touch - you close your eyes, and slowly inhale deeply. The fragrance pulls your mind to fields where daydreams roam, clouds float like foam on invisible waves, and the wind sweeps through your hair like the fingers of a lover. For just one moment reality succumbs to the dream - the dream often smothered under the noise and bustle of everyday life. In those fleeting moments you realize that the dream may not be just a frigment of your imagination; rather, it could be a possibility. Then, suddenly, it comes to an abrupt stop, sending the dream flying through the air like a casualty of an accident. You pricked your finger. Your eyes flashed open as drops of blood fell on the silky petals smearing the artistic masterpiece of the rose - your dream is over. One thorn is sometimes all that is needed to kill a dream.     
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the beginning we were created to live forever.      What a truth. I guess most people don't think about that much, but if you do, it brings up all sorts of things to ponder.   If we were to live forever today would we take the time necessary to be a friend to someone like we should? I mean, we'd have the time right?   If we were to live forever today would we take the time to say the things we always wanted to say, or would we even need to?  If we were to live forever today would we work so hard? After all, there wouldn't be a need for retirement, right?  If we were to live forever today: * there'd be no retirement homes * there'd be no funerals * there'd be no graveyards * there'd be less wars (I mean, if no one died, why fight?) * family reunions would be HUGE * no one would get an inheritance * we'd all be antiques eventually * artists would be noticed during their life instead of after their death * Elvis would still be around (but maybe "all shook up") * there'd be no murders and less prisons * there'd be less of a police force * George Bush would know that BinLaden wasn't dead for sure * our families would get REALLY sick of us * no one could afford Christmas time * no one could afford all the birthdays * everyone would have time to go to college, get a masters, a PhD, etc * a house loans would be longer * we could all have antique cars * women would never have to worry about someone asking them how old they are * we could all have ETERNAL life without worrying how * we'd have the time to do the things we always regretted not doing * We'd end up changing a lot of diapers over the course of eternity * where would we all fit?
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Inside of each of us is a soul, a friend, a lover, a unique individual - all waiting to be released. Over our lifetime we release a little bit of ourselves out to those around us, and occassionally we open the door wide to a friend. But that door opens and it shuts - and sometimes it even slams. There are those who have come to our doors and tried to turn the handle, but it was locked, and no matter how much they wanted in, they didn't have the key to open the door. They may knock, they may call or they may beat at the door for a time, but eventually, if it's not opened, they will walk away. Were they a stranger? Were they a pesky neighbor or nagging family member? Were they a friend turned traitor? Why was the door not opened? Why was the door closed to begin with? We all have doors to our lives. These doors guard us - protect us. They keep the world out, or ... maybe, they just keep us in. Door have hinges and were made to be opened. A closed door of yesterday doesn't mean it has to be closed today. Can we open the door again? Can we trust?   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       	 		 		 This is one of my favorite photos I've taken. There's something about it that makes me feel safe. Maybe it's how the branches seem to reach out for you and pull you inside its branches where you won't fall. Maybe it's because it makes me feel like I can sit up there and look down on the world and not be interrupted... I don't know. 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Beckoning 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink cclabaugh .			 		 	  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not too long ago I took my six year old son to a nearby lake where we had planned on feeding the ducks. Really, I just wanted to spend some time with him and take some more photos. He was more than happy to go with me and excitedly fetched our oldest bag of bread from our homemade bread keeper (our microwave.)   When we got to the lake and began our descent down the ledge to the water I noticed a piece of bread stuck on a nearby tree branch. I thought that a bit odd, but interesting. The further we went, the more bread we seen splattered on tree branches like marshallows on stick.          It didn't take us long to realize why such a sight met our eyes. The edges of the water were filled with floating bread slices, soaked through but not submerged. You'd think with bread so pourous that it would immediately sink. The ducks were quite oblivious to these floating lily pads of dough as they wandered aimlessly around them, not even attempting to nip at them.   Great! So much for our excursion, I thought. My heart was sinking with the thought of how to explain this to my son, who was happily throwing dough balls into the water, hoping to entice the drifters closer where he could pet them. I tried to tell him that they weren't hungry but he didn't really even pay me any mind. He was off in his little world, playing pitch and catch with his new little friends. You would have thought he would have gotten bored quite fast, but all it would take is just one duck to occassionally catch his little dough ball and he was set to go another inning. So, I just decided to root him on.   It wasn't long before his dough balls changed into rocks and pebbles and sticks. If it was able to be picked up, he would throw it. I remembered those days of when I was young. Everything smelled so clean and fresh, and all you really cared about was just having a good time your own little world of make-believe. I envied him, as I glanced at my watch, knowing dinner was beckoning me home.   Before we left I spied this little bush off to the side by some trees that were laying in the water. It didn't have any leaves at all, it just sort of stood there, naked in the early spring sun. But was caught my eye was not its nakedness, but it's lack thereof; it was covered in more bread slices, on almost every branch. I just stopped and looked at it, amazed by the thoughts that had created such a masterpiece.   For a moment, I felt like I had been the one to put each of those slices on it. I felt proud, as if it had been my greatest work of art. Then, I remembered that it wasn't mine at all. I never touched it, I never carried the bread, and I never even thought about doing it... yet, I felt like I had. So, with a smile on my face, I snapped another picture, and grabbing my son by the arm, we left hand in hand... quite happy with our day.   Life. Sometimes you just have to take the time to see it.     
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This past weekend I saw the movie "The Day After Tomorrow." It was a fairly good disaster movie due to global warming. It showed so many lives lost and suffering. Then over Memorial Day weekend my mind wandered onto those who lost their lives in the war and 911. The effects of such things are devastating. Then I thought, how much more devastating it is going to be when the Lord returns and thousands are missing. Lives will be lost in the process and though people will try to explain what happened, they will never all agree. I would imagine that the emotional toll of losing friends and family and knowing you were left behind (if you believe in the rapture) will be tramatic. I don't think it will stop there. How will people cope? How many will take their lives in the process? How many outbursts of anger and violence will it ensue? Or, will this bring the anti-christ - the peace-maker - to the scene? Will it just be considered another terrorist attack? We never know, but watching such movies and recalling past disasters makes one wonder what the next devastation will bring.   I still cry at the lives lost at 911. I watched another memorial video last night that a church in GA did for 911. To see the towers falling again just made me want to close my eyes and pretend it never happened rather than to remember it really did. I felt guilty because as I watched it happen on television that day, I was alive while hundreds were being killed at that very instance. Hundreds would never again see their families, never laugh again, never hug a loved-one, never get to pay their final respects, and never have another chance to have their soul saved. I am alive today, and yet I still find myself taking life for granted at times, and forgetting to really LIVE it today like there was no tomorrow.   We should LIVE, with everything inside of us... if not for us, then for THEM, who will never have another chance to do so themselves.                   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was so beautiful when I left for work this morning. The temperature was at that perfect place where you feel like you and the wind are one - not hot and not cold. It would have been great to just go for a walk along a country path somewhere and end up forgetting about the rest of the day while you found a creek and let the water lap between your toes. I remember doing that as a kid. I loved it then, but I think I didn't know exactly what to appreciate about it then. When we are kids we just want to grow up but now that I am, I wish I were a kid again. It seems like we live so much of our lives for tomorrow without appreciating what we have today. If reincarnation were real, I would imagine that many of us would lead better second lives if we could remember the first. But then again, we are human, so who knows what we'd do.  I hope today, after I have performed my daily duties here at work and all the tasking and phone calls have ceased, that I can go home and grab my kids and find a way to appreciate them and life together; because one day it's going to be too late to do so.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Waking up this morning my thoughts went to an old song we used to sing in church years ago:   "I am blessed" "I am blessed" "Every day that I live I am blessed" "When I wake up in the morning" "Or I lay my head to rest" "I am blessed" "I am blessed"   It's hard to sing those words when you are going through troubles and trials in your life. Nothing feels blessed when your heart is aching. Yet, no truer words have been sang. No matter how bad things get for us, we are still blessed, as long as we have breath in our lungs to breathe. I AM blessed today. I am blessed because I'm living. I am blessed because my husband and children are living. I am blessed because I have a house over my head, food in my cupboards, a vehicle to drive, clothes upon my back, and health in my body. I am blessed because I can see the sky today while others are in prison, in mental wards, in detention homes, or hospitals. I am blessed today because I am free and sitting here typing this while others are trapped in their minds, seduced by the world, unable to cope, unable to think straight, unable to comprehend, and unable to escape addiction. I am blessed because I'm not what I used to be. I am blessed because I could be dead, I could be in prison, I could be addicted, I could be divorced, I could be alone, I could be sick, I could be homeless, I could be lost, or I could be dead.   Compared to what I could be, I AM completely, absolutely, wholey, and entirely blessed. What right do I have to question the Lord about anything in my life? If a lost, homeless alcoholic on the street could see my life, would he or she have a better understanding of being blessed than I do? Perhaps.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was reading a newspaper article this morning on a local sheriff who has the  job  of disposing of unclaimed bodies. I can't imagine being someone who died and not having at least one person in my life who would take care of burying me. Of course, I know that they don't always find people that know you, but the article mentioned how they did find many of the relatives. Unfortunately, these people would not take the effort in many cases to accept responsibility. Some didn't have the money, and others were just upset at the deceased person; I can understand some of it. But what a sad thing to go out of this world with no one lamenting or appreciating  your life.   I hope that I live my life in such a way that people will WANT to remember me after I'm gone. If not, then what was the point of living?       urlLink https://gx.gallup.com/gsatenant.gx 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, call me cruel, call me insensitive or call me whatever you want, but this 'give-me-everything-for-free' mentality in America lately is getting out of hand. Read the link provided to read one of our local news articles on a redevelopment project here:    urlLink http://home.hamptonroads.com/stories/story.cfm?story=71348&ran=142912   It really irritates me that people today think that they are owed everything, and if they are inconvenienced in any way that the government - and therefore you and me - should pay for it. Ok, it's like this... The new buyer of this land gave the people living there six months to move. Six MONTHS! Now, in six months I'm sure that I could find a place to live. It may not be a fun experience, and yes, it may inconvenience me but I think I could handle it without losing my mind over it. These people expect to receive food, clothing and money just because they were asked to move? Come on! There are people living out on the street without any homes, food or clothing whatsoever and no one is writing about THAT in the paper!  How ridiculous that our society has forgotten the good ole rules about hard work, honest living, and respect for themselves. A few decades ago most people would have just accepted the fact that they had to move and they would have done something about it; after all, it's LIFE! They would have been out on the streets, not with their hand out, but looking for a new home and not expecting everyone else to do it for them. Why has America accepted the idea that it's ok to be lazy? Why has America accepted that people have a right to get everything for free while others are working hard to provide for themselves?   It irritates me to no end to see how low we have stooped to cover our laziness. Every time we don't like something we find a way to sue for it, claiming we are INCONVIENCED and should be compensated for it. Let me ask you one question - what would America be today if our founding fathers had taken on that attitude? Our country was built on blood, sweat and tears, not court cases, freebies, and handouts. Men died to win our freedom, they didn't sue anyone for it. Men and women worked the land to provide food, shelter and clothing for their families; they didn't sit on the street corners protesting how unfair it was that someone else didn't do it for them.  I AM a proud American, but I wish that America still stood for what it used to stand for - honest living, hard work, freedom, and self-respect. Pursuit of happiness is now seen as "what-can-I-get-for-free" and "how-can-I-whatever-I-want," because after all, that is what makes me happy. Our founding fathers would be disgraced if they could see what their hard work turned into.   America... where is your roots? America, where is your honesty? America, where is blood, sweat, and tears that made you great? America, where is the self-respect that made men and women honorable?   There is a phrase that has been spoken millions of time, and I reiterate it again here. If you can't stand the heat, then get out of the kitchen. But let me rephrase that for you people who expect everything for free... If you can't stand LIFE, then get out of America. Let our country go back to what made it great to begin with.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I read this today on  urlLink http://www.thisistrue.com  and had to share it. --------------------- "A construction worker in Lancaster, Calif., is expected to make a full recovery after accidentally being shot in the head with a nail gun -- six times. Three of the nails penetrated his brain; one entered his spinal column, but luckily not his spinal cord. Witnesses say Isidro Mejia, 39, fell from the roof of the house he was building onto another worker who was using the gun below. "The guy holding the nail gun was grabbing to keep from falling, and just gripped tighter on the trigger," said a Los Angeles County sheriff's investigator. "It's a nail gun they use for framing. It can drive nails through 2-by-4s." (Los Angeles Times) ...It's the first time L.A. cops have said it: a Mexican guy really was framed."      
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNN.com - Madonna reinvents herself as Esther - Jun 17, 2004    Good grief! How pathetic. Here she is, touting about she's changing her values, and then she turns around and says, ""I did spend, you know, at least a decade taking my clothes off and being photographed, saying bad words on TV, and, you know, that sort of thing," she told ABC's Cynthia McFadden. "I don't regret it, but it's just ... I mean everybody takes their clothes off now."   I don't get it. She says, "If it's traditional to be a decent human being, then I'm traditional,"  and then expects the world to think that she's decent????????? Well, maybe in the world's eyes she is but she's not going to get very far in the religious world like that. You can't take your clothes off, not be sorry, and then expect to be as the image of Esther. Maybe she's studied Jewish beliefs but she needs to study the Bible. Having a spiritual name doesn't make you spiritual. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In progress: -------------- Linger Still  one rose attention captured life radiates allures, beckons  attention captured I take it softly allures, beckons I hold it close  I take it softly breathe it in I hold it close mine forever  breathe it in now it’s mine  mine forever then laughed the wind  now it’s mine breezes captured then laughed the wind my flower stolen  breezes captured floats away my flower stolen to another  floats away fallen, fallen to another trodden, crushed  fallen, fallen I search, I find trodden, crushed my beauty gone  I search, I find petals broken trodden, crushed uncaring feet  petals broken I hold remains uncaring feet pass me by  I hold remains hopes and dreams pass me by I breathe them in  hopes and dreams can never die I breathe them in they linger still 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A few years ago, early in the morning, I was getting ready to go to work and looking out of my window I seen the field nearby. It was covered with a thick fog, very close to the ground. It looked like a wooly blanket, and far enough off the ground to crawl under. It was very beautiful and mysterious at the same time. You just felt safe looking at it and wanted to go to it, even if just to walk inside.  As I stood there admiring it the Lord, in the strange way that He does sometimes, spoke to me and said that His love for me was just like that fog; thick, and safe. His love wraps around me like the fog circles around our feet, and though we may not see it 24hrs a day, it's there at times to remind us He's never left us.  Sometimes in my mind I think that I have to find ways to earn the love of God. But that morning He spoke to me, and shared His love with me and I didn't do anything at all. I can't earn His love; I'm still trying to understand that.     urlLink    photo source   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know, sometimes having friends is really crazy. I think I did something to upset one of my friends recently and really have no idea what it was. Actually, we are just becoming good friends, and I was really hoping it would work out. It has taken me a long time to trust someone as a close friend again and I thought... well maybe...   My first instinct is to stop trying. I mean, it seems easier to walk away than to try to force the issue, right? My prior thinking would have convinced me that if it isn't easy than it isn't meant to be. My mind still tells me that, but not my heart.  It just seems that relationships can become so complicated sometimes that it makes you want to pretend they don't really exist. After all, you could go on about your life and have a whole lot less stress without all the hassle, right? Yes, but then life would be empty, and you'd feel lost and unattached. I'm certain that that's not any better.  I hate uncertainty, but at least there's always a possibility and that makes it worth trying.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I remember the lazy days of summer, when all you had to worry about was how you were going to spend your day playing and goofing off. I probably rode my bike a few hundred miles back then. It's funny though, how the older you get the more you relish those days, when all you wanted back then was to grow up.   Now, I'm not a child anymore. My life is filled with repsonsibilities, a career, a family and a home. Rarely do I find the days where I just spend them doing nothing productive; though I make myself sometimes. There was something special about being a kid. Everything seemed so magical and if it didn't somehow you could make it seem that way with your imagination.   I'm not sure why it is when people grow up that they feel they have to grow out of that creative world. I love to imagine, and moreso to investigate life and discover new things.   When my boys grow up, I want them to see those things in life and not just responsibility. I don't want them to think that playing around is just for children. I want them to be responsible, but still alive and vibrant.   If we can't imagine, if we can't dream, if we can't make believe anymore, than what good did growing up do us?   I don't know what these boys will become, but I sure imagine.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        My sweetie!  I took this photo at the Chrysler Museum of Art, June 12,2004. He is a wonderful man that I've been married to for almost fifteen years now. I can't say that it's always been easy, but today we are closer than we've ever been before, and better friends.   It takes two people to make a marriage works. There were a few times I didn't do as much as I could, and neither did he. If I wanted to I could linger on all the bad moments we had and use them as leverage for an attitude of bitterness, but then, I look on my own life and see he could the same. Thankfully, neither of us are like that. We love each other, and we even LIKE we other. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sunday evening we had a guest speaker at our church, though his name has escape my mind. He started preaching on faith and ended up preaching on how we need to let God change our thinking. I completely agreed with him; we all need this and I've prayed it fervently so many times.   As he was preaching, he started mentioning people he knew who had things so much worse than some of us. Some of them overcame while others did not. He mentioned how we often look at God like we do our own father. I have said that myself many times, and I do believe that it's true. As he was talking though, the more he said the more I wanted to cry. I felt foolish, and though I really tried not to cry I couldn't help but do so.   I'm not sure what it was that upset me so much. I think some of his examples of how people have been hurt, abused, etc in their lives struck home a little too much. I have experience so much trouble in my life, things that most of my friends don't even know about, yet, I've been able to overcome most of them. You would think that once you overcome them and you allow the wound to heal over that it wouldn't hurt anymore, but sometimes it still does.   I know that I look at God like I've looked at others. My mother was married six times, and my own father wants nothing to do with me. I've never had a close relationship with any of them, and not even her. For me, I find it difficult to understand sometimes how to have that perfect and proper relationship with God when I never had it with my own family. I don't know what a real, close father is like. I feel awkward sometimes feeling that I want to even be that close to Him. Subconsciously I think He wants nothing to do with me, like my own father does not. I feel like I have to find ways to please Him, so He'll like me, like I have had to do with my mother.   I have come so far, but I've never quite arrived. Honestly, I don't know if I, or anyone else, ever will. We all like to feel that we have it all together. We all like to act like we are perfect and don't have any problems, hurts, or even questions. But I do. I don't voice to others because they are my own. I would be a liar if I said I was just full of absolute faith and always trusted God. I'm learning to, but I don't always succeed at it.   I don't think having questions or having problems makes you weak, or any less of a person. I think it makes you real. We can learn from our experiences in life, and we definitely should help others, but we should never assume that we know more, are better than, or have risen above anyone else. Inside of all of us, is a silent person - our conscious, and who we really are. If we could read each other's thought, or know each other's conscious, I think that the majority of us would look at each other differently.   I'm so far from perfect, but at least I'm trying.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We had drama again last night - dowel rod & dramatization. I'm not sure why some of the members come. I know in they are interested and think it's fun (at times anyway) but it doesn't seem like too many have a passion for the things they are involved in.   As their director I know that I have to have the greatest passion, and I need to stir it up in them, but frankly, it's nearly impossible sometimes. They just come and sit there expecting me to do all the work for them. So, I thought I'd try something. Before we got started on the new piece for the 4th of July we are doing, I had my sound tech play a song which they listened to. Then, they had to break up into groups, or singly, and come up with dramatized actions or dowel rod movements to that song. Of course they didn't like it; they never like it when I put them on the spot. But, they actually came up with some decent ideas. It was good to see them use their brains and creativity. I just wish they'd take those things and use some of it on their own to enhance their talents without me forcing them.   I also gave them an assignment for our next meeting. THey have to find their own song and come up with a dramatized or dowel rod piece to it, all by themselves. I can teach them all day long but if they never study or practice on their own, or use their own ideas, they will never challenge themselves and thereby grow their talent.   In the bible it tells us the parable of the Talents, and how God honored the one who took the talent he was given and he multiplied it. I guess that's what I try to do in my own life, and what I hope to instill in them as well. I never want to be satisfied doing or even knowing the amount of things I know and do now. I'm always looking for new things or different ideas or viewpoints. I like to try things and figure things out. I love to learn. I think that's honorable to God, because the Bible teaches us how God doesn't like lazy people.  I don't know what it's going to be like in heaven, but I hope that when we get there we will have the same opportunities to learn, to explore, to experiment, etc. For me, it's never enough - I always want to learn more.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is my son, Ethan Grant Clabaugh       At six years old you would think that all he would think of would be playing on his XBox, building with LEGOs or riding his bike, but this little guy is much deeper than that. From the time he was born we have had a very close connection. We laugh together, cry together, play together, and sing together. During times when I have had a tearsome or stressful day he will come along and sit with me, and look deep into my eyes while barging into my choatic world with his simple smile. Sometimes he looks so deep into myself that for a few moments everything seems to stand still, letting us enjoy another moment in suspended time. He just has this way of touching me like no one else but God can.   While I was gone on my trip to Californina, he cried several times, missing me and wishing I were home. He was worried; worried that something bad would happen to me like my plane crashing. I would talk to him on the phone and I could tell that he was trying not to cry.   When I was pregnant with him I remember wishing strongly that I would have a little girl; I already had a boy, Zachary. When I had my ultrasound and was told it was a boy, I stifled a cry and refused to believe that anything but my hopes were correct. I knew they were right. I knew I was wrong, but I refused to accept it. For me, anything was still possible.  Months later brought me crying in pain in the hospital, as my mind continued to try to convince my spirit that I would have a little girl. The moment came that I delivered him and when the doctor told me it was a boy, I cried with disappointment and a broken faith. But then, they laid him on my chest, all 10lbs, 6.5 oz of him, and in one moment all that sorrow went away as I held him for the first time. Our skin touched each other and that's all it took - him and I, together; mother and child. He was all I needed.  Sometimes when I think of it today I feel bad that I ever cried those tears. He has been everything that I needed to make me feel complete. We've shared more joys than I would ever want to replace with anyone else. I love my boys, both of them. My oldest son will always be my firstborn, and I love him dearly. But my youngest son I desperately needed, and I never realized how much.   I pray that I can be the type of mother to my sons that they can always be proud of and will want in their lives. I want to be a strength for them, and a source of hope, and help, and especially love. One day, some other woman will enter their lives and will fill them with love that they never knew, but I know... the love of a mother can never be replaced, just as the love of a son can never be replaced in the heart of a mother.   I love you Ethan and Zachary.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I just got back from the drama conference in Hanford, CA. I had a really good time during the 2 1/2 days of training and performances. I taught two classes myself, "Organizing a Drama Department" and "Acting 101", both of which turned out well. I think that overall we watched over 25 performances, most of which were very good. There were a few that I didn't really care for, but it was still interesting to see how people use their creativity in different ways.   There were more people at this conference than attend the East Coast CODE conference. I believe some of it has to do with advertising, which the East Coast representative doesn't do much of, while the rest is because California is more drama oriented than our churches here. It was good to see so many interested.  The drama group there in Hanford put on a full length production Friday night called "The Wardrobe," which was based off of C.S. Lewis' "The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe." He changed the production a bit to give it a Pentecostal flavor and to enhance the gospel message in it that C.S. Lewis intracately interwove into it. I thought it was fabulous! The four main characters were all played by children and youth, who did an absolute fabulous job. The lion was played by an adult of course. I didn't think he was as convincing as the rest and he seemed a bit unsure of himself, but nonetheless, I thoroughly enjoyed it. I would love to do that play here myself, but I think I'd have to use mostly adults in it.  I talked to Howi Tiller ( urlLink http://www.howitiller.com ) about the lack of promotion for the East coast conference. He said he was not at all opposed to moving it to here in Norfolk. So, we're going to see what happens during the conference next month and then he'll make his decision whether to move it next here next year or not. In a way I hope they do because they'll probably get a better response, but it would be alot of work for us. We shall see...  The rest of my trip was less than I had hoped for. I had the plane trip from hades both there and back. Our departing flight was cancelled, then rescheduled with three flights instead of two. The first flight had mechanical malfunctions, the second flight had mechanical malfunctions which left us stranded on the tarmack for two hours, and then we missed our third flight, which had to be rescheduled three hours later. By the time we arrived in California we were six hours late. So, there went our touring time for that day. My flight home was delayed due to weather, so my second flight was missed and I had to reschedule another flight for three hours later. ARGH!   We were supposed to get to see San Francisco and go visit the Stockton, CA campus, church and bookstore, but we never got a chance to. The rest of our time there was spent with friends of my friend whom I went with. She had a ton of friends to visit, which was ok, but I didn't know any of them. We spent Sunday  going to her old church, again which I knew no one at.   The trip was pretty terrible except for the conference. If I go again, I'll plan on getting my own car and go sightseeing or something besides hanging out with my friends acquaintances. I can't believe I was in California for all those days and didn't get to see anything. At least the place we stayed after the conference was interesting to take pictures of. I'll have to post some of them in the next few days.         
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm thinking of how wonderful God is. We all know that God loves us and see us as special in His sight, but so few of us really believe it. We question ourselves, we question God, we question everything, even if just inside where no one can hear us. We look at our lives through everyone else's eyes. We view our faults as more important than our successes or good qualities. The thing about God is this: He always sees us for our good, or else His mercy and grace would have failed a long time ago. He sees things in us that we can't understand, conceive of, or even sometimes believe. I absolutely believe that through God we really can do anything. We each have desires living in the depths of our soul that are screaming to be let out, but we're scared and so we just stifle it, as if it's something bad or something wrong. Yet, we still entertain it, because silently we believe in it and hope in it.   God is wanting to do some awesome things in our lives, but we're just all so afraid sometimes. He's screaming for us to let Him, and we're screaming to be let go, yet holding on to the past, holding on to other people's viewpoints and ideas, and holding on to boundaries that others have set for us. It's sad, in reality, to know what we are possible of doing, yet never do.  If we REALLY believed that God wanted to use us, then just imagine what we would do.
     

    
</post>


<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'd like to read you paper, too, if you don't mind. Did you include anything about tv watchin' chickens?  :-)   Cindy
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I turned in a research paper for my college class. The topic was to be something on a local issue and it also had to be persuasive in nature. I chose PETA's (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) latest campaign against KFC restaurants using their  "Bloody Buckets."  If you care to read about it in case you haven't heard, visit:  urlLink http://www.kfccruelty.com . Though their cause is a good one how they are going about it is just so ridiculous. Anyway, I just found out today that I have to take that same topic and make it into a poem. Hmm... ;) When I'm done I'll try to remember to post it here... if I'm not too "CHICKEN" of course! HA!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I saw you in the grocery store. I expected to be angry the first time I saw you,  but I wasn't.  I just wanted to rescue you from yourself and from all the lies you wanted me to believe, and that you believe yourself.  A wasted life... Dreams oppressed as  selfish. Goals oppressed as  vain.  Friendships lost because you were afraid to admit that you didn't hate me after I chose to leave the  lies, and move on to seek Real Peace.  It's different from the  "truth" that only benefits the teacher.  There is life beyond  those walls.   There is peace beyond  those lies.   There is hope beyond that fear.   All you need is the desire to  Move on, and not give up or go back no matter how hard it gets.  That's where I am now.  Moving On.   Cindy Smith 3/28/04
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rescued  My heart lies hot within me A tear rolls down face The cry within my throat demands freedom I let it go, but only a little at a time  Injustice taunts me It demands to be recognized I know it’s there But I try to ignore it  I search for hope Injustice provides no escape I look to the left and to the right But can see no way out  I am lost in the darkness I am enveloped by death Then a hand grabs a hold of mine I feel its security, its guidance  I look into the face of my six-year-old son His eyes and face smiling into mine “Mommy, I’ll never let you down” I know it’s not all true, but it is hope, and it rescues me  Colleen Clabaugh 3/1/04 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Below is a poem I found today that I wanted to share: -------------------------------------------------------- My Life's Journey   How do I convey my thoughts, my feelings. How can I make sense of this life, this confusion, this jumble of emotions? Can I bring to it all some depth, some meaning?   My mind is like a maze with no beginning, no middle, and no end. I turn every corner and meet a wall. Inside I am lost and alone. I need to find my way out. I must answer the voice crying out in my head. If I stay in this maze it will be my downfall.   Everyone wants a piece of me. I wonder -- is this my soul purpose --  to be a rock that they can chip away at? Is that my role? They take, take, take. There is not enough to go 'round. I am left incomplete. I am not whole.   The eyes are the windows to one's soul. Look deep into mine and tell me what you see. Is there a void? Is there emptiness, or is there a glimmer of something waiting to be set free?   I must not give up hope. I must let go. I cannot cling to the side forever in fear of drowning. I must let the tide carry me and not fight against the flow. I will hold my head high above the murky depths. I will not be weak. I shall keep on going, and eventually, I will find clear waters and the place I seek.   I will wait for you there, my friend. In my mind I will guide you through the journey of life, through the forest of torment, across the oceans of love, through the valleys of despair. And I will lead you to the path of self-discovery which will bring you to this place, this haven I speak of, and I will be waiting. I will be there.   -   Alex Meadows 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      by Colleen Clabaugh I am thirty four years old. For thirty four years I have enjoyed life, went the distance, laughed here and cried there... all for everyone else. I look at my life and see that I haven't really lived it for me at all, but for them - the other people in my life. Oh, I try to grab a few minutes here and there in a desperate attempt to retain my identity but those moments are fleeting and few. While I bask in the glory that those minutes give me I find myself being pulled out of them by the wishes that others demand of me. Smiles fade, laughter trails off and dreams awaken all too soon; reprimanding me for wasting time on such frivolous things. Like an obedient child I drop my head and sullenly go about my day, heeding the commands of Life with the "Yes, Maams, yes sirs, ok dears and right-aways of a worthless slave.   I'm enslaved to them, yet without shackles or whips. There's no one to hold me down and yet I can't seem to get away. My taskmasters are many, sending me in whirlwind of attempts to appease them all, and all at the same time. I know more about their lives than they seem to know about mine, and such is to be expected. To share myself would waste precious time.  In the midnight hours I find myself singing the forgotten hymns of hopes of deliverance. I convince myself that it won't be long before I am free. I smile in the darkness as my mind replays my dreams come true. I can almost feel freedom; I can almost smell it. I can almost taste how sweet my life will be when I no longer have a master. Then, I remember it's getting late and I hear morning coming in the background. My smile fades, and I pull the covers up to wipe away a tear as I obey Sleep's command. After all, I'm just wasting time.   I am enslaved to them - all of them - to Life. Yet, as I fall asleep, my mind goes over the task list that I will hand to another when I awake. And they will listen to me, with that same sullen sense of loss I know so well. They are my slave, and I am their master, and we all are pawns in the game of Life, living it for each other.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No, the nice thing about people coming by they would have to bring their own shell and pull up along side you, because your home is just big enough for you and your family.   If a sales person showed up you could kindly remind them you are a snail with a shell large enough for you and your family, and your shell does not have any extra storage space. So your purchase abilities is very limited.  This is almost the best part of being a snail, you would have a work shell (kind of like a cubbie or cubicle) and you pull up and park your house shell parallel to it when you are at work and when it is time to leave, your work stays with your work shell.  Now, this is the best part of being a snail, snails are all muscle they have no bones or spinal cord.  They never suffer from slip disc or rupture of a vertebrae.    I can see it now, beautiful earthtone draperies hanging from the living room windows of my new and improved shell of a house.  Wouldn't it be just great?
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cool concept.    Some Bad points:  1. You'd have to ALWAYS keep your house clean because people would always be coming by 2. You could never pretend that you weren't home if a sales person showed up 3. You could never just  t away from home'  4. You would always be taking work home with you 5. You'd have a tremendous chiropractor bill   Some Good points:  1. You could always have traveling dinner parties 2. If you ever forgot something at home, well... I guess you really couldn't 3. if you got sick, you wouldn't have any excuse to stay home from church 4. You'd always be home when the AC, plumbing or cable guy had to come by 5. There'd be no yard work to do 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wouldn't it  be something to be able to take your home with you everywhere you went?  No more worries about hotels being booked up at family vacation time.  No more inconveniences of relatives during family reunions.  You can change the size of your house as often as you change your coat if you like.  Snails have utilized this concept for years.  I say it is about time we follow suit. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      to flea or not to flea isn't THAT the real question?
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Great creativity Cindy! I never thought about writing about fleas before! HA! I guess sometimes you just get an 'itchin' to do something different, huh? :)
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just a funny poem.  Originally it had no title, and was more like a riddle, but everyone who read it said they couldn't figure it out, so I added the title.  Enjoy!  --Cindy  ________________________________________________________  Fleas   Hard to be without a home Seek out a forest in which to dwell Some red or blonde or brown   Scurry about the forest Play hide and go seek  Between the roots Hide well, or be plucked  From your warm, safe home  Watch out for the  Rapid fire rake That wants to strake you Off of the land  Can’t blame them You leave dirt all over You don’t start fires, but You do cause a burn And you always Always invite all of your friends  Some forests are at an  Advantage Other fight you on the Frontline Either way, they are sure to lick you.   Question: When your forests run Do you hang on tight and  say “Weeeeee”?  -Cindy Smith  2/24/04
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, I tried to anyway. It really wasn't a funny research paper so I didn't want the poem to be, although I could have made it. ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You pulled it off without humor. Love, love, love it!  Cindy
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To understand the poem you may have to visit the http://www.kfccruelty.com website to understand that this campaign is about: --------------------------------------------------------- When the Rumbling Ceased ( A poem about PETA’s “Bloody Bucket” Campaign)  Tummy Rumbles Thundering, thundering Drops fall You cry We leave – desperate Driving, driving Tummy rumbles Searching Spying, red and white ‘Round, ‘round it turns Nose perks Aroma entices Your eyes close Tummy rumbles, rumbles Stopping – we exit Hand-in-hand You smile; we walk Faster, faster now Aroma captures Senses alert Hand reaches Pushing, pushing One obstacle Almost there Hand on shoulder One man - stopping, stopping Red and white Put in your hands A bucket of bliss Hoping, hoping Tummy rumbles, thundering You look at me Smiling, smiling Thundering will cease In your bucket of bliss Man departs Bucket opens, opens Saliva festers Almost tasting You reach Grabbing, grabbing Pulling out You look Eyes widen Bigger, bigger Mouth falls open Chin quivers You look at me Crying, crying You scream, curdling You run Bucket falls Blood spilling, spilling Bones clatter Feathers fall You vomit Spewing, spewing I shudder, gasping I pinch myself in vain I run to you Faster, faster You sob; you quake I grab you, holding You beat my chest Harder, harder We leave I apologize You cry, unceasing Why, why? I explain You don’t understand Rumbling stops Nauseous, nauseous You close your eyes But the vision remains A bucket Bloody, bloody PETA’s campaign Cruelty versus cruelty Some things are hard to explain to a six year old  Colleen Clabaugh 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This quote from Roosevelt has always been one of my favorites. Enjoy ! -Cindy S.  _______________________________________________________  It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbled or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena; whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs and comes short again and again; who knows the great enthusiasms, the great devotions, and spends himself in a worthy cause; who, at the best, knows the triumph of high achievement; and who, at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who knew neither victory or defeat.   -Theodore Roosevelt
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a great poem that truly reflects each of our lives. ----------------------------------------------------------- A Work in Progress  I am a work in progress never to be completed always in a constant state of upgrade or maintenance   I will never achieve all my goals fulfill all my dreams or grasp everything I long to hold.   If I did, there would be nothing left to pursue.   Rather than be complete and have no future, no purpose I prefer to be a living breathing moving growing work in progress.   - Michelle True  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ahhh, Sis. Cook, now you've tempted me with the lifestyle of a snail.  To have a perfectly valid excuse to NOT to invite people inside my little shell...hhmmm...that does sound rather good, doesn't it?  Of course it would get rather lonely. If a friend can't come in then we wouldn't be able to sit together on the couch looking through old photo albums and laughing at how each other looked when we were younger.    I couldn't hold hands with my sister (who was visiting from out of town) while we reminisced about the family members that we both love and have lost.   While it's tempting (you have NO idea how tempting) to want to live inside my little shell all alone, I know that to do so would mean missing out on some of the greatest joys this life has to offer.    Thanks, Sis. Cook for this fun and VERY thought provoking post. I can easily see how you earned praises from one of the best poets this country has ever produced. :-) What else ya got? :-)  Cindy
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Colleen,   That is such a beautiful monologue.  I love that with writing we can express things that we would probably never just come out and say, but through our writings we can put those thoughts, ideas and feelings out there.   I have more to say to this, but I'll try and put it in an email tomorrow. This was really beautiful and touching.  Now, I'm going to dry my eyes and get back to studying. :-)  Cindy
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A Monologue By Colleen Clabaugh "Mirror, mirror on the wall, who is the ..."   I've wanted to ask those questions all of my life, but I cannot; I fear to. I hate them - mirrors that is - I hate them and I'm afraid of them. I'm afraid of what I see, and what I don't. I would rather throw a hurried glance it's way than to take a long, deep look at what it holds. I thought that mirrors were supposed to be for me to look inside, but instead, I find it looking inside of me, and what it shows me is frightening.   No, I'm not some sort of horrible person who society should detest. I'm not a convicted murderer, convict, abuser or addict. I'm not the most beautiful and I'm not the most wretched. I'm just me...all the MEs' in fact. I am who you want me to be when you are around. I am who she wants me to be at church, and I am who he wants me to be at home. When Sis. Sally comes around I am the perfect Sunday school teacher who is always prepared with her lesson and crafts. When Bro. Michaels comes around I am the hard working secretary who had the reports done before he asked. When Sis. Jane needed the sanctuary cleaned I was there. When Sis. Parish needed help with the baby showers I stayed until midnight decorating. When Bro. Samuel couldn't get his computer to work right, I jumped right in. When Sis. Smithers needed encouragment I picked up the telephone. When the Flowers family needed a miracle I fell to my knees.   I have become a professional at changing who I am. I can turn from saint to technician to teacher to hostess all in the same hour. And what else can I do... I am expected to. I don't mind, but sometimes, when I look in the mirror, I'm not sure who it is I am looking at anymore. I see the eyes of a worker, the mouth of a teacher, the hair of a mother and the mind of them all. But who am I really? If I were not able to perform any of those services, who would I be. Would anybody even be interested in me anymore? If I had no talents at all would anyone even notice me?  	I am afraid of the answer, so I never ask the mirror - I just ignore it. I only look long enough to switch my character for the next audience and then I go about my way, never looking long enough to see beyond my own image.  	One would think that a life like this would drive a person insane, and I agree. But there are two mirrors in my life that I own - one that I fear, and one that I love. The other mirror captivates me, and each time I look into it I am fixated on what I see. I see beauty and wonder that I never thought was possible. I see smiles where I used to see tears. I see color instead of black, white and every shade of gray. I see hope where I used to only see failure.   In my hands are two mirrors - your word, and God's word. In one I see who I am through your eyes and who the world expects me to be. In the other, I see who God sees...and who He knows I can be. It is easy to get lost in the one, trying to find myself midst the personas I've grown to service you with. It's easy to be afraid. It's easy to look away. But in the other, I never have to fear, because He doesn't ask me to be anything except who I am... His child. And I can ask any question I want, and He'll show me.   "Mirror, mirror in my hand,  who's the one you love so grand?"  He always responds with, "You." And I never have to search around to see who He was talking about.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is really nice what you wrote Cindy, I like writing about the water too.  I always have, it does something for me.  I can place my myself at water edge and I can hear the sounds, feel the moisture on my cheeks and smell the salt in the air.  Thank you for taking me to the sea shore.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cindy, I loved this posting. It makes me want to go to the ocean today. Too bad there aren't more beach places for us apostolics to go without all the immodesty. The reason I liked this was because you accurately depicted the type of things that go through our minds when we reminish like this. We don't even realize it most of the time. It's funny how such places can be so beautiful while they last, but they eventually have to go away like all things, leaving us with a small feeling of regret. I can only imagine what heaven will be like. I hope that it's like those days at the beach but without the time constraints that make us leave.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Very nice Cindy, and very, very true! We would all benefit in life if we learned to live by words such as these.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I usually try to avoid this much melodrama, but hey, we're all entitled once in a while, right?  :-) _________________________________________________________   The Wisdom of the Sea   When I walk along the shore and hear the soothing sound of the sea, I become almost at once nostalgic. I can look across the miles of warm brown sand and see a mother laughing as her child splashes in the water. I can see a father helping his baby to build what they both think to be the biggest, most beautiful sand castle ever created.   I can hear the laughter and feel the contentment of those bygone days, and I smile.  As I remember that these memories are just that – memories – I try to hold for just another second with my mind before allowing them to fade and be carried away by the quietly blowing breeze. But fade they do, and once again the shore is empty of the child laughing, of the child splashing. I turn my stare toward the open sea.   As the tears flow, and they often do, I can almost feel a hand on my shoulder as I look back toward the sand for one more glimpse of days that are gone now. We sometimes try to recapture, even if only for the length of one heartbeat, moments that passed away so long ago.   My eyes look toward the water and linger there, staring at the wide-open expanse of blue. Sometimes these waves get rough, but eventually all is peaceful again. Until next time. The longing for those days is sometimes more than I can bear. Can I survive this emptiness? My answer comes in the sound of the waves crashing onto the shore.   The sea has been witness to every tragedy since time began, and yet it survives.   So, too, will I.   -Cindy 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is a first draft, so it may still be a little rough around the edges.  I wrote this after having lunch with a friend.  Our conversation reminded me that we've all been let down and hurt, but it's up to make sure that we don't - to steal a line from Hallmark - let yesterday use up today.  ____________________________________________________________   A Choice   There are failures  along with the victories. Friends who’ve been true and those who have fallen short Of our vision for them.  There is joy, but sometimes it is hidden or forgotten, behind a rambling wall of deceit and hurt.  We have a choice to make: The pain can hide the joy or increase the preciousness of it.  The failures can be why we quit or the reason we strive harder than ever.  False friends can be why we trust no one or the reason a true friend humbles us with respect and admiration.  It’s where  we allow our minds and hearts  to linger That will ultimately decide.  -Cindy  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This was nice.  I love your style. You can really hear your unique voice in this. :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I use to think things were for free. I would get very irritated when someone would say nothing is free. I would mumble under my breathe, oh I know of several things that is free.  But as I got older a little wiser I realize how silly that was to really think that way.  Nothing is free, nothing.  I learned early on that even my salvation is not free and if I plan on making it to heaven to see Jesus I can never forget that.  Jesus death was my prepay for my mansion in heaven his death bought me knee and elbow space for my praying at God's mercy seat, his stripes prepaid my health insurance policy up.  When I went to the alter back in January of 1988 in San Diego, CA I had to start making my own payments, I had to put down a large lump sum deposit called "repenting of all my sins".  In order for me to maintain this precious gift I have to make daily payments, those payment are made by me getting down on my knees and repenting of anything and everything I may have said or done.  So without a doubt nothing is for free.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am so thankful for the touch of God in my life. There are many times in my life that I go through struggles, reminders from the past, and questions that I can never really seem to find the answers to. Sometimes it just snowballs and I feel so anxious like I need to find the solution quick before I sufficate. But it's in those times that God touches me with His peace - sometimes when I don't even ask Him to. He just has this way of touching me, and I feel like I become saturated in warmth and I'm safe again.   The first time I felt the Holy Ghost was like that - warm and safe. I wasn't scared to go home that night, though I wished I could stay in God's presence like that forever. I remember being so light, free and happy like I was dreaming and walking on clouds. I'll never forget that day because I never knew until that day that love could be so real and strong.   Many times in my life I look back to that day for strength, and hope that the turmoils of my day will meet that peace again. I don't understand God's ways or His timing, but I'm so glad that He touches me when I need it, and when I don't even ask Him too. If I was ever ABSOLUTELY and TRULY in love with anyone to such a degree, I would have to say it would be Him. My family will eventually be gone, but He is always there.   Sometimes I think I am too dependent on Him, but then, as I pull my head up from another crying session and problem, I realize that that's ok.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This song, while not a "christian" song, helped me to get through a very dark time in my life.  It speaks to the fact that we often don't take chances based on past hurts.  We don't always take every opportunity to be the best we can be.  We pass up opportunities for peace, joy and fulfillment because sometimes it's hard.  Colleen's earlier post made me think of this song. As promised, here are the words.   Cindy  ----------------------------------------------------------   I Hope You Dance   written by Mark Sander and Tia Sillers  I hope you never lose your sense of wonder You get your fill to eat but always keep that hunger May you never take one single breath for granted God forbid love ever leave you empty handed  I hope you still feel small when you stand beside the ocean Whenever one door closes I hope one more opens Promise me that you'll give faith a fighting chance And when you get the choice to sit it out or dance  I hope you dance....I hope you dance  I hope you never fear those mountains in the distance Never settle for the path of least resistance Living might mean taking chances but they're worth taking Loving might be a mistake but it's worth making  Don't let some bitter heart leave you bitter When you come close to selling out reconsider Give the heaven above more than just a passing glance And when you get the choice to sit it out or dance  I hope you dance....I hope you dance  Time is a wheel in constant motion always rolling us along Tell me who wants to look back on their years and wonder where those years have gone  I hope you dance....I hope you dance
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This posting reminds me of one of my favorite songs.  It's not a "christian" song, but the message is so beautiful.  It's called "I Hope You Dance".  When I get home I'll post the words. We do indeed only get one of these things that we call a life, and wasting it is truly a shame.   Some may think that laying on the beach listening to the ocean is a waste of time. Someone else may think watching a movie is a waste of time. Some may even think that spending a relaxing evening with friends is a waste. We all have different interests, and we have different ideas of what is meaningful and enjoyable.    This past winter I got an awful cold because I went to the Botanical Gardens to watch the snow fall. I was freezing, and I wanted to go home, but I realized that (especially living in Virginia) this could be the last time I see a snowfall. I didn't want to miss the beauty of it.   We won't all spend our free time the same way, and that's ok.  I think we've just got to remember that life is short, and each opportunity to do a certain thing could be our last opportunity.  Let's choose wisely.    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Life is like trying to catch a beautiful, fleeting butterfly without damaging it's wings. It all depends on how you catch it.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This morning I was reading an email from someone who was venting anger over a very small issue to me. They went on and on making something very small into a very large problem.  As I read this, I was grieved at how we have wasted so much time that we have been given. When I think about all the arguments, the spats, the misunderstandings, the projects we've never completed, the friends we never take the time to meet, the get togethers with our friends that we never have, the pouting sessions instead of prayer sessions, the hours we watch television instead of doing something worthwhile, the walks on the beach we never have, etc etc... how much time we have wasted indeed.   I wonder how much in our lives would really count if we were to take away all the rest that didn't.   I wonder how much greater life would be for everyone, if we took that wasted time and did something worthwhile with it.  The problem is, you can't regain time... not even one minute. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really like the way you worded this Jan-Marie.  It really touched my soul.  It was not long, nor was it to short it was was just enough.  Thank you.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      How do I measure the blessing in my life? Do I measure it according to the world's wealth? Nay, for it is fleeting and fickle - here today gone tommorrow. Do I measure it by the friends I have? Nay, how ever nice -they are only temporal. Wealth is nicehave and friends enrich any life but to measure my blessing by them I can not.  How do I measure the blessing in my life? Do I measure the blessing by how healthy I am? I can not for health comes and goes.  How do I measure the blessing in my life? Do I measure it by the children I have or the man I share my life with? Nay, wonderful as they are, they are not promised to me tommorrow.  How can I measure the blessing in my life? Do I measure it by how often God's hand moves on my behalf? Do I measure it by the number of prayers I have answered or the number of souls I win to God? Nay, by these never!  They serve only to remind me I am blessed.  How do I measure the blessing in my life? Do I measure it by the number of spiritual gifts I operate in? Or the works that I do for God? Heaven forbid!  For these only serve to remind me I have been entrusted by God to share what He has given to me.  How do I measure the blessing in my life? I can measure the blessing only in Jesus Christ.  I am His and He has made himself mine!   This is the full measure of the blessing.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1.  Participation:  Each person must contribute to the friendship. Each must give and take and be conscious of the other person's needs and desires. It's never about just YOU or THEM, it's about US.  2.  Loyalty & Trust:  Traitors are not worth your time. To pretend to be a friend to someone and then to talk about them behind their back, to belittle them to another, to use them for your own purpose and then walk away or to use them temporarily while you search for another friend constitutes treason of the highest degree. In the old days, if someone was caught in treason, they were SHOT! ;)  3.  Fun:  Who wants to hang out with a porcupine or crabapple? Having fun makes lasting memories. However, fun can be relative. What's fun for one person may not be fun for another. We all like it when we find common ground on what we both enjoy, but there are times we should indulge our friends in the things they like, so they will indulge us as well.  4.  Be Available:  We all say at times, 'I'll always be there for you,' but many times we break that promise. We get so busy that the encouraging phone calls cease, the shoulder to cry on is in use somewhere else, the get-togethers are like holidays or always being rescheduled, etc, etc. If you're going to be a friend to someone, then be there for them, even if it inconveniences you. Sometimes what we need the most is just someone to listen to us. A good friend doesn't have to give good advice, they just have to give a good ear.  5.  Common and Uncommon Interests:  Some people think that the only people they can be friends with are those who are just like them. It's true, that in friendships we need to have some common interests. Common interests spark conversations, projects, roadtrips and memories. However, some of the greatest friends that we may ever have may be the ones that we don't have everything in common with. You can learn a lot from someone who is involved in something that you don't know. If you take the time to be interested, you just may end up learning something new in your life that you'll end up thanking that person for later. Expand your base, experience life and each other.  6.  Spirituality:  We are God's children. And therefore we are required to be like Him. The people that we hang out with have a great influence in our lives, even if we don't think they do. Some people think that they can hang out in sinful areas and never get affected by it. Well, that may be true the first couple times, but over a period of time you WILL be affected by your environment. Though I do not agree that all of our friends are REQUIRED to be saints, I do think that those who are not need to be not far off. There is a difference between an acquaintance and a friend.     
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This was a beautful post.  The thought of God running to us has been explored in songs and poems, but this post brings together our pursuit of God's love with His love that is also always pursuing us.  I've not seen the two ideas together in a writing before, and it's so effective.  Love it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All throughout our lives we seem to have one thing that follows us wherever we go, and however old we get - the pursuit for love. We love and then we let go only to search for another love again. When I was nine years old I felt the love of God for the first time. I didn't know what that kind of love felt like, though I knew that's what I wanted when I felt it. From that time until now, I have pursued that love, day after day. My idea of love has grown and stretched to excessive degrees. At nine, though you can feel love, you do not have the understanding of its depth - Life and experience can only teach you that. God has shown me that love is real in the good times as well as the bad. God has shown me that love can be hard when we want it to be gentle; love can be silent when you want to hear its voice; love can scream when all you want is silence. His love goes beyond what we understand it to be. Over my life I have become dependent on God's love. I have dreamed of all that it can be - a love that not only do I pursue, but one that pursues me. I have taken off the limits of love in my mind, and come to believe that love is not just what I've already experienced, but it's everything that I have fathomed it could be. So, I search, I dream, I pursue - this love - only to find out that as much as I run to find it, it's running to find me.   Thank you Lord, for letting me love me to the degree I want to, and I dream to. With you, anything is possible.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I already had responded to your blog Sis. Clabaugh so I won't repeat what I wrote, just in case it post.  But I think it was a great idea to write something to everyone wrote so I wanted to do the same.  I am sorry it is late, I have not signed onto blogger in a few days.     Sis Cindy  - Thank you for your kind words, I wanted to tell you that your writings has inspired me and I look forward to reading them.  I am glad to have met you and I pray we get to know each other better.  You have a gentle spirit that makes anyone that comes around you feel special. Thank you.  Sis Holtzberger  - I have liked you from the first time I met you, you are tenacious and full of life.  What I really admire about you from all of our talks and time of fellowship together is that you encourage me and I know others because of your love for people and your ability to find the best in others. Sis Sneed - Your strength in the midst of your storms and how you are with your family.  You give your all and then some, your children will call you blessed.    Sis Clabaugh  - It has been a joy working with you over the past 4 years, from youth through now.  You have always made me feel that I am important and my feelings does matter.  There has been some dark times even in the last few months but you have encourage my heart.  Thank you for all that you have said, giving and done for me.   Last, but certainly not least - Angela,  you are the joy of my life.  I am blessed you are a part of my life, you have loved me and been by my side through some of the most difficult times of my life.  I pray that God blesses you with a man that place God on the throne of his life because then and only then will you be treated like the beautiful and decent young lady you have grown up to be.  I love it Angela when you and I have our bible reading challenges. It gives me great joy, unspeakable because Angela you could be doing a lot of other things but you choose to live for God.  I am a blessed woman. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Colleen,   Again, thank you for inspiring us to tell the other members of our writing group how much we appreciate them TODAY.     Sis Cook  I love that you allow yourself to be vulnerable. That takes such great strength and trust in the people you confide in.  It's inspiring to see such openness and honesty.  You're a truly special person.    Sis Angela  You are so fun to be around.  Are you ever not smiling?  Your desire to spend your summer doing mission work is a testament of where your heart is.  Whatever your mother did, she did it right.  If I ever have children, your mom will surely be one that I ask for advice.     Sis Sneed   You're a talented and special woman.  You have that special ability to make people laugh, and I look forward to the time we are able to spend together at the writing workshops.     Sis Holzberger   You have several small children, yet I rare are the moments you are without a smile.  Your oldest daughter loves holiness. That is a testimony to YOU and your skills and prayerfulness as a mother.  I have heard from others in the church that you have touched thier lives. You are clearly a very special person.    Sis Clabaugh   I love being around you.  You are so talented in so many areas that you encourage others to find the best in themselves.  I guess maybe I'm not one for public displays of gushiness (if it wasn't a word before, it is now), but when someone touches me then it doesn't seem fair not to let them know. You have, and I look forward to a long and growing friendship.    -Cindy
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wrote this in 1997 shortly after losing my oldest brother to the effects of Agent Orange. He had served as a marine in Vietnam. This poem remains unfinished. I don't know why, but one day I stopped working on it and haven't pulled it out until today.  Maybe I'll work on the ending this week.    -Cindy ----------------------------------------------------   The Forgotten Wounded   All wounds can’t be seen.  It’s true, you know.    Maybe we’ve seen a man missing a leg And we know he’ll never walk the same.  But I know men who stood next to that man on the battlefield,  And though none of their blood was shed,  They will never walk the same either.  All wounds can’t be seen.   For these men with invisible scars, A sound, a look, a name, a song Can send them there again.  And you’d never know  as you sat next to them That a war was being fought in their mind.  All wounds can’t be seen.   A friend, a brother, a husband lost So others could be free. A woman knows her father only in pictures And by the medal that is in the case with the flag Folded so perfectly No purple hearts awarded to these battle-weary. All wounds can’t be seen.  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Geeez...this was like Christmas!  What better gift than the kind words of a friend?  Thank you very much for that entire post.  It is so sad that the nicest things anyone usually says about those they love are spoken at their funeral.    Colleen's advice is so important.  There is nothing worse than that feeling of regret at not telling someone how we felt about them.    This was a sad memorial day for so many families. I looked through some pictures of the men and women we have lost in Iraq, and the wounds of those families are still fresh.  I thought of them throughout the day.    In the Sunday paper Doonesbury (the cartoon) used his entire strip to do nothing but list the names of all of the war dead.   It's so hard to look at those names...just words on a page...and remember that everyone of those names represents many broken hearts of the loved ones s/he left behind.   Thanks again for a great post.   Cindy  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a cute poem I found this morning. I totally relate because two weekends ago I bought a new mattress for my bed (after 15 years of having the same one) and since then I had not been able to get a full night's sleep. My bed was so nice and comfy that you would have thought I would have drifted off into a coma, but NO... there I was at 3:00 a.m. looking around at the shadows in my bedroom wondering if 15 years was really that long after all. ;)  Insomniac's Prayer   Must the day be day at night?  Trying to sleep, getting uptight  worry and wonder and toss and turn  desperately needing the sleep I earn.  Still, I think while counting sheep,  Must I die to get some sleep?   Author: Mark C. Carroll
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I so enjoyed what you wrote Sister Clabaugh.  I like to let people know what they mean to me.  I enjoy telling others how they have touched me, encouraged me, made me feel special. It is so important and doesn't take much time.  I feel that to hold back our thank you, our admiration, our praise is take for granted someone special.  They may not be there tommorrow to tell it to.   I thank you for your kind words.  I try to pray for those things that are found in the word.  Sometimes I reach too far and fall flat on my face but even in those times Jesus is there.  Through your prayers and the prayers of others He picks me back up and sets me on my feet again.  I'd rather reach too far than not reach far enough.  I pray for others as I "see" the need.  The real need isn't always what is visible, but sometimes hidden behind the smoke screen of a wounded spirit.  The bottom line, I do love to pray!   I thank you for all the times you have carried me in prayer and fasting.  Without you and few others praying for me I wouldn't be here today.  I would have given in to a wounded spirit and believed a lie.  May I have the priveledge to help carry others in the process.   Thank you again for your kind words and your sweet spirit.   I am grateful for all that you do.  You have helped me grow so much.  How can words ever express the gratitude felt toward a friend/sister that helps you grow and heal?   I never had sisters growing up.  I thank Jesus that now I have whole large family of sisters.  I also thank Him that they are not in my bedroom into all my stuff.:] I thank all of you my sisters!    Sister Sneed  for listening to me just because!  You put up with a lot.:]  Sister Cook  for your example of consist faith.    Sister Angela  for you letting your shine in adversity and your smiling face.  Sister Cindy  for a fresh perspective on life that you bring out in your writings.  I look forward to getting to know you better. Life is wonderful even on the sour apple setting:] Love Sister Holzberger
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      PLEASE READ ALL OF THIS:  Today is Memorial Day. For most of us our thoughts are on the picnic later today (yum) but if we were to take a minute and think on the meaning of this day, what would we have to say?  I cannot say that I have a lot of family members that I have died to reflect upon. I have a few, like my two sisters who died as babies - one of a disease and one of SIDS. I don't remember much about them because I was so young. I remember the latter because I went with my mom to wake her up that morning but she was already gone. It was a disturbing site that I still remember today. And I remember her funeral somewhat. Though I wonder at times what my life would have been like with them in it, that's all I can really reflect on. I don't have long lasting memories with them; nor do I know what I've missed out on without them.   I also lost my grandmother due to emphazema. She was a good woman. She wasn't spiritual my any means so I didn't have her to strengthen that part of my life. But, she played a mean game of cards, which I always enjoyed. I remember being somewhere around six or seven years old and she would lay on the bed as I would scratch her back; she really liked that. After about ten minutes I would fall asleep and when I would wake up later she would give me a quarter. I thought I was rich; my grandma had made me rich! ;)  Fortunately for me, my parents are still alive and the rest of my brothers and sisters. I haven't lost any best friends or even close friends. I know what deep loneliness feels like so I can imagine what it must feel like when such things do happen.   I am fortunate. But many are not. For those who lost their friends and family members during 911, or during the IRAQ war, or any war, or any other way, all I can say, is remember everything good about them that you can. Cherish their memories, talk about them if possible, and before you die, leave a legacy for them behind you, and someone may do the same for you.  For those of you in our writing group, I leave a memorial today for you, before it's late to hear for yourself...   To Sis Cook:  You are a wonderful woman, who has shown so much faith during your trials that if I had a mountain close to yours I'm sure it would have moved as well. I admire your spirit in the midst of trouble. I admire your zeal to encourage others (like the woman at the courthouse) while you are in need yourself. You are always full of hope and that gives others hope. You are great woman of God.   To Angela:  There is probably not a better child that your mother could have ever had than you. Angela, you are a pillar of strength for your mother. When other young people would have withdrew inside, or acted out their trials in sin, you stayed strong, and you stayed by your mother's side the whole time. Your presence alone to her, I'm sure, was worth more than any words you could have ever told her. You always make me feel special when I hear you call... "Sis. Clabaugh..." You make me smile. I can only imagine how the rest of your life will touch others.   To Sis Sneed:  Girl, you are great! You have so much wealth built up inside you that I am rich just knowing you. You have raised wonderful children that love the Lord and you are the strength in your home. I know things have been tough, and it would be easier to walk away... but look at you... you are still standing! You are awesome.    To Sis Holzberger:  Sister, what a wonderful woman of prayer you are. I always admired your cheerful spirit and the way you smile when you worship, even when life isn't so good to you. I don't know how you do that, I always end up crying! :) You have prayed prayers for others that they wouldn't even pray themselves, and you are always thinking about others more than yourself. I hope you never lose those prayers, or that smile. You've encouraged me many times, and I can't express how thankful I am for the many times you've thanked me for the smallest of things I've done. We need more people like you.    Sis Cindy:  I know you don't like public gushiness (if there is such a word,) but I am so glad that you have come to our church and became a part of my life. I enjoy every minute around you, and I can see why so people have said they like you. You have such an admirable spirit. You never degrade anyone, or belittle them, or talk bad about them... you are just you, and I always feel good being around you. Your talent in writing is awesome, and I hope you continue to let it come out. Your testimony is tremendous. Our lives share many common things so I know how you feel about some things without you even telling me. Thank you for being a friend and being yourself.   Sorry for the long post.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Waking up this morning my thoughts went to an old song we used to sing in church years ago:   "I am blessed" "I am blessed" "Every day that I live I am blessed" "When I wake up in the morning" "Or I lay my head to rest" "I am blessed" "I am blessed"   It's hard to sing those words when you are going through troubles and trials in your life. Nothing feels blessed when your heart is aching. Yet, no truer words have been sang. No matter how bad things get for us, we are still blessed, as long as we have breath in our lungs to breathe. I AM blessed today. I am blessed because I'm living. I am blessed because my husband and children are living. I am blessed because I have a house over my head, food in my cupboards, a vehicle to drive, clothes upon my back, and health in my body. I am blessed because I can see the sky today while others are in prison, in mental wards, in detention homes, or hospitals. I am blessed today because I am free and sitting here typing this while others are trapped in their minds, seduced by the world, unable to cope, unable to think straight, unable to comprehend, and unable to escape addiction. I am blessed because I'm not what I used to be. I am blessed because I could be dead, I could be in prison, I could be addicted, I could be divorced, I could be alone, I could be sick, I could be homeless, I could be lost, or I could be dead.   Compared to what I could be, I AM completely, absolutely, wholey, and entirely blessed. What right do I have to question the Lord about anything in my life? If a lost, homeless alcoholic on the street could see my life, would he or she have a better understanding of being blessed than I do? Perhaps.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a poem I found that says alot: ------------------------------------- Petal in the Wind  Lying on my back on a dark green lawn spotted by dandelions I gently pull one out by the stem; the yellow petals having long since fallen off; all that remains are clouds of soft, white cotton, barely holding on with whispering threads.  I hold it near my mouth and blow with all my strength, sending a small cloud of softness to join its siblings on the west wind.  I discovered not long ago that I could just as easily force difficulties from my life.  I take a deep breath and exhale; all my current sorrows and pains become like petals on the wind.  I refuse to let them take root in the garden of my life.  Michelle Ailene True
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I happened to run across this website today. It amazed how this guy can overcome as much as he did. It should be a reminder to us of how blessed we are, and even the worst of our days are VERY GOOD because we have God in our lives, and we are still breathing.  urlLink http://www.cameronclapp.com/home.asp 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I ran across a old checkbook today and it got me to thinking about the revolving account I have had for a long, long time. This isn't any ordinary account although it was setup and established for me way back before I was even created.  This revolving account is so special to me because no matter how many times I check the balance it always has enough funds to cover my every need.  I have never overdrawn this account, I must say I had not always been consistent with my deposits either. I am so glad that the Bank Manager knows me so well that he would already have my check register and balance sheet corrected and back on track, before I had caused myself too much grief.  There had been times when I took things for granted and I didn't think much of this account; I would misplace my check register and I also would not care whose ATM I used as long as I got what I needed at that moment.  I would get caught-up and tied up with a different banks that just charged me an arm and a leg in fees and penalties.  What made it worse is that I never really was satisfied with their service, but I would feel bad and embarrassed to have gotten in such a mess but somehow I always made it back to my original banking institution and would have to reconcile my carelessness and start afresh and once again my Bank Manager would be waiting to return my well balanced and intact account back to me.  I am so thankful for my revolving account which is managed by the Awesome Bank Manager, Jesus Christ. Now the question is,Who are you banking with?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thank you for this piece.  I like that.  It is true, I must confess I stand guilty.  Not nothing to be proud of but it is something I desperately want to change.  I thank you for writing this it is something I needed said but could never say.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm thinking of how wonderful God is. We all know that God loves us and see us as special in His sight, but so few of us really believe it. We question ourselves, we question God, we question everything, even if just inside where no one can hear us. We look at our lives through everyone else's eyes. We view our faults as more important than our successes or good qualities. The thing about God is this: He always sees us for our good, or else His mercy and grace would have failed a long time ago. He sees things in us that we can't understand, conceive of, or even sometimes believe. I absolutely believe that through God we really can do anything. We each have desires living in the depths of our soul that are screaming to be let out, but we're scared and so we just stifle it, as if it's something bad or something wrong. Yet, we still entertain it, because silently we believe in it and hope in it.   God is wanting to do some awesome things in our lives, but we're just all so afraid sometimes. He's screaming for us to let Him, and we're screaming to be let go, yet holding on to the past, holding on to other people's viewpoints and ideas, and holding on to boundaries that others have set for us. It's sad, in reality, to know what we are possible of doing, yet never do.  If we REALLY believed that God wanted to use us, then just imagine what we would do. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>