<Blog>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The week is getting worse. Toady i spent 3hrs staight wrirring an easay for the stupid MAP test. But its all good. I made the final descion to join guard, now lets hope that i make the try outs. thas it, thats all i did. I am back in the rain season, so it is hard to mountainboard or rock climb b/c of the mud. But i can bike. that would be a good thing, to go biking, a good 15mile ride does a person good. ok see ya
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HELLO ALL!!!!!!!!!!   I was way to busy to post this weekend. But it was all good fun. Saturday i went to a color guard comp and had a great time. On the way down thereit was kinder borin. I talk to Jamie and Amber and Rayna and the rest of the peeps on the bus. The we got there and did nothin for several hour except the show. Nothin else really happened that you would like to read, so i wont write that. But i did have fun hangin with jamie and then having been used as a human pillow.Sunday on the other hand was not fun. I went to aplay practice at church for around 4hours. Not Cool. thas it for the weekend.  Today at school we did nothin but stupid standardized tests. ok bye. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok here is the deal. My good friend said that he was glad that he did not get asked to the Sadie Hawkins dance tonight. Hell Fighter said this because he thinks that our school is full of crazy weird chicks. Well for the most part he is right. But I believe that out there some where there is a very cool gal lookin for him. But hey I am sure things will get perkier for him soon.   Check out his post at the Hell Fighter Boy link. And see what he says. Bye again.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok sory about the bad spelling and grammer and typos in the last post. But hey i still like it. you should really quit wasting tim on this post and read the other one. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hola!!! Today was a good day. It is raining outside. i woulndn that rayn is a bad thing, but it is not sunny. nothing really happened except my passin most of my tests. School was normal. Nice and boring. My younger sister is havoing me run her and her friends all around town. Its crazy! Wow in writing this post i realized that these are boin. I might have to step things up a notch. maybe post a short story or something else stupiddly entertaining. But hey ya know, whatever. Or maybe i could i am super depressed and talk about killing my self in here. that would be a fun thing. not that i would ever do that. i could leave my email with the message asking for help and see if anyone trys to help. That would be fun. But then i would feel bad for the nice person who wanted to help. And i would go off in a depressed manner and kill my hamster. but then the realization that i dont have a hamster hit me and i woould become more and more depressd pushing me to the limit, over the edge, so then i would be forced to start taking all kinds of thing that just further depress poeple. At this piont i would be so depressed that if you were to put the sun inside me, its light would not show. Now that i think about, i probably should not write a post about killing because i dont want to be that depressed. Thas it. see ya later. i am gunna go kill myself. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok here we go. the first real post. Today was great. We went on a field trip, I got out of school for the whole day. Butt the draw back is I did not do my home work and i have like 4 tests tomarrow. Anyway... i got to see some peeps i dont see very often. that was nice! Also on the lighter side of things, i finished my mystery for digital video editing. thas about it. life in a nutshell. Have a nice day. Andrew.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hello! And welcome. i will try to keep you up to date on my life and thoughts. So just sit back and enjoy the text. Because here on out i am gunna put my life here.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a little after thought, Even though yesterday and the events of yesterday were great, i hope that me and heather make sure that we grow in a reltionship and not just look forward to the other benifits of a realtionship are. I know that we have more than that. not that i mind any of it. sorry about the pronouns. if you can figure it out good for you. by the way make sure to read the post before this one. it will make this make more sense. bye bye
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello world. Saturday was awesome. I worked!!! allright that may not sound like fun but it was the best job i have ever had. I basically  got paided $10 and hour to pack up someone's house and hang out with my wonderful girlfriend. Things were great. I guess you could even say i learned to kiss Saturday. i want to go into that one but then again i dont know how. I guess its just kinda personal, although i do have to say the peopl;e house we pact has a nice Western Room, Garage, Dock Shed, Closet, and Stair Well. And the state park on 42 is a nice place. sorry inside joke. But yeah i had fun. Me and Heather went to the movie Walking Tall, it sucked. But i did have a good time, except the arm rest in the theater has a tendancy to get in the way. You know i think i like heather, and not just b/c of yesterday. She cute and fun and several other things. I know she is alot smarter and a much deeper thinker than she acts like sometimes(not that she acts in a bad way ever)She is just what i wanted. I do feel bad though b/c she paid for the snacks at the movie when that should be my job, but i will live. As for the rest of life it is just as good. School is almost out and my grades seem strong. Things seem to be cooling down with my sister and all of that though there is still a long road ahead. I need to do something with my friends now b/c we have not done anything in a long while and we need to have fun. I think stress is starting to take its toll on everyone. I was thinking on a rule they have at church, it is a no PDA rule for the youth. At first i was kinda upset about it because me and Heather would like to hug and hold hands and stuff of that nature little more. But as i thought about the no PDA i realized it was mad for a good reason. I realized Pastor made the rule b/c PDA takes your mind off of what you are really at church for, which should be god, and the same goes for youth trips, you should be there to learn and grow in god. Aslo PDA distacts others too, the silly people. Its hard to refrain from just grabbing heather and not letting go,not just b/c she is incredible, but b/c it is the only place i really get to see unless i drive forever and a day. not that i mind. i would drive forever and two days if i had to. But that is the major dilemma of the day. You know i waited 16years for yesterday, i waited 16yrs to kiss somebody and kissed somebody, i very cool somebody. And i do have to say it was worth the 16yr wait. It was really worth it. WOW is all i can say and thank you heather for yesterday. it was one of the best days of my life, though i have had many of those lately, yesterday was better than others. Sorry to ramble about yesterday but it is all i can really think about. The question that is goin through my head is the wonderment that did Heather enjoy it as much as i did. I think she did, she seemed to anyway. I hope. I bet she did. she did say i was a good kisser, that made me feel good about myself. Here is a question for ya. What makes a good kisser a good kisser.  is it something you cant descibe i feeling an emotion. Or is a good kisser good b/c of the way they kiss, the use of thier mouth and body actions. I bet it is a combination of it all. I am thinking about a new hair cut. something shorter but not short. its a sercret so dot tell. The one thing i refuse to do is sweep my bangs to one side of my face, its so ugly and i wouldnt feel put together enough. I like to be clean and put together. If i did me hair like that i dont think i would feel like me, so sorry heather im not doin it. hehe. Life is good. sorry i had to say that. its my new saying. Because right now life really is good for me at least. It seemed quick and kinda sudden me askin heather out. but i am glad, it wasnt that quick really i mean we did know each other for several weeks and we spent a weekend together on the youth trip. i guess it just seemed like it wasnt long b/c we only saw each other once a week. Although some how we have managed to fix that problem of not seein each other. its all good. i better go now my friends want to talk to me believe it or not. bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By the way i am not that violent, and i dont have alot of anger built up. I just thought it would be fun to beat some peeps up without a reason. ok bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello its third hour and i am supposed to be lookin at poetry. But im not. Life is just to full of better things to do than school work at the moment. One thing i would like to do is most likely not a good thing but it would be fun anyway. I was thinking it would be alot of fun to just grab the person standing next to me in the hall and just throw a big punch right to his face for no reason. Then i would grab the guy behind me and knee him in the stomach. Just as the 2nd guy started to fall i would jump up and roundhouse the guy coming at me from the opposite direction. At this point there would be 3 guys on the ground crying b/c they are to weak to put up a good fight and there friends would start to gather wanting to take me down. Then i see it. The key to my escape. The janitor is walkin by an and he has a mop. I jump up backflipping over two of the hurting guys and landing right in front of the mop. I grab it as a 6ft tall beast of a kid trys to hit me with a strong uppercut, but he misses. I take the wet mop and shove it into his face then swinging around the handle and hitting him across the cheek. the beast takes afew steps back and falls limp against the lockers. I turn to face the rest of the burly men who came to fight but they turn and run in fear. So i throw the mope to the guy against the lockers and walk off into class.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HOWDY!! Life is good, thats my new motto. i cant wait till saturday i might get to spend the day with Heather. Of course i will be working, but it will be with her. Anywho, school is boring, i need to get together with my friends, and i need to do something with Heather. thats all sorry i got to go. one of these dayz i will post something worth reading bybybybyby
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK nothin happened today, so am gunna reflect at this time. Mainly about heather, but still about life. I would have to say thank God for heather and i do. It is a good relationship, not only is she my beautiful girlfriend, but we keep things rolling in the regular friendship. THats just the way i like it. She sent me a blog she did before she ever talk to me, wow it was cool. She like predicted the future of me and her almost. Anywho I miss her during the day it stinks, its even worse is that i get to see her not very often. ok got to go. Bye Brando and Heather.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things are gettin better. Fri night i asked Heather to go out with me. Lets just say that relationship is awesome. Oh yah, fri night we went to the fair, it was a blast. I hung with zach, kat, and of course Heather. We did not do much really, except hang out. i wish brando could have been there. Anywho, i asked Heather out as i took her home after the fair friday night. Made for a good car trip. Lets see, saturday i drove to branson to help somebody vidoe a wedding that was fun. Then came home and met Heather and Phronsie at the fair again. Although i liked Saturday alot, although we were bored out of our minds, me and heather had a nice time. our friends were bored, while me and her were acting as a regular couple more or less. Then this morning i went to church met some indians who were very spirit filled and a lot of fun. They were doin the service this morning. I guess the rest is bliss.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i will make this short----- Kat- Bad Heather-Awesome Adam- Sad Story Brandon-Great Zach-ignorant on the situation Me- Exstatic bout Heather Conserned bout Kat  BYE
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to make this short b/c my head hurts. But today was awesome. Me and Heather went to see Scooby Doo 2 then went back to her house to watch Wayne's World. It was great. you know i think this thing with Heather is a good thing. Ok see ya. Nght
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK! today was a good day and tomarow will be better. Today we did somr play at church were they made me play Jesus, mainly b/c of my long hair. It was not to bad i rather enjoyed it. Plus the even better side of all of this was that it got me goin to a church and now i am closer to god than i ever have been. Thank the Lord. I mean it is awesome ow he worked in this. About 4 or 5 weeks ago i walk into WOW just goin to see what thoings were like. Within 5 min of that visit i had people asking m to do this and that. So i got involved and went to church often. This led to new strong christian friends who constantl reamind me of  God and is wonders. This made me keep walkin with him and day by day i gat closer to God.   Ok sorry if i bored you, but it was important to me and thats what i have thise thing for. Anywho! Tomarrow i am gion too the movies with Heather!! Cant wait!! See ya
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey there everyone! My internet broke for a week but good news, its back up so all you guys can read what i have to say. Nothing really happened in the time that i could not get on but i will tell all anyway. Last weekend I went on a youth tripwith my church, it was awesome. Went to Silver Dollar City in Branson,MO. Then we did some other fun stuff. Oh yeah, I made a new awesome friend that weekend too. Her name is Heather. She is pretty cool, I wont bore you with the details(not that she is boring or anything, i least i dont think so. I guess i cant type fast enough to tell you what i would like.)  Then this last week we finished the MAP testing, most boring if you ask me. Nothin else really. I was reading Hellfighter's blog and now i am worried i did something to make him think i am not his friend. I hope not b/c he will always be my friend. So if you read the Hellfighter please let me know if I did something to make you think i was not really your friend anymore.   Well Happy Easter to everone if i dont get to it tomarrow. Oh and if you read this Heather, you never said good bye last night, so i shall say it to you now , Good Bye heather. and Good bye all!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there i have moved this blog to www.livejournal.com/users/andrew_kelley thats all bye bye
     

    
</post>


</Blog>