<Blog>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh.... sian... another boring Sat.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Day 3 of exams   Aahh... today's chem i think i flung it. Hope can get full marks for chinese listening comp coz not too hard. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Disappointment   Never felt so lousy after a maths paper... didn't do quite a number of question... Hope i can get at least a B... hai... study for chem lo....
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yippie!!!! bio and gp ct over le!!!!   bio and gp... the papers which need lotz of writing instead of calculation... really makes me mad. hahaha... today first day of school! I WAS SO happy when i saw my clzmates again after a long break! xinyee, joshua and peixin went overseas for scholarship programme le.... hai... these three malaysian scholars were really nice people... hahaha... surely will miss their presence in the clz... especially xinyee.. who had helped me a lot in school work! She so good, can study medicine in an attached university.. xinfu lor.... :) Good luck to her!   heee... today during bio at audi... my stomach grumble so loudly that neighbouring people can hear lor!!!! so embarassing... donno why. i ate in the morning le... still hungry.. hahah... the bio paper mcq was okay... structured ques can crap.. but my mind went blank at the essay part... i guess i'll get 1 out of 20 marks lor... haiya... i knew it'll be like that.. hope i can pass.. can pass i happy already :)  After bio paper went for lunch with derek and huazhi behind the school near presbyterian high... hahaha... derek can really eat... he bought rice le still buy carrot cake!! hahaha.. after that still say hungry. Huazhi... hahaha... so funny keep ogling at girls and giving them judgement. They're really different from people from mf... Adult le ma... can talk freely about such issues. I was speechless at the moment coz i donno wad to say. :X hee/....  then returned back to school fer gp paper in hall.. It was so warm in the hall..i was perspiring like hell... my seat was in a place where all the fans are far from me... found an i.c. on the desk.. hahaha... donno who ... a j2 girl... after gave it to teacher. I chose the question using elimination.. but after 15 mins.. i found out that i eliminated ALL the questions!!!!!!ALL so hard!! those very general questions... although teacher said it can do-able.  but don think so after attempting. I chose questions 5 in the end... "What do you look for in a celebrity?" The only questions which i have sufficient points to write 4 content paragraphs... Hahaha.... quite smooth.. hope i can pass too! But i know veryhard... Aj got a really fresh way of submitting our essays... it's like voting for a referendum like that... row by row, we'll walk up and put our essays in the respective boxes of different questions... I think a teacher is in charge of each question... hope the teacher can be lenient lor... the most popular question is question 4-- What makes a good leader? Hahahaha... i wouldn't want to do such a question.. :P sure fail.  Then can go home le... short day. Tomorrow even shorter! Don even haf to go to school in the morning... coz maths paper in the afternoon! hahahahaha......... yeahhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!! Saw Jennifer Chung today afterschool in Northpoint!!! I was so surprised! hahahaha....i was walking around ma... then suddenly someone tapped my shoulder... It was her!! Still rememebr that she was the chairperson of 2A in mf!!! She studying in Nanyang poly... can dye hair.. her brother so cute... If never remember wrongly.. her brother name is Jonathan!! hahaha... same as moi... :P I was too shocked when i saw her... never expect to see her after such a long time... very shock.   hao le.... i muz go study for tomorrow's maths paper le... stop here for today! Muz score A for tomorrow's maths! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       1 more day~~~!!!!!!!!!!!   Mugging day! hahaha.... strange to use the word 'mug', but got influenced by friends from aj.... 'muggers'--- at first i thought it's really an english word. HAhahaha... then shaun told me it is not... one more day to school reopen. i'll start with bio first ba... found out that my Gippy Times's still in the locker at sch.. donno whether to go back and take. Lazy to go out.. Still muz wear sch attire... anyway monday also got time ... :P haha...  The soccer match last night between FRANCE and GREECE was really once in a life time thingy... France team... which was once a champion team and won most of the matches... actually lost to GREECE~!! Hahahaha.... unbelievable lor.... Greece was so lousy for the earlier matches!... hei ma....  what puzzzzles myself alot is the sudden interest in the results of these soccer matches.... not exactly is how the ball got kicked in or who kicked in at which interval and the which minute stuff.... it's quite fun predicting the results and analyzing who could be the ultimate winner...:) felt that maintaining and updating a blog is not easy... still have to squeeze out time for studying and doing other stuff... quite hard. but i'll try.    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hahaha.... it's 1.47am le... imsomnia.... so trying to perfect this blog. :) Hope it'll really look grreat! want it to be original ... found this crazy thing that really caught my eye. it's quite cool... so i made one :O       Y     Yum       O     Outrageous       N     Noisy       G     Gorgeous       H     Happy       A     Astonishing       N     Nerdy       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       2 More Days to School Reopening!!!   Haiz... onli got 2 more days then school reopen... donno to be sad or happy. Found that actually those which-are-assumed-to-be homeworks like tutorials are not important. What's more important is actually the common test = midyear exams... Two days to get 6 subjects is equals to 1/3 day per subjects! hahaha.... But this exam is really important to me coz if i don get at least a D grade for all my A level subjects, i'll have to drop one... which actually not important but i had worked really hard to get that 4 a level subjs...   Not quite confident in this coming exams... downloaded lotz of songs this afternoon! All nice ones.. popular chinese pop songs. :) Whole day reading bio notes and watching tv.. sian ah... how i wished i can go Northpoint or Orchard Road with delp, kairong, koonjin... It's really relaxing and keeps my day busy. Days seemed long alone at home.. Don't feel like studying... weather so hot. haha.. wasted another day again....! Tomorrow muz muz muz muz study le! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Finally... the one and only Yong Han's BLOG!!!   Hahahhaa.... The blog design, settings and stuff are finally completed... Can Start blogging le!!! Can't believe i'm so creative and IT-savvy!!! haha....
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You Raise Me Up Lyrics  by Josh Groban  When I am down and, oh my soul, so weary;  When troubles come and my heart burdened be;  Then, I am still and wait here in the silence,  Until you come and sit awhile with me.   You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.   You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.   There is no life - no life without its hunger;  Each restless heart beats so imperfectly;  But when you come and I am filled with wonder,  Sometimes, I think I glimpse eternity.   You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.   You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       CO   Today in CO got scolded by conductor... coz never blow dizi well. Donno why... i think becoz i never practise enough ba. I felt like digging a hole at the moment when i lou feng while blowing... hahaha. Today there's also announcement of the new EXCO members in CO. Matthew is the new President!! I'm happy for him :) he really haf the kind of ability --leadership. ok... got to finish my tutorials and stuff before next week! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          My inner child is ten years old!    The adult world is pretty irrelevant to me. Whether I'm off on my bicycle (or pony) exploring, lost in a good book, or giggling with my best friend, I live in a world apart, one full of adventure and wonder and other stuff adults don't understand.    urlLink   How Old is Your Inner Child?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       End of nightmare   Exams are finally over. Like a storm that had subsided. HAhaha.... so happy. :I Today's Physics paper really HARD. Chinese was alright, except the first part. I couldn't answer most of them!! I left them blank!! And the cloze passage also very tricky. Got to work harder... 
     

    
</post>


<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've found that there are only so many possibilities that are possible. You are given the rules for manipulating trig functions, and there are a limitied number, so just try the one that looks best, and if that doesn't work go to the next one.   For example if you were given that alpha+beta+gamma had to add up to pi, and you were also given something that related all of them together like "cot(theta) = cot(alpha)+cot(beta)+cot(gamma)" and you were asked to prove something involving theta and and all the other variables, the form of the problem suggests that you would use the product to sum or sum to product formulas.   It's all in the practice though. Someone should post a problem having to do with trig.   thanks to steve for the invite. I work at a college math tutoring center one day a week, and am a landscaper the rest. Love to play music and read as well.   -austin   oh and: add this to the style tag at the top of your template.  table { display:none; }  it will get rid of the annoying banner  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In Trigonometry, lots of time you get a problem that you have to prove the identity of an equation.&nbsp; Sometimes I get stuck on some of the complicated ones.&nbsp; Are there any ways to visualize how the identities can be proved by just looking at the equations?&nbsp; How do you determine whether or not to change&nbsp; or leave something when proving a problem?&nbsp; Please share your experience me.&nbsp; Thank you! 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How about the sum and difference, double angle, and half angle formulas?&nbsp; How do you memorize all three forms of those?&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Anyone know what is the best way to memorize all the important trigonometry formulas?&nbsp; Can anyone give me some tricks for doing trigonometry proving problems?&nbsp; Comments are greatly appreciated. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I heard many people saying that if you sing along when you are plying a piece&nbsp;on your piano, it actually helps you to memorize and get use to the song quicker.&nbsp; People also say that if you sing, it also controls your fingers so they won't missed as many keys.&nbsp; Do you think this is true?&nbsp; Or have anyone experienced or tested this?&nbsp; Please post your comment.&nbsp; Thank you so much! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      When you start a brand new piece of music, how do you recognize the notes?&nbsp; By just reading them off one by one or looking at them chords by chords, phrase by phrase?&nbsp; What do you think is the best and quickest way to&nbsp;read and recognize the notes of a piece of music?&nbsp; Please share your ideas with me.&nbsp; Thank you! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It is summer now.&nbsp; Everybody should have experienced the difference between hot and warm.&nbsp; Do you have a comment for HOT vs. WARM???&nbsp; Please post...&nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Please&nbsp;check out&nbsp; urlLink www.haitek.tk &nbsp;first.&nbsp; Thank you! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'll get these back to you by thursday.  and to enter them nicely... use Maple or I've heard of a scripting markup language called MathML that might work. check it out. I'll be posting the solutions using maple.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Prove the identity:  1. (tanXsinX)/(tanX+sinX)=(tanX-sinX)/(tanXsinX)  2. (1-sinX)/(1+sinX)=(tanX-secX)(tanX-secX)  For some other ones, I don't know how to enter them into the computer because there are squares and fractions.  Anyone having any ideas how I should do that?
     
    
</post>


</Blog>