<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      At the end of the day, am left with this thought ... what have i done today for others, to this world...??!!!  It was just another day, doing the daily chores ... doing this - doing that, solving a problem, browsing, talking, eating, driving etc etc.  half our life time goes sleeping, another half split between adoloscence and aged and whatever rest we are left out with we freak out, play, argue, enjoy and do what not!!!  but, whats that difference am i making here? am i a part of this ant colony, just another worker ant, doing its routine - if only to a larger extent?  that's a kind of thought, which goes undigested. mmmm.  each one of us can make a difference to the world around us... yes and i want to something! but where do i start? and in what way? I certainly don't want to do something for the sake of making a difference but  for what it is, wholeheartedly!  Thousand ideas, thousand thoughts go zooming past - but i need action. i need focus. i need more patience. i need to do something more ... to find that missing link!  let me see - try to sort out the spaghetti of unceasing thoughts, just atleast to find a focus - to square on something that would make me feel better in this aspect.  food for thought, challenges to the will.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
       urlLink Greek Mythology  This site has some good illustrations (at times comical), but i liked it. Interesting read...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
       Discovered blogBuddy!  After browsing through  the Blogger API, the first thought that struck my mind was to create a small tool and there i go, getting the XMLRPC implementation for Delphi and halfway through my search i bump across blogBuddy!   The project seems to be long dead, but what the heck, blogBuddy works! check it out!    its cool! urlLink      
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
         If you like contemporary art, don't miss this.    Even otherwise, its pure delight to watch these objects d'art  PS: How i envy the artist, let alone the girl on the painting  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      Am not alone, in this virtual world... shocked (should i be???) to find the rantings of these geeks   urlLink Revaz Musinz   urlLink The Rock 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

       
      I Discovered that am an INFP! (for those who want to know what's INFP, i suggest to check this out : http://www.humanmetrics.com/cgi-win/JTypes1.htm)  Here's a list of famous INFP's ----------------------------------------------- Homer Mary, mother of Jesus St. John, the beloved disciple William Shakespeare, bard of Avon A. A. Milne (Winnie the Pooh) Helen Keller, deaf and blind author  Carl Rogers, reflective psychologist, counselor Jacqueline Kennedy Onasis Julia Roberts John F. Kennedy, Jr. -----------------------------------------------  Whew, thats a nice note to start off my BLOG. lol.  Thanks to [sriram, my friend], for triggering the spark to BLOG, which i've lazily discontinued, after a brief start, earlier in 2003.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

       
       Intimations of Immortality       Ye that through your hearts to-day      Feel the gladness of the May!   What though the radiance which was once so bright     Be now for ever taken from my sight,   Though nothing can bring back the hour     Of splendour in the grass, of glory in the flower;   We will grieve not, rather find     Strength in what remains behind   (William Wordsworth)   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

       
       urlLink     Cat on the Move!!!  Finally! Revaz ventures out of the den. :o)  Way to go, buddy! Its a long road ahead...  Feeling so very happy for you. :o)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

       
      "The year is 2050, and you are standing in front of a vending machine. What form of payment will you put into it?"   -perhaps nothing- ? you just walk in, select what you want and walk away...! it could be your fingerprints, voice or ur retinal print or perhaps an embedded bio chip!  There might not exist a vending machine at all, standing out there, in the corner of the street!  mmm, what would be offered for sale on a vending machine?  well, well, that already leads to a chain of thoughts, tickling the creative bone...  Do we have the time to spend a moment and think about it? why isn't there any more of those ground breaking inventions, as of the early 19th, 20th and 21st centuries?  Where are we heading to?  Well, thankfully there are still some inventors out there... Check this...   urlLink The Impact Lab...   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

       
      Had been to the FORUM yesterday. Cool place. It has been modelled on the lines of a typical US Mall.  Quite colorful and too much of activity. nice to hang out...  will be back again
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

       
      Too much of action this weekend... Whew! Finally, decided to tie the knots! Gave the green flag, for the hunt!  Got to wait and watch, whats on store.  "I want to know God's thoughts; the rest are details."  - Einstein
     
    
</post>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This post stems from an attack of altruism. Faced with the sudden freedom of being unemployed, I think that some of this time could be best spent in helping fledgling souls find their way. (I define fledgling souls as beings that have finally discovered that they are a soul and not a body:-)). Or rather help them not lose their way. So here are a list of books that any soul worth its salt should avoid at all costs.  1. Illusions - Richard Bach - Richard Bach tops my list of purveyors of kitsch in the garb of neo-spiritualism. Bach attempts to peddle Advaita to the masses and succeeds for maybe 5 minutes. But if you are serious about wanting to know about the self, find a different Guru.  2. Conversations with God - Neale Donald Walsch - What put me off most about this book, is the author's claim that God ordered him to write the book. Don't read this book if you want a personal relationship with God or you feel you have one.  3. Notes to Myself - Read this book for a prime example of how you can convert an ego trip into a profit making enterprise. First you had Notes to Myself, then Spiritual Notes to Myself, Notes to Each Other and then Notes on Letting Go....yeesh!!!!  4. Autobiography of a Yogi - The first half is good, the second half is an exercise in excess. Reading the second half, especially the revelations of Yogananda's guru on life after death temporarily destroyed any interest I might have had in the spirit. It can confuse the daylights out of you.  5. A Bridge Across Forever - Richard Bach - This book, contrary to other Bach books, seems to go on forever. Maybe that explains the title. It is a long and tedious saga of Bach's quest for his soulmate. What compounds the tedium is not just that Bach divorced his soulmate but also subsequently explained it in suitably spiritual terms of being temporarily separated in his journey and all that blah. This was on his official website which now seems to have been taken over by his publisher.  There is a single thread that runs across all books (except the Yogi) - they are all pulp fiction in the garb of true spiritual experiences. They try to claim legitimacy for purely materialistic intents by portraying their authors as spiritually advanced beings who have been asked by the Divine to enlighten poor souls like you and me (and also make millions in the process). They make a mockery of what is essentially a personal and totally individual quest. There is a palpable lack of sincerity in the words. In essence, they lack 'Om' - a union of the spirit, body and the mind:-).  If you want a list of books that do inspire, start off with Gandhi. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The  Me cury  S urface,  S pace  EN vironment,  GE ochemistry, and  R anging mission (MESSANGER) would study Mercury. This is the closest we can get to the  Sun &nbsp;(for now that is :)).         The MESSENGER would be launched on  August 2nd, 2004  and it takes 7 years to reach -  March 2011  it would reach Mercury !!.     &nbsp;
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       - OM - in Hindu culture signifies an union of mind - body - spirit. This blog simply aims to unite the thoughts of (minds) different people (bodies) to acheive (the spirit) an unison of action. &nbsp;   
    
</post>


</Blog>