<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Señor Tequilas- Maldad Ritmo, 2/26/04 bday bash...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Tequilas--Jagerbombs&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      welcome to my world of blog-ness.  today there is a protest in appleton and i would like to be at it but my car is broken and i am stuck at work.   ps. i'm having trouble begining to let go of some things i will need to let go of when i graduate this may. gotta just let it go with the flow, but its a little harder than people think it is. again later.  -s*funk
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My car is FIXED! here's the damage: Altenator: $42 (used) Speedometer: $36 Waterpump: $38 new serpentine belt: $12 Cylander Head: $100 a bold to replace one that broke off the cylander head: $26 Various Engine Parts: $240 New rearview mirror: $10ish. 2 12packs of Amber Bock for dad: $20.00  What i still need:  2 new tires (i'm gonna just get all 4 new)  and and oil change pretty soon.  whooeeee! i have a car again that doesn't cost me $12 in gas a day!!! (i've been driving the boyfriend's Monte Carlo, and it guzzles so bad i HATE going anywhere, especially work.) Yay good gas mileage!!   *~*~*~*~*~*~ que dia buena !! *~*~*~*~*~*~  this post was giong to be about how f-in sick i am today and i am cramping up in the neck, my head hurts, sore throat, cough, sinus issues, delerium... i'm a mess! but i get my car back tomorrow!! gonna go feel like i am dying now...  (PS! the OC is on tonight! JOY!)   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      somewhat of a memoir:   we used to celebrate april 20th by a campout it wasn't necessarily for the obvious and over-hyped herb reason, it was more a celebration of spring and a time to just be a little crazy, at least for me. the boys, well, they were all about the herb and the company.  we'd always be the only tents in the campground, two or three super campers (full with a satelite dish and a toilet-whoowhee) would be parked by the electricity hookups. We'd hike around the campground to our favorite spots to tell stories and catch up with everyone. The guys would go off to the 'bowl hole,' a place in the side of the old ski hill that was indented like a giant cereal bowl had been pressed into the side of it. It's quite a hike up. But then you can lay back and look at the clouds passing and birds flying about.  We are some creative people, our campsite was always a unique sight, with tents and tarps making a perfect spot to be seen and hidden at the same time. We made a swing in the back of the campsite past the little bridge and stream that ran through the back-there was a vine hanging down, and we constructed a crude swing. The hammok would be set up (sometimes more than one) and the fire would be a constant glow.  have you ever made stuffed pork chops on an open fire? DON'T DO IT! the stuffing lights on fire! and bring enough jack daniels so that you fall out of the hammok!  ahh, so much fun.   But its a tuesday and a campout is unlikely, and most of our little crew has jobs that they can't miss and school work due tomorrow.  maybe a round of discgolf this afternoon, maybe a cookout later?  so happy april 20th, may it be filled with sun and blooming flowers and well, good herb if thats what you like.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a weekend, tonight Chicago @ Zentra to see Paul Johnson, the best damn chicago house dj EVER, along with my homies Filament and Wobbler who will be spinning there. It's gonna be a blast!! i can't wait, i haven't parties with these mo-fos in chi for quite some time. Then tomorrow (Sat.) is RTF banquet, rumor has it i am getting an award and i am so super psyched! Yay!  Sunday i work 8-3, then i am going to take a nap and then to milwaukee dfor Paul Van Dyk! you do not know how excited i am about this (even if its at the Rave, where i don't like) Then Monday i am super booked btwn classes and appt and a Remote at the t-rats stadium... tuesday will be blah, homework papers etc, and then Wednesday, Crystal Method in Milwaukee... it's binge concerting. I'll probably make it to like 2 this summer (i am going to xtina and no one can stop me...my secret love affair with ms. aguilera...  anywhoooo its sunny and i wanna go outside 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am a huge fan of the  OC . Come to my dissapointment as i anxiosly await that hour of  OC  goodness, i flip to the channel and its the Golden Apple Teaching Awards. How does that merritt pre-empting the  OC ?!  Can't a woman get a decent few hours of TV? I got my simpsons fix, my southpark fix AND no OC :( well shit. ---- Long week soon to come: Paul Johnson, April 16th Karina's Wedding & RTF Spring Banquet, April 17th Paul Van DYk, April 18th Crystal Method, April 21st WRST BENEFIT Concert, April 29th ---- 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      apathy makes the world go round.  its why i am so busy doing other people's lives. yep lives.  WAKE UP AND LIVE YOU F*CKERS!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i really need a car. i hate putting 10$ of gas in J's car (Huge-ass-gas-guzzlin mid 80's monte carlo) and it being gone by the next time I need to use it and then him telling me, 'oh, well, i just put in $5' (which is about 2gal).   grr. I'm looking at used VWs from the 80's (because they runwell and get good gas mileage) i really want a VW Rabbit Convertable. Like the puke green one in the movie Fear. that car is HOT. love it. I found a cabriolet, but its in NY and it needs a top and the odometer sticks. but its only 1800$. On another note, i want to go swimming. i Haven't swam since high school swim team. sigh.  so, saturday is my radio show and i have been looking for djs for it for two months, but looks like april 3 is just not the day. oh well. i think config is playing but i forgot what day (i talked to him at the bar and i was a little tipsy, you see why i forgot)  ok, work beckons. yargh.   arrrr matey! unitl later! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hintzy is so right:   urlLink    Hintz is the shit, i'm gonna miss him after i graduate. i'm gonna miss all those crazy college radio kats when i graduate.  WE WILL PLAY SOFTBALL THIS YEAR, even if we can't get a field till after schools over. Lets book a field for fall, try something new. WRST FOREVER--  urlLink    ---- on another note, i am really pissed off at the moment, I am a memeber of National Broadcast Society. I sent in my forms to become a member of the Honor Society part of it, AERho. I got an email saying I need to send in my membership registration form before i can be an AERho member. UHM, I have been a memeber since September 2003. The forms were sent then, my check had long since cleared the bank. Now i am pissed because i want my honor cords, and i graudate NEXT WEEK. hopefully this can get worked out TODAY and i get my cords in time. wish this gets settled for me...  :(   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *standing ovation*   urlLink      urlLink     
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday a hummer was following an older couple, who were doing the speed limit in a cadi (i they were even going over it by a few), and i was behind the hummer, the hummer rode their ass, roaring its engine and gettin as close as possible without running it over, until the nice couple pulled into the parking lot of the library to teh book drop off, the hummer then accelerated hard, squealed it tires, and whipped around the cadi in a jackass ithinkihavebigballs move and proceeded to flip off the nice elderly couple.  i found it appalling. ------------------------ 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i woke up drooling. that never happens. hahaaaahaaa :tired:  so yesterday, after work, i go to the park with the bf, real quick like b/c i had important things to do later, and i watch him fly his nice lil stunt plane, we get ready to leave, we back up put 'er in drive and :stop: the car does nothing. he looks at the gas guage, chuckles and says, guess i should have put gas in 'er before we got down here. we pushes his ancient heavy ass monte carlo to the gas station. needless to say by the time we got gas and returned home i wasn't going to make what i had planned on, and i didn't want to be rude and show up in the middle of everything. so, i endup doing 2 hours of dishes. they have been there for like 3 months. now we can see the sink, the counter, the wall and the stove!! the stove is white!! holyguacamole. during this entire ish cleaning session, the bf is ont he phone calling everyone he possibly knows for green...over and over. i tell him, if you called me every 1/2 hr wanting to know if i had 'found something' i would turn my phone off too. so, he gives up, and waaaalaaa. the phone rings, but we can't find it, he put it down somewhere. it's my friend and she is like meet me at mollys in 1/2 hr (for hte bf). so we went there. i had a $.25 beer, and i went home. woo! we watched a show about planes. how fun.  great 1st day of summer, let me tell you. --------- Today after work, i am actually going to work out after (go figure the weather is nice today- maybe i'll do cardio and then go for a bike ride after...or i could do cardio warm up and then just do a good weight circuit and go biking. at least the sun doesn't go down so early anymore. i need to soke up the sun. ---- Oshkosh has all these lion statues everywhere, painted in different ways, and sculpted in various forms- for example: one lion is a paperboy, one is a sailor, one has wings, one lights up....etc maybe i can bike around and finally take the photos of them i want to take today.  They really remind me of Salamanca during fall of 2002, when it was Capital Culteral 2002- and all these bull statues were all over the city, each different from the rest, one was superman, flyingo ut of a phone booth, another was a beer guy pushing a cart of beer bottles, another had holes in it that you looked in and could see pictures of the city in it.  The lions connect me with my beautiful memories of Spain. Te amo España. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Sfunk traveling to Richie & Magda in Madison&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Richie Hawtin & Magda&nbsp; urlLink     RICHIE HAWTIN AND MAGDA last night at the Inferno in Madison was crazy-mad-fun! Both sets were exceptionally awesome. Magda played around alot and it was really sounding great and more intricate than Ritchie's.But Richie killed it too! damn fine time. I got to talk to Magda, she's super chill.  Both those two were well worth the price of admission even though I was on richies list. Totally worth the drive to Madison, the babysitting of drunken friends and not getting home until 5am b/c your friend is puking in a parking lot (rather that inside my car) and then gettin up at 7:45 to go to work, totally worth this back ache and the ciggarette burns. i feel like i lost 10 pounds it was so hot in there, and dancing, i'd bust out for a little while and then get so hot, i almost passed out!.  i heard mixed reviews from my NY & LA friends of this show and i think they should have came to the midwest shows b/c everyhting i hear & heard last night was fantastic!All reveiews Positive.  i am still in awe from last night. Very excellent show. WOrth the drive, the puking bullshit and everything.    TECHNO.TECHNO.TECHNO.TECHNO.TECHNO.TECHNO.  i am sure i want to add more but i am pooped out and at work, on 1.5 hrs of sleep.  UPDATES: pics (photos by Tyler and Brent - Please email me or contact tyler @  tneelis@tylerman.net  for permission on use-THANKS!)  urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Magda&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Richie&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Richie&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Richie&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Richie&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Richie&nbsp; urlLink      
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I want to congratulate Cass & Lee on their marriage. It was a really nice ceremony, and Cass looked stellar. seriously should have seen that beautiful woman, she looked like a medieval princess.  the dj at the reception was kinda crappy, but oh well, we had fun in the end with it. and those kids can dance, i see future break dancers in the bunch!! ;)  Congrats!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      is a beautiful state.   urlLink    Tyler's back yard. Vermont.&nbsp; urlLink     We went to Vermont over Memorial Day weekend (left wed may 26 at midnight, got back tues june 1 round 8am) Rented a car, it was a Galant--Very nice handling car, great ride, i give it 4 stars, needs more pickup-  urlLink    Tyler & Cettina's son Liam&nbsp; urlLink    anywhoo, we went to my friend Tyler's wedding. I will put the pics up soon, i just got back the wedding photos, so they should be up soon too.  We arrived at Tyler & Cettina's house in Vermont  Thursday  after about 20+hours of driving, all very crabby and exhausted, at around 7 or 8pm. We set up camp, met the other friends who were there to help set up, and met everybody who lived in the house, as well as Cettina's mother (like a true italian, she kicked us all out of the kitchen).  The next morning ( friday )we went into Burlington to check it out, do some shopping. I wish i had more money, there were many things i wanted to purchase, including this hemp skirt at a store named Hempys, and this really beautiful silk patchwork skirt. We met up with the bride & groom to be, and helped them pick out gifts for the wedding party, and rings and pick up Tyler's suit (Italian & expensive-but looking excellent on Tyler) Back at home I helped plant flowers in all the flowerbeds. It took forever, and i thought i was going to go insane at first, but it was actually really soothing to me.  More friends arrived, set up tents. We also had a port-o-jon parked next to our little 'campsite' so Cettina ordered the construction of something to hid the port-o-jon so it didn't stick out of the woods so much. Man, hippies rule, you could barely tell it was a toilet under all that branch cover.  That night we hung out inside (they live in the mountains, its kinda cold)shared stories with each other to keep everyone up to speed on what is going on with everyone's lives now.   Saturday  was crazy, many more people showed up, lots more hippies! I was put back to work on flowers, then i helped put together boquets for the wedding tables. We were assigned to run into town and get pizzas for everyone. well, not just a few pizzas, like 12 of them, and it was this place called positive pie, way cool! And delicious!!! That night everyone was exctied and getting ready, so we had a fire and a drum circle. It was really exciting. Tyler & Cettina hung out with us for a while, because the next day would be crazy!  Sunday , the wedding day! All i remember pre-wedding is moving vases with flowers, and cooking on a grill by our campsite. i must have been pretty busy and excited. Also, we were waiting for people to come in from the airport, so the wedding was delayed a little, but that didn't make it bad. We had to wait for Tyler's brother to get in, but Northwest delayed his flight and Nate almost had to fill in for him in the wedding. But he got there just in time and about 20 min later the wedding party arrived.  The ceremony was really beautiful, full of different traditions--the wedding party was smudged, then the couple walked through a laberynth (sp?) and they designed the ceremony so personal. They invited in the North, South, East & West. Their vows were personal and really wonderful. Then at the end they tied thir hands together, they then walked the laberynth together. At the exit, they jumped a broom to sweep away the past to focus on their future together.  Also, on the table was a quilt. it is part of Cettina's family tradition to have a quilt with untied strings and each person send the couple their blessings and wishes by tyeing the knots! :)We celebrated with honey wine- i forget what it is called, and that is how the word honey moon came about b/c couples are supposed to drink that for an entire moon cycle.  the band was a fun, we started another fire and had another drum circle.   Then crap happened, J & Nate & his gf were in a tent (smoking) and he was telling J how i am not right for him and needs to break up wiht me. Little did nate know i was within earshot and i came up to the tent opened the door and told him he doesn't know anything b/c he never sees us and is only around us maybe 3 times a year. It was just a really swell ending to the night.  I just went off and walked away and hung out with the hippies, banged on some drums.   The drive back started at 9:30ish in the morning Monday. we got back tuesday morning.  i'll post the pictures soon. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      suck ass! Last night a deer ran into the side of my car.   i am ok. the car is not.  i can hardly open my drivers side door. and the front panel is VERY messed up. I am now missing a mirror as well.   Nothin like watchin a deer's head bounce off your windshield on your way home.  UPDATE: The total cost on repair is close to $1400. That sucks. I guess i was the 4th person who hit a deer in like 10 minutes that night. woo! Not sure what i am going to do about fixing the car yet.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so...freeking...busy!!!   work all day, try and spin reccords after, then clean the house and yell at the bf for being home all day and not lifting a finger to the mess like always. Then try to fit in workout time and correspondence time, and run to GB for a remote and then back again for the show, then gotta pack up and go home and sleep and then wake up a few hours later to go back to work and try and sound awake, then try and figure out what is all left to do from the past week yet.   like, say, transfer the car title that has been signed in june and it is august. jeebuz. I still have to do that. damn, then back out the door again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So he's in WI today, makeing stops to the  public . Wait. no he isn't. he is using our tax dollars to have a lil meeting with his supporters. A friends went to get a ticket to the president's stop in GB, but was  denied  because when asked "are you voting for Bush" he said "probably not" The man ahead of him was undecided and told the person at the ticket booth that he should get a ticket. When told no, my friend asked why he could not attend if his tax dollars are going to fund Bush's stops in WI. He was again told no. The undecided man ahead of him  gave back his ticket  to see Bush, and said he had now made up his mind and will not be voting for Bush, since these stops are supposed to be for the general public. But they are not. He is using the publics tax dollars to make stops that are only allowing his supporters and the undecided. This is wrong, and he is wrong and needs to go. ~~~~~~~~ I got this today:  To: Chamber Members  From: **** ******, ***********  Date: July 13, 2004  Re: President George W. Bush Tour  On Wednesday, July 14, the President George W. Bush motorcade is scheduled to come through Oshkosh on its way from Fond du Lac to Green Bay. Specifically, he is scheduled to be on Main Street at 2:15 p.m. We are encouraging anyone that is interested to meet and be on Main Street in the 100 – 300 blocks to welcome the President. While his motorcade is not scheduled to stop, this would be a great way to show support. So, please gather prior to 2:15 along Main Street. Feel free to bring U. S. flags to wave. Let’s give President Bush a warm reception to Oshkosh as he comes through town. -------------  He'll be going right past Peace Park. I can guess there will be plenty of protesters there, and I might leave work for a while and go downtown, stop at Winnebago Peace and Justice center and grab a sign. my co-worker said she'd join me if i went... ---------  Edited aug 5:   I did leave work and go down to Peace Park. Its interesting to see men on roofs with machine guns and such.     
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pisces (Feb. 19-March 20)   This is a wonderfully playful time for you. You couldn't pick a better time for a vacation. Romance, love affairs and playful activities with children plus entertaining getaways are tops on your menu now. Indulge your creative side as well. Give free rein to your impulse to paint, draw, sing, carve, write, knit, sew, dance -- whatever. It's very important to let your soul sing! The only dark cloud on your horizon is something confusing or even shady connected to your employment scene and possibly your health. This could be a simple misunderstanding. However, you won't really know sure for the next 2-3 weeks. Just hang in there and enjoy yourself.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know i haven't been faithful in writing to you, dear blog, and for this i apologize with my entire heart. How could i be so blind on our fantastic relationship; i devulge random tidbits of my life and you listen. oh dear blog, what have i done.  I know i didn't take you along to see Dan Efex, nor my wanderings to the peace and justice center and the peace rallies to paint and soothe my soul. Forgive me blog, for leaving you behind to go up north and help with the cabin. I also regret the time lost by not taking you to the fireworks and the drunken debauchery that followed.  Blog, my cupcake, i will try to be less careless in my ways. Shall i wander again, i will give you advanced notice.  sfunk.   ----------------------- nocturnal dimension 10-12 saturdays, 90.3 wrst-- now playing: Abaddon from Appleton, and from 11-12 Arsenal from Wausau-- http://www.angelfire.com/electronic2/n_d_wrst last show (sadness) July 31. 10pm-2am   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its   A  ugust  . Now, i live in Wisco and have all my life so i can't complain about the cold, EXCEPT when its summer and August and the typical 80-high 90's degree days are what we are not getting. Come on, and high of 75?! and last night it was so cold i was shaking. Tonight it says lows of 48! dear christ do i have to get out my sweaters in august? -- ok enough about the weather. its going to be  sunny  out today and tomorrow-- I am really excited about tomorrow, i don't have everything all planned out yet, but i think i tend to over plan so i just want to go with the flow on this one. I need to get groceries and being the sound equipment to the house so i don't have to do it tomorrow. I still need some pallets, i only have 12 right now, but i have a bunch of people offering to bring wood to the house today and tomorrow. It's going to be some fun bonfire action tomorrow, and I am happy so many people have rsvp'd with a yes! I decided i am going to kabob some veggies and make a fruit salad. I also need some munchie food for anyone getting hungry later on, and MARSHMALLOWS chocolate & grahms-- don't forget those steph! -- So far a few of my friends are going to throw down, including  mike-e-fresh, filament, sunkissed, &amp; interpid & maybe some others.   So what i all have to do yet:     Bring equipment to the house (decks, mixer, sound, vinyl)     Buy food (veggies for kabobs, johnsonville brats, buns, fruit, munchies, marshmallows, chocolate &amp; grahms) soda & beer    Buy a glowstick or two to mark the road since there is no street light    Pick up more pallets &amp; wood, direct other wood bringers to the house for drop off.    Pack up some blankets, clothes, swim suit &amp; find my tent    Get Luke's tiki torches or go to menards and buy them for $1 each.    I think that is all. I have a hour massage today at 6:15. It's going to be pimp.   ---  at home we moved around the stuff in the bedroom and it looks wonderful and alot bigger, we're going to move my desk in there also for more room in the living room. All this work and i really just want to move to a different apartment. I'd like to move by the end of this month in all honesty. I've been looking for apartments.    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>