<Blog>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heard the song "The Reason" by Hoobastank on the radio a couple of times today and many more in my head before I really listened to the words.  Then, I realized what I was hearing.  I investigated.  The lyrics:   I'm not a perfect person There's many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears That's why I need you to hear  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is You [x4]  I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I've found a reason to show A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that I do And the reason is you   Isn't it funny how this band isn't "Christian" and probably weren't aware when they were writing this that it could be interpreted that way, but put it in a spiritual (I hate that word, BTW) context.  Sing it to Jesus.  It's almost perfect.  Acknowledging your faults, knowing you need to change and WHY.  Sometimes, I think there's more Christ to be found in some secular pop/rock than in so-called Christian music...but that's another post.  Something to think about.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it's Amy going.  OK.  I can live with that.  But didn't you see "I deserve to go" written all over John the Redhead's face?  Going on a trip tomorrow with the family to the Smokies.  I hope it's a good time.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I told my bestest friend Kristy about the fine art of blogging.  This should be fun.   urlLink Click here to see Kristy's blog! 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reality TV is so much better than scripted garbage.  Don't you think so?  It's so much nicer to see real people than grossly overpaid actors in comedies that aren't even funny or predictable dramas.  "Raymond" and "24."  That's about it for me.  Maybe an occasional episode of "ER."  Gone are the days of "The Cosby Show."  But I digress...  Motown night.  It was disappointing.  Not even the best ones were that great.  Camile has to go.  John the Redhead should be next.  Sinatra's not what pop stars today are made of.  Fantasia looks like a winner so far.  What a voice!  Diana and Jasmine are great, too.  And you gotta love JPL...even on the not-so-good nights.  Rich.  Out.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just figured out how to change links.  I'm learning fast!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who am I?  I'm 24.  I'm a substitute teacher.  I'm a son, brother, uncle, and friend.  I like to type, which is why I'm surprised that I've not done this before.  Typing is theraputic.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Days like this make me wonder why I'm doing this.  I really wonder if it is worth it.  Why bother talking when  nobody  will listen?  Why go through the stress of trying to keep 30 12-13 year-olds in order when they prefer chaos?  Right now,  urlLink this ,  urlLink this , and especially  urlLink this  look  really  good right now.  I have  earned  this weekend.  I  will  enjoy it.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a dream that the Louisville water supply was somehow (I don't think it was terrorism...just a breakdown in the system) unfit for drinking and that they were rationing the purchase of bottled water inside Jefferson County.  So, Carolyn gave me $20 and said, "Get some water and take it to Bart.  Just make sure you get it before you get to Jefferson County."  Anyhow, I got to where Bart lives (not really...more like a downtown apartment complex).  It was the middle of the night and it was raining.  Nobody was there at first, then I ran into one of his roommates.  That's kinda where it ended.  I didn't get the case of bottled water to him (if I even got it at all).  Just thought it was bizarre.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      John-John is gone-gone!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just heard "Midnight Train to Georgia" by Gladys Knight and the Pips.  I don't know why, but that song puts me in such a good mood.  Had a day off today.  Nobody to tell me I looked handsome.  (Sigh.)  We'll see if my phone rings at 5:30 tomorrow morning.  Who will go on American Idol tonight?  Talked to a good friend today who is a big fan of the show.  All she said was, "He  has  to go tonight!"  We all know who  he  is.  The redhead count after tonight should be 0.  Post positions drawn for  urlLink Kentucky Derby 130  today.  The best 2 minutes in sports and an unofficial state holiday.  Thank you, God, for making me a Kentuckian.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can't beat that Latin rhythm.  (And that's the honest translation.)  FANTASIA BARRINO--She's been compared to Macy Gray before.  I didn't completely see it until tonight.  First verse was BAD. GEORGE HUFF--What a great personality!  Keep it up George! LA TOYA LONDON--Very natural dance moves.  It didn't look forced.  And a great voice.  All around AWESOME! JOHN STEVENS--He lost his place  again .  It SUCKED.  America,  if you respect music , don't vote for him!!!  (Didn't it seem like everyone--even  Ryan --was giving him the "Ya done good, best wishes, here's a copy of the home game" speech.) JASMINE TRIAS--She was so strong at the beginning of this competition.  Now it seems like she's just doing enough to survive. DIANA DEGARMO--Man!  Great rendition of a great song.  Sure, her dress got caught in the paper shredder.  Who cares?!  Great performance!  After last year's tremendous trio at the top (Ruben, Clay, and Kimberley), this year is so disappointing.  None of these players are on the same level those three were.  Top to Bottom:  Diana, La Toya, George, Fantasia, Jasmine........................John
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a first for me.  One of the elementary school teachers (who I got to know during my banking days) called me last night to see if I could sub for him today.  He teaches PE.  I hadn't done elementary.  Nothing against elementary schoolers, but I find it more rewarding to work with older youth with more "life experience."  However, we often underestimate these creatures' inate brilliance and keen perception.  For example, today a darling little girl named Diana (Kindergarten) approached me at the beginning of class and said, "You look handsome."   Totally unprovoked!   I think we need to start giving young children more credit for their smarts.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great news!  This blog is now offically certified "low carb" for those of you watching your wasteline.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Reds are tied with 4 other teams for the 2nd best record in baseball coming into today.  Hope we can keep it up!  I sang a  beautiful  song this morning at church:  "Who Am I?" by Casting Crowns.  I was  so  proud of how I did during second service.  See, I was standing there, going through the second chorus, leading up to the dramatic bridge, when one of our elders  could  have distracted me.  (And it was the only elder who possibly could've done this.)  See, he had gone upstairs to look over the congregation and get a head count.  As he came back down, he brushed the plastic thermostat cover and knocked it to the floor, creating a very noticeable "crash."  Half of the congregation instantly moved their focus away from me, as if to say, "What was that noise?!"  He spent a good part of the rest of the song fumbling with the cover as I tried my best to stay focused and keep from busting up.  I succeeded.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to report.  Spent a good part of the afternoon watching the NFL Draft.  Oh, Eli, Eli, Eli!  You'll forever be remembered as the guy who dissed sunny San Diego.  Still a little under the weather.  One would think that after so long one would run out of snot.  Just bested my  urlLink Lemonade Stand  record with $173.50 in profit.  STILL haven't beaten Carolyn's mark, which irks me, but I'm getting close.  I'm scheduled off all week (so far) because of state testing...but when I left yesterday the secretary's tone was "Don't run off to Florida on me."  Hopefully, I can get a couple of days in.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This guy  has it pegged.  Read "How do you choose a political party?"
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With testing coming up next week, we had a motivational speaker come in this morning to loosen the kids up, make them laugh, and encourage them.  It was a  very  good assembly...one of the best I've ever seen.  His name was "Mr. Rick."  He really made a connection with the students...all of them.  One of the things that really impressed me was when he asked, "How many of you, honestly, are told each day that you are stupid or that you'll never amount to anything."  A good third of the students raised their hands.  I know middle schoolers, and I know that some of them were just being goofy and raised their hands anyway.  I also know that some of the students who didn't raise their hand were saying, "That's me."  He stressed continually the value of a good education and the importance of an "I can" attitude.  Then, toward the end, he did something amazing.  He asked all the teachers to line up on the gym floor.  Being a sub I went reluctantly, encouraged by some students and was convinced that I should when another sub went down, too.  He had all the students come down and thank, hug, shake hands, etc. with the teachers.  Nearly every student made their way down and we all shook hands and shared hugs.  Then, the teacher standing to my right tapped me on the shoulder and said, "Brett wants to shake your hand, Mr. Bishop."  Brett is a student in the behavioral disorder class where I've filled in a few days this year.  I greeted him and shook his hand.  One of the most "I don't care" kids in the entire building shook  my  hand.  I nearly lost my composure but kept it together.  You have to do that as a teacher, you know.  A few teachers and  several  students lost it.  At lunch, one of the staff members mentioned that, as I had noticed, "Some of our worst students were the ones crying the most."  Realistically speaking, I don't think this will have been a day to change Sharp Middle School forever.  But, perhaps for the first time in their lives, some students today heard someone speak and said to themselves, "Yeah.  He understands me.  He knows what my life is like."  And those children listened to an inspiring message of hope.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      $158.39 profit!  Pushing  urlLink Carolyn's  mark.  I would've beaten it IF I'd have bought ice on one of the 98 and overcast days.  No doubt that would've been an easy $20-30 more.  Grrrr.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So...it's Jennifer Hudson.  WOW!  I can't believe such a talent is off the show.  (Mom just about cried...literally.)  I think Jennifer's problem (and La Toya's and Fantasia's, too) is that there were two VERY similar styles up against her.  It's such a shame that she can't win, but (as we know) winning isn't necessary to become famous.  Just ask Clay Aiken, Tamyra Gray, Justin Guarini...well...maybe not him.  But you know what I mean.  :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are the comments and my predictions, for what it's worth.  DIANA DEGARMO--If it took that long for me to find my key, I'd never make it inside.  Good chorus, though. GEORGE HUFF--Better each week.  Could give the ladies a run for their money. JENNIFER HUDSON--My pick to win this competition. JASMINE TRIAS--Pitchy and shaky...but I think it's satisfactory. LA TOYA LONDON--She hasn't let us down yet! JOHN STEVENS--Most emotion we've seen from him.  I'm not a fan, but I was impressed tonight.  Still not close to the top. FANTASIA BARRINO--Typical strong performance.  Another top pick.  My Bottom Three:  John, Diana, and Jasmine.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally hit the  urlLink blogger.com  list of the 10 most recently published blogs!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you think that's good,  urlLink look at this !
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.electionprojection.com/essay1.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      State testing starts next week.  In an effort to boost morale and lighten the mood a little, the school has started a door decorating competition.  The winning homeroom for each grade level gets a pizza party!  Usually, of course, I'm bouncing from room to room, but it just so happens that this week, I'm assigned to the same classroom all week.  Being the fun and competitive person I like to be, I  desparaterly  want to win.  The even better news is that I'm not artistic...but the student teacher who is in the room with me is.  She got the door done yesterday, while a walk around the building today showed that the majority hadn't even started yet.  I'm already starting to trash talk the other teachers.  Today, during my break, some of the top students were working on their door.  I gave them permission to go downstairs and spy...in exchange for a piece of pizza if  they  win.  Gotta cover all my bases.  :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Profit:  $77.92
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will be the first time I've talked about our group.  There are (usually) 8 of us that meet each Sunday evening in different people's homes.  We range in age from high school senior to me, 24, the senior member of the group.  Only 2 of us (myself and Chris) had been part of a group like this before.  We were selected by our minister to be the leaders, the "experts" in the group.  That first night last fall was interesting.  We're reading  The Purpose Driven Life  by Rick Warren.  Chris and I did almost all of the talking.  Some crickets filled in the gaps.  I wondered if everyone would show up the next week.  They did, and they have ever since.  We've been gradually growing and growing, becoming less afraid to open up about stuff that was important to us and that we wanted the group to know and be in prayer for.  We're all participating in the Pendleton County Relay for Life, benefiting the American Cancer Society this June (with others from our church).  Tonight we started talking about possible themes for our basket that will be auctioned off and for our team in general.  (Sports theme.  Any ideas?)  Just another sign this group is growing closer together.  Even more importantly, we're talking about different fellowship opportunities.  The topic of accountability came up.  Our author stresses the importance of memorizing Bible verses.  We're going to have a memory verse to memorize each week.  We also talked about (since we're evenly split, 4 guys and 4 girls) doing a "Guys'/Girls' Night Out."  Looks like the guys are going bowling and the girls will go see a movie.  That's awesome!  I think it would be great if we'd take some time this summer to do service projects in the evenings, just to give us more visibility and identity within the congregation.  Maybe mowing a lawn or picking up trash...fixing something for someone who needs something fixed, or just visiting someone who would enjoy the company.  Something to pray about.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      $74.68 in profit!  I think I've got this business down pat.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sure.  As soon as I brag about  my  Lemonade Stand accomplishments, this from my sister:  "$104.19 profit."  Keep in mind that she's 40, I'm 24, and I told her about this game after I saw some 7th graders playing.  Pathetic.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now it's 80 and sunny with a nice breeze.  It's a beautiful spring day, and it's a Saturday.  Glad it's such a nice day.  Glad for me, because I wouldn't have 30 kids begging me to go outside.  Especially glad for Phyllis, our neighbor.  She was on chemo last summer and had to stay indoors, away from the sun.  She  lives  for this weather and has waited so long (nearly 2 years) for it to come back.  Scored a profit of $46.49 on  urlLink Lemonade Stand  today!  A new high.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had dinner this evening (which in this house is a  very  rare thing when our "big," sit-down meal is at noon) with the parents, Bart, Brennan, Brett, and Kelsey, Brett's girlfriend.  It was the first time Kelsey had gotten to meet Mom and Dad.  I know she was nervous.  I know Mom and Dad were excited.  When they left, they were even moreso.  We were traveling from different directions, but Brett and Kelsey, Mom and Dad, and Brennan and I pulled in at the same time.  Mom and Dad were greeting Kelsey when we got there.  We moved inside where Dad tried to bore Kelsey to tears.  I'm sure Brett had told her about how Grandpa tends to go on and on about certain topics.  She seemed to enjoy herself.  Mom and Dad were so impressed, commenting many times on her winning personality and her attractiveness.  I also noticed her politeness and how she, despite her nervousness, fit in quite well.  Way to go, Brett, for picking a great girl!  Please know that she's welcome with open arms anytime.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe JPL is gone.  He did a great job last night and never really has been the worst.  I guess it goes to show that (say it with me) nobody is safe and you have to vote every week.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Days off (like today was) make me think.  If I were still at the bank (or if I had a "full-time" job), I wouldn't have had today off.  I'd be getting paid.  I'd probably be just as bored, but with a few bucks to soften the blow.  Right now, I am looking at the option of returning to school for a Masters of Arts in Teaching, which would give me the state-mandated Masters degree and teaching certification.  Five semesters worth of classes, which would mean that I could be teaching business classes on the middle or high school level starting in the 2007-8 school year.  At age 27.  That seems so far off and such a long time to wait for something full-time.  Of course, the good news is that I have nearly a full school year of classroom experience that I can relate to my coursework.  I don't know how many times over the past couple of years I've second-guessed staying in NKU's Accounting program.  I pretty much knew by the summer following my junior year that I wanted to do something else but what?  I didn't have a clue.  And many days I feel I still don't.  Anyhow, I stayed there, pushing to a degree I didn't really want, staying at a job where I was secure for the sake of having income and something to do, regardless of how claustrophobic and underutilized I felt.  Part of me, though, wishes I hadn't listened to my parents and others who questioned why I stayed at the bank after college.  (A lack of confidence on my part, I suppose.  Confidence I'm gaining each day doing what I'm doing now.)  Regardless of the fact that I felt claustrophobic and underutilized, I know where I stood there.  I was  so  respected by all my co-workers.  They had faith in me and my abilities to do work successfully and efficiently.  I wasn't a decision-maker.  I didn't sit on any important (or unimportant) committees.  But I could be counted on to do any task assigned to me.  When I announced my intentions to leave, my bosses tried everything they could to get me to stay.  They offered to give me the time off I needed.  They would've offered me more money if that was the issue.  (Obviously with me leaving for  no  job, that wasn't the issue.)  They did everything short of offering me what it all boiled down to:  moving me 18 miles closer to home to work at my local branch, setting myself up to manage the branch when the then- (and still-) current manager is ready to step down, probably within the next year or two.  A change of pace.  A future.  Hope for moving up...and 1/3 the drive time.  But, I know I'm better off.  I've become a lot more sure of myself (despite this post) and gained a lot of confidence.  And once this rough part down the road of my life is over, I'll be able to look back and see the good that came from it.  But for now, time to turn the lights on bright and step on the accelerator...destination to be determined.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK.  Person-by-person, as promised:  GEORGE HUFF--Not his best performance.  An off night.  But his personality will keep him around at least another week. JENNIFER HUDSON--Breakin' out the black dress.  Classy.  Singing "I Have Nothing."  Not true.  She has a great voice. JON PETER LEWIS--Can the dancing.  Keep singing.  Having fun, letting it show.  Sounded great! DIANA DEGARMO--Pitchy.  Not growing from week to week.  Not enough to impress me. FANTASIA BARRINO--Different.  Refreshing.  Controlled.  Amazing. JASMINE TRIAS--Aight.  She's not growing either. JOHN STEVENS--He  could  do his thing tonight.  He did.  Great rendition of a classic movie tune. LA TOYA LONDON--Seems like they always save the best for last.  What a powerful voice.  Projected Bottom 3:  George, Diana, Jasmine  Quentin Tarantino was the best celebrity judge we've seen so far.  He knows his stuff and was very constructive.  Camile did a radio interview this morning (via phone) in Cincinnati.  If you think she didn't have any personality on the show, you don't know the half of it.  Her standard answer was, "I don't know.  It's really hard to say."
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I learned about this from a 7th grade class that  loves  to play this game.   urlLink Check it out! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Time to celebrate!  Our Cincinnati Bengals will be hosting a Monday Night Football game this fall!  The first Monday night game for the Bengals in 13 years.  Seems like the Bengals have now earned the respect of the NFL and are expected to contend and bring in ratings.  Funny the things that happen when Mike Brown lowers his profile.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday.  Time for a brief look into the events of the past week here in good ol' Pendleton County in the weekly newspaper.  I know we're a small, rural county, where (let's be honest) not everyone is...shall we say...a college graduate.  Still, that is no excuse for not doing something right.  For years, I have read this newspaper and been embarrassed for our community.  Each week, the  Outlook  is sent out  full  of grammatical errors and has a very poor layout (although it has been improving).  It's almost as painful to look at as it is to read.  At the risk of sounding like Andy Rooney, let's take a look at this week's issue:  There are  8 stories  and 4 pictures on the front page.  Apparently, front page news is not a big deal in Pendleton County.  One of those stories is talking about a PCHS student named Brian:  "When  Brain  isn't practicing..."  In an Easter play picture caption/article:  "After his sentence was handed down by  Pilot ..." (My favorite.  I didn't realize they had planes in the 1st century.)  Every week in the new'spaper i's an adventure in mi'suse of apostrophe's's.  Then, there's the pathetic notice on the classified ad page:  "If You Find Mistakes:  If you find mistakes in this publication, please consider that they are there for a reason!  We try to publish something for everyone, and some people are always looking for mistakes!"  I don't  look  for mistakes.  They just can't be missed.  Get a life.  Better still, get a proofreader.  Mediocrity is not an option.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reds opened the new home of the Phillies by beating them. Got to teach 7th grade Science today. Found out I get to sub in one of my favorite classes for the next 2 days!!! 45 and rain showers all day today.  Spring, come back to us, please!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My beloved Reds are  hot  so far this year!  This team (so far) is showing that a great pitching staff can override a weak offense.  Sean Casey has done well with RISP, but the rest of the team has bombed in that situation.  Griffey is well.  (KNOCK.  KNOCK.)  The bullpen is doing a phenomenal job.  (MORE KNOCKING)  They've got nothing to lose.  That's the good thing about low expectations.  Let's go Reds!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In December, the 100th anniversary of the Wright Brothers' first flight was celebrated.  One day, in a Language Arts class I was subbing for (the "smart" group), we were reading a play and learned that their father was a bishop, but the play didn't specify a denomination.  The following exchange took place:  STUDENT 1:  How could he be married and have kids and be a bishop? STUDENT 2:  Maybe he's (phonetically) uh-piscopalian. STUDENT 1:  What's uh-piscopalian? ME:  It's a Protestant denomination.  They allow priests and bishops to marry. STUDENT 1 (sarcastically):  Are there Crap-copalians? ME:  No, no, no...it's EEEEEEpiscopalian.  E-P-I-S-C...  You just can't make this stuff up.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was the day Condoleezza (translated "smarter than God") Rice testified before the 9-11 Finger Pointing Commission.  The intentions of the commission are good on the surface, but the truth is this:   Nothing  will change what happened, and (most likely)  nothing  learned from this tribunal will aid us in the future.  What  will  help is pouring these resources into securing our homeland, providing better equipment for our military, and educating our people about what terrorists might be plotting and how to prepare and help...without crying wolf, of course.  Nobody should be looking to place blame, because we were  all  blindsided.  Remember Y2K?  Remember how absurd it seemed that terrorists would attack our water supplies, shut down our power grids, or bomb or gas our subways?  Yes, our government knew of some threats before that immortal day, but we were an innocent nation, never having experienced the unconventional terrorist methods al-Qaeda used that day on  our  soil.  Hijacking planes?  Unheard of in the USA.  Ramming them into buildings?  You've gotta be kidding me.  Remember how unifed we were in September 2001?  How we were ready to rid the world of terrorists, no matter how much it cost or how long it took?  We toppled the radical (understatement) Taliban in Afghanistan, and everyone rejoiced.  Two years later, we captured Saddam Hussein, and  some people  *cough* Democrats *cough* are politicizing this as it was unnecessary.  Never mind that his people lived in poverty while he hoarded billions.  Never mind that he and his sons ran a regime of rape and murder.  Never mind that Iraqis lived in constant fear.  And all of this is proven, not politics.  Then, there are those saying we need to be careful not to make the conflict a conflict of religion, fearing an Islam vs. Christianity conundrum.  We are fighting for Uncle Sam and freedom, ideals that know no god.    Terrorists   attacked us believing a paradise awaited them by killing thousands of "infidels."  We didn't bring religion into this war, and this is not a war against a religion.  This is a war against radicalism and the terrorists who propagate it.  Thank you, Dr. Rice, for your service to our country.  It is time to move on with a unified front.  Our enemies should not be the people across the party lines, but the people who look for ways to permeate our boundaries each day and strike fear and destruction into our lives.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it came down to Jasmine and Camile...and Camile finally went.  I wonder, since they divided them up into 3 groups, just which group was tops in voting and which was the middle 3.  I was thinking Ryan would tell us, but I should've known better.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The top two tonight were Jennifer and George.  Hands down.  John got the worst comments from the judges, but Camille has to go.  Still.  I think next week I'll start doing person-by-person comments.  Easier to track.  I think if Elton John were Elvis, he'd be spinning in his grave.  Another disappointing effort from our would-be idols.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First school day off in over a month.  And I know I'll be working at least the next 6 days.  It was a beautiful day to be off.  If I had to work in tobacco, today would be the day.  Of course, the beginning of tobacco season means another year of me doing the farmwork that I love to hate so much.  "Stand here and hold this.  Wait.  Let's take a 30-minute snack break after our hearty 1-hour lunch."  So not exciting.  It wouldn't be nearly as bad, though, if Dad weren't so critical of me.  As far as he's concerned, I'm incompetent when it comes to  any  type of manual labor.  And I'm expected to know exactly what he means by a gesture or instructions shouted from 30 feet away over a tractor engine.  I know I'm not the perfect little farmboy he always wanted.  All I expect is a little patience.  Either that or don't expect me to help.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here we go...     I am named after my Dad.   My middle name (Richard) was my uncle's name, too.  He died 25 years before I was born.   I have a  urlLink sister  16 years my senior.   I became an uncle at age  urlLink 5 .  Again at 7 and again at 10.  All boys.   Yes, I'm 24 and live with my parents.   Right now, I'm a  urlLink middle school  substitute teacher.   I think middle school students are the most unique creatures God put on earth.   Every day I see kids on the brink of being either credits to society, debts to society, or menaces to society.   I pray that they become credits to society.   I enjoy my job, but I wish it paid more.   I hold a BS in Accounting from  urlLink Northern Kentucky University .   I worked at a small, independent, community bank for six years.   I miss my former co-workers like crazy.   I lead worship at my church, Cemetery Chapel Christian.   I love to sing!   Sometimes, I think "church" is overrated.   I  never , though, doubt or question the importance of good Christian friends.   Arby's roast beef sandwiches and curly fries are God's gift to my stomach.     I've told myself for years that I need to exercise regularly, but I've done nothing about it.   My favorite sports are NFL football, MLB baseball, and NCAA men's basketball.   My favorite college basketball team is the  urlLink Kentucky Wildcats .   My cell phone plays the UK fight song.   My favorite baseball team is the  urlLink Cincinnati Reds .   Great American Ball Park is an awesome place to watch baseball.   I was 7 when I went to my first baseball game.  I went with my aunt.   When I was in high school, I went to California twice.   Those trips were 2 of the best weeks of my life.   I love to travel, but I don't get to very often.   I'm a registered  urlLink Republican .   I consider myself to be a compassionate conservative.   Election night TV coverage makes me salivate.   I don't see how anyone can give or receive an abortion and sleep at night.   Taxes would be a lot lower if the government was more responsible.   Safety, security, and schools should always be our government's top priority.   I believe marriage is between one man and one woman.  Don't change 6000 years of history for a few activists who crave attention.   Pop-up ads should be banned.  (Yes, I have a blocker.  It sucks.)   I wish I had high-speed Internet access.   My tastes in music are fairly eclectic.   I usually settle on alternative pop/rock or Christian pop.  Oldies are fun, too.   I play the trombone.  I can find my way around a piano, but not that well.   I'd love to be able to play guitar, but see  urlLink #19 .   I dream of having a wife and kid(s).   Having a girlfriend first would help.   My favorite TV shows are  urlLink American Idol ,  urlLink 24 , and  urlLink Survivor .   I also like to watch black and white shows, game shows, and  anything  live.   I don't drink or smoke.  Never have.  Can't say I never will.   I'm a WASP.   My dad farms.  My mom is a housewife.   Dad and I are Kentuckians.  Mom is an Ohioan.  I'm glad I got her accent.   The first thing I want to ask God when I get to Heaven is, "Why the heck did you put ME on a farm?"   I got 3 stitches in my chin when I was 3 when I fell off a wagon onto gravel.   I puked 3 times my first day of school.   I've puked more since then.   It makes me feel good to make people laugh.   I like to use what little Spanish I know whenever I can.   I can't sit still.  I always fidget or shake my legs.   A good friend of mine says I'm the "Voice of Reason."   I love my nephews more than they know.   I tend to obsess over finances.   I tend to obsess over a lot of things.   I highlighted my hair once and Mom almost cried.  Dad didn't notice for 3 days.   My eyes are green.  I'd rather have brown or blue, but I've been told that they are one of my best features.   When I'm home I snack  all  the time.   I'm still skinny and scrawny.   I've never left the United States, but I'd like to travel outside of the country.   I had a wreck once on a snowy road and totaled my car.   I drive a 2003 Ford Taurus SES.  It has a moonroof and a 6-disc CD changer.   I love Italian foods, but they fill me up too fast.   Mexican, American, and sometimes Chinese foods are great, too.   I don't like vegetables.  Period.   I have a good sense of direction.   I am a huge  urlLink Garfield  fan.   I think  urlLink Dilbert  is pure genius, just because it's so true.   I detest spiders.  If I see them, they're dead.   I'm not really afraid of heights.  They just give me the willies.   My only real fears in life are financial instability and being alone.   God has created a beautiful place for us to enjoy while we're here.   I just can't imagine how beautiful Heaven will be.   I truly believe there are a lot of stupid people in the world.   The only bad words I use (usually) are "crap" and "sucks."  I use them enough.   I  desperately  want a widescreen high-definition plasma television.   My favorite board game is Monopoly.   Exploring space is interesting, but I feel we gain little from it...nowhere close to the time and money we put into it.   I try to avoid caffeine.  I'm high-strung enough as it is.   My aunts, uncles, and cousins are just as precious to me as my immediate family.   I think that I look good in earth tones (brown, tan, etc.).   I'm much more of a logical thinker than I am a creative one.   My last grandparent passed away when I was 10.  I still think about them all the time.   I don't know how to swim.   Nothing feels better than listening to a great song.   I notice small details a lot of people don't see.   Dramatic sports moments make me misty-eyed.   Blue is my favorite color.   I've been to 12 states, counting Missouri and Texas (airport layovers).  California is my favorite.   I like for things (messy or clean) to be organized.   Fast food,  urlLink Wal-Mart , and Peter Jennings are necessary evils.   I prefer the term "ethnicity" over the term "race."   A favorite quote of mine is, "Support bacteria!  It's the only culture some people have."   God is constantly found in the small things.  Sometimes he does His biggest work there.   Whoever invented blogs is a genius.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alas, another Opening Day loss for the Reds.  7-4 to the Cubbies.  A 3-run double and 2 late unearned runs were our demise today.  But the parade was good, and there's nothing like Opening Day in Cincinnati.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The smell of something (probably some cleaning solution) was in the hallway on our way back from lunch.  One boy said, "My armpit smells better than that."
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just returned from a wonderful trip to the Smokies with the family.  Ate at a couple of very good restaurants, including the  urlLink Apple Barn  in Sevierville.  Wow!  Got some good shopping, browsing, sightseeing, and playing done.  And it wasn't like we were even gone!  Saw my cousin-in-law on the way down, my cousin and her family in Gatlinburg, and some friends at the Kentucky Welcome Center on the way home.  The annoyances included the typical traffic jams in Pigeon Forge, including Friday evening's Dolly Parade!  Dolly stayed in her limo to avoid the rain.  We all wish (some even more than I) that we could have avoided Dolly altogether.  Another annoyance was that we left with a van so full of crap you could barely move.  The women insisted that we take enough food to feed 1,000 men for a week.  There are only 10 of us.  Of course, we had to buy stuff when we got there and couldn't possibly leave anything behind.  Paper plates cost money!  On the way down, I got to write "100 Things About Me" as I've seen in a few other blogs.  I hope to post them in the next couple days.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Drug testing would be fair and mandatory for ALL players   Useless interleague games (such as Twins vs. Pirates, A's vs. Expos) would be banned.  The natural rivalries (such as Yankees vs. Mets, Royals vs. Cardinals) could remain, drastically cutting the annoying interleague schedule   A formal apology would be issued from Major League Baseball to the Cincinnati Reds for its overreaction and utter disrespect shown to Marge Schott.  It's a shame that she wouldn't be alive to hear it   Best regular-season record would determine who hosts the first games of the World Series.  Using an exhibition game to determine who may potentially get to host Game 7 is insane   The television deal would mandate that the Game of the Week broadcast begins the first Saturday of the season, not the first Saturday of June.  And full national coverage would be the rule   Bud Selig would be banned from baseball for the harm done to the game during his reign   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ThunderBats  surge from 11th to 5th after 10-0 victory!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I invited Kristy's Mom (aka "Mom") to 5th Sunday tonight.  It was just a "nice" thing to do.  I thought she and her family would enjoy it, which they did.  But something I didn't expect to happen happened.  Mom ran into a childhood friend of hers who she had gone through good times and bad with.  She hadn't seen her since their husbands died, each of cancer, nearly a decade ago.  As her friend was leaving, I saw them embrace.  Mom told me to let her know where the next 5th Sunday Singspiration would be.  She mentioned the possibility of seeing her friend again.  That made me feel really good.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Carolyn  needs to hear this quote from church this morning:  "Worry is celebrating tomorrow's catastrophes today."  Just checked the  urlLink ThunderBats  at the fantasy baseball page.  I have a 10-0 lead with one day to go in the week.  We're set to make a  big  move up in the standings.  Of course, when you are 11th of 12, there's only one way you can go.  Freaking a little about tonight's 5th Sunday Singspiration at church.  Some people have worked to hard on this for nobody to show up.  We're set for a great program, and I'm afraid that rain (or the threat thereof) will keep people away.  Hopefully there will be a gap in the rain and the sun will shine.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This article  from the  Weekly Standard  caught my attention.  It is lengthy but worth a read.  I thought I'd offer my humble response on this, my sounding board.  I support our troops.  I always will.  When the events of September 11 occurred, we all knew that our troops would be busy for a long time.  We stood together, and we vowed to see this difficult necessity through to its victorious end.  Nearly three years later, our troops are still busy, and while we support them as they do their unenviable jobs, it seems that support for the task has deteriorated for no good reason.  Let's investigate.   "The War on Terror is justified, but the war in Iraq has no grounds."   Many Americans still adamantly support the War on Terror, that is the war in Afghanistan, cleaning out al-Qaeda's terror training camps and searching for the elusive Osama bin Laden.  After all, it  was  his terror network that struck the World Trade Center, the Pentagon, and very nearly, I believe, the Capitol.  Many of those same Americans, however, saw no reason to attack Saddam Hussein's Iraq.  Give me a break.  "Conventional wisdom" said that Saddam harbored terrorists.  There is no doubt that he did.  Two embassies did not lower their flags to half-mast after 9/11:  Libya and Iraq.  We did not, though, attack Iraq because of a lack of remorse.  That was to be expected.  We attacked Iraq, and rightfully so, because of their links to organized terrorism, including al-Qaeda, and the desire of their government (read "dictatorship") to do harm to America.  But don't take my word for it.  Take the  Clinton  administration's word from Osama bin Laden's indictment in this excerpt from the article:   In the spring of 1998--well before the US embassy bombings in East Africa--the Clinton administration indicted Osama bin Laden. The indictment, unsealed a few months later, prominently cited al-Qaeda's agreement to collaborate with Iraq on weapons of mass destruction. The Clinton Justice Department had been concerned about negative public reaction to its potentially capturing bin Laden without "a vehicle for extradition," official paperwork charging him with a crime. It was "not an afterthought" to include the al-Qaeda-Iraq connection in the indictment, says an official familiar with the deliberations. "It couldn't have gotten into the indictment unless someone was willing to testify to it under oath." The Clinton administration's indictment read unequivocally:   Al-Qaeda reached an understanding with the government of Iraq that al-Qaeda would not work against that government and that on particular projects, specifically including weapons development, al-Qaeda would work cooperatively with the Government of Iraq.    Developing weapons, an "understanding" to be friendly to the government?  Sounds to me like there's a pretty solid connection--a connection formed long before 9/11.  A connection solid enough to justify a threat from the Iraqi government.   The African Embassy Bombings   We are all very aware of the bombings in Kenya and Tanzania.  We're also aware of the bombings of terror training camps in Afghanistan and the pharmaceutical plant in Sudan in the days after the simultaneous attacks.  The reason for the attacks in Afghanistan was obvious.  But why Sudan?  What connections were there?  Osama bin Laden had been in Sudan, but senior Clinton aides linked the plant to another familiar enemy.   The Clinton administration sought to dispel doubts about the targeting and, on August 24, 1998, made available a "senior intelligence official" to brief reporters on background. The briefer cited "strong ties between the plant and Iraq" as one of the justifications for attacking it. The next day, undersecretary of state for political affairs Thomas Pickering briefed reporters at the National Press Club. Pickering explained that the intelligence community had been monitoring the plant for "at least two years," and that the evidence was "quite clear on contacts between Sudan and Iraq." In all, at least six top Clinton administration officials have defended on the record the strikes in Sudan by citing a link to Iraq.   An attack in Sudan because of a link to Iraq.  The only reason we have so far to  not  attack Iraq would be either a total break-off in relations between Iraq and terrorist groups or because of a change in the regime or the policies of that regime.  Between late 1998 and early 2003 neither had happened.  Saddam Hussein was still in power and was still not budging.   Speaking of the Clinton Administration   The reason we are fighting such a broad-based an difficult battle right now is largely due to the failures of the Clinton administration to fight back when they had the chance.  There was the 1993 bombing of the World Trade Center.  Sure, the operatives were convicted and sentenced, but the larger issues were not resolved.  Sentencing or capturing one person will not bring in end to terrorism.  In 1998, President Clinton, amid his scandal, did little to fight (and even less to educate us about why we attacked) Osama bin Laden and his network.  He did not see the task through, which led to, albeit indirectly, the attack on the USS Cole in October, 2000 and the events of September 11, 2001.  We cannot say "what if" as to whether or not President Clinton's actions or lack of actions would have made a difference, but he at least would have made a point--an emphatic one.  Instead,  now  President Bush is left to fight a decade's worth of battles necessary to protect our country.  Sadly, support of the fickle American public is waning.  But at least those Americans are not alone.   Weak Alliances   Many have criticized our use of force and said that our reasoning for war could not be solid because we are doing most of the work on our own, without help from our allies.  In the days following 9/11, we often heard a phrase used in relation to the NATO charter:  "An attack on one is an attack on all."  It seemed at first that this would be a war between NATO and terrorists.  It didn't take long, unfortunately, to realize that it was just a dream.  Britain helped immensely and a few other countries did what they could to help, but the countries who could help us the most did the least (read "France and Germany").   The Real Issue:  The Media   It is easy to see why support may be waning overseas.  After all, France and Germany weren't attacked on 9/11.  But America was.  Why is public support waning here?  I am not one to point fingers at all, but the finger can only be pointed to one place:  the media.  The major media today are the three cable "news" channels that are really nothing more than tabloid trash outlets.  When they are tired talking about Michael Jackson, Kobe Bryant, and Scott Peterson, they try to stir things up by becoming anti-establishment.  (Notice, I didn't say "liberal.")  Cases in point:   Bob Dole .  In 1996, the media promoted the idea that Bob Dole was too old to become President, causing his age to become a major campaign issue.  As we know, he is still a popular figure today.  He is still very healthy eight years later and would have been a wonderful President.   Wagging the Dog .  After the bombings in Afghanistan and Sudan, the media was quick to jump on President Clinton, comparing his actions to a movie where a President started a war to take attention away from a personal scandal.  (President Clinton was in the middle of the Lewinsky fiasco at that time...which was his own fault...still)  A responsible media would have educated us as to why the attacks took place instead of doing whatever it could to bring in ratings and stir up controversy.   Weapons of Mass Destruction .  The media continues to attack President Bush and his administration, saying that we went to war with Iraq on false pretenses, because no so-called "weapons of mass destruction" have been found.  Let the record show that two of Iraq's worst "weapons of mass destruction" are dead and their father is in custody, never to see freedom again.  Even more sad than the irresponsibility of the media is the sheer ignorance of the American people and their inability to think for themselves.  Why rely on the "talking heads" to give you all of your opinions?  Sadly,   very   sadly, the American public has become nothing more than a bunch of brainless lemmings.  In summary, let us think for ourselves and reason.  Then, we will see the necessity of this war and the errors of the past which we are doomed to repeat.  And support our troops.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing really to report.  I've not worked this week, and (surprisingly) it hasn't bothered me.  I  am  ready to start school again.  I'm ready to go back into the classroom and do my thing.  I don't miss the kids like I thought I might.  I don't miss the other teachers that much, either.  I  do  miss them.  I would jump if my phone rang at 5:30 in the morning.  This week really has flown by.  Tonight, Mom and Dad go to Ripley to celebrate Mom's 50-year high school reunion.  For me, this means at least 5 hours of peace, quiet, and solitude!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd forgotten about this, but I have to share.  Brett's friend Brandon had some bad luck with hitting or almost hitting a deer a couple of times soon after he got his driver's license several months ago.  His younger sister is in 7th grade, and I would ask her when I saw her, "Has your brother hit any deer lately?"  One day toward the end of the school year, Alison came up to me and said, "I'm supposed to ask you about being locked in the bathroom."  D'oh!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The contestant on "Super Millionaire" right now has been ranked as the 98th Most Influential Person in Idaho.  What?!?  There  are  98 people in  Idaho ?!?!?!  Idaho has  influential  people?  I guess somebody has to motivate the potatoes.  **Special note to my fans in Idaho:  The e-mail address on this page is no longer valid.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just spent a few minutes trying to explain Rock/Paper/Scissors to Mom.  She just doesn't get it.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was clear from the beginning that this was going to be a battle.  Diana took the gloves off when she belted out the Tamyra Gray original.  Fantasia's first performance was an OK rendition of one of the worst songs ever written.  Could it be that Diana has a chance?  Round 2 gave us another strong performance from Diana.  Fantasia pulled out "Summertime" again.  Third time, since she sang it in a Monday night special.  Not sure that was the best idea.  And can she end a song other than giving us a "Yeah, yeah, yeah"?  That's really starting to get on my nerves.  The final performances, though, showed who should win this competition.  The answer is simple:   Fantasia Barrino .
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today marks two milestones.  First, the end of the school year.  I was off today...not surprisingly.  Surely even an ill teacher can go in to say goodbye to the students they've had all year.  I ended up working 119 of 148 available school days, or 80.4%.  This was the answer to a prayer.  School days off have been a rarity, obviously.  Most importantly, through this opportunity I have learned so much and grown more than I ever could have dreamed working at the bank.  Second, speaking of the bank, it was exactly 7 years ago this morning that I put in my first day.  I walked in and my first instructions were from Betty Norton, "This is what you do if you get robbed."  Oddly enough, I returned the next Saturday and day in-day out for six years.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Surprisingly, I'm not that tired right now.  The past 27 hours are a blur, but here's a timeline.  Yesterday (Which feels like earlier today), I woke up at 6:30 AM after a night of about 6 hours of on-again, off-again sleep.  By 7:00 I was out the door and arrived at school at 7:20.  By 8:00 all the kids were in homeroom and I quickly took attendance so that we could head to the cafeteria and prepare to board our charter buses, which we did by 8:45.  Then, we were on the road to Columbus.  We arrived at the museum (after taking a while to park) at 11:30 and began our tour of the  urlLink Center of Science and Industry  in Columbus, a city I had never visited until earlier today.  I mean yesterday.  After 5 1/2 hours of chaperoning 7 good, if hyper, 7th graders (and constantly coming up 1 short), it was back on the road.  We stopped to eat around 6:30 and got back to Sharp Middle School at 8:45 PM.  When 2 teachers were waiting with only 1 student, I left (around 9:15) and headed home.  After showering, eating a bite, changing my clothes and checking my e-mail, it was off to church for a lock-in.  I arrived a few minutes shy of 11:30.  I walked in the door and Adam said, "I'm so glad you're here.  We're getting ready to do 'American Idol.'  You can be one of the judges."  Of course, you know my response:  "Can I be Simon?"  The kids did their acts, and I  tried  to be the nice Simon...complete with British accent.  Adam was an Arab guy who talked about camels and I made fun of.  Doug played a third-grade educated hick who started every comment with, "Weeelll..."  Laura was the Paula Abdul--the nice one.  After that, we played hide-and-seek, then I watched a little bit of a Monopoly game.  At around 2:00, I decided to hide in a Sunday School classroom and try to sleep.  I slept on-and-off (again) until 7:00.  By then, it was time to start packing up.  And here I am.  Very fun extended day.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seen on the sign at the local elementary school:  HAVE A GRAET SUMMER
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was really concerned that tonight's post would be called "Hawaiian Idol."  But Jasmine was voted off.  A good singer, but she just wasn't at the level of Fantasia and Diana.  We still have the La Toya and Jennifer votes hanging over our heads, but I truly believe we have the right two in the finals.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I talked about careers in banking, and banking and money in general to 6 classes.  I had prepared a paper that I thought would interest them:  pictures of money from different countries around the world.  I started to pass the paper around when a student opened his wallet and handed me  20 Mexican pesos !!!  I borrowed his money and used it to illustrate some similarities and differences in Mexican money and our money.  I was thrilled, to say the least.  "Marshall, you made my day!"
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This site  is  hilarious .
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Complaints:  First, three performances is too much.  Give me two 3-4 minute performances, "real songs," instead of this 90-second song stuff.  I can get that much listening to samples at  urlLink Amazon.com .  Second, Diana and Fantasia always seem to end the show.  Let Jazzy go last for once.  JASMINE TRIAS--First performance was a little pitchy but a good Jasmine performance.  Second performance was nice.  The low register on her final song was weak, but she can hit the high notes.  A strong third place finish.  FANTASIA BARRINO--After her first performance, I was ready to crown her American Idol.  Second performance was superb.  Final performance sealed her spot in the final 2.  DIANA DEGARMO--The first performance was OK.  Second performance was good, but Diana could have done better.  Her final performance was one of her best.  The past couple of weeks have gone back and forth between Diana and Fantasia, but tonight was Fantasia's night.  I'm looking forward to next week's presumed Fantasia/Diana showdown.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was in the 7th grade hallway today, monitoring my students at their lockers when Mrs. Chesnut, who I had seen walking in the hallway (but I had expected her to turn) came up to me.  "Mr. Bishop, would you like some Jello cake?"  "Jello cake?  Sure!"  Who am I to turn down free dessert...before lunch.  So, I went down to her room and got a piece of cake.  Her daughter had made it last night.  It was  very  good.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just saw where Sammy Sosa injured himself   sneezing  .  He sat out Sunday's game in San Diego after 2 sneezes that forced back spasms.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The middle school kids noticed and liked my new haircut!  Apparently, I scare 8th graders.  This was according to a 6th grader who told me this today.  I was puzzled and asked why.  "Because you know all their names."  It made me feel good, seeing as how my goal from Day 1 was to remember as many names as possible.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today in math class, one of they boys made a comment I often hear but rarely respond to:  "Man, I hate this class.  It sucks."  This time, however, I elected to respond:  "Sebastian.  In my life I have found that if I don't enjoy something, it's most often because I don't  let  myself enjoy it.  If you think this class 'sucks,' then maybe you should try to enjoy this class and have a better attitude about it."  Of course, the peanut gallery weighed in.  "He just burned you!"
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an exhausting day, but I'm not complaining.  Started out at church at 8:00, leading BOTH worship services and Sunday School.  I came to the realization that if the government wants to make sure prisoners aren't being abused but still want to torture them that they should send them to our second service.  70 people upstairs and  little  singing.  Say something funny, nobody laughs.  At least they don't throw produce at me.  Went from there back home for an hour, during which I rushed to burn the soundtrack for tonight's graduation banquet slide show, showing pictures of the graduates.  After a brief scare, I learned that it was going to be playable.  By 2:00, I and only 9 other people were in the band room at the high school practicing for our upcoming performance at the American Cancer Society Relay for Life on June 4.  A  disastrous  turnout.  Still, we practiced, had fun, and hoped for a better crowd next week.  After that, I crashed at the sister's house for a few minutes and headed to Kristy's mom's house.  I delivered the CDs that I burned for her (see a theme here), and she thanked me for them.  I hope she enjoys the music.  By 4:30, I was wishing that what my friend Jacob said in Sunday School today was true.  He said, "It'd be nice if everything we had to do was in a strip mall where we just go from one thing to the next.  But we have to drive."  We went to Brandon F's house for our D-group.  It was a quick lesson, since we were all heading to church.  Good discussion time.  Then it was off to church for "Old Friends Night."  It started off hectic, but quickly turned OK when we got the slide show file burned to a CD (see?) and working.  It was a good night with good food, good friends, and good fun.  Brandon H. was the guest speaker.  He was with us last year and left to focus more on his studies.  We have 2 weddings coming up in the church next month.  He hadn't heard about them, and said, "Rich, we must've missed the memo.  When are we getting married?"  "Brandon.  That's not legal in Kentucky yet."  I also got to see my great friends who I sorely miss, Jared, Angie, and their 18-month-old son Brennan Joel, who I call "Brennan Joel" to differentiate from my nephew Brennan.  Things are going well with them.  When they were sitting downstairs eating, it had felt like they'd never left.  I miss them so much, but I know they're right there.  So, it's off to the showers, then to bed.  I'm exhausted, but I need more days like this.  6th grade math tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Even though it is raining outside, I'm in a good mood.  Today is one day each year I look forward to...the day I get my 50 State Quarters Proof Set straight from the  urlLink US Mint .  Michigan, Florida, Texas, Iowa, and Wisconsin.  It's the only set I collect, so I'm excited.  6 down, only 4 to go.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As in a list.  Sometimes, I get to be my obsessive self and get so afraid that I'll forget something that I come just short of writing "breathe" and "shower" on my list.  Right now, since our minister is taking a couple of Sundays off, I have a few more things on my plate.  Among them:  Creating 4 Power Point presentations for the next couple of weeks, co-planning the 5th Sunday Singspiration and this Sunday's graduation banquet, and a Sunday School lesson to prepare to lead.  I also have a Career Day presentation at school Wednesday that I need to finalize, some CDs to take to Kristy's mom, and community band season begins Sunday.  I still owe Carolyn for half of Aunt Patty's Mothers' Day flower, I take my car for an oil change in the morning,  and  I need a haircut.  Now is one of those times.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was Track and Field Day, meaning we spent the whole day outside.  This was fine, of course, as we all watched the various races and events taking place down at the track.  I was assigned to the long jump competition.  It had started to sprinkle during the mid-morning, but the chorus teacher announced over the public address system that it was just "liquid sunshine" and that "by the order of the Athletic Director, it is not allowed to rain."  It was not too bad or too long-lasting.  But then it started to get a little heavier...and heavier...and heavier.  But we still had a round to go with the 7th grade girls, and we  were  going to finish.  Then, after a cat fell on my shoulder, the chorus teacher announced, "Everyone, to the building!"  Some of us laughed, most of us cringed and froze as we made our way to the building.  Air conditioning had never felt so cruel.  My hair had gone totally flat, and my shirt held just about as much water as the Hoover Dam.  Fortunately, I had planned to participate in the dunking booth and had brought a change of clothes, just in case.  After eating a quick lunch, I went back to the empty classroom and changed my shirt, before heading to the gym for the tug-of-war.  It had been quite a while since I've had this much fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This  was a strange dream, but last night's takes the cake.  The most pious woman in my church, if not the most pious woman I  know  called me a "dumbass."   TO MY FACE! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can hear the cries of racism going up across America now.  La Toya was one to go tonight, but, let's be honest.  Sure, Jasmine was the worst, but La Toya had an off night.  Diana was the star of the show.  La Toya never showed us a lot of personality.  (Neither did Ruben Studdard, for that matter.  And he was black.  And he  won .)  When you get to this stage, anyone can win...anyone can go.  America will pick a winner in the end.  Kelly Clarkson is.  Ruben Studdard is.  And we haven't heard the last of La Toya London.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, while I was on my planning period, 4 students came in to work on an "assignment" that they were sent to my room to do.  One of those students lost her older brother yesterday morning after a long illness.  She was handling the whole thing well, and I credit her being at school in the presence of friends for helping her handle the situation.  Still, it was really gut-wrenching sitting there and hearing her ask us, "Where is my brother now?  I don't mean Heaven or Hell?  But where is he?"  One of her peers, in a matter-of-fact manner, explained that he was most likely in the basement of a hospital, naked and refrigerated.  Her questions then moved to how they were going to dress him, what he would want to wear, how her father would want him dressed, and lighter topics, like, "I wonder if they put shoes on him?"  I didn't say much.  I just sat there, strong and supportive but sad, knowing that Katie is going through something that no child should have to bear.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mom just said that she wished she hadn't left  The Dick Van Dyke Show  so early last night.  She said that the entertainment reports today said that there were people on there "from Mary Tyler Moore's show.  I can't think of what it was called."  " The Mary Tyler Moore Show ?  "Oh.  Was that it?"
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just saw on the Fox News Channel ticker that  The Passion of the Christ  broke a record as the most pirated movie at online file-sharing sites.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Disco night on American Idol.  Welcome, Donna Summer, as our guest judge!  JASMINE TRIAS--First performance was off.  Waaay off.  Her second performance was better, but it's time to say, "Aloha." LA TOYA LONDON--First performance was "safe" and reserved.  Second performance was fun.  She performs and acts like a seasoned veteran. FANTASIA BARRINO--She's anything but reserved.  Her personality will win this competition.  Voice can take you far, but personality seals it. DIANA DEGARMO--Her second performance was quite possibly her best of this competition.  The top 4 in order: Fantasia, Diana, La Toya, Jasmine
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Probably the most well-known but overlooked cultural icon of our time is Vanna White.  Ever notice that when you're playing a game and someone is doing something related to the game but not actually participating they say they are "being Vanna"?  Everyone knows what it means without thinking.  Still, how much do we  really  know about her?  Think about it.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I subbed in a 7th grade Language Arts class.  The teacher decided to make May "Book Month," so today's assignment consisted of letting the students read and make notes quietly for 30 minutes, then going outside and walking around the track until coming back in and quietly reading the last few moments of class.  I took the opportunity to get out  To Kill a Mockingbird , a  great  book I read about 10 years ago when I was a freshman in high school.  I got a few chapters in.  Kinda hard to read a lot when you're in charge.  It was relaxing just to sit there and read while the students behaved so well.  Career Day 2004 is next Wednesday.  I need to finalize my presentation on careers in banking.  The last two years, I've really enjoyed presenting, but this year, knowing the kids and having been in their classrooms, it should be even more fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really don't have anything to report, but at the end of yesterday's post, I said, "Until tomorrow."  It was a  pretty  day.  A pretty heavy shower came through around 5:00 and cooled things off...not that it was too hot.  Not a bad day off.  I think I'm going to bed early tonight.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How do they keep their teeth looking so perfectly white and clean? Do people openly ask stuff like, "Kathy, do you spell your name with a C or a K?" How do you sleep with all those creepy-crawlies around? Do you notice the camera people after a couple of days? How many times does Jeff have to explain the challenge before everyone gets the rules down? Do the survivors get paid for "endorsing" the Home Depot, P & G, etc. they plug into the game? Where do they go when they get kicked off?  For once, the final outcome was really a non-issue.  Still, fitting that an Outback survivor wins this one.  After all, it was the best Survivor with the most memorable characters and incidents.  What can top Jerri, Mad Dog, the Beef Jerky Scandal, falling into a fire, rescuing rice in a raging creek...  Until tomorrow...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trying to get used to the new-look Blogger.  Nice.  Had some good eatin' today for Mothers' Day.  Turkey, noodles, and a dessert with "46 Oreo sandwich cookies, crushed" in the ingredients list.  Yes.  46.  Planted beans, tomatoes, cabbage, etc. in the garden.  Not good eatin' where this meat-atarian is concerned.  Tried to keep from getting burned.  I'll know tomorrow if I succeeded, but we weren't out in the sun too long, so I should be OK.  Donations of aloe are not yet necessary.  Speaking of eating, I gained 2 pounds today!  Woo hoo!  I'm up to a scrawny 122.  I would love to be up to a healthy 140 or so by Labor Day.  Eat, eat, eat.  Exercise, exercise, exercise.  I'd rather have muscles than a gut.  Tired of being a weakling.  I have 5 (count 'em) Power Points to do for church the next 2 weeks.  2 morning services each week and 1 evening.  I'm trying to get them done now, but it looks like they'll wait until tomorrow.  Survivor finale time.  Must pay attention.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have deleted a couple of recent posts.  Not something I want to be in the habit of doing, but I blew off my steam and feel better now.  Happy Mothers' Day!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today as I was walking out of the staff workroom, I was mobbed by some 6th graders changing classes.  Among them were a couple of the class drama queens.  STUDENT 1:  Mr. Bishop!  What are you doing today? ME:  7th grade Social Studies. STUDENT 2:  Why couldn't you do 6th grade Social Studies? ME:  Sorry, but they called me for 7th. STUDENT 1 (looking at Student 3):  Typo.  (Turning to me) Maybe, you could give them food poisoning, and then you could sub for us!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...And they are all women!  In an American Idol first, the final four are all the same gender.  It was 2 and 2 the first season, then 3 guys and Kimberley Locke last season.  These four all  could  win (and one  will ) but I look for it to come down to Fantasia and either La Toya or Diana.  Translation:  Pack your bags, Jasmine.  Who will be the Disco Diva next week?  Stay tuned!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I liked the format, for starters.  Usually at this stage they do one song at a time, but making them do the songs back-to-back helps us see how they handle transitions and a more "concert" situation.  And my comments:  DIANA DEGARMO--Classy performances.  Started a little weak, but that was forgotten by the strong ending.  At least 1 more week. GEORGE HUFF--He's the only guy left, so he's safe.  Aside from that, a solid pair of performances. LA TOYA LONDON--2 of 3 judges on their feet.  That's as good as it gets.  She found her groove and did a superb job. JASMINE TRIAS--One comment:  If you're going to play the part, do all you can to sell it.  She didn't  dress  the part.  Blue jeans and big band don't mix. FANTASIA BARRINO--Queen and Barbra Streisand are not typical big band fare, but it worked.  And it worked  well .  Bottom Two:  NO QUESTION.  Jasmine and George
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was in a good mood today, supervising a couple of students in a well-behaved Keyboarding class.  One of the brightest 6th graders in the building was typing away.  Unbeknownst to him, I assume, he shot back at the boy in front of him who was disturbing him.  "Dillon, if you don't stop, I'm going to kick my boot up your butt so far you'll taste it."  I tried my best to suppress the big grin on my face when I said, "What was that, Eli?"  "Well, he's  bugging  me!"
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a good day at school today.  All of the classes were well-behaved.  I was pleased.  The building seemed pretty mellow today.  Heard a story today from a teacher who was working at an auction this weekend.  She  thought  she saw a friend from  her  homemakers club bending over to get to a box, so she goosed her.  It wasn't her friend.  And to fully appreciate the story, you have to know her and the goosee.  Got an "I feel your pain" e-mail from Carolyn this morning regarding yesterday's "Blowing Off Steam" post.  That was comforting.  Maybe this evening my Reds can win one...a good ending to a good day.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am NOT in a good mood.  Sundays are a day to relax and spend time with people.  I know that, you know that, and the American people know that.  For me, Sunday means spending time with my friends at church in Sunday School and in our D-Group on Sunday evenings.  Well, as had been planned for the week, we would go to Uncle Marvin's Sunday.  OK.  Fine.  I'll probably miss D-group, but that's OK.  Mom and Dad had planned on going to early service, so I assumed we would go home after Sunday School, get there around 12:30 and spend the afternoon.  This morning, Dad informed me that we would be taking  my  car.  OK.  Fine.  Then, at church, Mom says, "We're leaving after church.  We're not staying for Sunday School."  My knee-jerk response was, "That's it.  Just because I live under your roof doesn't mean you dictate my schedule."  So, we spent the day away and got home around 7:30...long after my D-Group meeting had ended.  I'm tired of doing things just because I'm "expected" to or guilted into doing them.  I'm tired of not being able to do things I want to do.  I'm REALLY tired of going places and sitting, sitting, sitting while my Dad monopolizes the conversations.  We could have accomplished all we set out to do today  and  been in home by D-Group time.   Please  don't misread me.  I enjoy spending time with my family, and I wish I could more often.  Still...you know what I mean.  I did salvage  some  good from today:  I met my 9-month old cousin Holden for the first time.  This is my Holden impression ---> :-D  I got to see my cousins'  HUGE  homes.  I'll  never  be able to afford a home like those.  Of course, I really don't think I'd want to.  Two people don't need 4000 square feet.  I also learned that 95.3 FM in Lexington has changed from a K-Love (Christian Adult Contemporary) affiliate to an Air-1 (Christian Hit Radio) affiliate.  Something to note when traveling to Lexington.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm thinking the only way he won't be  Jeopardy!  champion will be to resign.  Nobody will beat him.  The man is smarter than Condoleezza Rice.  Today was his 21st victory bringing his total winnings to  $697,760 .
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know some of you read this, so I thought I'd post the quarterly returns for the four 401(k) mutual funds.  (Of course, you can count on the money market to pay you about $.01 per $1,000 invested.)  Don't take these for gospel but rather a good approximation.  You know, give or take 10 to 20 percentage points.  International Fund:  -0.30% S & P 500 Fund:  +1.64% Mid-Cap Fund:  -1.79% Bond Fund:  -3.60%
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you want to watch the game  and act like you know something about it , learn the Infield Fly Rule.  When it's called, the batter is out if the ball is caught, dropped, lands on the first baseman's head, is swallowed or never comes down.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No...not the blogging streak.  That's at 32 days.  Ken Jennings (of  Jeopardy!  fame) is up to $622,760 over 19 days.  Both unprecedented feats.  Tonight at band practice, I was the trombone section.  And, if I may say so, the trombone section sounded pretty good.  As much as I didn't want to go to practice tonight, I had a good time.  I always do.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had  3  students in our group.  One would think that we would have had a cake day.  No.  Today was one of the more stressful days of the last 4 weeks.  Maybe because we spent the day with the 4-5 group and I had to put up with Kevin WHO HAS TO SCREAM EVERYTHING HE SAYS.  And Bobby, Amber's Younger brother, just needs to learn the meaning of the word  restraint .  Missy, the boss two levels up, asked Carolyn if I was enjoying myself.  She was concerned, because it's a tough group and Carla isn't (to her) "helping much."  I don't know if things would be better on my own...or with someone else.  Who knows?  Off to community band practice.  For the 2nd time in 4 nights.  Sigh.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know I complain about all those people who just check "Yes" without even thinking about it.  This morning we had elections.  I actually thought about it, though, before I marked straight "Yes."  How could I say no to any of them?  Ron is a very logical man.  Billy and Carroll agree with my views, and David F. is just a great guy.  Impossible to say "No."  And I didn't have to say "No" because Mark didn't run!!!  Happy day!  Kara visited, too, this morning with her brother and sister-in-law.  I think they're intent on fixing us up.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Doing the news live from Baghdad tonight.  What an incredible individual.  Puts  urlLink Dan Rather  to shame.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Best line of the show last night, as he was going for a Daily Double:  "I'll bet you don't get a lot of Mormons betting big in the 'Bartending' category."  Total Winnings (so far):  $601,760
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just found out that there is a rift between a dear friend of mine at church who I am usually in agreement with and another member (also a dear friend).  Apparently, Aprile provided some feedback on the form that the VBS committee provided to workers that was not welcome and she received a scathing e-mail from Maria.  I don't know the specifics of either side.  All I know is that Cheri M. gave Aprile a heads-up after a sleepless night, because she knew what was coming.  I usually agree with Maria on issues and may even agree with some of the things she said to Aprile, but sending a sharp response to requested feedback is unnecessary.  If you don't like it, disregard it.  Don't attack someone when you've asked for their opinion.  I just hope that this issue is resolved quickly and doesn't bleed over into other people of the church.  This is just ugly stuff.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night before I went to bed, I checked the weather.  Fridays are pool days at Summer Recreation, and pool days have been rainy days.  The weather said there was a 20% chance of rain.  It rained.  Fortunately, it didn't rain much.  It remained overcast but stayed dry and we got in our full 3 hours.  I just checked the weather for Tuesday.  It says partly cloudy.  I'm taking my umbrella.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Local television news has gotten out of hand.  Gimmicks abound and Cincinnati has one station that is really pushing the limits of insanity in its promos.  Every time channel 9 promotes one of its upcoming newscasts, someone always says, "We're on your side with all these stories plus breaking news, tonight at 11:00!"  What if nothing is going on?  As I've mentioned to others before, is Clyde Gray going to go out and torch a building if it's a slow news evening?  (And don't even get me started on "Local 12.")  Why don't they just change their slogan to  urlLink "We're Investiga-Awesome!" ?   On another note:   urlLink Carolyn  just didn't tell me something interesting. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      17 days, $552,959.  Those are the total winnings for Ken on  Jeopardy! .  Since they doubled the clue values a couple of years ago, I've been waiting for this.  At first, it seemed people gambled more and winners weren't making much more than before values were doubled.  Now that they've taken away the 5-day winning cap, it has been a blast to watch this guy who, to the avid watcher, has become as common to the show as Alex Trebek.  This has become such a story that it was a topic of conversation on ESPN's daily afternoon debate-fest,  Pardon the Interruption .  All I know is that when Ken is gone, he will take a  big  check back home to Utah and will leave a record that will be extremely difficult to break.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The possible world-record blogging streak is now at 28 days.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had only 5 kids in our group today.  It was  wonderful !  We did crafts in the morning before the rescue and drug dogs did their demonstrations.  What an amazing sight!  Those dogs pick up scents and go to work.  And their reward is a tennis ball.  Oh, how simple the life of a dog.  After lunch, we went to the gym to play with the 4-5 group.  Something bad ALWAYS happens, but today it wasn't one of our kids!  Anthony kicked the ball directly at TJ.  Even though TJ was being annoying, that deliberate action was totally uncalled for.  We spent the rest of the day outside after I made the greatest comeback in the history of HORSE against Carla.  I had H-O-R-S before she had anything.  And I WON!  Bryon had an afternoon activity for the K-1 group.  They were going to wash his car.  And they did.  His, Samantha's and Stephen's.  Get 5 and 6-year-old kids around water and they'll have fun.  One of the boys came onto the playground later saying, "K-1 Car Wash is here!"  Going to have to have Phillip and Brennan over for supper so I can whip up some fettucine alfredo for them.  They don't know what they're missing.  Yum!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had music day today.  A lot of singing and a lot of fun.  I just wish it was rainy.  We spent too much time inside and it was a  PERFECT  day.  A good day on Wall Street today.  My IRA is happy.  Still getting used to this Tivo thing.  I get annoyed when I forget to fast-forward through the commercials.  Speaking of forgetting, I have community band practice  Friday  evening.  I don't think I'm going to remember as we usually do this on Sundays.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every once in a while, when you're working with kids every day...How do I put it?  They...well...they get on your last nerve.  Today was such a day.  But I'm home, I'm ready to eat a good supper, and if I knew I'd have peace and quiet, I'd take a shower, kick back with some popcorn, chips, etc. and watch  The Fellowship of the Ring .  I think I'll have to settle for  Jeopardy!  and the Reds/Mets game.  Still, no teens, pre-teens, or anyone under 4 feet tall will be around me.  I'll take advantage of it.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and the ThunderBats are in 8th, 20.5 games behind the leaders.  This week we face the #5 team in the league, the Shady Cubs.  I like my chances.  Fantasy Baseball season is starting to heat up.  Be excited with me.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been making a lot of assumptions lately, mostly at my job.  I know better, because what they say about assuming usually comes true.  It has for me, anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes!  It finally happened!  The monkey is off his back and onto someone else's.  A great accomplishment for a man who is finally on top of his game.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a couple of down weeks for the team.  We suffered 2 losses with a combined score of 17-3.  However, things are on the rebound.  We have an 8-2 lead coming into the final day of the week.  This would set us up to gain 2 spots in the standings, moving from 10th to 8th.  My goal is the top 6 so I can make it into the championship bracket come September.  As of now, we'll be 19.5 games out of 1st place come tonight.  I've got my work cut out for me now at the midpoint of the season.  Of course, you can keep up with the progress of the Ky ThunderBats by clicking on the link in the Links section of this page.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Only one person outside of the "inner circle" knows this.  "Inner circle" being the D-group people who've listened and the parties involved.  And Susan C. happened to be sitting beside me at lunch on a day I was feeling particularly talkative and open.  I know (think) she's not said anything to anyone.  Neither have I.  Until now.  Last fall, Jacob, Amanda, and Jacob's mother, a teacher at the middle school, began plotting to match me up with Kara, Jacob's older sister.  In January, Mrs. Orr sent me a very nice e-mail that included Kara's e-mail address.  We have been trading e-mails a couple of times per month since then and finally talked face-to-face tonight.  It took me a while to go over and introduce myself, especially since I wasn't 100% sure the person I'd pegged as her was actually her.  (I wonder who is going to harass me about this at church tomorrow.)  We talked about this and that.  She's really easy to talk to.  I like that.  A little shy when it comes to the dance floor.  I was there once, but now I just don't care.  Get out there and look like an idiot with everyone else.  I know at least one person was pleased with our conversation.  I went to tell Amanda goodbye as we were preparing to leave.  "We're leaving in a minute.  Have a safe trip.  I'll see you when you get back."  "Okay."  Then she mouthed, "Say 'bye' to Kara."  "I will."  I said goodbye and told her to e-mail me (and that I'd do the same).  If nothing more, tonight I learned that I have another friend I can turn to.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, for the second Saturday in a row two friends tied the knot.  Jacob and Amanda were married this afternoon in a wonderful ceremony at church.  A few years younger than Chris and Bridget but just as much made for each other.  And Jared was part of the ceremony!  I was fine last week, but when Jared starting talking about Amanda growing up and serving as her Youth Minister, it brought back memories and made me again realize that even though when they come around it seems like they've never been gone, they have and there is a void there.  I couldn't help but shed a few tears.  We went on to the reception where we ate some  wonderful  food and danced, danced, danced again.  It was a time for fun, friends, and pleasant conversation.  Clay and Mandy tormented me:  "Congratulations on catching the garter."  "I didn't catch it."  "Of course you didn't!  You're not going to with your arms crossed."  And even though our church  stinks  and is not functional for regular church activities, it's a great place for weddings and funerals.  It was beautifully decorated and set a perfect mood for the ceremony.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Partially edited response.  Glad someone sees it my way.  Next time, though, I wish she'd not hold back so much.  ******************************************  1.  You're right.  CCCC will never change because they don't have vision because vision means that things change and they don't want that.  2.  Why in the world would a response to something such as that attack on Jared NEED to go before the board (bored)?!!  We're not told as Christians to take such matters before the board; we're told to address them personally, then with another person if the personal contact doesn't work, then to take the person out of fellowship.  Having a vote on something so outright outrageous IS outrageous!  (Rich's comment:  EXACTLY.  The elders who felt compelled to should've gone anyway.  And that person is too stubborn to change and  should  be taken out of the fellowship.  I've barely spoken to the man since.)  3.  Why do you think we left?  You can only stand so much of do-nothing anything.  These folks have no faith in God; they only have faith in their building with its stained-glass windows (or a camp with its all-business set-up).  They don't care about people (our father included); they just care that their pockets aren't called upon and that their sense of decency is not tarnished by some kid with piercings, dyed hair, and a need for someone to accept him--which they will refuse to do in the first place.  And to top it all off, that kid and his family may use the facilities without donating any money to pay for them.  Shocking!  4.  When people there get guts, it will be for the best.  I grew up with that crew and I still get upset with myself because I'm never sure how to deal with controversy and outright wrongs.  I hold them partially responsible.  Maybe I'm wrong for doing that, but I do anyway.  I saw them gloss over things too many times (such as the incident you cited) just because they're a bunch of cowards who don't want anyone to be upset with them.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, I'm not talking about separation of church and state (or prohibiting the free exercise thereof).  That's another blog post.  I'm instead talking about the pathetic state of affairs at good old Cemetery Chapel Christian -- Where Leaders Fail To Lead.  Our leadership...no...excuse me...our Board of Elders and Deacons has done nothing for years to address issues and solve problems that are important.  Among them, the fact that the church building itself no longer adheres to safety codes, disability codes, or even common sense.  The stairwells are narrow.  Two people cannot pass each other.  The classrooms are not functional.  Walls and doors are paper-thin.  During Vacation Bible School, I was continually annoyed and distracted my two nights of teaching by noises coming from the nursery across the hall and from the kitchen area.  They all had the right to speak, but I feel I had the right to a quiet classroom.  Never mind the fact that due to a growing congregation we went to two Sunday morning services 16 months ago.  Some people still can't see why we did that.  For one, we were growing too quickly to allow it to stop simply because we were out of room.  For two, there was division within the musicians due to using more modern music during the worship service.  Going to two services greatly placated some heavy emotions on my part.  In 2002, before going to two worship services, we had a building proposal.  The board generally approved it for a congregational vote, but I know some board members didn't even want it to go that far.  Like the members of the church shouldn't have even had a say, even though there was support for it.  After that, two services were clearly going to be the solution, but it took nearly a year to begin them.  A couple of months later, Jared and Angie left after 7 wonderful years.  They left due in part to the building proposal failing even though just under 1/4 of the congregation opposed it.  The other part was because a member of the church verbally attacked Jared at the store (the town square) in front of God and everybody.   Nothing  happened.  A member told Jared (who built the youth program from  nothing ) was lazy.  " You sit on your ass all day and don't do a damn thing. "  The issue went before the board and they decided "to let sleeping dogs lie" as opposed to going to the member in question.  (At least one elder was ready to go.  All they had to do was say the word.)  Sometimes, those dogs can come back and bite your ass.  (Even if you don't have a donkey)  So is the CCCC board.  So, CCCC stands now with a  laissez-faire  board that does nothing, a congregation where the will of the minority rules, and a minister who easily (and rightfully so) becomes frustrated by the lack of action.  The fact is that nothing will change at the Chapel.  No building plan will pass.  No members will find  their  ministry in service to the church but will continue just putting their time in on Sundays.  There will be no excitement.  The minority will continue to either rule or complain endlessly when something doesn't go their way.  There is only one way to fix the problems we have at the Chapel:   Clean Out the Board   Each year deacons and elders are voted on for 3-year terms.  Every man always passes the vote.  Never in my 24 years, and I'm willing to guess never in history has  anyone  failed to be elected.  People just automatically check "Yes" and drop their ballots in the plate, regardless of the leadership abilities of that person.  (Of course, I'm willing to be the ranch that 2/3 of the people don't really know about leadership abilities or the lack thereof.)  I saw the ballots from the last election, and a couple of board members did get a few "No" votes--a couple of members who  needed  to get more "No" votes.  (Yes, my father was one of them.)  The congregation needs to hold the board accountable to their decisions and to make sure they are looking forward and in the church's best interest.  I've been asked to serve, but I refuse to serve as long as my father is on the board.    Many times over the last 5 years I've wanted to walk out of those doors.  Relationships have kept me from doing that.  My roles and responsibilities in the congregation have kept me from doing that.  Still, I wonder how long I can last in such a stagnant, lukewarm environment.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning we were waiting to leave on our trip to the park when Brennan came up to me, inquiring as to the whereabouts of his friend.  BRENNAN:  Where's Phillip? ME:  He's waiting on the bus. BRENNAN:  The bus is already here. ME:  Yes.  He's waiting  ON  the bus.  As in board. BRENNAN:  Yeah.  I'm bored, too.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not exactly, but Summer Rec is turning into  The Young and the Petty .  It seems that people are getting upset over a lot of things.  Some people say that Nancy is "reaming" us, when really she's just correcting situations, not necessarily people.  Nancy's son is seen as having "preferential treatment."  He's a good kid.  He's trustworthy.  He just needs to learn not to flaunt his perks.  Nancy is upset about people leaving early or taking days off.  That I totally understand.  People just need to stop acting stupid.  We're counting down the days until we're done.  (Just like I'm counting the blogging streak.  21 days)  On another front, Mr. Aulick wants to run a "business proposition" by me.  I don't know for sure, but I think it has something to do with what Nancy told me.  She  may  be moving to the alternative school which would leave me in the #1 sub position, meaning I would work pretty much every day at Sharp Middle School.  Not that I didn't this past year, but this would make it nearly guaranteed...and a possible answer to my prayers.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw  Showboat  at the Kincaid Regional Theatre today.  Two people commented to me on the way out about how well-behaved the kids were.  I breathed a huge sigh of relief.  It was good, for a musical.  I like musicals, but they are cheesy.  How often in real life do people come together and burst out into a song never heard before and nail all the words, melodies, and harmonies?  Sorry, but that's how my mind works.  Carolyn and Bart are stuck in Newark, NJ right now.  100% metropolitan area, but it's still called the Garden State.  Go figure.  They'll be getting home about 3 hours later than first planned.  I told them to make the most of their time in New Jersey.  They hope to see the New York skyline light up.  Makes me jealous.  When I was a HS senior, I had  no  desire to go to New York and Washington on the senior trip.  I chose to go to Orlando with my band friends, who I was  much  closer to.  I'm glad I did, but I want to go to New York and Washington now.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heard Fantasia's single on the radio today for the first time.  Worked concessions again tonight.  No hot dogs, though, so no grilling for Brennan.  Really ticked at McDonald's for forgetting to put sweet and sour sauce in the bag with my freaking McNuggets.  Waiting now for Griffey to hit #500.  Intentional walks don't cut it.  Cousin Mabel (a young 85) continues to improve after a valve replacement.  She was sitting up and eating today after yesterday's surgery.  I'm on call to pick up Bart and Carolyn at the airport tomorrow evening in case Brian doesn't make it home in time.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Brennan had his first experience cooking with a gas grill Saturday morning.  He was going to let me use it, but he quickly picked up on it.  Now he wants one.  Go figure.  Today was a good day.  Dodgeball this morning and most of the afternoon outside.  Right now, you take all the outside time you can get.  I didn't realize we had a monsoon season.  Found out today that Randy checks my blog.  And I thought nobody but Carolyn did.  Yay!  He enjoyed my locked-in-the-bathroom comment from Alison, Brandon's sister.  I didn't mention the story about getting locked in the  classroom .  I was doing 7th grade Social Studies one day and the doorknob was loose.  I was closing the door during my planning period and the doorknob just fell off in my hand.  I called the office, then repaired it myself.  The custodian tightened it.  Of course, one of the kids happened to be in the office at the time and knew everything.  Such is my luck.  Makes me wonder why I still lock doors.  D-Group under Dave & Cheri's tree last night.  Very peaceful.  Our weekly tangent was about Presidents.  Who was President when you were born?
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I guess I'm going rafting in Tennessee next month.  Maria put  my  name on the list.  David F. said this morning, "Oh, Rich, I see you're going rafting," to which I replied, "What?  No, I'm not."  I knew the writing wasn't mine, and it smelled of Maria.  During the service, I asked for a confession.  She quickly admitted that she was the guilty party.  I didn't take my name off the list.  God help me.  The blogging streak has now hit 17 days.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. WHAT IS YOUR FULL NAME?  Alvin Richard Bishop, Jr. 2. WHAT COLOR PANTS ARE YOU WEARING?  Light grey shorts 3. WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO RIGHT NOW?  Wednesday's  The Young and the Restless  4. WHAT WAS THE LAST THING YOU ATE?  Cookies and doughnuts at church 5. DO YOU WISH ON STARS?  Only when I feel like it, which isn't very often 6. IF YOU WERE A CRAYON, WHAT COLOR WOULD YOU BE?  Blue 7. HOW IS THE WEATHER RIGHT NOW?  Sunny, a little muggy, T-storms are supposedly coming 8. LAST PERSON YOU TALKED TO ON THE PHONE?  I think Carolyn, Friday morning from Puerto Rico 9. DO YOU LIKE THE PERSON WHO SENT YOU THIS?  Of course!  I like anyone who lets me express my opinions  10. HOW ARE YOU TODAY?  Pretty good.  A little worn out 11. FAVORITE DRINK?  Caffeine Free Pepsi 12. FAVORITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK?  Don't drink alcohol 13. FAVORITE SPORT?  To play:  Dodgeball.  To watch:  Baseball 14. HAIR COLOR?  Brown 15. EYE COLOR?  Green 16. DO YOU WEAR CONTACTS?  No 17. # OF SIBLINGS?  One older sister 18. FAVORITE MONTH?  Probably June 19. FAVORITE FOOD?  Chicken Casserole 20. LAST MOVIE YOU WATCHED?  Theater:   The Passion of the Christ  (I think)  DVD:   Monty Python and the Holy Grail  21. FAVORITE DAY OF THE YEAR?  Any day I can fill with good times  22. WHAT DO YOU DO TO VENT ANGER?  I don't vent.  I stew 23. WHAT WAS YOUR FAVORITE TOY AS A CHILD?  Probably a road atlas 24. SUMMER OR WINTER?  Summer 25. HUGS OR KISSES?  Hugs.  There are a couple people in this world who I love to hug because they make me feel so loved and appreciated 26. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA?  Depends 27. DO YOU WANT YOUR FRIENDS TO WRITE/ E-MAIL BACK?  Yes.  I like getting personal e-mails 28. WHO IS MOST LIKELY TO RESPOND?  I'm not sending it.  It's in the blog 29. WHO IS LEAST LIKELY TO RESPOND?  I'm not sending it.  It's in the blog 30. LIVING ARRANGEMENTS?  With Mom and Dad 31. WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU CRIED?  Friday night when Nancy Reagan was crying over the President's casket 32. WHAT IS UNDER YOUR BED?  A guitar (in a box) 33. WHAT DID YOU DO LAST NIGHT?  Went to Chris and Bridget's wedding 34. FAVORITE SMELLS?  Any good food cooking 35. WHAT INSPIRES YOU?  Encouragement from others 36. WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF?  Being injured in some way that I would never fully recover 37. PLAIN, BUTTERED OR SALTED POPCORN?  All of the above 38. FAVORITE CAR?  I love my Taurus 39. FAVORITE FLOWER?  Haven't given it much thought 40. NUMBER OF KEYS ON YOUR KEY RING?  1 41. CAN YOU JUGGLE?  No.  I'm not coordinated 42. FAVORITE DAY OF THE WEEK?  Saturday because I can relax 43. WHAT DID YOU DO ON YOUR LAST BIRTHDAY?  Went to church  44. DO YOU OWN A DONOR CARD?  No
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight, I celebrated the union of two people who have become dear friends of mine over the past year.  Chris and Bridget are in my Sunday School class and my Sunday night group.  They've been together for 5 years and truly belong with each other...so much so that you almost have to say it like "ChrisAndBridget" when you're talking about them.  It has been a pleasure to get to know them better, and I wish them the best as they move on to this new phase of their life together.  And Aunt Cora made it to her great-granddaughter's wedding!  It was so nice to see her there.  As for the ceremony, it ran super-smoothly.  Aside from a CD skipping and Pam's torch having trouble firing up, everything was wonderful.  Gary did a great job with the ceremony itself.  When we made it to the reception hall, we ate right away.  Then, after some food and some conversation, it was time for cake, then dancing.  It was a lot of fun.  I even got to match wits with Kyle H.  I told him he needed to get out on the dance floor instead of standing in the corner drinking pop with Austin K. and meet some ladies.  "Let's see what my choices are.  3rd graders or 3rd graders?"  I informed him that there were some ladies his age or even older than he is if he really wanted to get out there.  He quickly shot back at me, but I had told him I had been out on the floor and had fun.  So, here's to love, good friends, and good times.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week is  finally  over!  A great VBS and a fine start to Summer Recreation, but MAN I am glad to slow things down.  It really makes me wonder how I spend my spare time.  If I can put in an 8-4 day of work, come home and eat, then go to church for 2 1/2 hours, come home and go to bed every day for a week, how am I really spending my time?  Something to ponder...but not now.  I'm too tired.  We got rained out at the pool today.  Thankfully, we were on the road when the heavy rains hit.  We were smart and left when the sprinkles started.  Of course, that big, black cloud coming our way was a good sign that we should hit the road.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I noticed a little boy in the K-1 group today.  I could tell from a distance the shirt he was wearing had a Bible verse on the back.  Later, I walked by him when they were playing.  I stopped him and said, "Mecaiyal, let me read the back of your shirt."  He turned around, and I read the passage from Ephesians.  I let him go and he said, "Put on the armor of God."  That little moment was priceless.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Minor security breach this afternoon in Washington, DC, as an unidentified plane flew into restricted airspace.  People were told to make a run for it and for about 10 minutes, things were up in the air.  It was quickly determined that the plane was fine and the threat was over.  Later, the plane  had  been identified.  It belonged to the  Kentucky  State Police.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a little over 2 months and I've already hit 100 posts!  Let's pop open a bottle of bubbly...or maybe Aquafina...and reminisce.  It all started with a  urlLink simple post  about who I am.  We've been through it all.  I've made my American Idol opinions made known to the world, and we saw Fantasia win, just as we should have.  I shared 4 examples of Why I Love Middle Schoolers, including the hilarious (and infamous)  urlLink EEEEEEpiscopalian  story.  I shared  urlLink 100 Things About Me , barely scratching the surface.  I've gone on a couple of political rants, presenting my rational and  correct  opinions.  There was the  urlLink Lemonade Stand  contest.  We took away the carbs, too.  And, of course, the ThunderBats are still going strong.  And right now I'm in the midst of a 12-day blogging streak.  Here's to the next 100 posts!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We took our first trip to Kincaid Lake State Park's pool this afternoon.  Things were going well, but then everyone had to sit out for 30 minutes, because some kid (THANK GOD it wasn't one of ours) took a dump in pool.  Yes, #2 IN THE POOL.  #1 is common, but #2?!  Poor Kyla said, "This is  disgusting !"  Glad it's not my job to clean it up.  Heard the song "All Things New" from Steven Curtis Chapman's upcoming release  All Things New .  Great stuff.  Can't wait!  Today on Y & R, Nikki asked Sharon how she could be sunbathing "at a time like this."  NEVER ask questions when Sharon is in a two-piece swimsuit.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK.  How  stupid  is Kevin.  Using a tranquilizer on his nurse?  He's going to stay locked up forever when he gets caught.  You know he'll get caught.  He acts like he's not mental, but he is.  Wonder what Nick is planning to do to Cameron.  I wonder if he's going to hire a hitman.  He is very cryptic when he talks to Sharon about it.  Maybe he could get Kevin to be the hitman, then he could get off on insanity and Nick would be as free as a bird!  Grace is  so  evil.  I love it when she rears her head.  (Notice I didn't say  ugly  head.)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was fun.  The middle schoolers were a little immature...disappointing, actually.  But it was still a good time.  We didn't go without casualties, though.  Within the first hour, Phillip scraped his elbow something awful, and Erin (who is a high school senior-to-be) turned her ankle.  After Carla helped her in:  "Erin, are you OK?"  "Yeah, RICH, I'm fine.  Don't make fun of me."  "I'm not making fun of you.  I'm trying to be compassionate."  "Yeah, you're going to go tell Brett, 'Guess what Erin did?'"  "I wouldn't do that."  "Yes you would."  She was fine after some rest and a pack of ice.  Brett has a song stuck in my head, "Penny and Me" by Hanson.  A sad week of remembrance begins...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's services were down at church.  Tobacco had at least something to do with that.  I'm sure summertime had a lot to do with it, too.  Carolyn and Bart are (presumably) on their way to San Juan.  The flight to Newark arrived 14 minutes late; the flight to San Juan took off 6 minutes late, so they had 22 minutes to go from one plane to another.  I hope they made it to the gate.  Summer Recreation starts tomorrow.  So does VBS.  It's going to be a busy week.  My ThunderBats are losing 9-1 this week.  That will likely be the final score.  I should fall to 8th place.  ThunderBat of the week is Ken Griffey, Jr.  5 home runs and 8 RBI.  Saw a good deal of President Reagan coverage today.  More to come this week, I know.  Part of me right now wishes I had been a little older during his Presidency so I could have appreciated what a fantastic leader he was.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is a sad day here in America, as we honor the life of our 40th President, Ronald Reagan.  He was the first President I remember.  I liked him, just because he was the President.  The more I learned about him, his way of governing, and the impact he made, the more and more I liked him.  America has lost a great citizen, and (dare I say) perhaps its last truly great President.  Some Quotes:  " The men of Normandy had faith that what they were doing was right, faith that they fought for all humanity, faith that a just God would grant them mercy on this beachhead or on the next. It was the deep knowledge  and pray God we have not lost it  that there is a profound moral difference between the use of force for liberation and the use of force for conquest."  On 40th anniversary of Normandy invasion, June 6, 1984    "I've always stated that the nearest thing to eternal life we'll ever see on this earth is a government program."  April 1986    "I was pleased last year to proclaim 1983 the year of the Bible. But, you know, a group called the ACLU (American Civil Liberties Union) severely criticized me for doing that. Well, I wear their indictment like a badge of honor."  January 1984    "My fellow Americans, I'm pleased to tell you today that I've signed legislation that will outlaw Russia forever. We begin bombing in five minutes."  Joke while testing microphone, Aug. 11, 1984    "So, you can see why, to me, the story of these last eight years and this presidency goes far beyond any personal concerns. It is a continuation, really, of a far larger story, a story of a people and a cause. A cause that, from our earliest beginnings, has defined us as a nation and given purpose to our national existence. The hope of human freedom, the quest for it, the achievement of it, is the American saga."  Last weekly radio address as president, Jan. 14, 1989    "In closing let me thank you, the American people, for giving me the great honor of allowing me to serve as your president. When the Lord calls me home, whenever that may be, I will leave with the greatest love for this country of ours and eternal optimism for its future. I now begin the journey that will lead me into the sunset of my life. I know that for America there will always be a bright dawn ahead."  Nov. 5, 1994, announcing he had Alzheimer's disease     Mr. President, your legacy will live on.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a reasonably quiet week.  BUT...here we go again.  Tonight, I have to be in Falmouth around 6:00 for the Relay For Life, which will last until around 7:00 in the morning.  We're supposedly setting tobacco tomorrow.  VBS decoration is tomorrow at 4:00.  VBS kickoff is 6:00 Sunday evening.  Monday, I start working with Summer Recreation (8:00-4:00), followed in the evenings with VBS (6:00-8:30, approximately).  Plus, with sister and one nephew in Puerto Rico and my brother-in-law possibly being out of town, I'm "on call" to stay with the other two nephews if I need to.  Why couldn't some of this have happened this week?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That was the winning word at the National Spelling Bee today.  Those kids  amaze  me.  They reason it out so well.  They ask for definitions, alternate pronunciations, and word origins to try to figure it out and give it their best shot.  It makes for good television.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got my DirecTV DVR with Tivo today.  Can't wait to use this thing to the fullest of its ability.  I love pausing live TV.  That means I don't have to wait for commercial breaks to pee now.  God bless technology!  Bengals tickets went on sale today.  You didn't see me in line.  I'm content watching from the couch.  However, for those who did stand in line today, Coach Lewis came out to thank the fans and shake some hands.  This guy's a class act.  Meanwhile, my Reds just can't stop winning!  A 3-1 victory for my guys today.  Sean Casey continues to have the hottest bat in baseball.  Let's just hope we can keep this up.  (He's a ThunderBat)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Received this in my e-mail.  So very true.  Read and enjoy   OLD VERSION:  The ant works hard in the withering heat all summer long, building his house and laying up supplies for the winter.  The grasshopper thinks he's a fool and laughs and dances and plays the Summer away. Come winter, the ant is warm and well fed.  The grasshopper has no food or shelter, so he dies out in the cold.  MORAL OF THE ORIGINAL STORY: Be responsible for yourself!  MODERN VERSION:  The ant works hard in the withering heat all summer long, building his house and laying up supplies for the winter.  The grasshopper thinks he's a fool and laughs and dances and plays the Summer away.  Come winter, the shivering grasshopper calls a press conference and demands to know why the ant should be allowed to be warm and well fed while others are cold and starving.  CBS, NBC, and ABC show up to provide pictures of the shivering grasshopper next to a video of the ant in his comfortable home with a table filled with food.  America is stunned by the sharp contrast. How can this be, that in a country of such wealth, this poor grasshopper is allowed to suffer so?  Kermit the Frog appears on Oprah with the grasshopper, and everybody cries when they sing, "It's Not Easy Being Green."  Jesse Jackson stages a demonstration in front of the ant's house where the news stations film the group singing, "We shall overcome."  Jesse then has the group kneel down to pray to God for the grasshopper's sake.  Tom Daschle & John Kerry exclaim in an interview with Peter Jennings that the ant has gotten rich off the back of the grasshopper, and both call for an immediate tax hike on the ant to make him pay his "fair share."  Finally, the EEOC drafts the "Economic Equity and Anti-Grasshopper Act," retroactive to the beginning of the summer. The ant is fined for failing to hire a proportionate number of green bugs and, having nothing left to pay his retroactive taxes, his home is confiscated by the government.  Hillary gets her old law firm to represent the grasshopper in a defamation suit against the ant, and the case is tried before a panel of federal judges that Bill appointed from a list of single-parent welfare recipients.  The ant loses the case.  The story ends as we see the grasshopper finishing up the last bits of the ant's food while the government house he is in, which just happens to be the ant's old house, crumbles around him because he doesn't maintain it.  The ant has disappeared in the snow.  The grasshopper is found dead in a drug related incident and the house, now abandoned, is taken over by a gang of spiders who terrorize the once peaceful neighborhood.  MORAL OF THE STORY: Vote Republican
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When lineups were announced for the game today, Marty said, "The umpires are brought to you today by LASIK+ Vision Correction."
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, nearly 2 months after my  urlLink first 100 posts  (Post #100 was the 12th day of the blogging streak), I've hit 200 posts.  So quickly, thanks in part to the now-65-day blogging streak.  In the last 100 posts, I've bragged on the blogging streak, you've heard about my Summer Recreation exploits, 4 friends have gotten married (2 weddings), there was the rafting trip to southeast Tennessee, and a couple of church gripes.  We've followed the hard-luck  urlLink ThunderBats  (who can't seem to get into the top 6) and  urlLink Ken Jennings  (who is still riding quite the streak of his own).  Do you know the  urlLink infield fly rule ?  We added comments to the blog posts.  I've conquered the GRE.  The news has become a larger part of the blog with an  urlLink offbeat news story  and some political insights (that are always "right," it seems).  I've done a few "compound posts," too, with several items in one post.  Those work well.  There were the 2 cell phone blogs on rafting day to ensure that the streak lived.  Lance won, and the blog has survived recent phone and power issues.  The state of the blog is strong.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Long-time Reds play-by-play man Marty Brenneman has no equal.  Why?  Statements like this:   Just before 1:00 this afternoon, top of the 11th of a 2-2 game at Great American Ball Park between the Astros and the Reds, suspended last night in the middle of the 6th due to rain, resumed at 11:30 this morning    It's raining again.  A torrential downpour and not a thing is showing up on weather service radar--which shows you how blasted useless that thing is.  And now they're bringing out the tarp. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looks like the Florence Freedom have become the Montreal Expos of the Frontier League, being run by the league itself.  Some people thought baseball in Florence would be the end of the Reds.  Minor league baseball is minor league baseball.  And I'm afraid finanical issues will mean the end of baseball in NKY's prized city.  A black eye for Florence.  (I have to say, when Spuds resigned as manager before the first game, I knew it was the beginning of trouble.)  Nearly 3 1/2 inches of rain in the last day.  I don't care where Randy Johnson goes, as long as it's not to the Yankees.  They have too many "rock stars" as it is.  Reds trade Todd Jones to Philadelphia.  Good move.  Didn't particularly care for him as a pitcher, despite his good record.  Better him than Casey, Pena, or Dunn.  Too bad we can't unload Griffey...who somehow is "injured" right at the trade deadline.  I smell a rat.  We can get 2 Paul Wilsons for his salary.  We need 2 more Paul Wilsons.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a nice day today visiting with Mabel (Mom's 85-year-old cousin who recently had a heart valve put in and her hip and shoulder operated on after breaking them in a fall) and Gleason (her husband).  She's doing well.  We had heard that she was doing fine, but seeing it, I think, made us all feel better.  I thought today's post might be about other things, but I think I'll let those rest for now.  But, I will say that I'm kinda upset that I can't go to Cleveland with Kristy for  American idol  auditions.  I think it would be fun to audition, just to see what happens, but Kristy has a real shot at getting somewhere.  If you've heard her sing, you know what I mean.  She's not going now, and I feel a little guilty.  Not that she can't go without me, because she can.  Still...I just wish I could go somewhere with my friend without having to worry about "how it looks."  She's my  friend  and the best one I have.  Bar none.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I were Bill O'Reilly last night, I would've just pulled a Dick Cheney at Michael Moore.   O'REILLY: Al Qaeda was given refuge by the Taliban.  MOORE: But we didnt go after them, did we?  O'REILLY: We removed the Taliban and killed three quarters of Al Qaeda.  MOORE: Thats why the Taliban are still killing our soldiers there.  O'REILLY: OK, well look you cant kill everybody. You wouldnt have invaded Afghanistan  you wouldnt have invaded Afghanistan, would you?  MOORE: No, I would have gone after the man that killed 3,000 people.   Why not just take it one more step, Michael, and say, "Osama wasn't flying the planes.  Why attack him?"  There's more:   O'REILLY: Look its a worldwide terrorism  I know that escapes you   MOORE: Wait a minute, terrorism? Iraq?  O'REILLY: Yes. There are terrorists in Iraq.  MOORE: Oh really? So Iraq now is responsible for the terrorism here?  O'REILLY: Iraq aided terrorists. Dont you know anything about any of that?  MOORE: So, youre saying Iraq is responsible for what?  O'REILLY: Im saying that Saddam Hussein aided all day long.  MOORE: Youre not going to get me to defend Saddam Hussein.  O'REILLY: Im not? Youre his biggest defender in the media.   What an idiot and an embarrassment to everything American.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We've been having problems with the electricity intermittently going off in half of the house.  This morning, Bob, our electrician friend, came over to try to figure out the problem.  (To no avail, unfortunately.)  When he and Dad went to the basement, they found a bottle of Kentucky Straight Bourbon Whiskey.  Crab Orchard.  (It was empty.)  We figure it has to be at least 40 years old, but it's no more than 65.  A piece of history in this   very   non-alcoholic house's basement.  And the power problem still exists.    Pardon the Interruption    Tony and Michael are out this week, so we get Stephen A. Smith and Skip Bayless.  Stephen isn't that bad, but Skip is like a cross between Al Gore and a board.  When Tony and Michael are there, they do such of a good job arguing.  They even argue when they agree.  These imposters are barely watchable.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have to say that as far as speeches are concerned, the 10 minutes or so I saw of President Clinton's last night was pretty brilliant.  Coming from me, that's strong.  I don't even apply sunscreen liberally.  However...Notice how the Democrats always define "millionaire" as a person who makes $1,000,000 per year?  Just listen next time they talk about tax cuts.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Get it?  Dixie Chicks song.  Remember?  Only 66 degrees today.  A record cold high temperature for July in Cincinnati.  This is NUTS!  It's like Thanksgiving weather in July.  Note to Democrats:  When the  bottom  tax bracket is cut,  everyone  benefits.  Rich, poor, and in-between.  Ahhh, convention time.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Downloaded a  free  accelerator from Fuse that is doubling the speed of web page downloads.   Very  nice.  If I can't have Zoomtown...  Extremely upset with Dad.  There was a time not long ago that he was usually right about the way of doing things.  Now, he's not usually right and he's all the more adamant that his way  is  right.  And I'm not the only one who has noticed.  And it's not just the family.  Really stupid stuff, too.  I know he thinks the same thing about me, but he needs to get his act together before he starts losing the people around him.  I know how he is, but it still hurts me very much when I can't do   anything   to suit him.  It's all about me not being his perfect little farmboy.  That makes me incompetent.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you know if you follow the ThunderBats (and I know you do!), I've been kinda stuck in 7th for a while.  This week, I had the opportunity to face "Arod is Overrated," the league's top team.  I got shelled in batting.  They  easily  won the HR, RBI, and Batting Avg categories.  However, my pitching held up pretty well.  I was even able to survive Eric Milton's (PHI) 8+ hitless innings against the Cubs.  We won 6-4, which will pull us within 1 game of 6th place.  An easier opponent next week, so maybe we'll fare even better.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ricky Williams reportedly   RETIRES  ?!?!?!?  After FIVE seasons?!?!?!?  What?!?!?!?  He's only 27 years old!!!  What now?  "He's bored with football.  He wants to travel overseas.  He wants to take pictures."  Astonishing.  Is he insane?  I don't think so.  I say good for him.  Live while you're alive.  (And still young!)  Lance Armstrong easily wins his sixth consecutive Tour de France.  First to win 6 period much less consecutive.  An inspiration and a warrior.  Did you catch the A-Rod/Varitek fight yesterday?  Now  that's  quality baseball.  No love ever lost between the Yanks and the BoSox.  Best part is Boston won in dramatic fashion.  Sunday Night Baseball is a must-watch tonight.  Fantasy team is up against the #1 team this week.  I'm up 5-4 but several categories (especially pitching) are close.  More to follow after today's games.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nurse Griffey Pamper Griffey Then DUMP Griffey Buy pitching
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The previous posting's title is a line from Simon and Garfunkel's "Mrs. Robinson."  "Mrs. Robinson" also includes this line:   Where have you gone, Joe DiMaggio? A nation turns its lonely eyes to you Ooo ooo ooo  Joe DiMaggio is best remembered for a 56-game hitting streak.  Yesterday marked day 57 of by blogging streak.  And today is day 58.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The first person to comment with the significance of this title will get a special mention on my blog.  Who's the detective in the crowd?  Who's paying attention to the goings-on here?  It's a 2 or 3 step process...one I'll explain if nobody figures it out.  But we'll let it sit for a few days.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ken's season on  Jeopardy!  has come to a close.  No, he didn't lose.  He'll be back in September when the quiz show starts its 21st season.  Tonight, though, Ken made sure people would not forget about him over the 6-week break.  Going into Final Jeopardy! with a total of $51,400, he wagered big and ended this season by  smashing  the one-day total record with a total of  $75,000 .  This brings his  38-day  winnings to  $1,321,660 .  His next record to aim for will be 46 appearances on a game show, set by some guy on  Tic-Tac-Dough  back in the '80s.  What an amazing run!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Visited Sarah and Emma (Carolyn's and Brian's Chinese-American nieces, ages 4 and 1) at her house today.  What cuties!  Sarah talks so plainly and is so smart.  "Emma pulled my hair when we were in China."  "This is a messy room.  Someone needs to clean it."  (Carolyn's house is under construction.)  "Do you like spaghetti, Sarah?"  "Yeah, I like anything with noodles."  CUTE!  And it was my first time meeting Emma.  She doesn't cling to guys like Sarah does.  Sarah was awfully clingy today.  Seeing Emma was a sign of things to come.  I looked at her and saw my little niece who will be toddling the house around this time next year.   Talking Football   Running Back Shaun Alexander (of Boone Co. HS, University of Alabama, and Seattle Seahawks fame) was on CNBC talking Fantasy Football.  And Mom wants to watch the NFL Draft next year to see where Dr. Grover's son goes.  Go figure.  Of course, I'm not going to tell her she'll probably be parked in front of the TV all day--even if he goes in the first round.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today marks the 1-year anniversary of my last day at my first job.  Hard for me to believe that I've been gone from Farmers National for a year.  If I were blogging early last summer, there would be no doubt that you would be reading daily about my frustration at work and my need for some change to happen in my life.  I decided that the change would be to leave the only employer I had known for the Wonderful World of Unemployment.  Two months later, I would begin working for Pendleton County Schools as a Substitute Teacher.  Emotionally and financially it has been a trying year.  Without a full-time job, it's been hard to hold my head up sometimes.  I feel like I'm letting people (family, friends, etc.) down; I feel like I'm letting myself down.  Failure has never been in my vocabulary and to see myself as a potential one has been very rough.  And seeing my new monthly paycheck (when I get one) not much larger than my old bi-weekly paycheck has been a challenge to the checkbook and the emotions.  I've done a lot of second-guessing.  Should I have been more open about my feelings with my bosses?  Would I have been better served going to counseling?  Should I have taken a brief (1-2 month) leave of absence to sort things out?  (In hindsight, that wouldn't have helped  at all  given Dad's health last summer and fall.  I  still  feel like I need time to clear my head.)  Should I have moved out of the house instead?  (That might have pinned me down more but it could've opened doors.  And I would've felt like I had something to work for.)  One thing I  do  know is this:  I feel great about the relationships I've been able to build with the students of Pendleton County this year.  I have been placed with a lot of responsibility at my job and have succeeded to the point of  possibly  being the #1 sub at Sharp Middle School this coming year.  I've gained so much that I never could have at Farmers.  I needed to build my confidence and assertiveness.  I'm better but not yet where I want to be.  And my nervous stomach acts up about 20% as much as it used to--a big plus.  It's natural to second-guess.  It's natural to have questions about whether or not I did the right thing.  It's also natural to have regrets.  Given all I've gained from the last year at school vs. spinning my wheels at FNB, I can't say I have many.  And now, I have a new issue:  Dealing with the reality of a 1400 GRE composite score.  A friend of mine who works at a university was flabbergasted.  My first thought when I saw the score (forgive me if I've mentioned this already) was that I can get into almost any program anywhere with that score.  And the seeds of doubt start to sprout again.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Megan (Adam's wife) didn't pass her Series 7 exam.  Talk about kicking someone while they are down.  Judy was really upset by Gary's article in the church paper.  She took it personally.  I give it the benefit of the doubt and say it has to do with the current sermon series.  Unity in the Church (universal) last week, leading to unity in the  church  (local) this coming week.  Still, it is coming at a suspicious time.  Plus, I've learned more info that leads me to believe that something is up.  Sorry to do this, but I can't discuss it now.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 35 straight wins (that's 7 weeks) for Ken.  Tonight, he broke the all-time record for  Jeopardy!  winnings.  Tonight's Total:  $29,200 35-Day Winnings:  $1,164,660
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lance Armstrong finally has the lead in Le Tour de France.  He is now 85 seconds ahead of Ivan Basso.  Do we hear 6?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Working with the 9 & 10 year-olds this week at Camp Northward.  One of the assignments this morning was for them to draw a picture of what they thought God looked like.  One boy asked, "Does God shave?"
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ThunderBats Update   Only 7 weeks remain in the regular season.  We're still in 7th place, 3 1/2 games behind the 6th place team and the championship playoff bracket.  Our opponent this week is "Arod Is Overrated," the top team in the league.  Last week, in an abbreviated 4-day week, we fell 6-4 against "The Lastros."   Ken Update   $1,135,460 in 34 days.   Rafting Follow-Up   My shoes  still  reek of the Ocoee.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I mentioned after the successful GRE and in the context of going rafting the significance of Philippians 4:13.  When we arrived at the outpost Friday morning, awaiting our time to go rafting, I saw a gentleman wearing a blue T-shirt.  Written on the back, perfectly serving as a reminder that all would be well:  "I can do all things through Christ who strengthens me."
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      D-Group at Marilyn's house this evening.  She seems to enjoy having us visit.  Great conversation as we looked over a catalog deciding what book to do next.  We started at 5:00 and didn't leave until around 6:45...one of our longest meetings.  Learned about the new news lineup at channel 5.  You heard it here first:  5-7 am--Todd Dykes, Lisa Cooney, and Kristen Cornet Noon--Michelle Hopkins and Kristen Cornet 5:00--Sandra Ali, Sheree Paolello, and Jim O'Brien 5:30, 6, 11--Dave Wagner, Sandra Ali, Jim O'Brien, and Ken Broo  Weekend AM--Jonathan Hawgood and Suzanne Horgan Weekend PM--Courtis Fuller and (presumably and unfortunately) Dennis Jon Bailey  This is one messed up news operation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Our trip began Thursday evening, 6:00, in the church parking lot.  We loaded our stuff and ourselves into two vans.  Ronda saw the notebook I was taking and said, "Rich brought his will."  First, let me introduce the players.  (I was the only one traveling "alone.")  DAVE & CHERI--Trip coordinators and experienced rafters.  Drove 5 of us in their van.  Stayed for Saturday morning rafting trip.  GARY & RYAN--Preacher and his son.  Stayed for Saturday morning rafting trip.  LAWTON & MARIA--Church elder and his hilarious and sarcastic wife.  Lawton stayed for the Saturday morning rafting trip.  DENNIS & TRISH--Dennis drove the church van down and part of the way back.  Trish did the rest of the driving.  PAUL & LAURA--First-time rafters.  Family friends to us and the Moneyhons but very new to the church.  Their son has been coming for a few years.  Paul was off-and-on for a while.  They've both been coming for the past couple months.  Paul is a fun guy, and Laura is pretty quiet.  RANDY & RONDA--First-time rafters.  Have been coming to church faithfully, every Sunday, for the last few years but aren't involved much beyond that.  Both, especially Ronda, are pretty quiet.   Thursday Evening   We started off with the regular chit-chat.  A few of our crew in the van asked me if it was true that Mom and Dad were looking for a house in Falmouth.  I said that it was and showed them the one they are interested in as we went by.  Trish, impressed by irony, said, "It's not often that you hear rumors about Alvin."  We stopped in Cynthiana for gas and light refreshments.  Gary asked me to let him know if they started talking about the preacher.  I told him that Maria and Trish hadn't gotten past talking about their husbands yet.  Then it was full steam ahead (75 mph on I-75) to the state line.  We stopped at the Tennessee/Kentucky border for a potty break before arriving around 10:00 in Knoxville for the night.  I would've been content to crash then, but the group wanted to find some food.  We went to the Hardee's next door before settling in around 11:15 for bed.  I roomed both nights with Gary and Ryan, so I got a bed to myself.  One funny moment after the lights were out was when we heard the toilet start to run.  Ryan got up to go jiggle the handle and banged his head on the headboard getting back into bed.  His dad quickly remarked, "It's called the headboard but that's not what you're supposed to do."   Friday Morning   After a continental breakfast, we were up and out by 8:00 on the way to our destination:   urlLink Outdoor Adventures Rafting  in Ocoee, Tennessee (not far from the Georgia/North Carolina/Tennessee border)  Trish and Maria did there best to scare us "rookies" to death.  We crossed over the Tennessee River, and Trish leaned back.  "Laura, see that nice calm river there?  That's not the one we're going on."  Ronda told Trish, "That was just mean!"  We stopped right next to our motel at Cracker Barrel for breakfast (and games!) before moving on.  We arrived at the OAR outpost around 11:00, well before our 12:00 reservation.  While we were waiting, we got to sign our waivers, freeing them from liability in the event of our "injury including temporary or permanent paralysis or death."  We also go to tour the shop and the selection of T-shirts.  "This is not a souvenir...It's proof of survival."  Maria had that one picked out for me, but Dennis...always the pragmatist...said, "Don't buy it until we're back."   Friday Afternoon   By noon we were gathered together with another group of 45 who we would be on the river with for our safety talk.  We learned to tighten our life jackets and helmets, to ALWAYS keep a good grip on your paddle.  We also learned how to sit up in the water in case we came out of the raft and what to do in case we were too far from the raft to be pulled in.  We got in a van and rode down the road past all of the river we would be rafting.  It didn't look too ominous, so I was not very nervous, even though we were going to be going through Class III and IV rapids.  (They are graded from I-VI with VI being impossible for human survival.)  We finally made it to the dam where we were starting out and had to wait a good 15 minutes for our guides and our boats.  We divided into two groups.  6 who preferred a smoother, safer ride:  Randy, Ronda, Paul, Laura, Maria, and me.  The other 7 who didn't mind a rougher ride (even though I don't think there's that much of a difference):  Gary, Ryan, Lawton, Dennis, Trish, Dave, and Cheri.  We were told by Josh E, our guide, that we would have to do a little extra work since he was the trip leader.  This meant that he was responsible for the 9 OAR rafts going down the river, as well as keeping the first aid kit handy.  We also would have to lead, sometimes pull off to the side for the other rafts to go through, then have to go back to the front of the pack.  We picked up our raft and carried it down a ramp to a platform right at the river.  Then, we actually had to get in the water, drag our raft into the water, and get in.  My first thought was, "This isn't bad."  Then Josh spoke.  "All right, we've got a Class IV rapid right away here.  Everybody, all forward!  Go!"  Here we go.  Down the river and through the bumps and sways of the first rapids.  Nobody fell out, and it really wasn't too rough.  The thing that surprised me the most was how the rapids weren't as concentrated as I was expecting.  I thought the whole river was nothing but white water.  (Actually, recent rains had made it pretty brown.)  We'd have some rough spots, then we'd have some really smooth spots.  Of course, it wasn't always that smooth.  We hit either a rapid or a rock that caused the front end of the boat to pop up and Paul and Randy to pop out.  Paul fell back over me.  If it weren't for my foot being wedged in the tubing of the raft, as instructed, I would've gone in.  Likely minus my left foot.  I thought I'd pulled a hamstring either way.  Luckily, I was fine, Paul was fine, and Randy was fine once we finally reeled him in.  On down the river we hit another rapid, and Maria met the river.  She didn't want to go in, because it makes her panic.  She was fine, though, when she found out she came out right by the raft.  That was the end of the falling out for our raft.  We made our way on down the river and had only a couple of scary moments.  One of these moments was when our guide directed us  toward  a rock.  We "parked" on the rock by a pretty strong rapid to allow everyone through.  One raft picked up one of their passengers just in time as they went through the rapid.  Then there was "Flipper."  A rapid  not  named after a dolphin.  And our other crew now fully understands all too well why they call it "Flipper."  The raft went upside-down.  I'm sure if the 7 of them had blogs, they would tell this story in better detail.  Cheri was the first to be recovered.  The rest were just grateful to make it back in.  Gary provided the best quote about the experience.  "I'm sorry, son, but my first thought wasn't, 'Where's Ryan?';' it was, 'Where's up?'."  Ryan, in fact, was the last to be recovered.  He was picked up by another group and later reunited with the rest of the crew...which we got to see.  One of the benefits of being in the trip leader's raft.  Ronda, Laura, and I--the ones Trish and Maria were trying to scare to death, in jest--were the only ones to  not  fall into the Ocoee.  But my clothes  still  smell like the Ocoee.  I imagine it runs with the sweat of the dozens upon dozens who fall in it each day.  We regrouped at the end of the line and got back in the van with Ross, our driver who also happened to be Josh's brother.  Small world.  When we returned to the outpost, I bought my T-shirt and filled out a comment card for a chance of winning a free rafting trip.  Wish me luck!   Friday Evening   It was back to the motel in Cleveland for a shower and a change of clothes, as well as questioning the time on our cell phones which somehow had gone to Central Daylight Time.  Hmmm.  We went to Logan's Roadhouse where the waitress advised me to order  anything  but the Chicken Fried Chicken, the only thing on the menu she wouldn't recommend.  I settled for Sirloin Steak, well-done.  And some  awesome  cinnamon apples on the side.  We went back across town to the motel, wondering what to do.  Randy and Ronda stayed in their room, as did Paul and Laura.  Ryan stayed in to watch  Ocean's Eleven .  The rest of us took a walk.  After the walk, we settled in a lobby area on our floor to play euchre.  I'm still pretty new at it, so it was a learning experience.  I think I'm a better rafter.  Caught the tail end of  Ocean's Eleven  before getting a solid 7+ hours of sleep.   Saturday   We were all up and checked out early and departed after a few minutes of chatting in the parking lot and a word of prayer.  Five of us for a second round of rafting and the rest of us were on our way home.  Two hours later, we were crossing the state line.  We stopped for breakfast in Corbin before heading back north.  We made it home at 2:00.  It was a 44-hour trip all told.  The highlight, of course, was going down the Ocoee River.  When rafting the Ocoee, you're going through the Cherokee National Forest looking at the beautiful tree-covered, rocky hillsides, seeing the rushing river rapids in front of you and the rocks you end up attempting to dodge.  It is very beautiful, very inspiring, and quite exhilarating.  I'm already looking forward to next year.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gone two nights, but I got my  Jeopardy!  fix today.  Ken won each of the last two nights.  Totals of $28,000 and $50,000 bringing his 33-day total to $1,100,460.  I wonder if he still has a job.  If he doesn't, I wonder if he cares.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Brilliant!  and absolutely hilarious.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got home from the rafting trip.  Details still to follow.  I sent a text message to Bart around 10 this morning that said, "Stopped in Corbin.  Home around 1 or 2.  Please call Grandma.  Thanks"  The message Mom got was that we would be home in one or two hours.  Keep in mind that this is about 160 miles from home.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a super time. Details tomorrow when i get back.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Conquered cracker barrel golf tee game for first time ever. Streak lives.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Getting ready to go rafting in Ocoee, Tennessee.  The computer is staying home, but, hopefully, this won't jeopardize the 49-day blogging streak.  I know now how to  blog in absentia  so you can expect to see at least something from me tomorrow.  Watch your back, Joe DiMaggio.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We were working on beans again today when a commercial came on TV.  It was one of those drug commercials that never tell you what the drug actually is for.  This particular commercial was the one with Della Reese.  It came on, and I asked Mom, "OK.  Tell me what this is for."  "It's a drug.  That's all I know.  I wouldn't have known that if not for the 'Calvin Klein Smith' on the screen."  I said, "You mean 'Glaxo Smith Kline'?"  "Whatever."  "'Calvin Klein Smith.'  Those must be designer drugs."
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Presented July 12 by "Jeopardy" Champion Ken Jennings on  The Late Show with David Letterman :  10. "Ask him on air, 'So who did your Botox?'"  9. "Instead of responding, get his attention by throwing nickels at his head"  8. "Buzz in without using your hands"  7. "Give Courtney Love directions to his house"  6. "Whenever he says the word 'potpourri,' you mumble, 'Woman'"  5. "Tell him he's no Wink Martindale"  4. "Remind him that although he's a naturalized citizen, he'll always be a product of the evil Canadian empire"  3. "Complain that he's not nearly as Trebek-y in person"  2. "Your only response: 'Who gives a rat's @$$?'"  1. "Insist on buying a vowel"
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ha!  That's the anti-title of my post about Bud Selig and last night's All-Star game.  The game itself was fine.  I can't believe Roger Clemens got rocked for 6 runs in the first.  That's insanity.  No, that's baseball.  Letting an exhibition game determine home-field advantage for the   World Series  .   That's  insanity.  And that's Bud Selig.  Trying to make up for the tie-game debacle of 2002 by making the All-Star game mean something in the "real" world of baseball and giving the game the stupid "This One Counts" slogan.  Selig has done more harm to baseball than any strike could ever do.  Bob Costas for Commissioner.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The fact that I'm blogging shows that I survived taking the GRE.    Carolyn often talks about Romans 8:28 (And we know that in all things God works for the good of those who love him, who have been called according to his purpose) and how she's seen it work time after time.  For me, if there's a verse that has shown itself time and time again it is Philippians 4:13, which states  I can do everything through Christ who gives me strength .  Oddly enough, this is a favorite of athletes.  I'm far from an athlete, but I see it as a verse that speaks to will, determination, and perseverance.  After a little over a week of extensive preparation for the GRE, I took my test in Lexington today.  Needless to say I was well-prepared for anything they threw at me.  It was  just like  my study book.  I settled in and answered the questions.  At the end of the test, there is an option of cancelling your scores or viewing (and sending) them, but you have to decide  before  you see your scores.  I felt good about how I did, so I chose to view (and send) them.  I clicked, hid my face, waited a few seconds, and looked at the screen.   VERBAL:  610 QUANTITATIVE:  790   I about  FLIPPED .  It's not every day that you are overwhelmed by your own intelligence (and modesty!) like that.  It was better than I had done on any of the model tests, and here I was in a room with about 6 other people quietly testing wanting to shout.  Instead, I just covered my face and clicked on through to the end of the test.  I think scoring that well deserves a cash reward.  Seriously, though, with a score like that you can do pretty much anything you want to.  Almost any program at almost any school would take scores like that.  Perspective.  And this reminder came at a fitting time.  Right before the rafting trip, proof that I  can  do anything I can set my mind to.  Even if I can't swim.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ken is!  Night 30 on  Jeopardy! , win 30 on  Jeopardy! .  Add $32,000 tonight for a grand total of  $1,004,960 .
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's not even 2:30 yet, but I've already accomplished so much today.  Especially considering that I didn't get up until around 8:30.   Final Day of GRE Prep   I took the 4th model test (of 5) and scored my highest total yet.  1340.  I about flipped.  Long way from the 970 I started out with.  Hopefully I can do that well tomorrow.  Speaking of which, I got my map out.  Did you realize that Lexington looks like a target?  You've got this big circle in the middle and roads branching out from it.  I don't know.  Maybe an old Japanese flag would be a better description.   Trip to NKU   Each year, since I'm under 25, not married, and a graduate, I still get the good student discount on my auto insurance.  (Fortunately, this was the last time I'd have to go down there and park illegally to get it.)  This year, unlike last year, I got it done without incident.  Last year, I got Blondie who couldn't figure out what to do since I hadn't gone to school there in 2 years.  This year, I got someone competent.  At NKU, oddly enough, go to people  with  foreign accents.  They are the competent ones.   On to Kohl's   I   love   Kohl's.  It's clean.  They have nice things.  Pricey, but reasonable, too.  And  not   urlLink Wal-Mart .  That's enough for me.  Anyhow, I got a new pair of trunks for the rafting trip.  They're yellow so I'll be easy to spot floating down the Ocoee.  I got a wife-beater shirt, too.  Not much for going sleeveless (or topless for that matter) but if I'm going to be rafting on the river for 3-4 hours under mostly sunny, 89-degree skies, the pits will need airing out.   Credit Card Bill   You know the saying about putting the frog in the pot on the stove and turning the burner on?  The water gradually gets warmer and warmer while the cold-blooded frog just sits there and cooks not realizing that he's boiling until it's too late.  Welcome to my credit card bill.  I get the bill around the 20th of each month.  Last month, when I paid the bill (in full) I had nearly $360 in charges:  a drug store pickup for Mom and Dad (which, of course, was reimbursed), the DirecTV bill, and a tank of gas.  Since then, I've racked up that much more in charges:  gas, cell phone, a couple pieces of clothing, a few CDs, another DirecTV billing, and the big-ticket GRE fee.  Nothing too big, but a bunch of little things adding up and the frog is feeling the heat.  I'm going to try to accomplish some more now.  Bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight's total was another record-tying $52,000, bringing his total to $972,960.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A brief scare this afternoon as my sister was "missing" according to Bart and Brennan.  She left around 5:00 to go "to the bank" and wasn't home by 6:30.  Needless to say, they were concerned, and we were too (to some extent--I'll explain) when we found out about it.  Let me back up.  Bart and Brennan are two of a kind, which is why I didn't put a lot of stock in their concern.  Carolyn could have said, "I'm going to get gas, wash the car, get my hair cut, go to the grocery, climb Pike's Peak, and go to the bank."  Bart, no doubt engrossed with his guitar, and Brennan, no doubt parked in front of the PlayStation 2, would later confer after Mom left and didn't come back.  "Where did Mom say she was going?"  "I think the bank."  "Yeah.  When did she leave?"  "I don't know.  Maybe 5:00?  How far away is the bank?"  "1 minute."  "Oh.  She should be home by now.  Let's freak out."  "OK."  All you need are Jim Carey and Jeff Daniels to play the parts of Bart and Brennan.  Turns out that Carolyn was at a meeting at school.  A meeting Mom and I knew about but had forgotten about in the excitement.  We so wrongfully assumed that the nephews knew about the meeting.  And you know what happens when you assume things, don't you?
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Good is the enemy of great."
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes a story just is too good to not pass along.  Enjoy.     Luckless Casanova trapped stark naked   Drunken Swede found stuck under a gate calls himself 'fine beef'   OSLO, Norway - Police, ambulance and fire crews rescued a drunken Swede found trapped early Monday without any clothes after he tried to crawl under a gate in downtown Oslo.  The 22-year-old, who insisted upon being addressed as something that sounded like fine beef in Swedish, had tried to visit a Norwegian woman at her apartment house in the early hours.  When she refused to let him in, he turned to leave, but found the gate leading to the street from her apartment was locked. He tried to squeeze beneath, but didnt fit.  So, police said, the young Casanova figured if he slipped off his clothes, hed probably slip right under the gate.  He was wrong and spent the rest of the night stuck with nothing but the chilly Norwegian night for company.  About four hours later, someone spotted a pair of naked legs sticking out onto the sidewalk from beneath the gate and called the police.  After police and rescue crews were unable to remove him from beneath the gates, they called the fire department, which used a hydraulic jack to lift up the gate. He was freed about 7 a.m.  His rescue was caught on film by a crew of Norwegian journalists and photographers who gathered to watch.  Ever optimistic, the man, whose real name was not released, urged reporters to say hed gotten stuck while trying to save a kitten. Failing that, he asked them to mention that the object of his affections was a real stunner.  Police said the man, who lives in Oslo, wasnt hurt and was sent home with the recommendation to take a hot shower and a warm nap.   2004 The Associated Press  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Phase I:  Church   Church was good this morning.  I love the keyboard and need it to survive from week to week, but it was just voice and guitar this morning.  There's something special about that.  Maybe because it doesn't happen very often.  Plus, we sang "The Wonderful Cross."  That makes any service good.  And Trenton was there!  Long time, no see.  Sad, but true.  My heart goes out to him (and his foster parents) as he sorts out things in his life and decides who he is going to become.   Phase II:  Annual Bishop-Fest   Larry, Carolyn, the Crums, and the entire McCann clan were the only ones missing.  47 present in all.  Larry and Tammy are settling into London (KY) well.  Lydia (big surprise) provided the quote of the day.  Her 2-year-old son Spencer (the current family "prize child") calls her Iya, his version of Lydia.  She said, "You wait 35  long  years to become a mother and you have a kid who calls you 'Iya.'"  And he calls Uncle Scott "Un-Got."  And he counts to 12!  What a wonderful little man.  And Holden (the other family "prize child") is still the most pleasant kid on the planet.  There was something extra-special about today.  It was reasonably quiet, calm.  Just chatter, food, food, food, food, food, and fun.  Very serene.  I can't help but think it has something to do with who was there.  If you know what I mean, you know what I mean.  I hadn't seen Nicolas, Kayla, Kaylin, or Sela for a whole year.  It was amazing to see how they had grown.    Poppy chicken was  AWESOME .  So were the desserts.  I'm just now starting to get hungry again.   Phase III:  Extend the Blogging Streak   45 Days
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My "summer job" is over, and I'm neck-deep in GRE study material.  Then, I have another obligation or two to keep me occupied during the summer.  School starts August 12.  I was wondering if any of you had any ideas about what I could do to supplement my income.  Grad school is on the horizon and it ain't cheap.  Plus, I'll have 3:30-ish and after each weekday free.  But I'd like to keep my evenings flexible in case long-term assignments come up.  I get this ad at the top of the page sometimes (you see it, too, I know) that says "Blog and Make Money."  I wonder what that's all about.  Does it mean that I have to name-drop products into my postings, like, "I was drinking a Pepsi today" or "I'm sitting here typing on my Dell Inspiron 8200 notebook PC."  Or could I just put a signature line at the bottom of my postings that says something like, "Clairol Herbal Essence Shampoo--A Totally Organic Experience" or "Corona--Miles Away from Ordinary."  Maybe throw in product reviews every now and then.  I don't know.  Maybe I should check on that.  Until next time...  ***THIS SPACE FOR RENT***
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sure you've all heard the news recently where John Kerry said that he personally believes that life begins at conception.  Funny that his votes don't reflect this belief.  Kerry voted "Nay" on H.R. 1997, commonly known as "Laci and Conner's Law."  The bill is described as, "A bill to amend title 18, United States Code, and the Uniform Code of Military Justice to protect unborn children from assault and murder, and for other purposes."  (Even Sen. Daschle voted "Yea.")  John Kerry.  Turning his back on his beliefs for the sake of politics.  Playing both sides of the fance.  Yet again.  Skeptical?   urlLink Click here to see for yourself 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A record-tying $52,000 for our Ken tonight.  28-day winnings now total $920,960
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just saw this on the web.  Wish I'd seen it for myself on "Larry King Live."   KERRY PASSES UP TERROR BRIEFING: 'I JUST HAVEN'T HAD TIME' Fri Jul 09 2004 09:23:56 ET  Just hours before attending an all-star celebrity fundraising concert in New York, Dem presidential candidate John Kerry revealed how he has been too busy for a real-time national security briefing.  "I just haven't had time," Kerry explained in an interview.  Kerry made the startling comments on CNN's LARRY KING LIVE Thursday night.  KING: News of the day, Tom Ridge warned today about al Qaeda plans of a large-scale attack on the United States. Didn't increase the -- you see any politics in this? What's your reaction?   KERRY: Well, I haven't been briefed yet, Larry. They have offered to brief me. I just haven't had time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Continuing the math review of the GRE book.  I was breezing right along.  Then, I hit Geometry...parallel lines and corresponding angles.  I did OK, but I wanted my high school math teacher holding my hand, watching me every step of the way.  MRS. RUSH, WHERE ARE YOU?!?!?!?!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got  urlLink Kristy  to spruce things up a bit.  Check it out!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another $40,000 tonight.  27 Days, $868,960.  Unreal
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today  the phone rang.  "Rich, this is JoEllen.  I was wondering if you'd be interesting in teaching a community education class for churches or small businesses about setting up their books."  Yeah.  So, I have the possibility of a second job (for a few nights) during the fall.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've gone through 8 chapters of tests.  Here are the results:   VERBAL   Sentence Completion:  80% Reading Comprehension:  76% Analogies:  67% Antonyms:  64%   QUANTITATIVE   Quantitative Comparisons:  87% Discrete Quantitative:  87% General Mathematics:  80% Data Interpretation:  67%  I feel better about this than I did Monday.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've waited a LONG time this year to get a couple of quality starts from my ThunderBats.  Last night was the answer to my prayers.  Jared Washburn (Ana)--12-0 W @ CWS, CG, 0 ER, 4 H, 2 BB, 6 K Kyle Loshe (Min)--12-0 W vs. KC, CG, 0 ER, 6 H, 0 BB, 7 K  Combined, that's 18 IP, 2 W, 13 K, 0.00 ERA, 0.67 WHIP.  All numbers that will greatly help my pitching totals, which have been struggling.  We went from a 6-2 deficit at the start of the day yesterday to a 4-3 lead.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am wondering what to do between the rafting trip and the beginning of school, and the phone rings.  "Rich, this is Doug Beard.  I was wondering if you'd be able to teach during the first Junior week at Camp Northward?  It's the 19th-23rd.  It'll only be a couple of hours in the mornings."  "Sure, Doug.  I don't see why not."  So, cool!  That takes care of one more week of summer...at least in part.  And if I can get that Praxis II thing done, my summer will pretty much be shot--er--I mean--filled!  Yeah.  Um...bye now.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With the possibility of a super-ugly mud-fest in the embryonic stages at the Chapel, I thought it best to evaluate the pros and cons of potential new church homes.  Alphabetically, so as not to show bias:   Bethany Church of Christ   PROS:  Close to home CONS:  Closely tied to the Chapel, attendance around 30   Fairview Christian Church   PROS:  Close to home, good preacher (Evan), strong singing congregation, have recently purchased land CONS:  Closely tied to the Chapel   Fellowship of Faith   PROS:  Know several people, newer congregation CONS:  Seem to be a little liberal   Grassy Creek Christian Church   PROS:  Family and friends go there, similar to CCCC CONS:  Similar to CCCC   Harvest Community Church   PROS:  New congregation, meets at a school CONS:  Southern Baptist   Plum Creek Christian Church   PROS:  The most contemporary church in the area, large membership CONS:  25-minute drive  So...knowing me, which of these churches do you think would fit me best?  Or is it on the list?
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Un-freakin-believable.  Ken won  AGAIN  tonight with a total of $40,000.  His  26-day  total winnings are  $828,960 .
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "John Kerry could have selected Henry Clay as his running mate and it would not have improved his chances in Kentucky."   --Sen. Mitch McConnell
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep.  25 straight wins for Ken Jennings.  5 solid weeks.  His total winnings are $788,960, an average of over $31,500 per episode.  For a lot of people, that's an average yearly salary.  Or more.  And he almost had 2 opponents in the red but the guy against him got the very last question right to put him in the blue.  I wanted to see Ken fly solo in "Final Jeopardy!".  Maybe tomorrow.  Continued GRE preparation today.  I got 64% of my antonyms correct (I was  ecstatic ) and didn't finish the analogies.  Tomorrow is another day.  I think I should go ahead and review the math first.  MUCH more user-friendly.  For this user anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally today I got to see the movie that has had America buzzing with excitement.  I watched the first movie last week to get myself psyched up for the new installment.  I don't want to give anything away for those of you who haven't gotten a chance to see this wonderful film.  I'll just say this:  If you liked the first one, you'll enjoy this one.  All the intensity and drama of the first and then some.  But the last 10 minutes make the whole 2 hours worthwhile.  Just you wait and see what I mean.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dad just got home from the board meeting at church, so I guess it's OK to divulge this.  Adam has been evaluated by the board and will be re-evaluated in 90 days.  Conventional wisdom says this means he is as good as gone unless he makes some great strides.  We don't need this again.  Two years ago, Jared left.  Then, we were without a full-time youth minister for a year.  Last May, Adam came.  The work he has done with the kids (Jr. High and younger especially) has been awesome.  He always seems to be doing something and keeps tabs on what's going on in their lives.  I know there have been issues with him not doing certain things right or on time, etc. but you have to ask:  What is in the best interest of the church?  Do you go through the painstaking process of finding someone new?  Or do you "leave well enough alone."  A year is plenty of time to learn and fix some beginner's mistakes.  Is Adam learning from his mistakes?  I don't know.  Is he making new mistakes?  I don't know either.  I  do  know that within the first 2-3 months he was here that he had to "wing" his Sunday School lesson at least twice.  I know that one or both of the sermons he did recently while Gary was on vacation were downloaded from the Internet.  He doesn't feel comfortable leading singing, even though I've told him tongue-in-cheek that all I do is stand up there and move my lips.  Nobody looks at you anyway.  They just stare at the wall.  Prayers are needed.  I'd heard at first that this was a firing.  Now, it seems it's just a  strong  wake-up call.  Whatever the case, PRAY.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just heard some news.  I don't know if it is true or not.  Apparently it is.  And if it is, it will most likely mark the end of me and Cemetery Chapel.  Unless there is a good explanation.  More to follow.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm preparing to go whitewater rafting on the  urlLink Ocoee River  in southeast Tennessee later this month with a group from church.  Surprisingly, I'm less concerned about the inherent danger of rafting (combined with the fact that I can't swim) than I am about how I'll keep the blogging streak (currently 38 days) alive being gone all day Friday.  Or at least I was until this morning.  Dave, our trip coordinator, gave us an itinerary this morning.  Part of it reads:   The trip lasts about 3 hours   My eyes grew large, and I asked, "Three hours?!  We're going to be in the raft for three hours?!"  Jacob quickly shot back.  "Well, in and out of the raft."
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A lot of people put comments on their blogs.  You've seen them, I'm sure.  There's usually a link by the time the posting was logged.  I have opted not to do this, but I'm wondering if I should.  So...I'm asking for your comments regarding whether or not I should use comments.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mom and Carolyn have been wanting to visit the Amish for years.  We ordered a brochure from  urlLink Lancaster County, PA  and it came in the mail today.  (I won't mention the irony of ordering a brochure to visit the Amish from an Internet site.)  I could barely contain my excitement.  And, yes, I'm being sarcastic.  I guess in all these years of being a farmboy, the thought of vacationing in a rural location just seems silly to me.  "Let's go someplace quiet with scenery where you can see the trees and hills and hear the birds!"  I have a special spot just like that.  It's called the front yard.  Sure, you've got Gettysburg and Hershey nearby.  That stuff does excite me.  Still, I wonder...what elements  would  I   consider essential to a "vacation"?   No Cows .  I see them every day and have every day of my life.  I don't need a vacation to see more.  The thing that cracks me up is the rural vacation destinations that have farms and petting zoos as attractions so that "city folk" can experience "farm life."  Sorry for the loudness of my rolling eyes.  You want to experience farm life, City Slicker?  Come to my house.  Set tobacco.  Hang tobacco.  Get up in the barn.  Dump feed in a trough for the moo-moos to eat while wading through their crap.   That's  farm life, mis amigos.   Green space  .  The yard is green, the hills are green, the trees are green...give me less green and more something else.  Give me roads, concrete, brick...urbanness.  I'll settle for suburbanness.  Green is good.  Just in moderation.  It gets old after a while.   Sand and Sun .  Ahhhh...YES!!!  We've hit the spot!  The waves crashing on the shore and the sand between your toes.  It sounds like heaven.  It's been so long, and I miss it so much.  I think Southern California is calling me home.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bart wants to go see  Spider-Man 2  tonight at some college student hour like 10:00 pm.  I'm not up to that.  It's been a full 4 weeks and I'm tired.  I hope they got the same guy to play the editor of  The Daily Bugle .  I'm glad Summer Rec has come to an end.  At least part of me is.  Another part will miss all the good times I had every day.  The games (after games after games) of Knockout, outside time, pool days, and card games.  Playing for pay like a pro athlete.  I'll miss the serious conversations with Phillip, the hyperness of Rick, the challenge of dealing with Bobby and Josh who have personal issues and need people to support them, the brother/sister love spats between Charissa and TJ, the genuine goodness of Scott, Alex's sweetness, the carefree and adorable K-1 kids who always offered hugs, and CJ--simply the world's best kid.  I won't miss the drama.  I had no idea that 4 weeks of Summer Rec would produce more drama per day than an week of soap operas.  Now I know what goes on in the halls of the middle school during locker time...and why it takes them 10 minutes to move to the room next door.   Ken Update:   He scared us tonight, but won AGAIN.  23-day winnings total $755,360.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Instead of logging several entries, let's just make 1 big sectioned entry.   Top Story:  Final Summer Rec Pool Day   Today was the last pool day, so (as promised) I got into the pool.  I was anxious about it.  Not because of the water and the fact that I can't swim.  That's nothing.  A 5-10 guy can survive in the 3-4 foot end of the pool.  It wasn't because of seeing 6-year-olds swim around me while I just stood either.  It was because I have not had any good "topless time" this summer, so my beautifully bronzed arms, legs, and neck made my torso all the more white.  I was paler than Michael Jackson.  Of course, 20 people decided to point out my tanline from the time I had my shirt off to 30 seconds later when I was in the pool.  Kasey the Lifeguard was a little covert and sarcastic.  "Rich, take your shirt off."  Very funny.   The Grocery Store   After work, it was off to the store where I got a chance to see Brett bagging groceries in his girlfriend Kelsey's lane.  (It was sweet.)  It gave me an opportunity to ridicule Kelsey about her at-work mistake.  She accidentally bagged the half-used bottle of Windex she had behind the counter to clean the surface of the checkout lane.  The lady in front of me had a pretty full cart, but I was intent on going through Kelsey's lane.  When it was my turn, I greeted her saying, "I know I could've gone through another lane, but I hear you get free Windex in this lane."  She grinned and talked about how embarrassing it was when she did that.  I harassed Brett for tying my bags before I could put my receipt in.  If only I'd thought, I'd have asked him to put my groceries in a  urlLink Big Mac .   The Cingular Bill   I have a good plan on my cell phone, which I don't use much, and try not to complain about the bill.  Last month's bill was outrageous, mostly because of a $9.00, 12-minute call received  at my house .  See...I live near the edge of the service area.  If the wind is blowing the right way or if I'm in a certain room, I'll go into the roaming area.  However, when I was on the field trip in Columbus, I let a student use my phone to call home.  The 1-minute call was billed as a  local  call.  I just rolled my eyes.   Brushes with Fame   Heather, a teacher at the middle school, (and of  urlLink "goosing"  fame), was on channel 12's weekly feature "Grillin' with Tim," hosting the meteorologist's weekly cookout.  And I saw Phyllis, Jenna, and Debbie B. there, too!  And, no, the goosee wasn't there.   My Spidey-Sense Tells Me    urlLink Spider-Man 2  is a hit!   Ken Wins Again   He had me worried in round 1, but shined in the Double Jeopardy round, rolling to a $40,000 total, bringing his 22-day winnings to $737,760  I can't wait to see him in the Tournament of Champions.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Community Ed class is on the back, back burner.  I need to get back at it.  Two months from today it begins.  I've made good progress, but it won't be top priority anymore.  I'm REALLY hoping nobody signs up for it.  Application to Georgetown, minus employment info, is in the mail.  Waiting for financial aid info.  If I'm employed, Pendleton sends info to Georgetown so I can be finally admitted.  If I'm admitted, Georgetown sends info to Pendleton so I can get Rank III pay.  Interview for the job is Tuesday.  Meanwhile, there is a classroom to get ready, lesson plans to prepare, etc. and nobody to do it "officially."  I hope they don't have great expectations of me for the first week or so.  Good thing is I would have 3 1/2 hours of class one day, 4 1/2 hours the next.  Anyway, I'm downloading Core Content info, "best practices," info on IEPs, and am getting ready to look up some books Carolyn recommended.  I'm already looking forward to Labor Day.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Your Mom gives you  her  credit card to order stuff online and you type in  your  credit card number.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got a congratulatory phone call from the head of the Special Education department at Sharp.  I guess it's official, unofficially.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My, oh, my they can.  Right now, I'm (patiently) downloading pages to an application for admission to Georgetown College.  There's an opening at Sharp MS for Special Ed Math.  To qualify for it, I need to be enrolled in an education program, hence the download.  Georgetown has the program to fit the bill, and you can enroll at the beginning of each 10-week term.  Translation:  I can start this fall.  Still need to call them and get details.  I'm, for some reason, feeling really stressed at the moment.  There's all the stuff to apply to Georgetown, the thought that school starts next Thursday, I could be teaching AND taking classes simultaneously, and, of course, there's that Community Ed class thing in October.  One thing at a time, I guess.  Oddly enough, I've been doing math, crunching numbers to find out exactly how much I'd need to "make it" on my own.  Did you realize (between us) that it would cost me an (estimated) $13,000  more  per year to live on my own?  That seems like a lot.  Did you realize that it costs me about $650-700 per month to live now?  And you guys KNOW I don't live extravagantly.  Food for thought.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Of course, compared to  urlLink Ben  I don't have much of a chance.  I did laundry today, for the most part.  And I got a fan out for the bedroom tonight.  It's pushing 90 for once this summer.  Watched an episode of  The Young and the Restless  in 20 minutes today, thanks to TiVo's fast-forward function and closed captioning.  Really a dull day.  REALLY dull.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just found out that Brennan didn't use the gas grill at their cookout last night because the label on the tank said "Flammable."  Really.  I guess he thought there was a "warming fairy" in there to cook the food.  On a less embarrassing note, Bart and I did "Sea of Faces" by Kutless at church this morning.  Both services.  It went  really  well and came together quickly.  Definitely have to do that again.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>