<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i never knew being free could hurt so much.    free from the restrictions that once held me.  today i had my soccer match against massey high.  we played really well in the first 15 minutes.  i played above average after getting nailed right in the nuts.  it was quite funny, cause TG came running to me as i rolled on the ground and said "bandaid?  ...there's not much we can do".  we were losing 3-2 in the last minute but managed to get some queer ass goal that saw us the tie.  i came out of that match with track and sprig marks on my thighs, but it doesn't really hurt.  my predators looked beautiful covered in mud.  as it dried, my shoes looked started to look organic.  that'd be cool, to have a living pair of shoes.  they could increase your speed and stuff.  science fiction (for now).    i watched the first XV play - they whooped the opposition 50-5.  after that i came home and took a shower.  i had left my phone in my jacket and mom put it in the wash. that marked the end of it - the last text message i sent was to lisa.    the friendship that lisa and i had ended today.  i guess we just wanted different things.  i wanted to be listened to and she wanted clothes and toys.  i'm not pissed off at her.  i'm glad she expressed how she felt i was a "little shit", "a victim", "a low blow".  i wish you all the best lisa, you're still a good person.  i kinda wish that it would've worked, but i guess it never did.  the one thing i'll take from her is to be true and happy to myself.  my dad found out that he has some growth behind his prostate.  it gives him blood in his urine.  hopefully it's nothing serious.  i worry about it more than he does.  i hope this will be some kind of a reality check to make him quit smoking.  i was thinking about smoking today (not actually doing it, just about it).  people who smoked back then say they never knew it was harmful but..how can inhaling any form of smoke be good for you?  did they really think that it would make them better?  i've set two rules for myself in my life.  one: no drugs, and two: no premarital sex.    no premarital sex!!!!!  i do think that my virginity is special, and i dont want to lose it in a relationship that i'll regret.  these two rules get harder and harder to live with as i grow older, but i will stay true to my word.  so yeah.  my week's been all right.  yesterday i went to watch georgia's waterpolo game with amanda.  it was really exciting, she got the opening goal! our team almost broke the tie in the last second, but the goal didn't count.  the 3 of us went for a supper desert after that at dennys in the city, and it was quite fun.  georgia got me to talk about my dad's incident after that and i got kinda moody for the rest of the night.    as i saw georgia play...i just stared and stared..and figured that the only reason why i ever liked her was because she was so flawed.  i understand what she goes through - she's not the most liked girl at school, and she gets played by some people.  i liked her because she isn't passive like all the other girls at school.  she serves it straight.  she's honest about stuff...i've always liked that.  i sat across her at dennys and wondered if we would still be in contact after we went our separate ways.  that.  she has really brown eyes.  she got her belly button pierced today and her parents don't know.  naughty :).    i also felt really bad about amanda, cause i only got to know her cause i wanted to know more about georgia.  and...i lead her in the wrong direction.    chanelle broke up with j.  i think she'll enjoy being single.  she wasn't with us at waterpolo.  i don't think amanda wanted her there, cause when i asked amanda she just said "cause she isn't here".  i'd love to hang out with chanelle alone but...i don't think amanda would be too happy.  she'd probably think we were seeing each other, but i just want to get to know chanelle better.  and if amanda's not happy, she'll bitch to georgia, and georgia'll get really pissed off with me.  we haven't argued in ages and i don't have any plans to resurrect that..heh.    my song of the moment is 'she will be loved' by maroon 5.  the lead singer's voice is unique, and i think the lyrics are very meaningful.  its funny how i can always relate to the lyrics.  i finally talked to God again today.  i've placed him on sidetrack ever since i left church.  got school chapel tomorrow, and i'm kinda looking forward to it :).  sigh, anyway, that's about it.  i'm going to start planning my exam revision tonight.  i intend to do very well.  yes..even in physics! haha.  i've lost so much today..but i gained even more.  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well...not quite, but it was fun anyway :).  my day started at around 7 in the morning.  i was still tired, but i managed to drag myself to the shower and slap the tap on.  the water felt really good as it ran down my cheeks.  anyway, after that i got into the soccer uniform and packed my shit (thanks eb).  the drive was REALLY long.  it was like 30 km from the city.  we left at about 8:50 and got there at 9:40.    so yes, we drove out to the middle of nowhere and then they didn't have enough players there.  so i had to play for them.  they were shit.  we won 2-0.  i felt kinda sorry for those people though, cause they were like really poor and stuff - you could tell.  since i played for them, their crowd gave me support!   so i drove out of orewa with the respect of the community.  HAHA.  after that we (laurence, his dad, hiro and i) went to support the school's 1st xv rugby team playing in mangere.  it was cool, cause i actually knew the people playing, and some of them came and talked to me :).  our team won.  sarah forman turned up on the sideline, but she didn't say hi to me or anything.  by the way, the predators were great :).  after that laurence's dad bought us mcdonalds, which was really nice of him.  laurence has a nice family.  why couldn't i have been their homestay instead of going to boarding school :P?  came home at around 2, and i showered then took a nap on the couch.  my mom made a pillow case for the mogu pillow...so it doesn't really feel that great anymore.  but i still managed to sleep...big surprise there eh?  woke up and it was time to go to a family friend's house for dinner.  she made some awesome food :).  amanda n chanelle were trying to contact me throughout the day cause they were free to hang out.  so they picked me up from the family friend's house and we went and watched king arthur.  king arthur sucks, by the way.  the movie i mean.  the characters were pretty cool.  keira knightley = yummy.  had fun with amanda and chanelle :).  amanda skipping around was quite scary, though...  anyway, i got a chance to see chanelle drive!  more like experience it, actually.  it was...different.  you were either blazing or braking, chanelle :).  but it was fun, as always.  tomorrow's sunday - back to the boarding house.  i don't actually mind, now that i'm settled in.  already agreed to kick david's butt in warcraft.  on monday after school i'm playing soccer, same on tuesday, and probably on wednesday too.  maybe on thursday too :P.  that's about all.  i think i'll have an early night.  ma's probably out anyway.  nighty night.    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      long.  but hey theeeerre.  it's nice to be back home again around mom....and have my freedom again :).  the week's been full of things - most of them surprisingly good.  i've been in a good mood this whole week.  i think i love school.  my friends are kick ass.  sunday checked into the boarding house on sunday, around 4pm.  was feeling grumpy and miserable for having to move back to my little room.  the day eventually passed and i maanged to fall asleep.  monday woke up at 3 am.  not sure why.  i decided to email a couple of people and then tried going back to sleep at around 4 am....but it didn't work.  so i laid in bed for another hour, and then at 5 i got out to play on my computer.  i played king of fighters.  fun.  then i showered at about 5:10 and then david woke up.  david ryu, the korean dude :P.  he's funny.  he woke up early cause he needed to study for the bio assessment.  i ended up just talking to him, and disrupted his study..haha.  school that day was pretty good, it was nice to see some friendly faces again.  especially georgia!  she gave me this little wave accompanied by a smile.  that made my day, hehe.  after school i played soccer with some of the boarders.  my predators gave me a few blisters but i guess that's the way it is when they're brand new :).  tucked myself into bed at 9 and fell asleep STRAIGHT away :P.  tuesday sat my practice bio assessment.  it was pretty bad, but i think i did better than the majority of my class.  had soccer practice with my team after school.  it was good.  i get a liiiittle better each week.      wednesday what i thought of during wednesday: georgia.  thursday homework n deep thoughts.  friday today :).  woke up really happy cause i'd finally be able to come home for the weekend.  learnt that i only got a merit for physics.  sigh...everyone in the class got either merit or excellence.  i think i messed up on the units.  and this assessment counted :(.  oh well.  just gotta try harder.  had a good time in maths, as i always do.  harry's actually a pretty cool guy :).  we're friends.  tight!  the school newspaper was published this week.  it's weird, now that i've written in it i don't want it anywhere near me.  i haven't read any of it, and i don't intend to.  ugh.  keep it away :P.  been listening to a few songs lately - songs of the moment are 'today' by the smashing pumpkins and 'broken' by seether, with amy lee from evanescence.  i managed to get talking to chel again :).  she's this neat little girl that lives in pennsylvania that i email every night.  we're really open to each other and questions, which is something i want (or rather, need).  sorry jocelyn :( i guess now you know why you didn't get a reply recently!    some of you might know of my recurrent dreams of georgia.  haha.  it's like...we were playing tag and i sat on her and she became jennifer garner.  queer.  btw i also saw the next NASA spacecraft set for launch in 2010 in my dream.  it's spherical with a yellow skeleton and 9 astronauts.  i don't have much planned for the weekend.  tomorrow's soccer match is at orewa...laurence is coming to pick me up.  i'm looking forward to it.  he's coming at 8:30 in the morning, so i better go get some sleep.  laaaater! 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lol.  what a surprise.  it's 5:16 am.  i spent the last 3 hours lying in my bed, trying to sleep.    didn't work.  i have church in 4 hours.  herman says that i can stay up for as long as i want, its limitless.  i'm only aiming for about 16 more hours.  sooooo...i decided to spend my 'free' time here.  writing to the world (actually, more like....4 people).  hi, i'm simon...how do you do?  i was born in saudi arabia and i've lived half of my life overseas.  i make lots of friends, but i always lose contact with them.  is it just me, or do i sound like a prison inmate about to die by lethal injection?  haha...(sorry to any prisoners or prison-related people).  so i have 40 days of school excluding weekends, starting monday, 19th july.  40 days equates to..... -240 class periods -10800 minutes of lecturing, excluding lunchtime and morning interval -900 minutes of soccer practice -1200 minutes of leisurely soccer on the astroturf with my friends -1000 minutes spent in the shower -1200 minutes spent eating breakfast, lunch, and dinner -320 pieces of toast -640 knivings of butter -120 scoops of cornflakes -120 shakes of sugar -12,000 mililitres of milk (for the cereal) -20,000 mililitres of milk (to drink) -120 "thank you"s to bob, the chef at the boarding house -40 changes of my bedsheets -80 kilometres spent walking and running around the campus -48,000 words sent in emails to my closest friends -3 x 10^999 thoughts of georgia (she's a very cool, and earthly person).  georgiaaaaaaaaa hi.  you don't know about this site, so you won't be reading this.  but i'm writing to you anyway because i like to pretend you listen to me.  you know that i liked you in that way....and i know that you didn't like me in that way.  when did i ever tell you?  i can't remember.  it was pretty obvious, wasn't it?  everyone in school kinda knew.  ask sarah :P i told her everything.  i don't like you *just* in that way now.  i think it's expanded, we have a really neat friendship.. you'd agree.  i like how i can tell you everything that's on my mind and how you always thoughtfully reply with "batty bitch".  sigh.  i don't really know what i hate about the boarding house.  ok wait i do. i have no freedom.  i cannot use msn messenger because it is blocked, 24/7.  the boarding house keeps me away from my family.  but it's good in a way.  absence makes the heart grow stronger.  when i got back to singapore and saw my mom at the airport, i just felt this huge relief.  she won't be coming back in the term 3/4 break, so i'll be stuck here with instant noodles and my studying.  i know i've said this before but...i'm going to do well this year.  just like i did in 2002, i ripped ass.  i ripped and hauled ass halfway across the himalayas.  maybe i should blog to God.    hello God.  sorry for my behaviour as of late.  i kinda sidetracked you, didn't i?  sigh....foolish me.  i wish it could be like that night when i surrendered myself to Jesus.  everything was seen in a new light.  now i take everything that makes this world work for granted.  sorry.  please take care of my family, my friends, my enemies, and...may more people get to know you.    i've always been interested in how others pray.  i can't really do ye old english praying, and i dont think God really cares how you do it.  you could do it in sign language and he'd understand.  cool.  have you ever wondered what would happen if earth didn't exist?  and space itself?  could nothing not exist?  i mean, nothing itself.  if nothing doesnt exist, then what does it look like when there's nothing there?  i have so many questions...where do races come from?  what about accents?  i have a really annoying cold.  and i'm deaf in my left ear.  haha.  i'm profusely coughing and my blistered foot has split further.  so...i guess it'll only get better from here.  yesterday joycelyn from primary school said hi to me.  shit, i haven't heard from her for 6 years.  she sent me a postcard but i never replied.  i think she's pretty much the same....she's really nice.    sigh...it's 6:28 am now.  should i go to sleep?  3 hours...there's no point.  but...im really tired.  and....  z.....z.....z....zzzz.....
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yes i am, i am gracing all with another entry into this shithole that is my corner of the internet.  how have you been?  i'm all right.  in less than 18 hours i'll be in the stupid boarding house.  sigh.  that means restrictive internet (msn messenger, *.blogspot.com and the likes are all blocked).  i'll be coming home the first few weekends while my family's here, and then i'll be staying in there full time.  sucks huh?  that'll last for 8 weeks.  the brief break i have between term 3 and term 4 is intended for preparation for the national exams.    so my focus for term 3 is academic and sporting.  i deleted my copy of warcraft 3 and its expansion pack cause they're too much of a distraction.  i wanna concentrate on my physics, maths, and bio and soccer to be specific.  social wise....i don't really know what i want.  i'm gonna be a little louder this term :).  and hopefully i'll get to see more of my friends outside of school.  i wanna get to know you better, chanelleeeee!  do you think amanda would get mad if we hung out without her?  i also need to strengthen myself spiritually - i've been off the path for too long, and it's not how i want it to be.  so God, hit me :P.  anyway....my holidays have been good, all in all.  singapore was definitely fun.  more fun than auckland will ever be!  i remember hearing the captain's announcement that we would be touching down real soon.  i raised the blinds and stared out to blackness, then a few minutes down the track i saw the pretty lights of home calling to me.  it's hard to explain to someone whos never been away from home for a long time.  there's just nothing that can substitute for it.  i dont think anything in new zealand can compare to a durian....  today i was suppose to go watch something with chanelle and amanda, but they were too busy.  so i guess i got stood up? heh...that's okay.  i talked to them just now.  chanelle :P when are you coming to get your socks?  mom went out with her friends for dinner.  good for her, she needs a break.  i finally finished my english homework.  tomorrow i'll study for bio, and do the physics, and i should be SWEET.  "on fire" is a tight song.  so yeah.  the boarding house is so depressing.  would any of you readers mind me living with you?  i can learn to iron and wash my own clothes...i just want my freedom.  everytime i want to get out of the hell hole i need to fill out forms and have a guardian or caretaker sign it.  that's such shit.  the "in the end" remix for linkin park is pretty good, too.  tomorrow i'm going to church with my mom.  i don't really want to go to my own church, cause i don't really want to see tahne.  it's hard.  what am i suppose to say to her after a shitty night?  sigh....my first school ball, and the worst night of my life.  $345 gonnnnnnneeee foreverrrrrrrrr.  $345 to make me feel self-pity and sadness.  introduce me to girls, someone.  not you maryann :P.  heeey maryann i wont be able to talk to you for awhile.  i'll email you...but in case i dont, email me.  my school address is 9543@fc.skc.school.nz.    so i have 40 days of school starting monday.  im not really looking forward to it...but wee i get to see georgia b.  i'll be counting down the days till i get to checkout of bruce house (that's what the boarding house is called) again.  im gonna make the most of my opportunities starting tomorrow morning.    take care everyone.. :).
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      --- I am driving up 85 in the Kind of morning that lasts all afternoon I’m just stuck inside the gloom  4 more exits to my apartment but I am tempted to keep the car in drive And leave it all behind  Cause I wonder sometimes About the outcome Of a still verdictless life Am I living it right Am I living it right Am I living it right Why, why georgia, why  I rent a room and I fill the spaces with Wood in places to make it feel like home But all I feel’s alone  It might be a quarter-life crisis Or just the stirring in my soul Either way  I wonder sometimes About the outcome Of a still verdictless life Am I living it right Am I living it right Am I living it right Why, why georgia, why  So what so I’ve got a smile on It’s hiding the quiet superstitions in my head  Don’t believe me Don’t believe me When I say I’ve got it down  Everybody is just a stranger But that’s the danger in going my own way I guess it’s a price I have to pay Still everything happens for a reason Is no reason not to ask myself If I’m living it right  Am I living it right Am I living it right Why, why georgia, why ---  those are nice lyrics.  i just talked to her.  we talked about heaps of things...like, from my senile grandpa to her slutty sister.  heh.  she's a really nice person.  i wish every conversation with her was like our first - i was really shy, she kept nodding..we were talking about chemistry.  heh.  she'll never know how much i think about it :).
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, that last post was shit.  the direct translation of the title is 'cream with gums, please!' :P.  im actually feeling really happy now.  puberty and its mood swings are fun, sometimes.  all of a sudden i feel...i can handle the english workload.  i feel like i could read a 300 page biography in a day.  which, i probably could!  i'm haaaappy..from talking to herman and maryann.  thank you ma, you're a really nice person :).  and i've only known you for less than two weeks.  i'll be bitching to you for a long time, so i hope you're all right with that.  too bad i can't talk to gummy-grrl as much..are you there, gummy-grrl?  i wanna lick ur gums! yes...just like you're doing to yourself now.  haha :).  so yeahhhh.  i'm meant to be doing the english thing.  MEANT.  im talking to herman and listening to my itunes playlist :).  it's okay that i didn't get an ipod, or a camera.  ignorance is bliss.  what are you listening to?  try these!  last train home - lost prophets the reason - hoobastank goodbye to you - michelle branch don't stay - linkin park one flight down - norah jones dance with my father - luther vandross  >  yeah, some of them are pretty old.  i tend to listen to one song until i get sick of it, then a few weeks down the track i'll start playing it again :).  music always sounds better with headphones, have you noticed?  so...i guess i'm meant to write about some recent events.    my flight steward on the flight back to auckland was gay.  like...sexually gay.  he giggled, fluttered his eyelashes and did those 'hand pat' actions.  it didn't really bother me, in fact i think his service was exceptional.  :P.  i don't really have anything against gays.  if that's what makes them happy then go for it.  not sure what God's opinion on it is.  do you think he would mind?  cause like....gay people said they're born that way.  maybe gay people have a different type of love.  I NEED A GAY FRIEND!  if you are gay, and willing to talk about your sexuality to me, please write to:  Bruce House Saint Kentigern College Pakuranga Highway Auckland, New Zealand.  woo.  so anyway.  just went for a piss.  heidi's room looks smaller now that all her stuff's out of it.  she's probably still awake in her little city apartment.  it's quite a cozy little place, although the view was overhyped.  it's shit, all you can see is the fatass base of the skytower and stupid cars zooming past.  she seems happy there.  good.  think i'll stop there.  im gonna go nibble some kfc :).  say hi to me.    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was better than yesterday.  however, my nokia phone charger has misplaced itself and so im back on my sony ericsson for the timebeing.  i don't really mind, i've been thinking of selling the nokia to some guillable shithead.  sony ericsson makes sexier toys anyway.  BAYE.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fuck you to the fucking ends of the earth.  fuck your fake personality. fuck your superficial shit that makes you 'cool'. fuck your hypocritical thinking. fuck the tone that you speak to me in.  sometimes i question whether or not i really want you in my life.    what have you done for me?   what have i done for you?   what do i want to do for you?   nothing.  it's like you shoved a wedge in between my brain.  fucking annoying.  
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so here we are..saturday night, 11:21 pm.  i'm nearing the end of my trip, and i'm feeling really sad.  it's weird.   during my first few days here i felt i didn't fit in very well, and i hated the weather.  as i finally manage to settle in, it's time to take to the skies again.  sigh.  what is it about singapore that i love so much?    it's my home!  i grew up in just another neighbourhood, in just another little flat.  i spent afternoons and evenings playing at the playground and saturday nights walking to the local market with my dad.  i love this country.  i love the really stupid things...like...how the basketball courts are always occupied by little kids just trying to get some nets.  heh.  i love walking through the rows of stores, taking in the scent and watching store vendors casually sit on stools.    there's simplicity in the complexity of the society.  haha, good one.  what i mean is...the society is complex because everyone is going about their own business - the old men drinking their coffee, the students flagging down their respective buses, the housewives queueing at the atm machine...everyone knows exactly what they have to do, and it makes it look so simple as a whole.  it's hard to describe when you live away from home for so long.  singapore's a part of me.  i was just like the kids in the basketball courts.  man, this sounds so shit.  it's a sad but warm feeling.  didn't do much today.  heid, my mom and i just went out to meet some family friends - namely my godparents.  heh, i can recognize my godpa but not my godma...she's a pretty lady.  their kids are very cute and playful.  my only regret is that i didn't really talk to them, i didn't hold a proper conversation.  just "yes", "no"...that kinda stuff.  they're really nice people.  i wont be seeing them for awhile, but it was nice to give them hugs.  so here's my answer to my self-imposed question - everything.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      outkast is nice once in awhile :).  today was quite a good day.  i woke up and went to regi's registration of marriage.  it was nice.  can't believe my cousins are already married.  that makes me an uncle :).  im a 16 year old uncle!  regi and lily both looked really good.  i feel really happy for them.  when i get married (if ever), i'll have the church bells ringing really loud.  and there'll be that confetti stuff!  after that, we went for a huge buffet.  i had 4 mango puddings.  this brings my total mango pudding count in 1 week to....11.  lol.  my mom and i caught a cab home.  it was the funniest and best ride ever. the driver's like "where are you from?"  my mom said "auckland, but we're singaporeans".   driver: do you believe in Jesus? mom: yes driver: HALLELUJAH!  anyway, the rest of the ride was just a lot of talk about christianity and stuff.  it was cool.  made me smile :).  after school we went and played soccer with kynan's classmates.  it was fun.  they're nice people.  a lot more...approachable than my friends.  heh :P.  i got some mean blisters, but they'll heal.  don't have much else to say..it's my final weekend in singapore.  im kinda sad.  but im looking forward to seeing some friends in new zealand.  not to mention handing in my 4 assignments that i haven't started.  !!!!!!!!!!!  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey.  today heidi went back to the old flat in tampines and got the photo albums.  she got locked in the house, for some reason or another - but lets not digress.  take a look! :)    HARHAR I AM SO HAP E!11    im serious.    heidi and i.    heid and i again.    "i'll take you all on!"    heh..i remember holding that balloon.    what i look like before being blinded by the camera flash!    static hair.    captain on the bridge.. :P    :)  that's most of the photos.  heh...brings back some fond memories :).  it was nice to be a little boy.  back then i didn't have to worry about the shit i do today.  back then there wasn't peer pressure, i didn't really care what clothes i wore, how my hair was styled...everything just fell into place and worked out.  gotta get up early tomorrow for reg's marriage registration.  laater!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey.  i just woke up from a reaaaally nice afternoon nap.  nice because i had dreamt of amy and my friends again.  everything was warped.  it was night time.  i'd just finish eating breakfast (or dinner?) at the boarding house, and was walking down to school.  halfway down, i realized i forgot to pack a drink so i ran back up and got something.  anyway, as i was walking back and this maori tribal house (marai) dropped down from the sky.  it was lighted with the fluorescent white lights, and someone was cooking in it.  uhhhh.  anyway, i got my drink - orange juice - and headed down to school.  for some reason or another, i was in my formal uniform.  i reached the road between the sportscentre and science block, and i spot her.. she was with some of the older students - one named caleb.  he said, "hi simon!" and she said, "simon dont..".  i screamed "HI!" as i bolted past, as i was already late for tutor group.  i got into the science block, and they were right behind me.  she grabbed my blazer and creased it (long story, will explain).  it was really funny, we kept laughing.  the science block's walls had these drawings on them.  they were life-looking crayon portraits of teachers.  one of the teachers was my math teacher - she's a good teacher and friend, and i tell her quite a bit about my life - and it said "brother and mother" below her photo.  haha.  that's pretty much it.  you don't need to hear the part about someone squeezing my ass.  i think it was caleb that squeezed my ass.  at this point i would like to indicate that my sexual orientation is hetero.  so anyway, to extrapelate on the 'crease' issue.  it all started with allan, i think.  we started using graphical calculators at school this year, and you can progarm all sorts of shit into it - e.g stupid messages.  so he wrote "simon takes it up the batty crease", and she saw it.  she thought batty crease was a really funny term, so i've been plastered with it ever since.  it's everywhere.  in my school diary, on my pencil case, on the tip of her tongue...everywhere.    siigh, it's confusing.  i don't like her as much as i used to, but i...still want to be close with her.  i tried to get closer to her by getting to know her friend from out of school, but i ended up going for her friend instead.  that wasn't the right thing to do.  i was kinda sincere about it but i knew all along that all i really wanted was her.  so was i toying with her friend's feelings?  yeah.  how do you make up for something like that?  i don't know.  blah. 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gooood morning :).  how are you today?  i'm pretty good.  i've only been awake for about an hour.  it's raining today in singapore!  do you like rain?  with the exception of vanessa and i, everyone hates it.  maybe because it washes hairgel and makeup off.  hehe.  walking in rain is such a calming experience.  anyway.  what's on your mind?  i'm not thinking of anything.  i can't recall my dream from last night.  but last night itself was quite funny.  kynan and i were talking about some of the funniest moments in our childhood.  i shouldn't really talk about the one incident that stood out :P but it involved national day, a bus driver, $2, and mc donalds.  heh :).  i talked to one of her friends today.  i dont think i impressed her friend too much.  in fact, she probably thinks im a crackhead.  sure, why not.  dont really have anything planned for today.  i finally have a day in my holidays where i can sit around and do jack.  later.  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dreamt about her this morning.  we weren't doing anything special, i just saw her and we started talking.  i can't remember what was said, but it was a nice conversation.  you know...nothing too stimulating, but enough to make you smile.  she smiled at me :).  we were just about to get somewhere when my mom woke me up.  30 minutes later i was sitting in the new zealand embassy.  an hour later i was out the door, in sim lim square.  that's funny, sim lim square.  that's my shortened name.  heidi decided to get her contacts so we had to sit around for ages.  im not sure whether or not she actually needs contacts.  some people just get stuff so they feel 'made'.    in some way, i'm that type of person.  i mean, why was i going to get an ipod?  cause it's cool?  cause my friend has one?  i don't even f'ing know!  my ibook's an mp3 player in itself..just a tad heavier.  so, i made the decision - for which i am sure to regret - to NOT get one.  yes, you read correctly...i'm not getting an ipod.  i have convinced myself that a portable music device to which i would play pirated music is not worth $500.  how so, you ask?  today in the cab we were driving along...and this person on the pavement caught my eye.  he was handicapped.  im not sure how.  he was like....crippled but still walking.  his jaw looked dislocated, and the fingers on his left hand were curled inwards.  he had a walking stick in his right hand as he hobbled towards the traffic light.  it was really sad.  he couldn't even walk with his face looking fowards.  the first thought that came to my mind was if whether or not he knew Jesus.  then i thought, if Jesus was here right now, he would put his arm on the man's shoulder...and the man would immediately start walking upright.  i know it's probably hard for you to imagine that, especially in today's high-tech-no-miracles-world.  after seeing that man, i just felt really stuck up.  i have a shitload of stuff that i could be content with, but all i want is more.  what did the man have?  not much...he had a bag of groceries and some kind of disease.  i wonder if he knew what was wrong with him, and whether or not he felt sorry for himself.  it must be really hard for people like that.  whoever said all men are created equal might have to rethink that statement, because on one side of the road you have a cripple and on the other you have a young businessman driving a yellow porche.  yesterday, when i went out for lunch with my mom's friend this old lady came around selling tissue packets.  she had a man - presumably her son follow her.  he was blind.  that's pretty sad, how someone has to support herself and her family by selling tissue packets.  3 for a dollar, i think it was.  poor people.  you know, there are enough resources in this world to ensure that noone goes unfed.  but then again, you can't have the rich without having the poor.  does everything in existence have an opposite?  the money i want to spend on the ipod could go to better uses.  maybe i'll ask my mom for the $500 so i can spend it the way i want it spent.  i'd like to spend some on myself, and give some away to the needy.  it's a nice thought, and im sure i'll find putting it into action much harder.  you know how people are around money.  we'll see how it goes :).   
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      would you like that chicken upsized?
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey.  it's been a really long week.  since my last posting there have been a couple of ups and downs.  the main thing being that i'm over georgia.  it's definite.  i haven't been thinking of her much, and she hasn't been in any of my dreams since.  it happened over the weekend - she got SO mad at me because i didn't want to talk to amanda.  yeah, wtf.  the whole reason why i didnt want to talk to amanda was because i wanted to talk to her instead... but she's just so fickle-minded (thanks chel :) to realize that.  on monday she just said one thing to me, and today she asked me another question, but i just told her that "i thought we weren't on talking terms".  she told me "i'm fine with that"...and looked like she didn't care.  haha.      i'm happy.  i feel quite independent now.  after the whole incident i felt a burst of inspiration.  i was thinking about trying to be a prefect, but i'm not so sure now.  who knows, i might change my mind in the weeks to come.  so anyway...the week was pretty boring.  i started paying attention in physics and i understand it perfectly.  in chem we're doing titration.  it's quite fun...i like the challenge of getting the amounts 100% on the dot.  today i stayed back at school to watch the orchestra and jazz band play.  they played really well.  i knew quite a few people playing - ollie, david r, david 'chaz' g, liam, m.j (ben morley-john), and sherry!  i brought the camera along, but because it was so loud i couldn't hold it steady....so a lot of the shots came out blurry :(.  i didn't get a good one of sherry either.  it seemed like she wanted to laugh everytime she played her flute - maybe it's just the way she blew it :P.  everyone i knew gave me 'the eye'.    it was cool, i'd like to go to one of those again.  classical music is pretty classy.  that sounded lame.  but it is.    i'm not playing soccer this weekend.  the 2nd XIs giving us 4 players so i get a 'rest'.  heh.  im gonna go watch the rugby tomorrow at my school.  hopefully i'll be able to get some good photos :).  the team's doing really well, tomorrow's the semi finals.  i think what's appealing about rugby are the hits.  it satisfies a primal hunger.  mm...mrs.cunningham has some truth in all her blabber :).  my dad's gonna be okay.  thank God.  thanks to everyone that expressed concern and prayed...i really appreciate it :).  oh yeah...I GOT A POSTCARD!!!!!! from chel :).  it's quite a neat feeling, knowing that she had the postcard in her hands.  i got it over lunch at bruce house, so the 99 other boarders started this huge commotion over this 'chel' girl from pennsylvania.  she's cool.  i've started making pen-pals (its not as bad as it sounds), just as an output of my boredom.  it's been quite interesting.  i'd like to meet chel one day.  on my big o.e...although i'm not sure i'll have time for one.  heh.  anyway, that's about all i feel like writing.  im gonna go relax.  night.  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sunday night, 9:27 pm at the boarding house.  i didn't get a whole lot done today.  slept at 4 am because i was up talking to *SOMEONE* :P.  you know who you are!  when i finally got up at 2 pm i didn't really feel like doing anything.  so i just came online and started talking to nicole.  she told me i have a natural affinity (that probably wasn't the right term, but it sounded good) for expressing myself.  that made me happy :).    i really like writing.  there's something about the written word that appeals.  i think even in today's tech-savy world people still like to receive hand written snail mail letters, but it's just a little too inconvinient compared to email.  it's a bit like a comic book - would you rather read a comic off your computer screen or be able to hold it, turn the pages, and read it?  it's a different experience altogether.    anyway.  i'm gonna go and snag some food from david.  later :).          
    
</post>


</Blog>