<Blog>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are working on puting a newsletter and a e-mail together with updates for the organization most likely going to be an update from every state.  We have not finalized a mailing list yet.  If anyone would like to help please e-mail us  at mike@aisforafrica.org.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the new blog for PA-AFA.  I am working on setting up accounts for the Pennslyvania Leadership to update this blog.  I am testing creating other accounts to update the blog with my school's network administrator.  Lets thank him and everyone else who is helping.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On behalf of the Pennsylvania A's For Africa team we would like to wish everyone a Happy and an enjoyable Easter Holiday!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michael recieved a call from Senator Terry Punt after talking to his inlaws. The meeting is tentatively scheduled for Friday April 30 at 3pm.  Michael will be presenting the organization to the sentator as well as the area of Africa we have chosen to "inflatrate" in, our goals and much more.  He are going to try to get atleast one picture with the senator.   Submitted by M. Brown 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The WASHS (Waynesboro Area Senior High School) Executive Council concluded their two day fundraiser on Thurdsay.  They asked teacher to bring in their prom pictures since there prom is today (May 8).  The student body at lunch voted on the best couple. Right know I do not know the amount we raised but I will update you on that at a later date.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The site is completely up.  As far as I can see there are no errors holding viewers from gonig to pages or anything like that.  If you find any erros please email me asap, mbrown2005@hotmail.com with what page they are on and describe if you can.  Thanks guys.  Lets do some great work
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all.  Some updates for you.  The 2004 Pennsylvaia State Studnet Council Conference is at one of our members high schools'.  He is a co-chair of the event.  We are working on what we can do for A's For Africa there.  We are also contacting a local radio host in the Waynesboro Area.  Her name is Delilah, she has her own program 7pm-12am Monday through Friday.  Why are we contacting her you ask, well does is astonish you that she is taking a trip to Africa herself.  Go visit her site to learn more about her trip www.radiodelilah.com.  I am working to see if she can put us on the  air or help us in anyway, like being a resource person.  Cross your fingers that she e-mails me  back and says "Yes I can help you guys"  Watch for more updates about this. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, all.  It is getting down to the end of school, the call of the summer is coming.  Remember that you can start a fundraiser this summer.  You can start one with donation jars by getting permission from a resturant owner or manager and putting it near the register.  You can also start one in your community.  Get the word out!  -Mike 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning all you A's For Africa members.  If you would like to recieve an account to update this blog for the Pennsylvania team to keep other states and the NAC up to date on what we are doing please e-mail Michael Brown at mbrown2005@hotmail.com or mike@aisforafrica.org informing me that you do indeed want an account.  In the subject line of the e-mail please have Pennsylvania AFA Team and in the body of the e-mail please put the username a primary and a secondary username and a password.  Thank you very much for your help and dedication to our goal.  -Michael Brown Pennsylvania A's For Africa Vice President Pennsyvlania A's For Africa Web Coordinator "The only thing for the triumph of evil is for good men to do nothing."-Edmund Burke
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, just got back from vacation adn Presidential Classroom. I would like to send an invite to all members of PA-AFA to become a committee chair.&nbsp; If you are interested please e-mail me (Mike) or Josh. Our e-mails are on the site.&nbsp; We will review your stats for being in this position.&nbsp; Again if you are interested please send me or Josh and email   Michael Brown-  urlLink mbrown2005@hotmail.com  Josh Hostetter-  urlLink joshhostetter@aisforafrica.org   Michael Brown- A4APA 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following new e-mail addresses you can send e-mail to by the end of July/begining of August.&nbsp; These will be used for e-mail address for anyone and everyone to e-mail us at. They are below.   urlLink AisForAfricaPA@hotmail.com   urlLink AisForAfricaPA@yahoo.com   Remember Josh's e-mail is  urlLink joshohostetter@hotmail.com  or  urlLink joshhostetter@aisforafrica.org .&nbsp; Mike's e-mail is  urlLink mbrown2005@hotmail.com .&nbsp; You can e-mail both of them at either of the two e-mails above.  Thank you 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>