<Blog>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today: bike riding, rowing machining, and DeBary going.  Good ride this morning, although i have to get the Emo off my iPod.  I used to keep a lot f music on there that i though other people might like (which accounts for the Emo), but any more to hell with it.  It's really hard to change the track while on the bike.  I have to reach around into the outside pocket of my back pack, and try and find the iPod, otherwise i ahev to go hands free, slip on strap off my shoulder and dig around in there while doing 14 to 20 MPH, and being totally invisiable to automobiles.  At the gym, i have to stop my faux rowing, and it can be kind of painfull to get back into the groove.  Ok, so i'll stop whining, but damn, I really hate Jets to Brazil.  How did i not know this about myself?! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, day three of not riding my bike is going just as planed.  Not that I wanted to not ride my bike, but it turns out that my occupation has required that I do some traveling as of late.  My destination is/has been the township DeBary, Fl which touts it's self as "The River City."  I'm not so sure that it is city so much as state road 17-92, and a "Lil' Champ" food mart some twenty odd miles from any place I’d rather be.  The pace of life is slower in DeBary, reminding one of the simple things in life like summer days, palmetto bugs, and Chinese water torture.  In DeBary a dollar will still buy you enough rope to hang a man where ever fine ropes are sold.  In DeBary the tap water smells like farm equipment.  In DeBary 12 year old children can vote.  In DeBary, I’ll watch another 5 hours of my life creep by today waiting for corporate pamphlets roll off the printing press.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       New Plan:   Joined a gym near the office, will ride my bike the 15 mile round trip from home to work every day.  Will bring change of clothes and shower at gym in the morning.   Expected Results:   Save money on gas, at least enough to off set the price of the gym membership.  Will save money on electricity; taking a shower at the gym saves hot water produced by my water heater, the most inefficient device ever created.  Will not be tempted to smoke in the car on the way to work, i.e. I will not be in the car, but on a bicycle.  Will be unfat.   Drawbacks:   While making sure that the gym provided individual shower stalls, that does not guarantee that you will be totally shielded from the naked people.  8:30 in the morning is way too early, rather it is always way too early to be in the same room with a naked man, much less engage in conversation with one.  One must get up early to ride to ones bike a particular distance.  When one over sleeps, one is unable to ride ones bike to work in timely order.  One is however, while sitting in traffic, able to see an old lady that looked like Lou Reed.  Had one been responsible, one may have missed out on this anomaly.      
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today: day one, not smoking.  Came up with alternate plan, no name, but it is centered around the notion of not quitting smoking.  Lisa does not think this is such a good idea.  Stay the course.  We have abandoned ship on TGSO.  Yesterday we pooled the cigarettes we had left for the remaining days of the program, something like 15, and smoked them all.  Today in place of cigarettes I have had three bagels and a bike ride through college park to my bank.  Feeling ok.  A little spacey really with is better then the full tilt anger I experienced this morning while working on the database (Angered at my Disappointment, might I point out.)  Curse you Sir Walter Raleigh you were such a stupid Git.       
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      TGSO plan is turning into a farce.  This is ridiculous.  For all of you who dare tread that well worn two lane path of kicking the smoking habit/cruel addiction be forewarned TGSO is not for every one.  Many disclaimers say “contact you physician before starting any…” I say contact your compulsive edgy side, he/she knows you better than any M.D. ever will.  For those of you who would rather not read The Sloth in its entirety, or for that matter Lisa’s copious chronology of the process known as the TGOS (http:/thegreatsmokeout.blogspot.com) I’ll pair it down for you.  Smoke many cigarettes on day one and then systematically cut back over the following 14 days.  Sounds pretty good right?  Bite me!  It’s like quitting every day for 14 days.  14 days of angst and panic, and having no excuse to go outside during the work day.  Actually it’s worse than that because you are still smoking, and smelling of smoking, and feeling crooked in the eyes of healthy bright skinned nonsmokers who make more money than you do, and who have a gym membership that they actually put to good use, and kitchen appliances made of stainless steel, and a water heater that runs on gas which predates 1985, and cuts back on electric costs.  My friend Sandie has been off the squares for a year now.  While she was never the nicotine fiend that I was/am she did it (Go you!) and tells me that cold turkey is the only way to go.  I’ve never understood why they call it cold turkey, (Is cold turkey a cure-all for the shakes of smack withdrawal?) never the less, I think I hear that chilly bird calling my name.  3 smokes down, 3 to go for the day.      
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sigh, just smoked cig # 5 on day 5 of TGSO.  Damn it.  Only alotted eight today.  Down to 3.  Wow.  Sorrow.  That is all.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A so-so day behind the desk:  Hair becoming difficult.  An awkward stage.  No amount of product has the wherewithal to tame my wayward locks, and too long to wear a hat.  The hair that curls up underneath the brim dwarfs the hat and makes “My Big Ted Kennedy Head” look even more mellony.    The Disappoint (of the mighty beast known as Anger and Disappointment) is beginning to creep into my soul as day three of phase two in the Great Smoke Out wears on. I am disappointed in my anger (as opposed to angered by my disappointment.)    Our friend MSN messenger records:  Dave, David, Dutch says: what are you up to?  Lisa says: i'm learning how to make shoelaces  Dave, David, Dutch says: haha  Lisa says: Just taking care of random stuff.  And waiting for Sergei.  Dave, David, Dutch says: that's interesting, but i ment butt count  Dave, David, Dutch says: how many squares you done smoked today?  Lisa says: oh, i'm a dumbass  Lisa says: we've both had 3  Dave, David, Dutch says: alright fuck it, record this:  #4 1:18 pm      Which found our hero sitting on the stoop smoldering once again, smoking number four out ten allotted cigarettes on the day.  Lisa and I have been keeping a log of the times we smoke with little notations in the margin, “c” for example to denote that the cigarette in question was smoked in the car.  In this manor we hope to identify potential stumbling blocks in the daily grind.    A note I might make in the future would be an “s” to signify that Stu, trouncing me in Ping Pong a record 5 matches helped exacerbate my current state of Disappointment.  But no, I’d hate to admit that Stuart drove me to number 4 today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today's post comes from inside the world of The Great Smoke out courtesy of Microsoft Instant Messenger.  What follows may be unsettling to some readers:  Lisa says: hey, did you smoke while you were gone?  Lisa says: the last cig i have listed was 1:06  Dave, David, Dutch says: yeah, 2:40  Lisa says: that's it?  Lisa says: you only had 1 smoke?  Dave, David, Dutch says: yep  Lisa says: you went an hour 35, that's fantastic  Dave, David, Dutch says: i could go again though  Lisa says: i'm fading, i'm about to need #6  Dave, David, Dutch says: yeah, took a bagel in the car  Dave, David, Dutch says: what am i at 5?  Lisa says: yesterday #6 was about 2 for us  Lisa says: you just sat in the car and ate a bagel?  Dave, David, Dutch says: that's cool  Lisa says: you've had 5  Lisa says: so have i  Lisa says: actually, you had #7 at 2:20 tyesterday, you are doing awesome  Dave, David, Dutch says: go me!  Lisa says: we are rocking, i wish this never had to end  Lisa says: i hate quitting smoking  Lisa says: let's go smoke  Lisa says: please, please, please  Dave, David, Dutch says: the quitting so far is cool, it's the parts not smoking that suck  Lisa says: smoke smoke smoke  Lisa says: smoke smoke  Lisa says: need cigarette  Lisa says: smoking time  Lisa says: need cigarette or die  Lisa says: help help  Lisa says: need to go smoke  Lisa says: please smoke  Lisa says: smoke smok  Lisa says: e  Lisa says: help, need cigarette  Lisa says: only a few days left  Lisa says: will suffer and die slow death  Lisa says: help, come smoke  Lisa says: where the hell are you?  Lisa says: come smoke?  Lisa says: what is wrong, why won't you come smoke a cigarette with me?  Lisa says: when is smoking time?  Lisa says: please make it soon, i need a cigarette?  Lisa says: why won't you smoke?  Lisa says: where the hell are you?  Lisa says: please come smoke a cigarette.  Lisa says: i think i'm getting jumpy  Lisa says: i think that i'm getting anxious  Lisa says: i need a fucking cigarette  Lisa says: when is it cigarette time
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Discovered yesterday that I got the shaft from Dell on the Accessories > Calculator function.  Why would they do that?  Curious.  Day two of the kind of not smoking program.  Yesterday, smoke all you can, today, smoke only twelve.  Lisa and I have received a lot of flack from our colleagues, all nonsmokers, about our program.  Therefore, where once the plan raged under the banner reading "The Great Smoke Out," the plan will be here after known as "Butt Out!" to all nonsmokers.  That is to say with the exception of Lisa and I who are grandfathered in.  Once we cross the threshold and enter nonsmokerdom we shall still be able to refer to the utterly successful "The Great Smoke Out" program as "The Grate Smoke Out" of aught-four.   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Color change for the Giant Sloth, found someone who used the same template, and felt like a  jack-ass for just blindly using the blog template.  So, changed the color, also added the , oooo,what shall now be known as rock my sloth section, where you the user can say things to the sloth, and each other.  Good times, gotta scare up some work, and also today=day one of the serious plan to quit smoking.  Plan developed by Lisa entails smoking a lot today, and then scaling back over the next 2 weeks, Lisa will be using Zyban (lame) and I will be using hard work, perseverance, and exercise (awesome.)  Also, Tiffany now has a dream job at a bar.  Way to go pal! 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Food related entry.  Lunch yesterday: Uncle Ben's microwaveable rice bowl of the vegetable teriyaki variety, green tabasco, water, whole box of Cheez-it twisters of the hot wings and blue cheese variety (will not be doing that ever again)  Lunch day before yesterday: Grape-ape smoothie, bicycle ride to and from smoothie, actually bicycle ride to smoothie, hard ride back, drinking smoothie does not readily allow for breaking.  Lunch today: Pad Thai from the cheesecake factory (seemed like a good idea at the time), Pelligrino sparkling water, also some bread.     Work on roof finished, but who keeps tiping over the trash can outside?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah, so...Spending the morning searching the almighty google for images to use in an ad campaign.  Finding that the internet is largely a receptacle for digital images of chubby older women and their cats.  Also on the internet, pics of pg-13 models.  Also on the internet, screen shots of video games.  Also on the internet, not what I'm looking for. So far have discovered internet=rubbish bin, and where to get the magical sword in the tenth frame of "super lame dungeon master 5."  Did however buy a camera on eBay from a man in Russia.  So, that's a plus. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm being edited!    Today's Teatime talking point: "What statue would you erect in your home town?"  While divergent, my submission ran:   Dear Andrew, It astounds me every time I return to my home town I find it ever more littered with the gaudy effigies of Mayor Mc Cheese, and The Ham-burglar.  What, I ask you have they ever done for the city?!  Were I Mayor Mc Cheese I wouldn't be such an ego maniac.  Best, David C. Houder   Today Andrew read my email aloud, however he stopped after the first sentence. (punch line clearly lies in the third)  I am wondering if Andrew had to cut short his oration because of the DAB digital radio ad the station had to run, or because he was embarrassed by the fact that he pronounced Mayor Mc Cheese as "M.C. Cheese"  I clearly heard him chuckle as her read, but then upon realizing the error of assiging Mayor Mc Cheese a title that might give him "Street Cred" Andrew says rather sardonicly, (aprox.) "Ah well he comes from the land where McDonalds is found."  Caw!  Dear Blogger, how desperately I want to be accepted by the British!  P.S.  Ms Word Acting Up, Doing that thing where it types over other letters when you try to insert text, Possiable misspellings afoot. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1st official entry:  Today: At office working on company style guide for (nth) day.  Page 2 of the “font’s” section.  Listing to, and enjoying the daily broadcast on the BBCs 6 Music.  Teatime in particular.  Trying to stay off caffeine, coffee in particular, all the same, had tea this morning.   At Andrew Collins (host of 6 Music’s Teatime) prompting submitted an email on the talking point (aprox: “where were you not?”) which ran:      Dear Andrew, I wasn’t there at our last company meeting on Friday.  I was however enjoying a leisurely ride back to the office on my 1966 Schwinn bicycle, having just come from a delightful lunch at a local burrito establishment.  The consequences, alas, were having to endure much good natured heckling from my esteemed coworkers as I entered the conference room full of  more responsible employees who chanced to see me, quite sweaty, holding aloft a rather bulky vintage bicycle fresh from my climb up the stairs.  M.I.A. David C. Houder     Was it read on air to the whole of the British Empire and the internet audience at large?  Unknown.  Stuart called me to a ping pong match.  Left the series empty handed. I attribute the caffeine in this morning’s tea to a lapse in concentration which caused me to give away valuable points.   Will I go to lunch?  Unknown.  Tried to hold out yesterday, instead ate 12 ounces of pasta salad with green Tabasco.   Men working on the roof of the office.  Wouldn’t think it would require so much banging to repaper and tar the structure.  Bang. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well let us see how this works.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, in fact, it seems as if Blogger is a bit buggy.    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, as you may be able to tell I have changed my blog template.  It's a good looking template, there's no two ways about that, but I've never cared for templates.  I rather do it myself, but today I am tired of fighting with blogger.  I have not as yet been able to make my damn images load.  I don't know what the hell the problem is.  To make matters worse every now and then they do load, and instead of being happy for my Jpegs of Capistrano I am just confused which makes me angry and disappointed in that order.    A side note before I get onto other matters.  Am very tired today because I shamefully stayed up late last night to watch Notting Hill.  What an awful film!  I hate Julia Roberts.  You can tell she is a totally soulless flake, and what's more is that she has two bottom lips, which is really the least of my gripe.  Anyway dear reader, I wanted to speak to you on a matter that has been on my mind as of late.  Over the past few weeks I have developed a friendship via email with someone.  I have never laid eyes on this person before, but the individual in question seems affable enough, and friendly, and is not a leper from what I can tell.  Were this relationship to have developed in the space outside my computer screen I would never give it's nature a second though, but the fact that I now have an internet pal is disturbing to me some how.  I know this should not be the case after all we live according to a gazelshaft societal model.  I remember back in fourth grade we were assigned Russian pen pals to whom we would write letters that would be returned just as you were losing interested.  Was the Berlin wall down yet?  I don't think so.  I guess that means the KGB got hold of the sea shells my pen pal asked me to send him.  It could be that 8 ounces of coquina shells and I sent my poor comrade and his family off to Siberia to farm snow for the good of the state.  Man, I never thought of that until just now.  Cor!  I feel totally ok about my internet pen pal now.  I'm glad we had this talk.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "Why does everything have to fight me?" - a pontification by Deli Sage and Uncle Edward Kelly   So why is that?!  Is it some kind of Bruce Lee-esque curse that plagues my family line?  Did my ancestors anger the gods of all things tedious, thereby turning any task into a Sisyphean ordeal?  This bitching and wining stems from the fact that the Sloth's title graphic went down yesterday.  I have since shuffled said graphic through 3 different web site providers with mixed results.  In hope that either Blogger, or my service providers have decided to stop being little bitches I checked in on The Sloth moments ago to find that not only was the graphic missing, but also all of the text.   Bite me! (I'm fairly sure I the fuck up didn't happen on my end.  I think.)  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey WTF?!  When I checked The Sloth to see if the post posted, my title graphic was replaced by some ghetto "image hosted by a self-serving web provider."  Then after clicking refresh a few times it went away.  If that happens again please let me know.  Please, Guys, c'mon.  Echo....echo......echo.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, today an excerpt from life inside data management:   Lisa says: i wish i could go and you wish i could go  Lisa says: you might ask christine  Dave, David, Dutch says: no, i'm just being lazy  Dave, David, Dutch says: and what's with the database?  Lisa says: you can just give me the $5 if you want  Lisa says: i hate the f*cking db  Dave, David, Dutch says: no, it's not the same  Dave, David, Dutch says: tell me about it,   Dave, David, Dutch says: it's soooooooooooo high matinance  Dave, David, Dutch says: i think serg is just fucking with us  Lisa says: do you think the db is really a sandwich  Lisa says: and he just sticks stuff in it to mess with us  Lisa says: like today he put some bologna and legos in it?  Dave, David, Dutch says: he's probally not in the ukraine at all, he's probally some 14 year old kid who lives down the street  Lisa says: omg, i bet you are right  Dave, David, Dutch says: logos?! haha  Lisa says: that's probably the person who's been hanging outside my kitchen window  Dave, David, Dutch says: yeah i bet!  Dave, David, Dutch says: legos  Dave, David, Dutch says: i mean  Lisa says: yes, the legos  Lisa says: fuck that shit  Lisa says: i hate the fucking db  Lisa says: and no one, no one understands the pain except you and I  Dave, David, Dutch says: soul sucking database  Lisa says: no one else gives a shit or has to get stressed over mislabled providers  Lisa says: but yet it has to be fixed our the product is CRAP  Lisa says: one of the millions of things  Lisa says: fuck this shit  Dave, David, Dutch says: yeah, everyone else sucks and is weak  Lisa says: god i want a cigarette  Dave, David, Dutch says: i want to put the database in a figure 4 leg lock  Dave, David, Dutch says: and i also want a recumbant bicycle  Lisa says: hehehe  Dave, David, Dutch says: well, i think i've got my next blog entry  Lisa says: hehe, yah  Lisa says: hey, wanna play ping pong? i need to refocus and that will sure help  Lisa says: either that or yo-yo  Dave, David, Dutch says: yeah lets ping pong after i post  Lisa says: ok  Dave, David, Dutch says: guess who i am  Dave, David, Dutch says: ready?  Lisa says: uh, space ghost?  Lisa says: uh, ok  Dave, David, Dutch says: no  Dave, David, Dutch says: moment  Lisa says: sergei?  Dave, David, Dutch says: yes! you win!  Lisa says: lol    Time Passes Slowly    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "They're so depressing going 'round and 'round Ooh, they make me dizzy, oh fast cars they run me down Fast cars, fast cars, Fast cars, I hate fast cars"  -The Buzzcocks, "Fast Cars"   Yeah, so Bike to Work Week (http://bike-to-work.com/) - May 17th - 21st.  All of you bastards should do this.  BTW I know that some of you may be critical of the fact that seem never to spend the time to hyperlink the links I put in my text, and well you can go to hell.  Furthermore you are the lazy bastards that I am targeting in my support of Bike to Work Week.  On that note I am hereby dedicate the 17th thru the 21st Don't Be a Lazy Bitch and Copy and Paste the Link if You Really Care That Much Week.  Yeah, and fuck you and your car.  Some kids pointed at me and laughed as I biked my way home yesterday, probally because of my shorts.  I don't wear the bike shorts (God-Help-Me!) but I was wearing my favorite Addidas soccer shorts, and for some reason, shorts just seem to illicit laughter in my direction. Perhaps school children are just incited to giggle at the sight of my shapely legs.  But no matter, they were waiting for a city bus.  Haha!  You have to ride a stinky bus, and take home a progress report for your mom to sign, and eat rectangular shaped pizza!  I almost gave them the finger, but then I thought better of giving 4th graders the finger so I quickly morphed my gesture into an ambivalent thumbs up.  I didn't want those kids to know they'd gotten inside my head.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It seems as if the powers that be may succeed in arresting my will to live today as I will shortly be instructed by Sergei (A Ukrainian, living in the Ukraine, with whom we communicate over the MSN instant messenger [one of the more garbled means of communication, second only to gibberish I suppose]) as to how to access and manage our SQL database.  If a database were a animal I imagine it would be a  Lamprey Eel.  The Lamprey Eel, for those of you unfamiliar with it:    "When attacking, the lamprey fastens onto its prey and rasps out a hole with its rough tongue."   - http://www.seagrant.wisc.edu/greatlakesfish/sealamprey.html   After which the eel sucks the guts and the very soul from it's prey.  That's kind of what the database does to me.  (sigh) I am a graphic designer, however my initial job description, and indeed my business cards read "Programmer."  (Fucking Hell!) So, some of these tedious programming duties still fall to me and my reluctant knack for techsavy.  But sweet reprieve! The Overlord, C.E.O., and all around master of large Chocolate Lab hounds has indicated that she would like us to leave early today if we so desire. I desire it so, and in 20 minutes or less I shall be speeding across the cityscape (sounds better than urban sprawlscape) on my shiny blue bicycle.  Happy day!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>