<Blog>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        My sister...    No one knows my sister... most people just pass her by as if she is nothing important, like getting to know her is a big waste of time. I don't understand why people do this... I'm always having people coming up to me comparing me to her, or saying things like, "No offense, but I really don't like your sister."  When these people say that they don't like her, it is as if my entire world stops. As soon as their words leave their mouth all sound is cut off. My ears don't work and everything turns into a black and white picture. The world is moving in slow motion and my mouth doesn't work, nothing works. I'm paralyzed... I can't tell if it is the shock or the anger that I feel that is rushing to my head. Everything is horrible. They DON'T even KNOW her. It makes me furious but I manage to bring color back to my world. It takes me five minutes or so to get back, and the struggle of it all makes me dizzy. Once I am back I try to act nice to that person that dislikes her, but it is a very hard thing to do. I know that they are entitled to their opinion but sometimes I just wish that someone could keep their mouths closed.  I just wish that she met someone that loved her, like my best friends to me. (At least I think they love me)   My sister, lostwinds I call her, has friends but they are all so mean to her. They push and prod and anger and put down. Everytime I see them I feel like murdering them. Don't they realise that she has been through alot? She's helped me with my eating habits, switching schools, making friends, becoming independent, pulled me away when that guy reached for his gun. She's been through shit. She's fallen down far in the social ladder, climbs back up, and slides down again. She's dealing with grades, my family's demanding nice-ness, my revolving feelings, the guy that she likes, our ex-best friend, my parents trying to kill eachother, the rumours, our dying camp, our disheartened spirits... She's terrific... but no one realises... I didn't even realise until today.  I was so wrapped up in my own crazy world that I didn't even realise how she was tumbling through her guises of fake smiles and faulty laughs. I'm so   ANGRY   at myself for not realising her tears, her depression...  I never noticed that she cried herself to sleep for I no longer sleep in the same room as she does.  How do I know all of this? Of her dying hope, strength, and love? Of her crushed dreams and her broken faith? How? Easy answer... I read her secret poems, stories, and such... I even broke into an account of hers. It's not a great thing to pry... It's mean. However, I was so angry with her. Our fights seemed to have been all of her fault. I swallow my own tears now and let forth the compassion for her lost soul. I never knew how she was dying... But now, thanks to my ruthless spirit, I have seen something that I had completely ignored before... I have seen a girl that puts on giant, plausible smiles to hide the hurt that lies so thickly within her heart.  Thinking of Nicole reminds me the good ole days of my camp... My camp was a great place. All the words ever created couldn't come even close at expressing the beauty, the adventure, the lessons learned, the magic...  However, I have written something below to show of my feelings towards the below.    Dear Me,       Love isn't possible at this age, they all say. Yet how can one truly love their family and friends at this age then, I must ask them. This love argument has nothing to do with my feelings for any one person but for one lone place that is forever stuck in my mind... and that place is my camp...      Every day I think of my camp. Every moment I live, every breath I breathe, every step that I take, every turn that I make, every thought that I create, every artwork that I illustrate, is of camp. Whether it is intentionally or unintentionally it is always coming out. The passion I have camp is always there in the back of my mind. It never walks away, it never eases away, it is hold so tight that a few tears shred from inside and litter my eyes with wet sparkles. The magic has never left my heart or my mind. It is a never-ending story to remember as it is a never-ending grieving session.      My memories of camp are blissful. They reflect many pleasurable times filled with hidden secrets and wondrous magic... They are so enjoyable... They are so wonderful that tears drip out of my eyes like a drizzling rain after a thunderstorm. The tears pour from my heart and a feeling of loneliness and longing nearly completely replaces the once joyous memories. This pain erupts but the beauty of it all never fades. The splendor is beyond even the wisest human's comprehension. It is the toughest part to try to understand, why the beauty chose to awash me with its delightedness... However the most cunning and brightest people in the world would spend many years trying to figure this out for it is nearly impossible. Only those that are not fools but are not wise would understand...      Although many common folks seem to fit that description, it is not so... A background, a canvas, must be built and painted upon. The people need a special personality... or none at all... They, like I, would enjoy my camp's mystic scents of everlasting love and tenderness for many years, not letting the question go unanswered but neither resolved. One day, they too, would discover that answer. That is not very simple nor quite complex. The answer can be understood in many of different shapes and forms. It all depends on the person who asked it.     In other cases the answer to this question may be written in a paragraph or only a few sentences, but in my case it would take years for you to even begin to understand those simple words strung together to formulate the sentences that I shall write below this paragraph. The words are simple, much like two plus two equals four, but their meaning should never be repressed.       "The answer to this question has been neither easy nor hard to learn or understand. The answer is basic enough for even the youngest child to understand as well as the eldest adult. Camp blesses those with hope, love, faith, generosity, compassion, and/or crazy, almost impossible dreams. It blesses these people with the strength to pursue their wackiest ideas about life and love. However, although it is Certaintly marvelous gifts some people lose sight of these qualities in them for the growing power of greed that overcomes them. Camp does not do any service to those that do thus. Even though camp seems selfless in this act, it is not entirely NOT benefiting from this process. Along the way of your path of life, it teaches you life lessons. It teaches you things that will help you grow into a strong, caring, and wonderful person. The lessons are taught underneath your eyelids as you move throughout the waters, beaches, island, and other adventured places. It teaches you to survive and respect even your cruelest enemies even at your worst moments. The answer is one to ponder on... Camp shapes into a real "human." It shapes you this way without any damage to your soul. It does not act against your will. It changes your mind on things... It changes you until you realize that worrying about everything going on in your life is the most foolish thing to do at the moment. Your worries disappear with the roaring wind and your tears fall into the depths of the soothing lake. It turns your fears and your dreams into one. Thunderstorms are beautiful when you are there. Everything is beautiful when you are there. It is as if time has stopped. It teaches the most important lessons that a person can learn and with ease. It teaches you... so that in hopes of one day someone changes themselves because of the things you do that they taught you. It is saving the world, every person at a time.   Signed lovingly.    Why does Nicole remind me of my camp? Why, you may ask me a million times. I think the only one answer is  that Nicole has taken the magic of camp and has hidden it there in her heart. Something about her drives me wild. Everything she does has a faint aurora of camp attached to it. It's beautiful. I guess camp hasn't ever truly left me. It sustained itself in the hearts of those that have fallen apart. It pieces everything together.  You may say that I am insane. And I for one, agree with you. I am insane... A place is just a place and a person is just a person... right? Well, it's a great thing that I am crazy, for if I wasn't I would actually believe that crap.   In conclusion I've realized that my sister is something entirely different and something that will stay forever in my heart. Her spirit, her courage... She is invincible, despite her insecurities. 
     
    
</post>


<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It was a beautiful summer's day. The sky was a pleasant blue, the clouds were like giant, white cotton balls hanging in the sky, the sun was shining down in brilliance, and the temperature was not too hot but not too cool... Everyone was outside rollerblading, having picnics, playing basketball or soccer, swimming, jumping up and down on gigantic trampolines, and participating in many other social gatherings. Well, that is everyone but me. I, Kelsey, sat glued to my computer screen. Both my radio and t.v. were on. The radio was playing heavy metal music and the television was broadcasting a commercial on coffee, but they were just background noise. I was typing furiously. However, the background noise grew louder in my ears... Frustrated, I turned both of them off and opened a window instead. I needed background noise in order to live, I never liked complete silence. It crept me out too much.. This noise would be much better, it would allow me to concentrate on my work...     I turned back to my computer and typed in the last few sentences of an entry for one of my blogs, 'Koala Peace.' After carefully reading it through for any grammar mistakes, I published the post. After five hours of neverending writing I was completely finished with my blogging for the day... I stretched back, lazily... It was time to get something to eat...     I walked into my kitchen and made myself my favorite snack, a peanut butter sandwich... I stared, miserably, outside the kitchen window. I knew that I should go outside or work out or something, but I didn't feel like doing things that I just had no interest in. I became rather angry. It wasn't fair that my interests didn't revolve around sports and things like that... I loved writing and reading, don't get me wrong, but I'd love to have in interest in something other than that, that kept me fit... With the creative mind of a writer, I envisioned a terrible storm to plague the beautiful day and ruin things for everyone outdoors. I had already had a plot and the beginning sentence for a story, before I snapped out of it... It was useless to put my anger into writing... It wouldn't change anything... Sighing, I went back into my room to a couple more hours of computer time.      Many hours later, I was laying on my bed trying to get some sleep. It was three o'clock in the morning. The lights were out, the television and computer both off, and the air conditioner was on at full blast. Besides the dull roar of the air conditioner, there wasn't a sound&nbsp;throughout the entire house. Suddenly I heard something hard bounce off my bedroom window. Frightened out of my mind and hopeful that what I had just heard was imaginary, I pulled myself deeper underneath the covers. Yet again something else bounced off against my bedroom window. I let this happen two more times before I summoned enough courage to see what it was.  &nbsp; Wrapping the covers around my body, I got up and krept over to the window. I pulled back the curtain and looked out the window just as a good sized rock smacked onto the pane. At first I jumped back on impulse but then I looked back out the window to see the figure standing on my lawn that was throwing the rocks at my window. Squinting, I managed to identify the figure. I pushed the window open. &nbsp; "What are you doing here?" I called in half whisper and half scream.      This story is not complete. I'll add more later.   
     
    
</post>




<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       All though I usually post about my summer on my 'School Fool' blog, which makes no sense at all, I guess I can write a few short sentences about it on here. My summer, thus far, has gone nowhere. I have sat by my computer, staring mindlessly at an assortment of internet websites, for the entire week or so that I have been out of school. Gosh, I am so lazy and fat... I can't drag myself away from the computer (what else is there to do anyways?), so I might as well make the most of it... I'll just type about my pathetic thoughts and a good story or two (if I can find any to tell) on my blogs... Yup, aren't I making the most of my summer vacation?    Today, I shall talk about my social skills. I don't know why, but I just will. All though I am generally "okay" (at least I hope I am) in writing my thoughts, opinions, and other junk on my blogs, I have no social skills in my real life... And I am being totally serious about this. You see, I have a little thing called 'A Bad Past' that further complicates every friendship and other relationship I have. 'A Bad Past' isn't great to have because it doesn't let you trust people. Nope, it makes you avoid nearly social situation that you are thrown into... It sucks an awful lot to have...    Anyways, I am not very sociable... Every time someone talks to me I am extremely quiet, my face turns beet red, and I can't do anything but give facial expressions and body movements to indicate that I'm still alive and listening. It's rather sad. I used to be a bright, bouncy, and lovable girl, though that may be very hard to believe... I've never really had lots of friends but I was pretty well liked. At least, I believe I was. People used to come to me when they had a problem with a friend, a parent, a boyfriend, a sibling... I gave advice, talked to people about my likes and dislikes among other many other things, never picked on anyone, and even gave people parts of my lunch when they didn't have anything to eat. I was well liked, and I liked being who I was. It used to be fun, just being me... Then everything turned upside down. People used me to get what they wanted, whether it was popularity or something else. This turned me off... I became cold, distant, and impossible to talk to. I cried myself to sleep every night. I hated the world, because the world hated me. The world hated me for being me. It sucked. All of my friends started being mean and rude. They said terrible things... Eventually I left it all, made new friends, and became slightly more opener... Well, unfortunately, I don't think I'll ever grow back to trusting the world as much as I used to. Some cuts are just too deep to heal.    Every now and then, a wound that was almost completely healed, opens up again... Sometimes it is my fault and guilty conscience, but other times it is the cruel people in my life who always bring up painful memories whenever they can. It hurts a lot when they do this to me... I mean, I was never really rude to them... Yes, I hid the truth under a blanket of lies once but should that send me off to hell? Is not telling your best guy friend of nine years, that you had a boyfriend, such a big crime? Other, deeper wounds, like Camp and such, I know aren't my fault 'cause I never did anything wrong with them. Yet, part of me still believes that I am responsible for them.    Not being able to trust anyone, sucks. It hurts you a lot. You go through this really long process. Beforehand, you trust everyone but then everything, all the good in your world, just collapses...    Firstly, you believe that you're just imagining things, or that things aren't as bad as they may seem. You say in your head things like, 'Everyone has problems', and 'It's not as bad as it seems.' You're optimistic about things in the first stage, usually. Then as things worsen for you, you slowly turn into a more pessimistic person.    Secondly, you are in shock and can not defend yourself. This stage may only happen to a person that has never needed to defend themselves or just someone who is really nice. During this stage, you are amazed that all of this crap could be happening to you...    Thirdly, you get angry or confused. It seriously doesn't matter which 'cause sooner or later you'll feel through them both. For me, I was a little bit of both at this point. I was angry at the world for sending me into a downwarding spiral and confused at why the world would do anything as mean to me, who had never done anything cruel on purpose.    Fourthly, you'll try to severe ties. You'll go around apologizing over and over again to people for ridiculous things such as keeping the eraser that they let you borrow, for a few days more then you intended. You may flatter them with compliments, gifts, etc... Basically, you'll try to patch everything up even though it may not be your fault.    Fifthly, your plan will not work. You'll end up either angry or confused at everything and nothing at all.    Sixthly, you will let the world hurt you, feeling that maybe you deserve it or that they'll leave you alone after a while. This stage can last for quite a bit, and for me, it was the most painful stage of them all. The words they say will cut into your skin like knives, in the future.    Seventhly, you will become extremely depressed, angry at the world, antisocial, and/or not trust anybody. I became all four of these. You'll be quite miserable... At least I was...    Eighthly, you finally give up... There still may be flickers of moments in the previous stages but basically you're done. You'll let the bullies or whatever was cutting you up before, destroy you... You'll become either determined to not let the pain show, or let them get to you. I practiced a little bit of both. This one isn't much better than the seventh stage but usually people will discover your misery.    Ninthly, you will get away. This stage in one of the few that you have to wait for. For me, I had to wait a little while to get even part of my pain away. This one is one of most scariest stages to go through... You're dragged into situations where you're not sure how to act anymore... Eventually, things will start looking up.    Tenthly, you'll join the 'Healing Process'. How long this process takes depends on how scarred you are. I have only one painful experience in this part right now and though it has been here for five years, it is not fully healed yet.    I have faith that one day my cuts and scars created from Camp being taken away from me and other painful memories (like when my mom tried to kill my dad) will make it through this process. I know that I am strong enough to make it through, 'cause parts of me are healing and feeling great! I know that I can make it through. I've survived hell, even though some people may say what I've gone through isn't hell. But to me, it was hell... And if you can survive hell, then you can survive anything...   
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       There seems to be no end of these tiring thoughts that keep bouncing in and out of my mind. Someone out there must seriously hate me, to punish me with long hours of thinking about the terrible, tedious things that go on in my life... Yes, someone out there, whether they be human, animal, or an unknown creature, surely dislikes me.    For some reason, the topic of religion is bouncing about in my mind right now. As a Roman Catholic I am supposed to believe that Jesus is my savior and that God created the world and it took him seven days... Yet, every day I find myself questioning my faith more and more. There are so many flaws in the stories told in the Bible. On several websites, I have read people's answers to other people's questions about God and they have written on how you're not supposed to take the Bible literally... Sorry to say, I want a religion that I can take literally, I'm not all that good at reading inbetween the lines...   I have SO many questions on the Roman Catholic religion. First of all, where did God come from? He couldn't have been there all along? And something can't come from nothing... And the Arc story... There are over a billion different species of animals on this Earth... How in world could he fit two of every one of them onto one Arc? Sorry but it's not scientifically possible...    Most of you religious freaks (no offence of course) are probably thinking that I am one of those scientist people who believe in evolution or the Big Bang Theory... I'm not. I don't really believe in any science theories about how everything was created... To me, they are as impossible as some things written in the Bible.    I'm not exactly sure what I believe in. I do know that I do not believe in God... All I really want to know is the truth of our existence. Actually, I don't think I do. There are some things that people should just not know. Sure, it is fun to guess, but hey, what's the point? I guess I don't really believe in religion. I think that other people do because they find it nice to imagine a world after death... It's not so scary to die if you know that you're going somewhere afterwards... Oh, well...    I'm outie.   
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sometimes I have things that don't fit into the subjects of my other blogs... So, I recreated Koala Peace, my first blog on this site which I deleted a couple of months ago or so... Anyways, there will be no mentions of my weight, my Camp, my school, or my EBGF... Well, at least I don't think there will be... I can't really control what my future self will do in the future...    I don't really understand my life right now. Everything is just so confusing. I mean, sometimes, there are a hundred different things that run through my mind every minute it seems. Other times there are moments where it seems like I have no thoughts at all, like my mind has gone completely blank.    Whenever I can't stop thinking about something(s), I always force myself to think of something else. That something else is usually a fantasy story that I create inside my head. It's a build on story where I can make anything happen. If I'm in the I'm-So-In-Love mood, then I make the main characters or whoever, in my story, fall dramatically in love... If I'm in an angry mood I can make my characters undergo some serious, traumatizing events that will make them cry their eyes out. It may sound incredibly weird or whatever but it makes me feel better.    Lately I have been seriously frustrated with my love life... I know I'm only 13 years old and therefore can have no love life but I'm just going to call it that, okay? Anyhow, I don't really feel like telling you about why I'm so frustrated... Am I even making any sense? No? That's great!    Anyhow, I'm gone...   
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't written for a while. I'm sorry about that. I was invited to Nicole's best friend, Mindy's, thirteenth birthday/slumber party and I haven't got the chance since then to type to you about my thoughts and stuff. I'll type to you all about the party and the events that occurred afterwards, of course...   Three days ago  I was invited to Mindy's thirteenth birthday party. I wasn't all that excited to tell you the truth. Mindy isn't a very good friend towards my sister. She treats her like she's her personal slave. Nicole MUST listen to her and conform with her opinions. Honestly, she is a complete jerk. She calls her "best friends" awful names and thinks that she is the greatest. I didn't really want to go to her birthday party when she acted like a complete ass hole to my sister. I also didn't want to go because I wasn't really her friend, much less her best friend. Well, Nicole had promised Mindy that she'd go no matter what. I really didn't want to go, as I typed in the previous sentences, but I thought that it was best if I went. Nicole could certainly not be left alone with Mindy. I joked to everyone that I was going for free chocolate cake, pizza, and ice cream. I didn't want them to know that I was worried for my sister. To be truthful, I was scared that people would find out that I'm not as cold and uncaring as I appear.   More people showed up at the party  then I believed that there would be. Most of them were people that Mindy's aunt invited or her relatives. The only person that I knew was Sarah. (She had come solo because Bridget was sick.) Mindy introduced us to several people, including a twelve year old tomboy named Morgan, a thirteen year old nonconformist named Terri, and a fourteen year old "loser" named Matt. We changed into our bathing suits and hopped into Mindy's aunt's pool.   The pool was heated . I didn't go under water much. The chlorine stung my eyes painfully. In fact, I didn't really move all that much. Personally, I hate swimming. Well, I don't hate it. In fact, I love settling down on my bum on the bottom of any given pool and watch the bubbles from my mouth float to the top, the transfixed world lie above me, and how the water ripples when the other people in the pool move. I guess I just don't like actually SWIMMING in a pool. Especially in one that was jampacked with complete strangers and a not so friendly "friend."   My hands were shriveling  when we finally got out of the pool. It had felt like hours had passed. Everyone went inside and changed. Then we all stood in Mindy's aunt's kitchen and ate our dinners. I had a cheeseburger despite the fact that I want to be a vegetarian. It was a merry time. Sarah had a lot of soda and was talking up a storm with the other kids. She was asking me questions a mile a minute whenever they left to get more food. After dinner we had cake and ice cream.     Present time arrived  shortly after. Mindy opened up all of her gifts and loved nearly every one of them despite the fact that they were rather cheap, bought at the last minute type of gifts. Her most favorite gift of them all, however, was a brand new cell phone. She almost cried with happiness.   We moved our sleeping things into the motor home  that we were to sleep in that night.   Terri, Morgan, Sarah, Nicole and I  were spending the night. Matt had to leave because Mindy's parents were old fashioned and just plain disliked the idea with one boy and six girls. We watched a really corny movie that Mindy got for her birthday before Terri, Morgan, and Sarah went for another swim. Nicole and I listened to Mindy as she talked about stuff for roughly over an hour. It was mainly about her cell phone.   Then Sarah came back  from swimming. Mindy rushed out of the motor home for some weird reason. Sarah, Nicole, and I were left alone. It didn't take too many goofy remarks and funny stories before we all became serious and silent. Sarah broke the tension by confessing that Bridget told her everything that I told her. She began crying. She thought that we'd be furious with her and her sister. Cole and I shushed her. We told one another about basically what anyone says to us. How could we get angry at her for that? It just wasn't logical. We would have done the same.   Before we knew it  we were spilling our deepest, darkest secrets to one another. Sarah started to cry. Nicole comforted her and told her it was all right. I just sat there. Sarah and Bridget were as miserable as I was. They actually pitied Nicole and I, and hated themselves for thinking that they had it bad. Suddenly I felt like laughing.     Your pain is always different compared to the next  person. People can only go on for so long before they crack. Some are stronger then others and can deal with a lot more tramatizing events before they break... Others can't deal with it and fall a part easily.   People feel things differently then you.  I felt like laughing because I knew that just because I've faced more obstacles to overcome in my life then Sarah and Bridget, doesn't mean that I've been more miserable then they have.   We all became closer  from our little discussion. Soon Terri, Morgan, and Mindy came back. We spent endless hours giving each other make overs and playing truth or dare.     Mindy didn't really participate  in any of our games. She played on her cell phone the entire time, trying out ring tones. Soon, Terri and the rest of us had, had enough. We tried desperately to convince Mindy to join us but she would not put down the cell phone. We tried so hard to capture her interest that she got fed up, swore at us a couple of times, and shut herself up in a cabinet. Terri, Morgan, Sarah, and I left to a different part of the motor home while Nicole tried to soothe the angry Mindy.     Morgan, Terri, Sarah, and I  talked the night away while Mindy, after Nicole had helped to heal her angry thoughts, played on the cell phone in the other room. Everyone didn't go to sleep 'til about four thirty in the morning. Since I forgot my medication, I was up 'til about six in the morning, though.   Terri and Morgan  left early the next morning. Sarah, Nicole, and I waited in silence for Mindy, who was still sleeping soundly, to wake up. Mindy's aunt ended up having to wake her up. Mindy called her aunt several crude names before getting out of bed.   We didn't have breakfast  which I was sort of dissapointed at. Nicole, Sarah, and I packed up our stuff and threw it into Mindy's dad's van instead. He drove us to the local cinema where we watched the movie, The Village. The movie was awesome in my opinion. It was so mind bending. I loved it. It twisted your thoughts and made you think which I love doing. Thinking is one of my most favorite past times. Throughout the movie Sarah gripped onto my fingers every time she got scared which was an awful lot may I add. She has the death grip I swear. I didn't mind it all that much though. I mean, she's so nice and understanding to me. She also gave me this lovely necklace that has a a golden, flying bird with a pink belly. I might as well let her squeeze my hand during a "frightening" movie...   Mindy's dad drove us home  after the movie. Sarah called us about twenty minutes after we got home to go to the mall to windowshop with her and Bridget, who was feeling much better at the moment. We instantly replied yes. A couple of hours were spent at the mall looking at various objects before Cole and I bought them dinner at the mall's food court. After we went over to their house and recordered talk shows and soap operas until about ten o'clock at night. Finally, at a little after ten, we returned to our home and went to bed.   Today we were supposed to go bowling with them  and maybe a few other of their friends. We didn't though. Nicole and I ended up going out to Burger King and the city library with our granny. We missed their call. It's okay though. I'm all right with it. I love Sarah and Bridget dearly though. (As friends, of course!) They know my entire past and like me anyways. I know their past and like them anyways as well. They feel for me. They're also very easy to talk to, unlike Katelyn and Chloe are to me. I mean, Chloe and Katelyn just aren't the type of friends that want to talk about things that I talk to Bridget and Sarah about. I like them too, and I thought that they were my best friends, but maybe I'm wrong. Maybe they aren't my best friends, perhaps Sarah and Bridget are. Yes, Sarah and Bridget definitely are...   Kate, you know, my new ex best friend, AIMed me  today. She told me that Hal died. (Hal's a fifty five year old guy that made old fashioned cars, who lived on our street until he died from a heart attack a few days ago.) Unlike she usually is, Kate was nice. She asked me a few questions and before I knew it we were goofing off and teasing one another like we used to. We slipped back into friendship.   Kate, Nicole, and I were going to go play outside together  but my dad unexpectedly announced that we were going out to dinner, right now, at that very second. We tried calling her but the line was busy. She wasn't outside yet and she wasn't online anymore. My dad, majorly frustrated and angry, yelled at us to get into the car. We obliged and sadly, left Kate to wait for us outdoors.   My dad was irritated  and when my dad is irritated, it is not pretty. He blew up at us all. I could sense that dinner wasn't going to be great. However, with a little charm, I got him to lighten up. Dinner was a lot of fun, fortunately...   Things have become "weird"  now. I'm questioning my friendships with everyone. Bridget and Sarah are more of my best friends then my "BFF's" are... It's just weird. Kate being my friend again sort of terrifies me and that's for a reason that I can not even type here for an unreasonable fear I contain inside my mind... Everything just feels "different."  Well, I'm gone.  Austa. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; Okay, sounds funny but I am totally missing school. Sure, it's terrible 'cause all I ever do is embarass myself in front of my peers but hey, at least it gives me something to do for six or so hours&nbsp;a day... I mean, sure, I hate talking to people but that doesn't necessarily mean that I hate to be around them. Well, actually, I hate being around people but, uh, at school I'm able to tolerate it. Besides, school isn't all that bad. Going to school and getting good grades really affects my future... It&nbsp;depends what type of college I get into when I'm older, and my college degrees open up my options for what type of job I get, and what type of job I&nbsp;get could&nbsp;make me meet all sorts of different people and one that I might eventually settle down with and start a family with... Okay, I'm going a little over the top with this, aren't I?  Well, believe it or not, I've got to go. Sorry for such the short entry. I wasn't going to write to you at all today but I decided that I just COULDN'T do that.  Austa! 
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ah, I am SO annoyed. This summer is SO slow. Katelyn, in her letter, said that the summer was going by way too fast. Is she crazy? This summer has been going by SO dreadfully slow... I have absolutely nothing to do. I HATE swimming, biking, and soccer. I can barely tolerate basketball anymore. I also can't rollerblade which totally sucks 'cause if you can't rollerblade then you can't ice skate and I LOVE everything about ice skating. The sport is the only thing that I can watch on TV without wanting to leave ten minutes into it. My favorite figure skater is Michelle Kwon, hands down. I wish she'd win a Gold Olympic&nbsp;Medal all ready. I don't think she's competing in the next Olympics though which stinks. She's a fantastic skater though...   Anyways, I've been trying to cut my computer time down but I can't help myself... There is absolutely nothing to do. I've all ready cleaned the house, updated all of my journals and books, read from a book of short stories by Stephen King, and been on the computer. Since I hate almost every summer sport that people find enjoyable then I have nothing to do.   Ugh, my mom just came down and asked if she could use the computer. I said no. Sorry mom but I have nothing to do at the moment and I&nbsp;wish to use my time up in the most time consuming thing that I can find. I told her that she could have it at six o'clock which, unfortunately, is only eighteen minutes away...   I hate time. It makes me irritated. Have you ever noticed that when you're dreading something, time goes faster? Also, have you ever noticed that when you're looking forward to something that it never comes? Time has slowed down just to make me miserable, I swear. If I could, I'd brutally murder time for making me so damn upset. Well, not really. I wouldn't murder time, I'd just yell at it a lot and maybe ground it or something.   Only fifteen minutes left to type to you in... It's gone by slowly, just like the rest of my summer will go bye... Hm... Perhaps if I make myself dread school then things will speed up a little. It can't hurt me, can it? Maybe July will end and August will begin, a lot quicker to me... I just HATE being bored... I'm such a lazy fat ass too. No wonder why I rank in the 74th percentile for weight and 81st percentile for height.   Isn't that great? I'm fat and tall. The lady in the emergency room thought that I looked like I was going into the tenth grade. UGH! My mom said that many girls my age WANT to look OLDER but fuck them... Seriously, I'd die to look younger. I don't like being well developed at thirteen. It's annoying I tell you. I mean, you&nbsp;barely fit into any of the charts at the doctor's office 'cause you've all ready got your adult body...   There's ten minutes left until I leave you and go back to my life of boredom. DARN! I wish that there was something to do. I've run out of ideas. I've made schedules, diagrams, restrictions, pictures, essays, etc... What else is there left to do? I could always go for an hour long walk like I used to but last time some lady made fun of my hat and I felt like someone was stalking me... I'm SO paranoid...   I can't stop looking at the clock right now... Figures on why I'm not getting much typed... I have seven minutes left. Seven minutes of personal space and something to do. After six minutes now, I'll be upstairs doing completely nothing. I'll probably read a couple of books, write some more in all of my journals, notebooks, etc, watch a movie or two... There's a good chance that I'll be on the computer later too... Ah, there is NOTHING to do... I hate summer. Though school totally sucks, it at least gives me something to do...   I won't be bored afterschool, once school starts 'cause I'm playing soccer again this year! Yay! The one sport that I completely loathe and have no skills whatsoever in, I'm playing again. Yes, I just can't wait to humiliate myself in front of everyone, like last year...   Three minutes left... I'll be spell checking at one minute left... Yes, this is quite sad. Stupid time... I hate time... Wait, did I mention that before? Oh, I've mentioned it over a billion times, you say? Oh, okay... Sorry about that...   One minute left until I spell check, two minutes 'til six...   Damn, it's 5:59... I got to go...   Lost in Nowheresville...     
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't stop thinking about this song by Avril Lavigne that relates to the whole EBGF situation in my life... It's driving me crazy. The song is running through&nbsp;my head so much that sometimes, when I'm not conscious of it, I begin to sing it out loud. Trust me, I have a terrible singing voice and you would NEVER EVER want to hear me sing. I have no idea on why I'm in Chorus or why my teacher told me that I was a fantastic singer when I am&nbsp;a&nbsp;positively horrible singer. I can not sing the song all that well either. Please, believe me, I'm really, REALLY bad at singing... Anyways, you've probably heard of it before. It's called My Happy Ending by Avril Lavigne. If you're like everyone else in New York, then you know this song and absolutely love it. It's a hit on 95 Triple X, my hometown station... It's in the Top 40. I don't like it just because of that. In fact, I don't like a lot of the songs in the Top 40... Yet, anyways, I like it because I can relate to it. Though it sounds weird, it feels like she knew about my situation with my EBGF and wrote that song about it. I know that it's impossible but to me it does...   Anyhow, here's the lyrics and why I&nbsp;think that it totally makes me think of the situation between my EBGF and I.    My Happy Ending By Avril Lavigne     &nbsp;   &nbsp;oh oh, oh oh,    So much for my happy ending,oh oh, oh oh,    So much for my happy ending,    Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh    Let's talk this over    It's not like we're dead    Was it something I did?    Was it something You said?    Don't leave me hanging    In a city so dead    Held up so high    On such a breakable thread    You were all the things I thought I knew    And I thought we could be     &nbsp;   CHORUS: You were everything, everything that I wanted    We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it    All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away    All this time you were pretending    So much for my happy ending    oh oh, oh oh, so much for my happy ending     &nbsp;   Oh oh, oh oh    You've got your dumb friends    I know what they say(they say)    They tell you I'm difficult    But so are they(so are they)    But they don't know me    Do they even know you?(even know you)    All the things you hide from me    All the shit that you do(all the shit that you do)    You were all the things I thought I knew    And I thought we could be     &nbsp;   [CHORUS]     &nbsp;   It's nice to know that you were there    Thanks for acting like you cared    And making me feel like I was the only one    It's nice to know we had it all    Thanks for watching as I fall    And letting me know we were done     He was everything, everything that I wanted    We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it    All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away    All this time you were pretending    So much for my happy ending     &nbsp;   You were everything, everything that I wanted    We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it    All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away    All this time you were pretending    So much for my happy ending    oh oh, oh oh, so much for my happy ending    Oh oh, oh oh, so much for my happy ending    oh oh, oh oh, oh oh, oh ohoh oh,...    Okay, now I'll explain to you on WHY I think that this wonderful song relates to the situation my EBGF and I are in. See, my EBGF and I aren't friends anymore just like Avril and this guy aren't talking anymore or whatever. I also live in a pretty boring city that Avril sort of mentioned in the first verse.   The chorus describes what I'm feeling very well. I felt that since we were such great friends that we were meant to be together. Yet, it turns out that he doesn't seem to care about me anymore, which makes me wonder if he had been pretending to like me all along. So, this makes me upset and all like  so much for my happy ending.    The 2nd verse illustrates the situation we're in quite nicely too. My EBGF's friends call me mean things like dyke, bitch, etc... They say that I'm difficult too. He also did things and hid them away from me or whatever...  Basically, that wraps everything up. I just felt like that my EBGF and I were meant to be together. I mean, we used to be the best of friends and then everything went wrong and all... It's just like the song, sort of.  Maybe it's not exactly like the song but hey, it's pretty close, right? Don't agree with me? Ah, I don't care... I think that it does and that's all that matters to me right now... Okay, what the hell did I just type to you? Oh, well, nevermind...  And I'm out.    &nbsp;       
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm feeling a bit better about myself right now. See, I went online to google.com and typed in the question,  am I fat?  It brought up loads of different websites but there was one that stuck out from all of the rest. It's a quiz thingy that you can take if you're a teen and if you're wondering if you're fat.&nbsp; I posted the address below, just in case if you want to use it.    urlLink http://pediatrics.about.com/cs/obesity/l/bl_amifat_quiz.htm &nbsp;   It's a pretty cool quiz thingy. Unlike most BMI (Body Mass Index)&nbsp;caculators and things like that, it's more technical. The quiz asks you for how many years and months old you are, etc... Most BMI caculators don't get technical at all. According to this thingy, I'm in the 60.2 percentile. Other caculators would say that I'm in the 75th to 85th percentile. This thing just has to be right, correct? I mean, it asks and uses way more information then the ordinary ones.   My mom thinks that I'm right, that it is much more accurate then the one at the doctor's office. She told me that the one my doctor has is practically ancient or whatever. Besides, this one just feels more trustworthy. After taking this thingy, I feel much better. Perhaps I'm not all that fat.   Anyways, I've gone back to writing stories and stuff again. I took a break from writing things like that for about six months to a year. Now, I'm back and better then ever! Well, not really but you know what I mean, right? At the moment I'm writing two short stories and a HP (Harry Potter) fanfiction that's full of angst. I love writing depressing things... It's a lot of fun... Besides, it allows me to express whatever I'm&nbsp;feeling.   Well, I'm out.     
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; OMG, I feel TERRIBLE. Seriously, I feel like that any minute now I'll just throw up all of the junk food that I ate today right&nbsp;on the computer monitor. My head is still&nbsp;spinning even though we left the park almost exactly three hours ago. I feel like I'm still on one of those roller coasters, dropping to my doom. The amusement park was wicked, the after effects, though, I'm not too crazy about. Before we arrived at the amusement park, things were pretty bad too though. I almost died of sleep deprivation. I couldn't even lay my head down because Sarah was talking to me a mile a minute and I felt that it would be really rude to close my eyes while she was speaking.   Anyways, let's skip ahead to the actual time spent&nbsp;at the theme park. We left home at around 9ish and arrived there a little before 11. When we got there we bought our tickets and all, got inside, grabbed maps, and headed to the nearest attraction, The Boomerang. The Boomerang, in case you couldn't guess, is a roller coaster. Okay, it brings you up at least a hundred and twenty feet in the air, drops you, you go through a corkscrew, then a loop, and then you do it all over again, BACKWARDS.&nbsp;I was terrified out of my mind. I mean, I&nbsp;nearly fell off Space Mountain when I was six years old and that wasn't even all that bad. How could I survive a roller coaster that was definitely at least three times as bad as Space Mountain? I&nbsp;honestly don't know why whenever they asked me&nbsp;if I still wanted to go I on I said yes. I&nbsp;must have&nbsp;been crazy. Or perhaps I wanted to face a fear or experience something new or whatever...&nbsp;Anyhow, I sat next Sarah. Just before they dropped us I thought my heart had&nbsp;stopped. All of my fears just came together. I suddenly wished I was watching them ride it without me. Well, those thoughts quickly left me half a second later when they dropped us. To tell the truth that first drop was totally AWESOME! I loved it. It felt so good. I didn't like it all that much with the corkscrew or when we did the ride again backwards but other then that it was great. It felt really good to overcome my fear of roller coasters.   Everything else there was pretty fun to do too. My favorite ride was definitely the mystery ride. It's a lot of fun. See, it's like a scramble ride, if you know what that is. Well, it's a bit different then a regular scramble ride, actually. The entire ride is in this large, green dome. In the dome, they have some dim lights on when you enter. Well, you all get in to the cars (2 people per car) and they start spinning you. They play heavy metal music throughout the entire ride which is a lot of fun to scream and head bang with. After a little while it sort of gets boring. I mean, you're going really fast and you're almost smashing into other cars and the walls but it's nothing seriously fun. At about that time, the lights go out. You start spinning faster and faster in the dark. It's getting kind of creepy but yet exhilarating. Suddenly, these bright strobe lights turn on and off. It makes everything go hazy and you start to get dizzy. Then the strobe lights disappear and everything does dim. A red search light (it looks like one from a light house except red colored) turns on. It flashes across the room. Then these really weird pictures on the walls light up&nbsp;The light and the pictures stay illuminated for a while before going out. You're left in the dark again. Slowly, the ride comes to a stop and the rides over with. This was my favorite ride out of the entire park. It was positively thrilling!   The only annoying thing about this adventure was the fact that everyone always wanted to stop to get food. All I wanted to do was explore the park more. It really slowed our time down. We didn't even get to explore Splash Water Kingdom which totally sucks 'cause it was getting very hot out and I really didn't feel like fainting because of the heat. I guess it's a good thing that they made me eat 'cause I probably wouldn't have ate anything at all if it had been up to me.   Sarah, won a gigantic Care Bear from an arcade game. I am totally jealous because the Care Bear was my favorite, Wish Bear. Ugh, guess what, she named him? JEFF! Jeff? Poor thing, it was renamed... I tried to win one but seeing as how I've never won anything in my entire life, I failed miserably.   My least favorite ride that we went on would either be the roller coaster, The Comet, that bobsled roller coaster one,&nbsp;or that stupid swinging ship. I hated the Comet just because it was just so damn rickety. It wasn't a bad ride I'll admit though. The bobsled roller coaster just&nbsp;hurt a lot. Each time it shifted or locked into place, it hurt you. That was definitely the most painful ride I went on.&nbsp;The swinging ship ride was&nbsp;okay the&nbsp;first time I went on&nbsp;it but after a second time I instantly hated it. It made me feel way nauseous and jittery. I didn't like swinging&nbsp;back and&nbsp;forth, it made my stomach twist and&nbsp;turn into these horrible knots.   Besides the rides in Splash Water Kingdom, I wanted to go on two other rides that we didn't get the chance to ride on. One was the Merry-Go-Round and the other The Rainbow. The Rainbow looked cool. It was like the swinging ship but instead of just swinging you back and forth, it brought you all the way around... Anyhow, it sounds stupid but I really, really wanted to go on the Merry-Go-Round. I've never been on one before, at least I don't believe so, and it just looks fantastic. I like the very&nbsp;unique, sculpted&nbsp;ponies, horses, donkeys, mules, etc... I'm "too old" for the ride now though which completely sucks if you ask me. I wish I wasn't...   Well, that's all the main highlights and low points of my adventure to the theme park that I can think of right now. If I remember something significant, I'll write it in sometime later.   Austa!       
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; I am like so&nbsp;excited! Tomorrow I get to go to a theme park that's nearby with some of my friends. It's going to be awesome! I can hardly wait. I've been to the amusement park before. It'll be my second time there but I'm still totally anticipating it. See, last time I went there, it was on a&nbsp;school field trip&nbsp;with my fifth grade class. It was fun then but my group, which had consisted of Katelyn and Chloe, didn't do very much. We had went on a few rides but no rollar coasters since we were all terrified of them. However, this year I'm not as freaked out as before. I'm actually considering riding a few of&nbsp;them. I'm not&nbsp;going with Katelyn and Chloe this time, though. I'll be going with my other friends, Sarah and Bridget. Sarah and Bridget, like Nicole and I, are identical twins. Bridget, like me, is older then Sarah, except by thirty minutes rather than four. Bridget, though we don't&nbsp;hang out together&nbsp;much, knows more about me then any of my friends and that's including Katelyn and Chloe. I've told her some of my deepest, darkest secrets and she her's. Even though we don't hang out a lot, I feel this undeniable connection to her. She doesn't hate me for who I am. Maybe, one day I'll gather the courage to tell other people about my past, how I'm feeling, and all of that other crap.&nbsp;She gave me hope just by listening to me and trying to understand what I'm feeling. I hope that I gave her the same feeling.  Anyways, it's totally going to rock. Sarah and Bridget just came back from a two week vacation and since Cole and I took care of their pet, Bubbles, they're buying our tickets to get in. Isn't that nice? They seriously don't have to do that for us. I feel totally bad for allowing them. I'd gladly pay for my own ticket but they won't allow it. Gosh, I'm so happy that I know them. I'm not just typing that 'cause they're paying for my ticket. I'm typing it because of their generosity towards me, their compassion for how I feel, etc... Though I question my friendship with Katelyn and Chloe, I don't think I'll ever have to question my friendship with Sarah and Bridget. Bridget knows me better then Nicole probably does. She still continues to be my friend. I'm SO glad for that. Maybe I'm not such a terrible person afterall...  Ah, I am seriously loving my life right now. It's about time that I'm happy. I've been pretty miserable lately, whether or not I wrote you about that, I don't know... It's great though. I might not get the chance to blog tomorrow but I'll try to.  Bye. 
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night, unlike most nights, was full of dreams. When I say full, I mean FULL. Usually I never dream and when I do I dream about every night for a week. Every night during that week&nbsp;I usually have one to two different dreams. Well, last night was much different. I had several dreams. I only remember bits and pieces of most of them but my very last dream I remember much more clearly. It was really weird. It wasn't as crazy as some of my other dreams but it was definitely different.   Okay, it all started with Nicole, Kate (who is my ex-friend now), Alex, some other unidentifiable people, and I. We were in this big, deserted mansion. Honestly it looked more like a five star hotel then anything else. Anyways, we were all in the lounge, sitting around a warm fire on these comfortable, scarlet chairs and couches. Kate had just told a joke and Nicole and I were laughing hysterically. I took a sip from some fancy glass with an umbrella in it. Alex, who had been listening and staring at the fire, got up. He said some words to us, that he was heading up to bed or whatever, and playfully tossed a book at me. I didn't think much of it. After he left Nicole, Kate, and I continued talking. I sort of leafed through the book, but I wasn't really looking at it... I was just glancing at the pages. Well, it started getting late so Kate and Nicole decided that they were going to bed. I decided I'd go to bed as well, as I began to get up from the chair. I realised something in the pages of the book that I hadn't seen before. I waved Nicole and Kate off and they went up the wide, concrete stairs that led to the bedrooms. I opened the book up and saw half of a purple heart. On it, was a message to me. It was three sentences long. I don't remember what the first two lines said, but I remember the last one. The last sentence was,  I love you.  Underneath that was a crossed out A. The note was written to me from Alex. He loved me. Suddenly I couldn't breathe, or so it felt. It was a good feeling though. I stared into the embers of the fire, contemplating on what I should to&nbsp;do. With no decision made, I headed up to bed a couple of hours later.  There was something that happened after this but I don't remember it at the moment. I woke up with a good feeling. Usually when I wake up from weird dreams like this, I feel puzzled. I am confused now, but when I woke up I was happy and almost hopeful... Though it may sound stupid, I wonder&nbsp;if this dream has any specific meaning. Is it trying to tell me something that subconciously I know but mentally I don't? Hm... It sounds like a load of crap, doesn't it? Oh,well... What else can you expect from me?  Far, far away...    
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bored out of my mind, that is what I am. I'm trying to cut back on computer time but there is absolutely nothing else to do so I always end up turning to the computer for entertainment. What's a thirteen year old girl to do during the summer? There is absolutely nothing to do, I swear! I have watched like a hundred movies, gone swimming, gone bike riding, played basketball, watched television, played video games, etc... I've even started creating schedules for myself during the school year. The boredom bug has bit me. Anyone have any suggestions on what I can do? Anyone even out there? Oh, this is pointless.   You know Kate? Well, I think we, my sister and I,&nbsp;officially broke things off with her. I've probably wrote this once or twice&nbsp;before but this time&nbsp; I believe it's for sure. All right, Nicole was on the computer this morning, on AIM. Kate signed on. Things were going just&nbsp;fine until Kate badmouthed Nicole about something. This led into a big fight. It was just a regular fight of ours, that is until my 17 year old brother, Nick, stepped in. Kate violated his privacy and he didn't like that all that much. He totally blew up at her. This immediately caused her to be pissed off at us. So, therefore when we say her today, she gave us the "finger." She's such a lovely nine year&nbsp;old girl, huh? Don't you just want to hug her? NOT!!! Ugh, sometimes she can just be so incredibly mean, nasty, bossy and rude. I'm not just typing about her "flipping the bird." I'm writing about all of the other terrible things that she's said or done to my sister and I. Argh, this is making me think about her brother. NO!!!!!   I hate thinking about her brother. That was just another friendship that went bad. He's very cruel to Cole and&nbsp;I now. He calls us dykes, bitches, and other foul words. I don't even communicate with him anymore. It's SO stupid, SO pathetic. He seriously needs to grow up. Ah, if we leave him alone then why does he punish us so? What have I done, besides not tell him about my ex boyfriend, Seth? Honestly, am I terrible person? Am I the worst person in the entire world? Tell it to me straight now, I want to know. I'm so sick of all of the lies he tells other people about my sister and I, the cold jokes he makes about Nicole and I, etc... I'm tired of wondering. I WANT to KNOW WHY!!! Couldn't he at least grant the courtesy of telling his victim's on WHY he's torturing them? Or is he as ruthless as he appears? Ugh, I let go of him, I even wrote that in here... Did&nbsp; I really, though? I have the feeling that I'm still not over our whole friendship thingy...   Er!!! I'm going to bed. It's part of my schedule.  *rolls eyes*  Sometimes I am just such a freak.   And I'm out of here.   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; I just got back from my physical today. The good news is that I didn't faint or suffer from any other traumitizing event during it. Nope, there was no fast trip to the emergancy room for me. It was an hour and a half visit with her, my doctor, though. She was totally paronoid. She kept researching into my family history for like different diseases or whatever. She was completely convinced that&nbsp;I was about to die before her eyes. It was a complete waste of time, I tell you.  The bad part about this physical, despite lack of entertainment, was that I found out that I'm in the 75th percentile for my age.I know that I've developed faster then most people my age but that doesn't make it suck any less. God, why can't I get any skinnier? I don't eat junk food. I don't drink soda. I barely eat meat anymore. Why am I SO fat? Okay, maybe I'm not fat but I feel fat, 0kay? People online are all telling me that I'm fine and that I'm not overweight or anything but sometimes it is just SO hard to believe what they're saying. I barely ever feel trim. I know that people who are overweight and hate it are probably like really angry at me but I can't help what I feel. Every time I eat something I feel really, REALLY bad. I know that I need to eat more, since I fainted and all but it's hard now. I haven't ever ate right in my entire life. It's sort of scary to eat a lot now. I know that I'm supposed to eat a lot of nutritional stuff... It's just different, okay?  My friend, Katelyn, is way overweight. My other friend, Chloe, is way underweight. I guess I'm sort of the balance in between the two, though I'm getting pretty close to being overweight myself. It sort of feels awkward being around both of them. I mean, I can't exactly talk to them about how I feel 'cause they'll get all snappish.   They'll something like, "Well, try being my size. Trust me, you don't&nbsp;want to know what it feels like."  They both hate the way they are. Right now I'd give anything to be either. I hate being in the middle of things. It's just really annoying. Like, Katelyn sometimes talks to me about how she's fat and all and I'm not allowed to say a word 'cause it'll make her feel bad and stuff.  Maybe I'm not that fat, I'm probably stressing this way too much. Either way, I'm hitting the pool.  See you later alligator.  
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; Katelyn, my BFF from school, doesn't hate me afterall. I thought that she seriously hated me since she hasn't replied to any of the many&nbsp;e-mails that I've sent to her over the summer but it turns out that she hasn't had access to a computer to read and reply to them. How did I find all of this out, you may ask me... Well, you see, she sent me a two page letter about her summer vacation and why she hadn't wrote to me for SO long. She's been really busy over the summer. She has swim practice every morning and softball practice every evening. She's also been away to all sorts of different girl scout camps.   I'm so glad that she doesn't hate me. Katelyn and I got into a big fight at school. It was our first fight and we didn't talk to one another for an entire week after it... Eventually we became friends again with the help of some of our other friends. Once I got the letter from her today, I began writing back almost immediately. I filled her in on everything going on in my end of the pool, while writing down advice and a few other encouraging words to her. My letter is almost a page longer. I hope it's all right. I haven't seen or heard from her in an entire month. I really miss her. We used to talk about everything together. Hopefully my letter doesn't sound too sappy or whatever. Well, it's not exactly sappy. It's more happy and excited that I've heard from her, type of letter. I bet I sound like a blabbering idiot. Yet, oh well, if she's a true friend then she seriously won't care.  When reading her letter to me, I found out all sorts of interesting things. My other friend, Chloe, dyed her hair pink and blue. She's also having a&nbsp; very hot foreign exchange student stay at her house. I can't believe her mother let her do either. Chloe's mom is a VERY controlling woman. She hardly ever lets Chloe or her brother do what they want. I wonder if her mom even knew that Chloe was going to dye her hair. If not, I would have loved to see the expression on her face when she found out. Though it sounds a bit rude or whatever, I think I'd burst out laughing if I saw that...  Anyways, I've got to get going... I'm so happy that Katelyn doesn't hate me. Before&nbsp;I wasn't sure if she even liked me. This letter tells me otherwise, doesn't it? Or maybe Katelyn wrote it out of pity or whatever... Ah, let me forget about that thought... Write to you later...  And I'm gone... 
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; Today, guess what I have ate? I have ate four chocolate chip pancakes, white rice, seven strips of siamese chicken, a bowl of cheerios, and a sundae cone. Not to mention I had a Diet Pepsi, orange juice, and a glass of milk. I feel like a pig. It may not sound like a lot but, to me, who hasn't ate this much in one day&nbsp;for three months, it's a lot. I've ate from 1800-3000 or 4000 calories today. Ah, if I hadn't fainted or whatever I would kill myself if I had ate this much. Usually, for the past three months at least, I ate under 1600 calories. I didn't even lose all that much weight... I lost about 2.5 pounds since I've seen the school nurse and&nbsp;6 pounds from my last visit with my doctor.  I am so disappointed with myself. I know my body needs the vitamins and other ingredients from the food but I still feel really guilty. I think that from now on I'll just eat like six, very small meals consisting of carrots, apples, and other fruits and vegetables. I'm still not going to eat meat all that much. I might just cut back&nbsp;on the carbs too. There&nbsp;goes my favorite food group. I'll miss the breads, cereals, pastas, and&nbsp;the many others that&nbsp;I love so dearly... Yes, I think I shall become a vegetarian, again. This time I won't tell my family so they can't blackmail me... I'll turn to the Land of Salads... (No offence to all of the vegetarians out there.) Why not? I mean, it's healthy and it also saves animal's lives... Er, sort of...  Well, I've got to go. I know this is probably my shortest entry ever but I really have nothing left to type down to you. Catch you on the flip side.  I'm outie. 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I fainted during my physical. Seriously, I did. I got dizzy, stepped forward, smashed into a table, fell on my side, and started shaking. I regained sense thirty seconds later. My mother was screaming my name right into my ear. My doctor, two nurses, and Nicole stood around me. They called 911 and I was rushed to the hospital, where they made me take a couple of tests before discharging me. All I can say is that it was very interesting. It hurt a lot though. The right side of my face got hit as well as my chin. Neither of them were&nbsp;bruised though. Which is a very good thing indeed.&nbsp;The back of my neck is hurting really badly right now&nbsp;however...&nbsp;I've got a massive head ache too.   The doctor at the hospital said that I could have fainted from either dehydration, not eating breakfast, or stress. Though my sister and my mom might say that it was because I&nbsp;didn't&nbsp;eat breakfast this morning, I think otherwise. I haven't ate breakfast in probably about three years. I believe that it was stress. The visit to the doctor's was very overwhelming for me. I really didn't like it all. Everything was just very depressing. All of the things going on my life were in my mind too. Dr. Patel was lecturing me about my diet. I remember feeling angry, upset, and frustrated. I didn't need to be lectured about something as trivial as my health. There were other, more important things going on in my life. I didn't care about discussing my eating habits...   Before I fainted, I had my height and weight checked out. I'm 5 foot 5 and 1/4 inches tall and I weigh about 121.5 pounds. This totally depresses me. And I thought that I had been losing weight.  *sighs*  I guess I was wrong... Oh, well...   I'm out.     
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; All right, I should probably be writng this in my "School Fool" blog but whatever... I'm writing it all down in this one so too bad....  &nbsp;  On September 8th, 2004, I will officially be an eighth grader. This is my last year of Middle School. In about a year I will be venturing into high school! Anyways, though my summer has been pretty good thus far, I can't help but feel excited for the eighth grade. My fellow peers and I shall rule the school... Plus, we get to have our very&nbsp;own wing to use. It's going&nbsp;to be great... Anyhow, I'm not&nbsp;completely wound up for just those reasons. No, I'm&nbsp;acting all nervous and excited because I plan on changing a lot&nbsp;about myself this year and I can hardly wait.&nbsp;When I enter the eighth grade, I'll be the person that I want to be...  &nbsp;  Here's a list&nbsp;of the changes&nbsp;I'll be making.  &nbsp;   External&nbsp;Changes=     &nbsp;   Clothing:  For this year, I am changing my entire wardrobe. Finally, I'll escape the terrible striped pants and my mother's tee-shirts that&nbsp;I wore all last year in the seventh grade. This year, I'm planning on getting a larger variety of clothes. I plan on getting some knee length skirts, capris, more fitting tee shirts, nice and comfortable&nbsp;pants, shorts, etc...  &nbsp;   Hairstyles:  Another thing that I am changing about myself this year is my hairstyle. I always keep my hair down. This year I think I'm going to put it more up. I'm thinking of head bands and loose pony tails. I might even&nbsp;do pig tails every once and awhile.  &nbsp;   Internal Changes=     &nbsp;   Knowledge:  This year I am going to pay attention more to my studies. Last year I sort of just shrugged them off. So, this year I'm going to study much more then I did last year so I gain knowledge and actually understand it.  &nbsp;   Happiness :&nbsp; Last year I was positively&nbsp;miserable.&nbsp;When I go into the eighth grade, I plan on being a more happier person. Instead of&nbsp;remaining&nbsp;mute&nbsp;when I have a problem or suggestion for something, I am going to voice my opinion. I am NOT going to be so silent.&nbsp;Since, not speaking made me&nbsp;rather unhappy around all of my friends and others, I am hoping that I'll be much more enjoyable to be with after fixing this little problem.  &nbsp;  So, there is my list. It sounds lame, doesn't it? Ah, who cares? It's my life...  &nbsp;  And I'm gone...    &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;     
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What was I thinking before? There is no way in hell's way that my crush likes me back. I am totally serious, there is absolutely NO WAY. I am, Kelsey. I am&nbsp;the ugly, fat, stupid, pathetic, mute, girl that is extremely untalented and clumsy. What type of fantasy world was I living in? I was insane before, absolutely insane. I'll be totally lucky if one day I ever get a boyfriend. Oh, what guy in their right mind would want to get close to me? What was I thinking? How could I believe that he would choose me over all of the sexy, well dressed, popular, totally talented, coordinated, outspoken, skinny, funny, and smart girls that go to my school? Yes, why in the world would anyone want to hang out with me? Why would this guy, who I've liked for just about FOREVER, like me back when I am the way I am?  &nbsp;  What sucks the most about this situation is that there is like NO WAY that I can CHANGE the way that I AM. I mean, okay, I'm pretty smart. I even get better grades then he does, but I'm not perfect straight A's.&nbsp; Alright, though I am totally fat, I guess I don't look that bad for my weight. I am ugly though, how do you change that? My mom won't pay for a makeover! The other things like being pathetic, clumsy, and untalented are completely impossible to change too... Is there a way to cure yourself from being pathetic? I think not. Now, for the untalented thing... Don't tell me that I could practice things a lot and that I'd get better from doing so, 'cause I've tried that and for a wretch like me, it DOESN'T WORK! I could always work on my balance by trying to balance on stuff but it is more likely that I'll fail too... Ah, WHY AM I SUCH A LOSER?????????????  &nbsp;  He'd never give me the time of day... If he did though, it would probably be to laugh at me.  &nbsp;  Gone.      
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; Okay, I just totally admitted to my BFF, who I like practically am in&nbsp;love with. No, it wasn't that snotty Kate who almost exactly&nbsp;after I finished typing to you was a complete jerk to me. Nope, it was my twin sister, Nicole. Now, I don't understand what's the big deal of having your twin sister as your very best friend. Everyone always looks at us weirdly because we are so close. They just don't understand, Cole and I have been through so much together. When the entire fourth grade, including our teacher, picked on us terribly, we were the only friends that eachother had. When my mom tried to kill my dad and all, Nicole (and Nick) was there for me and I was there for her (and him.) Is it such a crime these days to have a family member as your best friend? My school is quite against twins spending time together. They put you in completely different classes. In soccer last year, my coach forbade Nicole and I to pick one another for partners. That was like totally UNFAIR. I mean, come on, all the other girls got to pair up with their best friends.&nbsp; Why couldn't we? Besides, I hated a lot of the girls on our team. Half of them were stuck up and the other half were mean... &nbsp; Anyways, back to the subject... I had been avoiding telling my sister who I really, really like or in other words who I have a little bit of love for. Shh!! Pretend I didn't say that last part, okay? Anyhow, &nbsp;Nicole totally knew that I was trying to edge away from the subject. So, she started guessing. She said my crush's name like a thousand times, but each time I said no, I didn't have any feelings for him at all. (OMG, I&nbsp;really need&nbsp;to work on telling the truth for once.)&nbsp;Today, after weeks of endless questionings, she found out... Okay, we were in a secreted place where no one can really hear us and she was asking me a million questions all at once. She kept asking me things about him which I totally avoided answering. Finally she got fed up with me and said that she wouldn't speak to me at all until I told her who I liked. Well, I couldn't stand the silence so I gave in. She got really, really excited and happy... She kept saying over and over again on how she thought that was who I liked (or loved). She was like OMGing every few seconds. See, she was totally OMGing 'cause I really&nbsp;liked this person beforehand, then I didn't really 'cause I thought he was a big prat, and now I really, really like him... Do you have any idea on what I'm talking about? No? Well, it's one of those love/hate thingys... One minute I disgrace the land that he walks upon and the next moment I&nbsp;practically worship him.&nbsp;Uh, well, it's not exactly like that... I don't&nbsp;really ever truly hate the land he walks upon or worship him totally... You know what I mean, right? &nbsp; &nbsp;Anyhow, it feels wonderful, having someone know who I like. I've kept this secret bottled inside of me&nbsp;for like a year or two. It's a huge relief to finally tell someone, you can say... Oh, I really hope he likes me... He used to like me, at least that's what my sister said.&nbsp;My sister and I&nbsp;haven't seen him in awhile so we couldn't exactly tell if he likes me now. Oh, I wish he did. I like him  SOOOOO  much; just don't tell him that. What happens if he hates me? I bet he doesn't like me... I don't think he even realises that I exist. AH!!!! That would be such a nightmare... He's seen me before, uh, at least I&nbsp;hope he has...&nbsp;Wait, what am I&nbsp;typing? He's seen me before.&nbsp;Honestly, I am such a liar. I really need to work on&nbsp;my honesty. On here, I haven't lied to you yet. Well, except just a few lines back, but I admitted I lied so that's not the same... &nbsp; Ah, I wonder if he likes me. Does he like me? Does he even&nbsp;know&nbsp;that I exist? Should I ask him out? (What am I thinking with that one? I'll never ask him out, I'm such a wimp!) Will he ask me out?&nbsp;(I don't know where that one came from either...)  &nbsp; Well, I've got lots to wonder about at the moment. I'll be leaving you know.  &nbsp; Austa! 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; Kate, my BFF, is driving me completely INSANE! I swear to God that she is being increasingly annoying and will never ever&nbsp;leave me alone... For the past few weeks all she has ever done is bug my sister and I to either go get ice cream, go to the Dollar Store, catch a movie, browse shops at the mall, play outside, go swimming, hang at her house or our house... We can't go anywhere without getting a phone call from her, an AIM from her, or her knocking on our&nbsp;front&nbsp;door... I swear,&nbsp;we have a stalker... It's creepy walking into her room sometimes. She writes our names&nbsp;all over&nbsp;her tissue boxes and stuff...  &nbsp;  Today, she asked Nicole and I to go to the Dollar Store to buy fake NAILS with her... FAKE NAILS? Who buys fake nails? They're a complete waste of money... Anyways, I told her that Nicole and I wouldn't go, we seriously didn't want to. She called me a bad friend just because I refused to go with her. Honestly, what does she need fake nails for? Anyways, I'm all like whatever and she's all like don't whatever me and I'm sick of you... I told her that if she didn't like me for who I am then fine,&nbsp;&nbsp;we didn't have to be friends. She wrote that it was my choice to be a witch and that I should go ahead and block her. I told her that she wasn't worth blocking over.&nbsp; Next she threatened that she wouldn't take Nicole and I to some amusement park sometime in August because "the way I&nbsp;was acting." She said she'd take someone that is nice to her. I'm all like, you do that. &nbsp;&nbsp;Kate responded with that she would and it would most certainly not be me. I responded with "like I care." She tells me that I probably do care, I just won't admit it. I tell her that before she even asked us Nicole and I had actually planned going to the same amusement park over the summer...&nbsp; Anyways, she got a little more angrier and said that she didn't give a shit about my life. "That's nice,"was my reply. Then she sunk even lower and said that at least she had friends. With much more anger than I had&nbsp;beforehand, I typed in that I didn't want any friends if all of them were going to act the same way she was acting then. Ouch, that was a low blow. She definitely deserved it though. Unfortunately, seeing as she isn't too great at reading plain English, she didn't understand a word of what I was saying. What a bummer... The one chance I get to tell her how I feel and she doesn't even comphrehend what I'm saying...  &nbsp;  I know what I said was a little harsh... It's just that she's been really irritating me these days. If she doesn't get what she wants, she throws a hissy fit. And when she gets what she wants and after hours of doing whatever she wants to do, she won't let us stop. I think she has seperation anxiety or something. Anyhow, we're all better now since she just called and apologized. She still wants me to go but I won't... I REFUSE TO GO! She can't make me!!! Great, now I sound like a toddler having a temper tantrum.  &nbsp;  And I'm out.    
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; I woke up at eleven this morning, took a shower, and then crawled back underneath the warm covers in my bedroom. I picked up a book , Chicken Soup For The Preteen Soul , and opened it up. I had already read this book once before about a year or two ago, so I&nbsp;miscellaneously picked a section to read.&nbsp;The one that I happened to&nbsp;flip open&nbsp;to was on the painful&nbsp;subject of&nbsp;death/dying.   No one, except my dog, has died yet in my family. You could say that I am very fortunate. I've never had to deal with the&nbsp;issue of death.&nbsp;I've never been to&nbsp;wake or funeral&nbsp;either. My family would almost be entirely complete except for my nanny, my mom's mom.My nanny died before my parents were even married. She never knew about us kids. It sort of sucks but I know that compared to other people's lives that I've lost nearly nothing compared to the people they've lost. Since I've never had to face the terrible grip of death, I wonder about where you go after you die and why we're here on Earth.  &nbsp;  I don't believe in God, though in my religion I am supposed to. It sounds terrible, doesn't it? Yet, I don't. I don't&nbsp;believe in any other religions except one, and that is MY own religion. You see, no one actually knows how things were created on this planet. No one can know for sure. There are lots and lots of different religions out there to believe in. Which one is true? Many people probably ask the same question. Yet who cares? Personally, I believe that you should believe in whatever you want to believe in. We're only on Earth for a short time, so why not? In my religion, the one that I made up, after people die they go to a place that they've always wanted to see, their favorite place in the whole wide world, etc... Once they're there they can review the happiest memories of their lives... They can do whatever they want. It's my version of  heaven . It probably sounds&nbsp;incredibly &nbsp;stupid to you, but that's your opinion. After I die, I'm want to&nbsp;go to&nbsp;my Camp. There will be shooting stars, brilliant thunderstorms, warm bonfires, magic, etc... There will be all of the things that I've always adored... It'll be wonderful.  &nbsp;  Why do people follow&nbsp;a religion? You've probably asked this before too. My answer, though it will most likely be very different then yours, is that people believe in religions because it's a nice thought that after you die you go somewhere. They also usually always tell you how everything was created which allows the mind to focus on other things besides how everything was made and who created it all.&nbsp;Don't get me wrong, religions are great. I don't like it when people of one religion call&nbsp;people of another&nbsp;religion false, though. You never know, maybe both religions are completely wrong. &nbsp;  &nbsp;  Since I have to go, I'll leave you with the one message I've been trying to get through to you, believe in what you want to believe because we're only on Earth for a short time and no one knows the truth about how everything was created in this world.  &nbsp;  And I'm gone.    &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; I go see my doctor this Wednesday for a physical. My feelings on this, you may ask... Well, let's just say I'm not exactly looking forward to it. See, I've been trying to lose weight for a little while, four to five weeks to be precise, and I'm afraid my mom will tell the doctor that I'm not eating. I AM eating, just not as much as I used to. I cut some things out of my diet, like chocolate and soda. Basically my changing has only improved my health status. I've lost probably about ten to fifteen pounds by restricting my day's calories to under 1700.&nbsp; My mom is freaked out by this. She says I'm getting too skinny. Ha, I wish I was skinny... Yesterday, I broke my rules and had a Reese's and a Coke. See, I'm not totally restricting myself... I still indulge every once and awhile. If she tells my doctor that I'm not eating then they'll make me eat a lot for months and I'll gain back all the weight I lost. I think that I can deal with the weight gain but I actually like my meal plan. I don't want to have to change it. I've gotten so accustomed to it.  &nbsp;  Anyways, let's forget all about weight loss and eating... Let's get moving onto my physical appearance. Rather regretfully I'm not all that pretty. The only physical attributes that I have ever been&nbsp;paid a nice compliment on&nbsp;are my hair, my smile,&nbsp;and my eyes. My sixth grade reading teacher, before I got&nbsp;glasses,&nbsp;said that my eyes were hypnotizing and that once I got a boyfriend he'd love looking into them. Ha, what a laugh. Anyhow, for my smile my cousin, Donna, said that it was very cute. I have no clue on what she's talking about. I've got partially yellow teeth for goodness sakes! Lastly, the comment that I recieve about my hair is that the color is beautiful. Whatever... Like I believe that.&nbsp; I am no beauty. I'm five foot five, hazel eyed, brown haired with awkward red and blonde highlights, glasses wearing, zit faced, yellow teethed thirteen year old girl. No wonder why I don't have a boyfriend. Not only am I antisocial, but I'm ugly too...  &nbsp;  Ugh, I'm gone...    
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; I know I over the top dramatized the entire thing with my EBGF, but how can you blame me? I just realised something that was standing right in front of me for months... It was quite heartbreaking, and it still is. I mean, it sort of sucks, realising that you practically&nbsp;broke someone's heart, threw it on the ground, and then&nbsp;jumped on it a million times. The worse thing is, I didn't even realise I was doing any of that to him!&nbsp;&nbsp;Oh well, everything's resolved now. I'll butt out of his entire life, forget our past together, and let him live a little... Oh, god, but it's going to be SO hard. Well, doing all of that isn't going to be that hard, at least I think it isn't... No, it is going to be SO hard not looking for his face when I'm at school and everything... It's going to be hard to not search for him wherever I go... Ah, yes, it's going to be really hard.  &nbsp;  Fortunately, I'm not the only one in the same situation. I've hurt Alex, and my twin sister has hurt Mindy. I turned Alex into the unhappy person that he is today. Nicole's place is sort of like mine. See, her friend Mindy is insanely jealous of Nicole. Well, James, Nicole's ex best guy friend, was in love with Nicole. Well, the problem was, Mindy really, REALLY liked James. Anyways, James called Mindy fat. So, Mindy turned anorexic for a week or two in hopes of becoming like Nicole. Unfortunately, this situation isn't exactly like mine. This only lasted maybe two weeks at the latest.&nbsp;(Mindy almost fainted and then turned back to food.) My situation has been going on for about two years! Well, not any more... I'm changing everything, yup, everything... Now, all I have to do is unclench my claws from him...  &nbsp;  Er, how do I do that exactly?  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        &nbsp;  You have no idea how bad I feel right now. You have absolutely no idea how terrible I am feeling. I feel positively awful. I think I have never felt this hurt in my entire life. It's not about death, illnesses, or anything like that. No, it is about something that most people would consider trivial. This is about my  EBGF.  Hard to believe, huh? Well, you better believe it, 'cause it is all about him and this time it is not his fault, no, this time, and every time before that was entirely &nbsp;   MY  &nbsp; fault, and there is  NO  way to fix what I have done... No, nothing actually happened... No, nothing important occurred... Well, yes, something important did occur. I just happened to realize why my  EBGF  is so angry with me... I was so stupid beforehand... God, I'll never be able to fix this.    &nbsp;  Just today, I learned that his favorite band is Linkin Park. I know about four or five of their songs, and love them all, but I decided that I'd check out some of their other songs. Well, I searched for Linkin Park lyrics on the Google search engine and eventually found all of their songs that they have. After reading several of the ones I hadn't ever heard of, I realized something, and what I realized made me almost want to cry. Almost every single one of their songs pertains to what is going on between  us ... I'm being totally serious here. Oh, and that's not even the worse thing about this situation. No, the majority of the songs are angry, angry at a someone who has created lies in a relationship, doesn't understand why someone could be&nbsp;mad at her or him, expects the other one to beg for forgiveness,&nbsp;etc... Well, honestly, that is  EVERYTHING  that I have been doing to my  EBGF . I've been wondering for months on how he's been feeling towards me... Well, now I know, don't I? He doesn't put his feelings into regular&nbsp;speech or facial expressions but drowns them in music. I hurt him more then I ever thought. The songs are simply wonderful, I will say that... Yet to me, they hold much more meaning. They're my only way into his heart, his feelings, his everything, everything that I lost. Once I lost his trust, I lost everything.&nbsp;What's a girl to do after this situation? Oh, I've got that figured out now... Yes, I've been wondering on how I'm supposed to act around him for months&nbsp;and finally I've found it. Though it totally and completely breaks my heart, I have to let him go. I have to walk away. I can't torture him. I've got to let him live. I've been hurting him for so long. God, I feel like such an idiot... Why didn't I see this before? How could I have not seen his pain? I'm walking away now. He doesn't need me. He doesn't want me. He  HATES  me. He'll always  HATE  me... I'll always love him though. He was the first  real  friend that I've ever had and I'll forever be grateful for all of the good times he brought into my life... Unfortunately, the good times have ended and it is time that I let go of him. He deserves to be happy. I've been holding onto him for way too long.  &nbsp;  I was so selfish before. I was stupid, insane, pathetic, etc...&nbsp;I feel incredibly terrible and hurt. What do I mean by hurt, you may ask me. Well, I&nbsp;guess&nbsp;I should replace it with the word hateful. I&nbsp;hate myself completely, right now.&nbsp;I'm "hurt" that I could have let&nbsp;this happen.&nbsp;None of this&nbsp;should have ever happened.  Nicole , my  EBGF , and  I  should have all grown up as best friends... I can imagine what things would be like if we were still best friends. First of all, we'd call  Nicole, Cole,  my  EBGF, Al,  and  me, Kel or Kels . Honestly, I believe that we'd be inseparable. There are just so many memories... There are just&nbsp;too many times that we'ved shared together... Things would be SO different now if I hadn't hurted him. Yes, everything wouldn't be the same.  My life, his life, my sister's life,  they'd all be different... I often think of the times that  we've  shared together. They're just so great. I can remember the pranks we pulled, the places we explored, the games we made up, etc., as if they were only yesterday. It's wonderful, looking back at them. It makes me feel like singing, I enjoyed them very much... Rather regretfully they also cause pain.&nbsp;I've felt&nbsp;it, and I imagine he's felt it. It's time to let&nbsp;go. He'll hate me until the end of time itself and maybe long after that, but I'll always love him. He was my first best friend. He was the only&nbsp;best friend that I ever got the chance to&nbsp;actually be myself with. Nowadays, I'm actually afraid of showing myself to even my&nbsp;very best friends. Well, at least I'll die having the pride of at least&nbsp;one true friendship that occured in my life, even if it was in my childhood. It's too bad that it ended horribly, but, hey, that's life.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Goodbye  Alex.  Thanks for the ride but now it's time for me to go. Maybe one day we'll meet and become friends&nbsp;again, but until that day,   au revoir   .    You were an awesome friend. You knew every trick of the trade. You were always there for me, through thick and thin. You were terrific. I'm sorry that&nbsp;I wasn't that great of a friend to you. I'll see you in the next life... Bye...  &nbsp;  Yes, I'm probably dramatizing this situation, but I seriously don't care. I feel like I've walked through hell, for the fiftieth time. You know what, this isn't the end. One day, we'll be friends again. It may not be in this life, but it will be someday...  &nbsp;  Do you know what I'm imagining right now? It'll sound silly, but I've sort of&nbsp;got a version of  heaven  that I like to believe that I go to after I die.&nbsp;My heaven is&nbsp;Camp, basically. It's full of the booming  thunderstorms ,&nbsp; the crackling&nbsp; bonfires ,&nbsp;the&nbsp;same twinkling  stars , &nbsp;the unknown  mystery , the feeling of sheer joy, the everything... However, it's not just my   Camp   that's in my  heaven . No, it's WAY more then that. It's my  Camp  and the muddle of my favorite memories. In my  heaven , you can revisit your favorite memories... It's like a scrap book in&nbsp;a way. I've already got a few memories saved for my  heaven . Now, I'm officially adding another one. This one concerns  Alex . The one I'm saving&nbsp;is on the Fourth of July in the last summer that we spent together as friends I believe. It's the moment in which I'm laying right next to him (after  Nicole  moved to lay next to  Kate )&nbsp;on the&nbsp;top of his roof top.  We're  not really talking,  we're  just lost in the moment. You see,   we're   watching the fireworks going off in the night time&nbsp;sky. The sky is star studded so it makes the entertainment level increase greatly. It was postively&nbsp;beautiful, it was  magical . Call me insane but it was probably one of the best moments that I've ever had with him. So, I'll save it for my  heaven . He'll never be officially gone then. Even if I grow old and forget about him, he'll&nbsp;never be forgotten. He'll always be in my&nbsp; heaven .  &nbsp;  Always.&nbsp;    
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I've done the right thing, I know I did. Then why, by doing the right thing, am I feeling rather guilty about the whole ordeal? Why? I shouldn't feel terrible about any of this, yet I do. I mean, I made the right decision. Things will work out just fine, thanks to my actions... How, after one does something the correct and moral way, can feel a bit upset of their actions? I shouldn't being feeling guilty or upset by any of this. I should just be caring, considerate, and understanding of my best friend, Kate's, actions. However, I do feel&nbsp;resentment to it... I don't know, maybe I'm just being weird...    Alright, Kate, my nine year old BFF, has been chatting&nbsp;online with this sick pervert who claims to be either thirteen or sixteen.&nbsp;(He's said both. Sad, huh?) They&nbsp;met&nbsp;in a Bacherlorette chat room over AIM.&nbsp;He AIMed her, asking for her ASL. She replied with that she&nbsp;was ten years old and a female. (She'll be turning ten in a little while.) She didn't give him her location just because she didn't&nbsp;feel like it. Anyways, he responded that he was a male, sixteen years old, and lived in Tennessee. He told Kate that he loved her and she was wooed. They became online boyfriend and girlfriend right after that. As conversations issued over AIM between them he&nbsp;told Kate disgusting, perverted things about his private parts. Kate asked him to stop several times&nbsp;&nbsp;but he just would not quit. Then, today, after a number of perverted sayings, she decided that it was the last straw for him. She threatened him that if he continued with this "gross" behavior on AIM that she would dump him. He pleaded with her desperately and eventually won her over. However, he did not stop with the remarks. She had to threaten him several times over and each time he played her like a fool. My twin sister and I watched this procedure. Finally, after he sent her an inappropriate picture of his male private part, I stepped in. I completely told him off. There was NO WAY in hell that he was who he said he was. I had heard about these type of people, they took advantage of children like Kate. I did not want Kate to become a victim. He had been playing with her mind the entire time, I just knew it. Even if he was who he said he was, I don't care... He deserved every word that he got. After breaking up with him and saying a few other choice words, I blocked him... This completely infuriated Kate. She yelled at me that she had wanted to do it in her own way at her own time. Though it may sound mean, I knew that she wouldn't have. In my heart, I know that I did the right thing. A potentional problem was issuing. He, I am quite sure of, would have wiggled personal information out of her eventually and used it to harm her and get what he wants from her. That just could NOT happen. So, I changed it. I know that it might have been stupid, but I did what I felt was right. Hopefully she'll never talk to him ever again and we'll never have to know what his real motives are.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   I'm a little upset with myself at the moment. I didn't mean to make my friend angry at me but I didn't like the possibility that she could fall into a maybe evil man's clutches... Hopefully she won't stay angry at me for too long. I had my best interests at heart... Come on, you've got to give me something for that...   Let's journey to the brighter side, shall we? Well, really, it's not that much of a brighter side.&nbsp;Nicole's AIM account was broken onto by Kate's brother, my EBGF. This shocked my sister and I both because Nicole had just created that account... How could have he have known about it in the first place? Her password had seemed almost impossible to guess, too. Anyways, we changed her AIM password to something that would be hard to guess,&nbsp;a bunch of miscellaneous&nbsp;numbers. Then we went to change her e-mail address account password, just in case he knew it and had the password sent to her address. It took forever to find the right thing to change it. Unfortunately we never got to change her password. Our e-mail thingy was updated and you currently can't change any of your account&nbsp;information.&nbsp; That totally sucks...  Anyways, it's been a long day... Kate, Nicole, and I spent the night at Kate's grandmother's&nbsp; last night. It was loads of fun. Her grandma lives in the open country which, to me, is positively beautiful. One day, I want to live in the country.&nbsp;&nbsp;It was wonderful, being there. Her home sat atop this&nbsp;magnificent hill. At the foot of the hill lay a tiny brook which was&nbsp;surrounded by weeds, wildflowers, stones, plants, and other wild things of nature. To the east of her home lay green, empty fields that seemed to stretch on for&nbsp;forever. I'd love to go running through those fields...&nbsp;West of her house was a few trees that seperated her house from a corn field.&nbsp;To me, it would be great&nbsp;fun, running through them when the corn was fully grown...&nbsp;Finally, behind her house were a few old barns, some trees, and a hay field.If&nbsp;I&nbsp;lived there,&nbsp;whenever I got bored, I'd explore&nbsp;them...&nbsp;Ah, it was wonderful. Her house, itself, was ancient. It was downtrodden but beautifully so. There were cracks in the walls and floors and no computer or any real technology&nbsp;but it was fabulous all the same. Ah, what I'd give to live in the country.  Anyhow, I HAVE to be going... I've been on the computer for way too long...  Cya later...  &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Lonely, that is what I am. I mean, I've got my friends, I've got Nicole, and I've got the rest of my family... There is no reason to be lonesome, none at at all, except for one, and that is that I don't have a boyfriend! I know that I am spending WAY too much time obsessing over this subject but I can't help it! I'm a teenager afterall! Don't nearly all teens obsess over their love lives? Okay, maybe it's not just a boyfriend that I'm craving for... Maybe, I'm really desiring someone that actually gets me... Ugh! You'd figure that after being yourself for thirteen years, that you would know how you thought or felt about certain things, but obviously I'm not lucky enough to possess such a sense.     I probably secretly desire for both. Or a two in one. Like, I most likely, subconsciously wish for a boyfriend that completely understands almost everything about me. That's a long shot wish, isn't it? Every girl or woman probably desires the exact same thing as I do... Well, if they can't find anyone that fulfills this then what are my chances for finding someone like this? Seriously, what are the odds that I'll find someone that even wants to know me? Oh, I know, the chances are exactly in the range from zero to none... No one will ever truly care about me... No one ever does...      Hopefully, one day, if I'm fortunate enough to have both my personality and looks repaired, someone out there will care about me and the rest of my life. One day, most likely when I'm older, I'll meet that someone, at least I hope so... It would be great to find someone that either feels the same way I do about specific topics or someone that is willing to try to get to understand why I am the way I am and other stuff pertaining to that... That would be positevely, completely, utterly, and wholly magnificent if I could find someone like that... I know I'd never let them go...     Anyways, I'm gone...
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Okay, I am seriously confused about things dealing with my EBGF. Alright, I did say that I wasn't going to mention him in this blog but give a girl a break, I can't be perfect!!! Anyways, this entire situation with him is like completely puzzling. You see, my twin sister and his little sister (my best friend) got into a big fight in which my EBGF was mentioned. My sister told her that she was sick of being tortured and tormented by her brother to which she replied that he was probably treating us badly because he felt we were treating him badly. Treating him badly? I don't even talk to him anymore!    Alright, I know that not ever telling my EBGF that I had a boyfriend hurt him but I didn't think it would hurt him so much that he HAS to find revenge... I mean, I have NEVER said anything about him to anyone at school, at all... Hm... Maybe that's issue... Do you think that's so? Do you really believe that he misses me at all? The chances are slim but oh, how great would that be, 'cause I miss him a lot too... Well, er, sort of... I miss the friendship we had with one another... If we ever start talking again, would things EVER get back to the way they used to be? Do we have anything in common anymore? I know that he shares the same love for the movie, Pirates of the Caribbean, and the same passion for the computer game, The Sims; but do we have anything else in common?    Honestly, I'm a little nervous about reinstating our friendship again. What if he sees the real me and hates me? I don't know if I could deal with that. I don't open myself up to others... How would he react to my expressions, my words, my thoughts, my everything? I'm scared that he'll see the real me and completely dislike me for who I am... Then I'd lose him, forever. I know we're not friends anymore but I know that in a case of emergency that I can go to him if I really have to. I know he won't turn me away, 'cause he saw me once, the real me and he liked what he saw... And I know, despite all of his mean, crude, and self-absorbed jokes, that the guy that was my best friend when I was little is still in there...    I'm hopeless, aren't I? I'm always trying to look for the good in people, don't I? Well, I believe that everyone has at least a small portion of good inside them... Some may just need some help in finding it... Oh, well...    I'm outie...   
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I can't stop thinking about love. In every movie that I see a girl and a guy ALWAYS hook up... It is SO annoying... Sure, I am only thirteen and therefore do not understand what love means but who cares? I'm calling like like or lust or whatever it is, love, so there! Anyways, it is TOTALLY depressing seeing everyone around me get girlfriends and boyfriends. It completely bums me out... Why don't I have a boyfriend? I bet no guy in the entire universe will ever like me! This guy named Tristan supposively liked me but he only liked my body, the perv! Jeez, I don't even have a great body! Anyhow, I just want a guy to like me for ME. I don't want some creep that would rather see me in a mini skirt then in anything else more suitable... I just really, REALLY want a guy who appreciates me.    If I had a boyfriend and I could choose his personality, I'd want him to be funny or sarcastic (in a good way), nice, and sweet. See, he'd have to be funny or sarcastic because I really need someone to show me the brighter things in this world. He'd have to be nice because I just don't respect mean people at all... And I don't know but he just has to be sweet. I don't care what he looks like, a guy with those traits is my Prince Charming...    I'm probably asking WAY too much... I am, aren't I? I guess I'm one of those girls that is dreaming for a "Happily Ever After." I'm clueless about the world of going out but I don't really care... I know what I want in a guy and to me, that is all that really matters. I'm pathetic about this entire thing... I'm looking for a guy that I can take things slow with and be with for a really long time. It would be great if I could find that guy now and we could go steady until at least our senoir year in highschool...    Am I a hopeless romantic or what?   
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Daydreaming, a lovable sport to play... All I ever really do is daydream. I'm more in love with fantasy than reality, you could say. I love daydreaming. It's a beautiful thing to do. You don't have to be a certain age to do it either. You could be young or old and you still can daydream. It's not very hard either.  You think about things a lot... You make the things that have happened to you in real life way more dramatic then they really were to entertain yourself. You envision different worlds and how their cultures differ from ours. You think about impossible things to do and create crazy ways in which you can do them. You make up pretend fights, love scenes, and tragedies for your own life... You even create those for other peoples lives and/or other fictional character's lives... It's awesome...     I'm not exactly sure if that's how you classify daydreaming. It might be, it might not be... According to www.rhymezone.com , daydreaming, is absent-minded dreaming while awake. But what is dreaming exactly? According to this website again, dreaming, at least the type I'm writing about, is imaginative thoughts indulged in while awake... Hm... Interesting, very interesting... Yet, what is considered imaginative? So, I asked RhymeZone yet again. They responded that imaginative is    marked by independence and creativity in thought or action. This was a very intriguing search to undergo. So, daydreaming is absent-minded independence and creativity in thought or action indulged in while awake. I was sort of close, right?     Anyways, however you define daydreaming, isn't it wonderful? Other people call it a complete waste of time, but to me it's WAY more than that... Ah, this subject is so stupid and lame, but do you know what? I seriously don't care...  
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm so angry I could scream. I am so frustrated that I could kill myself in a heartbeat. I'm so tired of all of this that this second I could just pack up all of my things, walk out of my house, and never look back. Oh, I'm feeling terrible inside... I'm seriously sorry for ruining this blog with my petty suicidal thoughts and rather unfocused feelings, but I can't help it! My life is driving me absolutely insane at the moment and I hate it... I don't like NOT being in control. I hate being me. It really, really hurts... It's not only my social interaction deprivation but it's everything else. It's my love life, my parents, my sister, my friends, school, Camp, things online... Oh, it's everything... I wish things could just slow down at the moment so I could stand back and take everything one step at a time or go really fast so that everything is over before I'd know it. If only wishes came true!    Okay, with my romance life thingy, I REALLY, REALLY like this guy but it's like he'll never see me. I never get to see him and whenever I do, he is always laughing with a bunch of other girls. What sucks the most is that I know I can never have him even as a friend because we come from such different social groups and I wouldn't exactly fit in with his group. Another thing is, I'm not the least bit attractive. I'm SOOO ugly. I wear the same baggy things over and over again... I've liked him for a really long time. I've never told anyone this of course... Anyways, it really hurts because I can't stop looking around for his face every single place that I go to. It's so annoying and whenever I see him my heart practically melts...    Then there is my EBGF. One summer, when we were little we climbed onto his roof and watched the fireworks that my city does every Fourth of July, up there. It was beautiful up there. I had loads of fun and I was sort of hoping that somehow this summer, we could have done that again. I know that we're not friends or anything and I know it was kind of stupid to think that it would actually happen, but I don't know, I just wanted it to happen so badly... I miss having someone who's not apart of my family but is my friend and has known me almost my entire life... Like someone that could totally get me... And my EBGF used to be that for me.    There is so much more, but I have no time to write the rest of them down. God, I just wish my anger would take a walk for once.    
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Confused, that is what I am. Everywhere I go I don't know how to act so I just either don't say anything at all or I remain sarcastic and cynical. Usually at school I am a mime during any given social situation that includes people other than my very best friends. I have no clue on what to say or how to act so I just don't say or do anything. I just sort of stand (or sit or lay) there, blinking at the person. God, I am SO clueless on how to behave around other people. People take this as good manners but that truly is not it. I don't know how else to act, I wonder what rude manners looks like... I suppose I don't want those, but for once I just want to be known other than quiet, smart, and polite by the general public... I mean, I don't want to loose my intelligence (though sometimes I've thought about it) nor my "good" manners, but I just don't want to be known as quiet. I want people to say things about me like, "Oh, she is SO much FUN to hang out with..." Or "She's got some seriously cool ideas..." Or "She's very opinionated about certain subjects but she's also very open minded about whatever you've got to say..." Seriously, that would be AWESOME. If only I weren't such an anti-social, paranoid, freak! I don't mind being a freak and paranoia doesn't hurt all that much but sometimes my anti-socialness gets to me... I mean, when I look around there are tons of kids hanging out with at least ten friends, doing crazy things... Ah, being different, sometimes sucks...  
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I'm lost. I'm crazy. I'm stupid. I'm weak. I'm reckless. I'm cold hearted. I've got nothing but cold feet. I'm pathetic. I'm just a waste of time to get to know. I'm hiding myself. I always ruin everything. I'm ugly. I'm fat. I'm incredulously spontaneous. I am unorganized. I'm messed up. I'm beat up. I'm wandering in hopeless dreams. I spend my day in never going to come true fantasies. I hide my thoughts and feelings in stupid poems and in the pages of books. I stay up late so my mind can not think about my day because it's too sleepy. I ward off others so they have no chance of ever hurting me. I can't admit when I cry, weeping...     What's the use in living anymore? What do  I  have to live for? I bet if I killed myself that no one would miss me either. I bet no one would care to come to my funeral at all. I bet they'd have a party to celebrate that I'm out of their lives, 'cause all I ever do is slip up and do all of the wrong things. I'm not nice and sweet and perfect... Nope, I'm just mean, cold hearted, and the farthest from being perfect that a human being with a heart can be... I suck. I should go to hell after all of the mean things I have done. I shouldn't be alive. I don't deserve the friends that I have. I mean, they're everything I'm not. I don't deserve my friends or my family or my neighbors... Why am I living? I've got no use here on Earth! I'm a pathetic excuse for a human being! God or whoever the hell created me must have been fucking insane when creating me because I am completely and totally worthless. I'm  WEAK ! I CAN'T BELIEVE I SHOWED THEM HOW I WAS FEELING.  WHAT WAS I THINKING?  I should have known that it wouldn't help... I should have known that no will EVER understand the pain I feel... GOD, I WAS SO STUPID.     If I could, right now, I'd hurt myself... But, no... I'm not allowed to because I made some stupid promises to my family that I wouldn't do anything like that... Well, who gives a damn about what I can and cannot do according to other people?? Well, I can tell you right now, at this very moment, I do not care at all on what other people have said. All I know is that I am DYING inside right now and that I HAVE to make it stop before it all completely breaks down and all hell breaks lose. I've had that happen once before and it wasn't too pretty... I need something to releive all of my freaking feelings that go away. I NEED something to do it. I hate it! I can't control the way I'm feeling no matter how much I try. I HATE LIFE! I can't control anything that goes on in it. I can't do anything right. I'm worthless!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I think I am falling in love... Falling in love with fictional romance, that is what I believe that I am doing. I am currently reading a book series that makes my insides melt. It is like one of those corny movies where the main character says the perfect, witty thing to the second main character before kissing her... I think I am turning into a hopeless romantic... Oh dear... When I grow a little older, I might actually turn away from my usual bookcase of fantasy books and historical fiction and to the mushy, gushy, romance novels!!!!!     Things in my world seem to be changing so fast. I'm loving romance novels, I started caring about my weight, I have completely different views... I thought that I would never change. I mean, I knew people changed but I just sort of thought that I'd always be the same, that everyone else would become different and that I'd always have the same interests and junk. Personally, I don't like change... It twists peoples thoughts... Like, for instance, I absolutely hate smoking for it pollutes the air and damages people's healths. What happens, if one day, I change and actually tries smoking, likes it, and then dies from it a couple of months after my first try?     It's weird that I'm posting to you about God, dreams, depression, and romance novels; isn't it? I guess you could call this entire blog thingy, 'Koala Peace: My Useless Thoughts on Miscellaneous Subjects and Other Things.' However, that would be too long of title... Perhaps something like, 'Koala Peace: Miscellaneously Me.' Well, that's a little better, don't you think? Oh, well. 'Koala Peace' is perfectly fine with me. I don't need anything more complex in order to keep writing in this blog. Nope, the simple way is the best for me.     I'm not a very materialistic person. I don't need precious diamonds, desinger clothes, shiny gadjets, and the rest of that other really expensive stuff that extremely rich people have. Nope, I'm much happier with the things I already have. I loathe change so what do you expect? Anyways, I liked older, antique things... They are full of memories. New things just seem to be pathetically big and phony. I'd rather have something that is steady and decent rather then anything big, bright, and bold...     Well, I'm outie.  
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        It is four thirty in the morning and my eyelids can not close. Even though they desperately want to, they will not heed to my command. My mind is so very tired. Not because of any physical exhaustion placed on my shoulders because of a long days work. Nope, I barely move from my computer screen all day long... No, it's this entire situation with my EBGF that is really driving into my skull, it is emotional and mental exhaustion in which I am suffering from. Ah, I promised that I would not write about it in this blog... I will not break my promise... No more shall I write about this dreary subject. I shall switch onto my other blog, 'The Conceited One' and write about my horrible, haunting thoughts on him. That is if I have enough energy to type anything down... Ah, I am so tired... I just wish that my eyes would close. Hopefully, whenever I fall asleep I will dream.     Usually my dreams are ones that concern great horror and/or mystery... Only once in a while will I get a dream that is completely pointless in meaning. Personally, I hate meaningless, pathetic dreams... My most remembered, pointless dream is one that concerns a boy from school, a glass of water, and some ketchup. It was completely ridiculous... Yes, I prefer different dreams... Of course I don't enjoy dreams that are filled with terrible events occurring or weird things happening. But hey, they're better than nothing.     The only dream of mine that I have ever truly liked was the one where this clown came to my neighborhood and taught all of the kids on my street different circus tricks... It sounds pretty lame but it was awesome... We did this enormous human pyramid where the person at the top was twice as tall as a two story house. I actually saw myself in that pyramid. I know it sounds pathetically stupid but seriously, it was fantastic. Yet, that dream, too, ended up in a mystery. Yet, it sort of ended in a good way. It was like the ending of a dramatic movie.     Oh, I've wandered off into my silly ramblings about my dreams and such. It may sound that my "dreams" sound more like "nightmares", and it's true, they are much more like nightmares than dreams. However, I rarely have any dreams, much less any good ones. I'll call them what I want to call them and you call them what you want to call them... Ah, I have been deprived of sleep too long... My eyes are slowly beginning to shut... I'm off to bed... Mayhap this time I'll actually get to sleep.  
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nicole and I had the best time together today... Well, at least during the afternoon/evening part. During the morning hours we went with our dad to help clean the apartments that my parents rent out to college kids every year, so it's presentable for human habitation again. It wasn't all that bad, I guess. We spent three to four hours running up and down flights of stairs and fetching things to either fix or clean broken and/or dirty miscellaneous objects throughout the three story apartment building... That place is so spooky and not to mention humungous... Last time that I went there to help my parents out, I got lost in there... Ah, it was positvely horrible. It was SO creepy. You couldn't hear anything at all. The walls were as thick as tar, I swear. It was very spooky. I was screaming for my sister who, though I did not know it at the time, was directly a floor below me. She didn't hear my shouting at all... Weird, huh?  I'm veering off topic here... Anyways, Cole and I, got back from the apartments around 12ish. We didn't really hang out until 4:30 or so... We talked for a half an hour and then decided to take a walk to the high school that we're going to be attending after this year... Oh my gosh, we had an awesome time! We talked about everything and anything that entered our minds... It was hilarious... We bumped into my brother's old friend, who just happens to be extremely attractive, while we were walking. It was funny.   We eventually walked back home, pigged out on Chinese food, and then set off to buy our favorite ice cream at our local Stewarts. Our favorite ice cream of all time of course, is chocolate chip cookie dough! Yum, it's delicious... If you haven't ever had it before, I highly recommend that you try it... Anyhow, we ate our ice cream and talked about silly things until we reached one of our city's parks. Then we went around screaming idiotic things like "marshmallow" and "teletubbies." We're freaks, aren't we? It was awesome. Tonight we're supposed to go see I, Robot... I don't know if we're going to be able to go though... My parents are a little cranky and tired after a days work at "the apartments."  Nicole's my best friend... Yeah, we happen to be blood related but does that matter? Some people won't become friends with us, at the times when I'm outgoing of course, just because Nicole and I are close. I find that extremely odd AND stupid. I mean, if Nicole and I weren't from the same blood line, those people would have no problem with being our friends at all... It's ridiculous, totally... I hate it when people won't be my friend just because I have a twin. I feel so discrimminated against... Well, not really, but you know what I mean, right? No? Okay, nevermind...  In soccer last year my coach forced the twins on the team to pair up with someone else. That's totally not fair. I mean, all the other best friends get to pair up with one another, just because we're blood related doesn't make the situation any different really! Ugh, some people just really make me mad. I seriously don't understand people when they do this... It makes me really, really angry... I wish people weren't so cruel... Someone told me to go have sex with Nicole once, just because we were twins... What the hell is wrong with people?  Ugh, some people just really annoy the hell out of me...  And now I'm gone...
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I hate to admit it, but the conversation that I had with my EBGF, which I posted yesterday, totally hurts. I mean, I know I'm a loser. The freaking kid doesn't need to tell me that for heaven's sakes. I've known that I was a loser, or a "fag" as he put it, ever since I left my old school, St. Johns.  I just wasn't born to be popular, like him, okay? Nope, I was born to be who I am right now, an anti-social freak that barely has any friends or a life.  I've never wanted to be in with the "in" group. When I was younger, before all that shit happened with my then best friends, I just didn't really care about popularity. I wanted people to like me but I wasn't like obsessed with being the coolest kid in my grade. I was always fine with the number of friends that I had. Popularity was NOT a big issue with me. Well, in the fourth grade, to everyone else but Cole and I it seemed, became overly obsessed with being in with the "in" crowd. My best friends of then, Keri and Bridgid, were especially obsessed with the subject. They always talked about popularity and kept asking why we couldn't be popular. This really annoyed Nicole and I, and I mean it REALLY annoyed the hell out of us. So, we always joked around that we were the misfits of the school and crap like that. Well, Keri and Bridgid couldn't take it anymore and tried to become "popular." They started dressing more "in" and acting more "popular." They ditched us. Keri also made fun of us every chance she got. She, along with Bridgid, completely ruined the life that I had, had at St. Johns. She made our other friends think that we were backstabbing, losers... Oh, it was terrible. I used to cry myself to sleep every night... Eventually Cole and I switched schools. It wasn't only because of Bridgid and Keri though. A little part of it was because of my ex boyfriend named Seth.  In the fifth grade I was totally Anti-Popular. If you were popular, there wasn't anyway that I would be your friend. I made friends with Katelyn and Chloe that year... During the sixth I was almost completely over with my Anti-Popular attitude. I finally began to understand that not all popular people are stuck up bitches, just some. However, I became Anti-Social... Several things just happened all at once which made me distrust people even more... When my mom tried to kill my dad, is just one of them...  So, it sort of annoys the hell out of you when your EBGF is telling you that you're a pathetic loner/outcast that will never have any friends because you're not updated with the current version of "cool." Since when have I ever wanted to be popular? Since when have I cared about having friends? Honestly, I don't need friends. This upcoming school year, all I wanted to do was to actually be myself around people. I don't need friends. They're nice to have and I love the ones that I've got, but I don't need twenty friends and/or admirers to make me feel special or whatever. I don't need popularity in order to live... All I need to know is who I am. Why should I be "cool" if it ruins who I really am?  Gone... 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A rather beautiful AIM (AOL Instant Messenger) conversation with my EBGF. Don't you just love him? NOT!! I saved our conversation and took out our real screen name's though you could easily find out my screen name by looking into my user look up. He was originally posing as Kate, but I guess he just broke...  EBGF: back Me: Okie dokie. EBGF: stfu biatch aaaaaahahahahahahahaha okie dokie biatch? Me: Yup. EBGF: ur outdated, nobodys says that shit anymore Me: And I care because? EBGF: ur a fag, u should care Me: That's nice. Too bad, I don't. EBGF: because number 1.. u have no friends... number 2.. by using words from 1995 you will never get any friends besides the shemales on aol chat room Me: 1. I do have friends. 2. I don't care how old the words I use are... 3. I don't talk to people in aol chat rooms, thankyou very much EBGF: sure Me: Yep. EBGF: living double life is hard Me: What is that supposed to mean? EBGF: ur trans sexual Me: I am not. EBGF: sure Me: Where did you get that idea? EBGF: lol Me: Okay...?? My EBGF signed off at 8:15:10 PM.  And that is how things work with him and I... Isn't it lovely? See, I try to be nice... I am nice to him... Well, most of the time. I've let go of our past and all but he just won't quit, will he? Oh, well, there's a jerk for you. 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm feeling so pumped up right now. I'm pumped up about school. There's only about a month and a little over a week left until it starts. My school starts on September 8th. It'd be cool if it started on September 1st, though. I don't know why I find that cool, I just do. Actually, it would be awesome if school started right now. I'm SO bored and I've got about a million expectations and such for it. Beforehand, I'd type that I hated school and wish that it NEVER existed, but now I can type freely that I'm entirely glad that it exists and that I want it to come, NOW!  I've told you all of this before, in one of my previous entries, have I not? Well, whether you believe it or not, I am way more pumped up and ready for the school year, then before. Hard to believe huh?  Why am I so pumped up? Just read the reasons I listed below and you'll find out.   Reason #1: Back To School Shopping.     I, like many other school kids that I know of, absolutely adore back to school shopping. Some kids love shopping for clothes and other things associated with their wardrobe while others love shopping for new notebooks, binders, pens, pencils, etc... Personally, I love both. They're both fun to do. Especially since this year I'm having my whole style done over.   Reason #2: Changing The Personality.     Nicole, Sarah, and I have all decided to be extremely outgoing this year. This makes my personality change that I mentioned in a previous entry, easier. There is always safety in numbers. We're not going to be mum this year and we're not going to stand for any shit piled upon us. If someone tries to walk over us, they are going DOWN. Trust me, if someone messes with me this year, I'm not going to take it lying down like I did last year. I'm sick of being made fun of... People are not going to drag me down. I'm going to say how I feel, when I feel it. I'm not keeping everything in. If you're nice to me, I'll be nice to you. If not, then you better watch out...  Ah, I have to get going now. Dinner calls...  Love,  Kel.    
      
</post>



</Blog>