<Blog>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a story i wrote for my english class. i got a 94 on it, i believe. enjoy.     And so it Begins…. by Caitlin   “That’s $1.95,” I said to the gray-haired CEO in front of me. Jeez, it’s only my first day working here and already I hate it. It’s so trés trés chic, it makes me want to puke. I keep thinking over and over, if only dad hadn’t left, I wouldn’t be serving overpriced cappuccinos and espressos to business people and rich little brats who act as if I’m lucky to be graced by their presence.  Yes, my dad, “the most wonderful-est, coolest, kindest, caring-est daddy in the whole wide WORLD!!!”- NOT! What kind of father just leaves his wife and 2 teenage kids, no note, no nothing? A no-good bastard of a father, that’s what kind.  The funny thing is, I never cried, not once. I’m not the kind of person that cries a lot- and he wasn’t really worth any tears, to tell you the truth. Besides, if I cried, the whole world would probably be thrown into a frenzied panic- “Dear Lord!! Syd Wolfmann is crying!! The apocalypse draws near!! It’s the end of all things to come!!” It’s as if me crying is equivalent to the Four Horsemen just a-galloping in out of nowhere to announce that they’ve met their deadline, you know?  So I didn’t cry- I mean, every time he was drunk, he kicked the crap out of my 13-year-old brother and me, if anything, I should be celebrating.  The only problem is, that my mom was completely oblivious to that- she thought he was a fine, upstanding citizen. So naturally, she was devastated when he left. And then there’s the slight issue of finances, which, of course, is my reason for getting this second job at a fancy French café that’s half an hour away from my house in Hartford, near Kenelly School.  After 3 hours of face after snobby face, I was finally done with work for the day. I ran out to my car- which was actually the van belonging to my band, Asylum Street- and was surprised to see our drummer, Jade, waiting impatiently.  “FINALLY!! Come on, we gotta go to Sarah’s house!” she exclaimed.  “Jeez, I’m fine, how are you?” I replied sarcastically.  “Syd, I’m serious!! We have something really important to tell you!” she screeched.  “Alright, alright!!! And doctors say there’s no known cause for an aneurysm?” I mumbled in response.   The half hour drive back to the neighborhood that we all lived in seemed excruciatingly long- normally, Jade can’t keep a secret, but so far she hadn’t uttered a word about what the band had to tell me.  We finally reached Sarah’s house, a small yellow house on Yale Street. We ran down the stairs to the basement to see Sarah, lead guitarist, and Ashes- short for Ashley- our rhythm guitarist.  “Ok, so what is sooooo important that you had to drag me here straight from my first day at Le Café what’s-its-name, which, by the way SUCKED???” I inquired. “Well, remember when we sent that demo to SubCity Records a few months back?” began Ashes. I nodded, praying that they’d say what I thought they’d say. “Well…. WE GOT SIGNED!!” finished Sarah.  After 15 minutes or so of jumping around like the moron I am, I decided to walk home- it was only 3 streets away, on Exeter St. During the 5 minute walk, I started to think about what this could mean. SubCity wanted us to start touring the next summer, a short 4 months away. It wasn’t going to be a big tour, just the East Coast, and we’d only be stopping at really small venues, but it was a start. The best part was that we’d be touring with my other best friend’s band, Memento Mori. Both bands sent in demos to Hopeless/SubCity- SubCity is a branch of Hopeless that’s for charity bands, like us- and we both got signed. Ever since both bands started, we always said we’d both go on the same first real tour, now that was really going to happen.  There was only one problem. What about Mom and my brother, Dameon? Dameon would love to come with us. He’s always wanted to see us play shows for more that 15 kids at a time, but Mom doesn’t have a lot of love for our music, and she probably couldn’t pay all the bills- I mean, that’s why I got a second job, to help pay the bills, and if I went on tour, she’d lose all of my income. She would most definitely not want me going, and she would NOT want Dameon to go if I did.  I walked in the door of our house- it was relatively huge, considering the size of some of the surrounding houses. Dameon was sitting cross-legged on the floor, watching Rockzilla on Fuse, and mom was nowhere to be found- either she was working, or she was in her room crying. I glanced up at the clock- still some time for practicing bass before I went to bed. I ran up the stairs, making roughly the same amount of noise as a stampede of water buffalo- it’s a habit I have to make as much noise as possible for the sole purpose of annoying people. I slammed the door to my room and picked up my Mark Hoppus Fender bass from the corner of my room.   The next day I went to my job at the café at 7- I was going to work until noon, then go to my job at Hot Topic, which I’ve had for a year or so.  “Medium Soy Latte, please,” said a voice that seemed oddly familiar. I glanced up to see my best friend and the frontman of Memento Mori, Zack Broderick. “Zack!!” I exclaimed, surprised. “Yeah, thought I’d see how your new job is… is it just me, or do I not exactly seem to fit in here?” he asked, making a big point of looking around at the occupants of the café, all of whom had extremely disapproving looks on their faces- maybe it had something to do with his blue and green Mohawk, misfits shirt and plaid pants. “Yeah, it’s possible man. Listen, my break is in, like, 3 minutes, talk to you then- this little rich girl is gonna have a temper tantrum if you don’t move.” I said quietly, earning a glare from the aforementioned girl.   “So the tour starts this summer man- it’s finally happening,” said Zack.  “Yeah, it’s crazy, man. I never thought we’d get signed this early.”  “Seriously, me too. It’s insane, we’re going to be touring and you’ll be just barely 18. But… what about your mom, Joey said she’s depending on you to make money, and you can’t exactly work when you’re on tour?” he asked, mentioning my cousin, Joey, who played drums for Memento. “Yeah, I haven’t exactly told her yet, but I will… I just have to wait until I’ve saved up some money for her to have while I’m gone.” “Man, you gotta tell her soon- otherwise you’re gonna end up telling her the night before we leave, and she’ll have found out by then.” “I know, I know… I’m working on it, man… I just gotta wait a little longer, if I tell her too early, she’ll find a way to keep me from going.”  Well, even though I promised Zack I’d tell mom, weeks went by, until it was only a month before we started touring. I walked into the house, fresh from another day at Le Café de Torture, to see the house seemingly empty with all the lights off.  “I heard something very interesting today, Sydney.” Came my mother’s voice from the living room. Her voice no longer had the scratchy tone of someone who had been crying for hours on end, the tone that I was so used to. Now it was cold and even, and downright scary. Whenever my father had used that tone with me, I had been scared out of my Doc Martens. But not this time, I was sick of being pushed around by other people.  “What was that?” I responded in an equally cold tone.   “Oh, I think you already know exactly what.” She was going to make this as difficult as possible, wasn’t she?   “Let’s pretend I don’t, shall we?”  “Alright then, yes, let’s.” she agreed. “I heard that you’re planning on leaving on tour with your little friends.”  “Ding ding ding, we have a winner!!” I said in a sarcastically animated voice. “Your prize is $10,000 worth of ‘big whoop’ and a lifetime supply of ‘I don’t care’!!!”  “I forbid it.” She said simply.  “Too late, we’re leaving in less than a month.” I said indifferently.  “I should have known.” She sneered, her voice layered with icy contempt and spite. “I should have known. First you drove your father out, now you yourself are leaving! It was so clear- ever since you started that band of yours—"  she spat out the word ‘band’ as if it left a bad taste in her mouth “- it should have made perfect sense. All those years, I prayed that it was a phase, that you’d grow out of it and become a respectable young lady, but it doesn’t seem to matter, you still managed to become a bass guitar playing little bitch, become a disgrace to this family! How dare you? How dare you leave This Family?! Do you know what I thought when I first found out? Do you?! I thought about how much better off the world would be without you, how much better off I’d be if you were gone! Do you hear me, I wish you would die!”  She continued to scream and rant, but it was all meaningless noise. The last 5 words that registered in my mind kept echoing back to me- “I wish you would die…. I wish you would die…” These are undoubtedly the 5 most powerful words in the world.  I was vaguely aware of stumbling up the stairs and into my room, slamming the door, and sliding down on the floor. My thoughts were a blur. Now I knew what it was like to be Justin Sane, the bass player that swallowed a bottle of cough syrup, or Sid Vicious, who overdosed on heroin on purpose, or the kid at school who put a bullet in his brain. It doesn’t take insanity; it just takes 5 words- “I wish you would die”. I stood up shakily and walked over to the desk where I kept all of my drawing materials, including the knife I used to sharpen my drawing pencils. I picked it up and looked at the blade, smeared with graphite. No matter how many times I cleaned it, that knife was still always covered in smudges and stains of graphite. If the blood loss didn’t kill me, then infection certainly would, this blade was anything but sterile.    I stretched out on the floor, staring up at the ceiling. I started to lift up the knife, but then I heard a noise downstairs. I realized it was Dameon coming home from his friend’s house. I heard him turn on the stereo and then heard Pantera blasting through the speakers.  WHAT THE HELL WAS I THINKING??????!!!!?!?!?!?!?!?!?  I sat up and threw the knife across the room. Mom was one person. Ashes, Jade, Sarah, Dameon, Zack, everyone else…. They were a lot of people. And the people that I’d make happy, there were only a few of them. The people that would mourn for me- there were just as many, if not more. I couldn’t let them down… and more importantly, I couldn’t let myself down by doing this. I couldn’t let one person’s words kill me, no matter how powerful those words were. It’s that simple.  I picked up a notebook and pen from my nightstand and started writing. If lyric writing had helped me through shit before, how come it couldn’t help me now? I scribbled, crossed out, and scribbled some more, until finally, several hours later, I had something that sounded decent. Then I put my notebook away and went to bed- I had to work and practice with the band the next day, and I needed sleep more now than ever.  The next day, after work, the band came over to practice. We played all our old songs first, taking up about an hour, then I told them I had some new material to show them. “Alright, then lets hear it!” said Jade. “Ok, I just wrote it last night- just bass and lyrics, I started on some guitar, but I needed you guys to help with that, I mean, you’ll be playing it- I didn’t even start on drums.” I played the song I had written the night before for them. When I was done, 6 minutes later, they were staring at me in awe.   “Sydney, I need to talk to you.” Said my mom as I walked up the stairs from my basement, where we’d been rehearsing. I looked over at her, not quite ready to talk to her. “I… I lost my job. They said I was out too often, ever since your father left.” She told me before running to her room and slamming the door, just as I had so many times.  Now I was faced with a new dilemma- if Mom still had her job, she could at least support herself if I took Dameon with me on tour, but now there was no way in hell. I picked up the phone and dialed my aunt- mom’s sister’s- number. I needed help, we needed help. There was no way we could survive without mom working.  “Hello?” said a voice at the other end. “Hey Aunt Katey…” I said. “Syd, what’s wrong?” she asked. “Mom lost her job.” I said flatly. “And I don’t see how I can tour next month if she’s not working, she can’t support herself, even if Dameon comes with me.” “Well, then it’s final. Your mother is coming to stay with me.” She said matter-of-factly.  “Huh? Are you serious?” I asked, suddenly realizing that there was some hope. “Yes, of course. If Dameon wants to go with you, then by all means, but if he doesn’t, he’s welcome to stay as well. “But… I mean, wouldn’t it be imposing…?” “Of course not, you’re my family too! Look, even if you stay, they’ll be out on the streets in a matter of months. If your mother stays here, it gives her some time to get back on her feet without having to worry about the mortgage. Give her some time to cool down, then tell her tomorrow.” She said. “Thanks!! Bye!” I replied.   The next day, we had another practice at my house, to finish writing the song. Jade had come up with a drum solo, and Ashes and Sarah had come up with some guitar.  We spent 2 hours putting everything together, then when we finally got it right, we decided to run through it one more time.  “Suffocation.  Your words force the air from my lungs, Air that now tastes cold and dead As images of days we had Run slowly through my head.” At first the vocals were soft and even, no signs of any screaming. But it slowly got louder and louder through the next few verses, until it was my signature shrieks and howls.  “Suddenly I can breathe again But the air still tastes dead to my lungs Now I can safely say  That my time is done…”  At this point, Jade flew into an angry drum solo, at least a minute long, followed by Sarah’s guitar solo, which started out as angrily as Jade’s drums, but faded into soft, mournful melodies. After the solos, I sang the last lines of the song, in the same tone as the opening lines:  “To those that I love, The ones I leave behind Please do not cry And please don’t try to save me tonight I still love you This is goodbye….” I glanced up, thinking I heard someone running away quickly, but upon seeing no one, I decided it was nothing. Still, I could have sworn I heard something…  We packed up and I went to find Mom and tell her what Aunt Katey said. I found her sitting in the living room. “Mom, you’re gonna stay with Aunt Katey while I’m on tour.” I said flatly. “I suppose Dameon will be going with you?” she asked. Her voice wasn’t the scratchy, crackly tone, but it wasn’t the cold, spiteful one either- she sounded resigned to the fact that I would go no matter what, and Dameon would be going too. “If he wants to. Sorry, but it’s for the best…” I trailed off. “I know.” I walked back downstairs to pack up my bass, thinking “And so it begins…”   From the Asylum Street online tour journal: We’ve been on tour for 2 weeks now- it’s so cool! We’ve been getting on each others nerves occasionally, but it’s no big deal- we’re finally living out our dreams, and it’s the greatest thing- well, ever. Dameon’s having fun, just like everyone else- he may be only 13, but he fits in really well. If there’s one thing I’ve learned from touring- and getting ready for the tour- is that not everything is as simple as we’d like it to be- JUST DEAL WITH IT. Remember to catch us when we’re in town- that is, if you live on the east coast. Check out the Tour Dates for more info.  Love, Peace, Unity, Syd   Hope you liked it. It was fun writing it. Later Daze. email me xXbloodyXvalentineXx@yahoo.com w/ feedback if you want.    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yes, i'm back so soon. i feel like working on a fanfic, so i will. If youre a fan of this band youre gonna wanna kill me- it's about avenged sevenfold. the only reason I'm writing about them is because i've never heard a serious fic about them before. Dont worry, its not a romance, the A7x guys are more of... i dont know, mentors for the main characters.  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  "Jillian, I've had enough! I'm sorry but I've had enough!" a sharp voice, full of anger and spite. "Peter, please!" hysterical sobbing.    Mom and dad, fighting again. They seem to be under the impression that just because it's 1 in the morning, no one can hear them. But I sure can, and I'm almost posotive that my younger brother and sister, Raechel and Chaz, can too.   "No, Jillian. Time and time again I've been here, but every single change that occurs in our life, and you start acting up again!" "Peter, I'm sorry, I can't help it-" "Jillian, I've had enough of your syndromes, your disorders, your imbalances! I just dont care anymore! You're on your own!"  It's been 3 weeks now. We've fallen into a routine- I get out of school, pick up Raechel from afternoon kindergarten, and try to get home before 13 year old Chaz so he won't burn the house down.  Why doesn't Mom do all of this? She's convinced that Dad's coming back, and she won't leave her room, for fear that he'll come home and she won't be there. She's too depressed to leave, anyway. That's chronic depression for you.  I don't know who I'm more pissed at- Mom for being like this, or Dad for leaving and making it worse. We just moved to Huntington Beach, I guess that's what set Mom's depression off, which is what "made" Dad leave.  "Adrienne! Mom wants you!" yelled Chaz, startling me out of my thoughts. I slowly stood up from the couch where i had been sitting and walked over to Mom's room, in no real hurry.  "Adrienne, where's your father?" she asked when she heard me walk in. She keeps convincing herself that he's still around, and has just gone out and she can't remember where. "He's gone, mom." "Gone where?" "Who knows, Mom? Probably in some bar, getting wasted. You know he left 3 weeks ago, and you know he's not coming back!" "You're lying! He just went for a walk, because he got in a fight with you! Yes, that's what happened!" "No, he was an asshole and he left, 3 weeks ago. He's. Not. Coming. Back. Face the facts, mom." "Go away! It's a lie! He's not gone, he'd never leave me! Never! Get out of my sight, you lying bitch!" "Mom..." "Out! He left because he was angry at you, you drove him away, but he will come back!" I ran out of her room and out of the house. I sat down on the curb outside of my house, and just as if God whas saying "ha ha, look what I made happen to you!" it started to rain.  I sat there for hours, just sitting in the rain. I didn't know how long i could put up with this. "So, what troubles bring you here?" asked a voice behind me. "Nothing. I'm just peachy. Just perfectly fucking peachy." I mumbled. "Hmm... naw, i don't think you are. See, when i was your age, this curb was reserved for people with relatinship, family, or school problems, which kind do you have?" I just sat there in scilence for a few minutes before i said "Family." "Oh, ok. See, otherwise, i'd have to kick you off the curb here. I'm Zacky, by the way." said the voice, whose owner sat down next to me on the sidewalk. I looked over and saw that he had eyes the color of ice, but didnt have all of the cold usually ascosiated with that color. His nose was pierced, and he was wearing a backwards black trucker cap and a black Misfits shirt with black Dickies. He looked oddly familliar, but i couldnt remember where I'd seen him.  "Care to elaborate? It's not like you have to..." he said after another uncomforable scilence. "It's complicated." i said. "Ok, well if you wanna talk later, I'm staying with my parents over there." he said, pointing to the blue house next to mine. He stood up and walked toward the house, leaving me to think in silence. ~~~ OK i'll continue it later, cos I'm too lazy to finish it now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here's a story i wrote. Well, it's not exactly a story, more of a summary, or kind of a retelling of edward scissorhands from his point of view.  I can't leave the mountain, not again. I did, once, and I was happy for a while. The family cared about me, they gave me a place to stay, and they were nice to me. Even though I'm not finished, they were nice to me. The neighborhood was nice to me too, for the most part. There was this one lady who said I was Satanic right from the start, but otherwise, not many problems. Then Kim and her friends came home from the mountains. Kim was scared of me, and her friends didn't like me either. Then, one day, her friend Jim asked me to help him take back something that was stolen from him. I knew what he actually wanted to do- steal something from his father- but I went anyway, because Kim wanted me to. When the alarm rang, they all ran and left me to take the blame. I should have told the truth, but I didn't. Because if I  told the truth, then Kim would get in trouble, and I didn't want that.  But after I got caught, the neighborhood began to hate me, began to agree with the lady who said those things about me in the beginning. They turned around everything I had ever done. The hedges that I had carved in the beginning, the ones that they had said were "beautiful" and "original" at first, were now mostrousities in their eyes. They stopped coming over to get their hair cut by me. Then, the night of the Christmas party, it happened. I was making an ice sculpture,and Kim came out to watch. She hadn't liked me at first, but I could tell she was beginning to admire my work with the hedges, and that she liked my ice sculpture. It was of an angel. Then, when I was climbing down the ladder, Someone yelled and startled me. I jumped a little, and jerked my hand- if you could call it a hand- and I accidentally cut Kim's hand. It was an accident, and I felt terrible- but Jim was the one who had yelled, and he was now convinced that I had tried to injure Kim. She insisted that it was just a small cut, but he didn't listen. He attacked me, and then I left. I didn't know where I'd go. I just needed to get away. I walked around town, only for a few minutes, but when I got home, Kim was the only one their. She told me that her hand was fine, and that her parents were out looking for me. She wanted me to give her a hug, I told her I couldn't, because if I did, then I might hurt her. So she helped me hold my arms out so that my hands wouldn't touch her at all. Then I heard a noise outside. I looked out the window and I saw that there was a van going down the street, and it was going to hit Kevin, and I had to save him, he had been so nice to me, hadn't objected to me staying in his house or anything. I ran out the door and jumped, and I pushed him to the sidewalk on the other side of the street. But I had forgotten about my hands, and I cut his face. The neighbors all gathered around and then Kim and her parents went and brought Kevin inside. Kim ran up to me and told me to run. So I ran, all the way back home. The cops chased me, and the neighbors chased me, but i made it upstairs. Kim got to me before the neighbors, she told me she had thought I was dead. But Jim had followed her, and he tried to kill me. When I finally stood up, I had no choice, or he would have killed me. I had to stab him. He fell out of the window, he was dead. I couldnt believe what I had done. I thought Kim would hate me for it, but she told me she loved me and then she left. And that was the last I heard of any of them. Sometimes I still watch them from the mountain, but I don't know what happened after I left. Did Kim tell the truth about what she and her friends did at Jim's house? I don't know. The one thing I really know is that I can never go back down there. It's too dangerous, because even if they've forgotten about me, the same thing would happen again. I just can't be with them. Because even though it was a mistake- a lot of mistakes, really- mistakes can't be ignored if they're made by a boy who has scissors for hands.   
     

    
</post>


<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay im writing again, a whole week later. vacation starts on friday, i'm DAMN happy about that. I need a solid week of sleeping until at least 10 for my brain to start functioning again. The bad news is, report cards come out on friday, and a lot of my grades suck. I brought up my English and Science grades, and my art grades are always pretty decent, but geography, math, and french i have all Ds and possibly Fs. YIKES!!!! NOT GOOD!!!! I'm gonna do some h/w now- i'm gonna start typing up my notes every night and putting them in my notebooks, thats how much i wanna pass all my classes next quarter. If i dont, then i'm grounded for the freakin SUMMER!!!   Playlist-  Rancid- Indestructable 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OOOkkk now. Don't ask about my Easter, it was just like any other, except for the lack of eggs, but thats ok i'm trying to cut back on dairy products anyway. Hm... what else do i have to tell you? Not much. I'm just barely passing most of my classes, which is NOT GOOD, i have to get all A's and B's if i want to keep babysitting, and the quarter ends TOMMORROW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Anyway, I have a shitload of homework, i'll write again later.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the good news- i saw the video for "Unholy Confessions" by Avenged Sevenfold. Go here ---> http://www.avengedsevenfold.com to download it. \m/   the bad news- the guy i like has a g/f blablabla im pissed but she's sort of a friend so i cant hold a grudge against her.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok im back and my brains are considerably more stable. I went to my dad's friends b-day party last night, played a reall bass guitar for the 1st time in my life. It was so cool, i seriously think it's THE instrument for me. I always felt incredibly awkward holding a saxaphone or a clarinet, or sitting down at a piano- the other instruments i've tried- but i seriously felt normal holding a bass.  soundtrack- lostprophets  mood- decaffinated- in serious need of starbucks- but otherwise quite alright  ok i'm gonna go d/l the new vid for unholy confessions by a7x, i'll post again when i'm done watching it
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      how stupid am i that i didnt realize that i already posted about the CAPT? well, that just goes to show you how much it mashed my brain. Seriously, when i shake my head, my brains move around and they sound  like when you shake up a bottle of soda before you give it to someone you hate. Ok maybe i exagerated a little  soundrack- the misfits mood- really stupid
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok yeah ive decided that this is just my musings/ thoughts, and some lyrics. so now i'm gonna muse and think.  Finished CAPT testing yesterday. For those of you who are lucky enough to not know what the CAPT is, it's the most dispicable of standardized tests from Satan's whorish inner circle of hell  gotta go, i'll muse/think more later.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, first post. There's a REASON that my name here is XangryXyoungXpoorX, and that the adress is republicansXbeware. I AM A LIBERAL. I AM AN ANTI-FLAG FAN. I AM ALSO A VEGITARIAN ATTEMPTING TO GO VEGAN. if you have a problem w/ that, then go away.  If, for some reason, you wanna talk to me....  email- xXbloodyXvalentineXx@yahoo.com AIM- X2ndXheartbeatX MSN- cashdogg213@hotmail.com yahoo- xXbloodyXvalentineXx  First introductions. Hi, I'm Caitlin. Nice to meet you. Or maybe it's not, i dont know yet. If you're an a**hole, then I'm fairly sure it's not nice to meet you. I'm 14, and I'm a freshman in high school. It's not fun.  Now I'm probably gonna use this blog mostly for lyrics/ essays/ stories, but i'll include any thoughts about my day if i feel like it/  -------------------------------------------------------------------------------  Current Soundtrack- Ozzy Osbourne \m/ Current Mood- Tired and bitchy, so WATCH OUT   Ok so CAPT IS FINALLY OVER!!! I'm so happy it's not even funny. (For those of you that don't know, CAPT is the standardized test from Satan's whore-ish inner circle of hell.  Not fun at all, I can assure you.) I have to go to the library tomorrow to work on a project. fu-u-u-u-un. I don't wanna make my partner do all the work, but it will NOT BE HAPPY, cause i hate school and i hate the library.  Second order of business- political talks. BLAH!     If I Were the President    1. Universal Health Care  I believe that if someone is SICK, they deserve to get BETTER. I find it amazing that anyone could seriously feel otherwise. It's sickening that someone could let a poor man die of cancer because he can't afford insurance while they take advantage of theirs on expensive stress management, etc. They need therapy, but thats definetly not the kind they need. I wouldnt be able to sleep at night if i had that on my mind.  2. Make Adoption Cheaper and Easier  There is a huge population crisis in the world, and it makes no sense to have more children while so many are homeless and without families. But many people don't adopt because it's too expensive, or difficult. I'm not saying it would be easy, but I'd at least try.  3. Try to get Minority Religions to be More Acceptable  Not by changing the religion, by changing peoples opinions of it. Religions such as Wicca and Voodoo are looked down upon and labeled Satanic, merely because they are misunderstood. In truth, Wiccans (witches) believe that everything you do comes back to you 3-fold in this life. In fact, "An it harm none, do what ye will" is a strong belief of wiccans- translated into modern american english, it means "do what you want as long as you don't hurt anyone." That sounds nothing like Satanism to me.  4. Redistribution of the Wealth Yes, i know this is a touchy subject. But i believe that the people who have unreasonably huge amounts of money should give the unreasonable portion to the people who have unreasonably small amounts of money. Everyone should have at least a certain amount of money. I'm not saying that freeloaders deserve the same as hard-working people, but they should get something. If anything, maybe things like wellfare could be dealt with on a case-by-case basis.  5.  Demilitarism I dont know if i spelled that right, but i want to make the military less glorified. There are kids who joined the military to go to college, and now they've lost their lives fighting our beloved POTUS's illegal war in Iraq. and that's pronounced "a rock", by the way. Anyway, ideally, each country should have a defense corps incase of terrorism, and nothing more. No warsif there's no armies to fight them.  Thats all i want to put now.  Later Daze. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a ramble that i wrote.  "Bush in 200 Words"  Mr. Bush, it’s easy for you to say “bring it on” while you’re sitting safe and cozy in the White House. You’re not in Iraq doing the fighting, you’re not facing people who behead people as a part of their culture and who would gladly blow your head off. You’re not the one they’re bringing it on to. The people in Iraq right now, fighting for your reputation, for your oil are the ones that they will “bring it on” to. And you say BRING IT ON?  Yeah right. They won’t be bringing it on to you, but we will. Oh, you better believe it, we will, Mr. Bush. Because we know. We know you don’t give a flying fuck about Iraqi blood, we know you don’t care about the troops, because if you did, you’d get them the fuck out of there, and we know you use the “terrorist threat” and 9/11 as a screen to keep people from seeing how you’re ass-fucking the American public, and believe me, we won’t be forgiving you for it, and we certainly won’t be forgetting. So when you say bring it on, you’re not only talking to them. You’re talking to us. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so now i shall present thee with a ramble on....  ANIMAL RIGHTS!!!!!  I am a vegetarian trying to go vegan, and i believe that it is completely unnacceptable (sp?) to consume any living creature. Now, for people in 3rd world countries, who would die if they didn't eat meat and have no other way to get food, i don't like it, but they have to. But I don't live in a 3rd world country, and chances are, if you're reading this, then you don't either because you'd need a computer. I have the option to abstain from eating dead animals, and i am using that option, and so should you. These animals are brutally slaughtered, and you don't need that to happen. That's blood on your hands every time you eat a hamburger or a chicken sandwich. Think about that.   So, in closing, i shall present thee with a link to an interview that  urlLink  Peta2   did with Quinn from The Used.  urlLink  click here   for the interview.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gay Marriage  	I’ve seen arguments on both sides of the Gay Marriage debate. I’ve seen people who support the amendment to the Constitution, waving around their bibles and their “God Abhors You” signs. I’ve seen people that support gay marriage with their rainbow t-shirts and protest signs as well. And I still go with what my gut told me when first asked whether I supported Gay Marriage or not. Yes.  I support the prospect of a man and a man or a woman and a woman getting married. I do not believe that being gay is evil, or a sin, or that God hates gay people. I believe that marriage is love, not the union of a man and a woman.   As I said in my last entry, the Bible has been written by man, and translated many times over, also by man. According to Christianity, man is imperfect, correct? So who’s to say that some parts of the Bible are inaccurate? Who’s to say that those who wrote the passages in the Bible that are homophobic didn’t slant the information, or that the people who translated the Bible were, somewhere along the line of translations that have been done, incorrect? Or- here’s a silly idea, but it’s possible- maybe you’ve heard that, since the bible has been translated so many times, there are potentially hidden messages written acrostically or diagonally that are missed because the meaning isn’t the same in other languages as it was in the original text of the Bible? Well, what if there was something like that in the homophobic parts of the Bible that read “This is total Bullshit, please disregard it”? I’d laugh myself stupid if that was the case.’’  Also, has anyone ever heard of a little thing called SEPARATION OF THE CHURCH AND STATE??? People shouldn’t be letting their religion get in the way of politics. If there were to be a constitutional amendment banning gay marriage, then the constitution would be contradicting itself.  All in all- marriage is whatever a couple wants it to be, and no one should be telling people that God abhors them because they’re different.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey and i'm back again after quite a long period of silence. what have i to tell you before i write my next ramble? Well, i don't know if you listen to A7x or not, but their bass player(Johnny Christ)'s dad (or at least thats who he said he was)said thanks for saying Johnny was my favorite guy in avenged. Also, he sent me this pic of Johnny holding his nephew... very cute, but i can't post it because i dont know how! 'Twas adorable, though.   Ok, now onto my long-awaited ramble.   Topic= Religion First of all, to the best of my knowledge, religion is a way of worshipping whatever supernatural powers you believe in. So why is it that some people believe that they have the   authority   to decide what is and isn't a religion?  Most of these people are Christians. Now, I don't want to give Christians a bad name, there are plenty of open-minded Christians who are nice people who worship their God the way they choose to. Heck, to a certain extent, I'm a Christian, because I believe in Jesus Christ being the son of God. But it is true that a lot of the people i know of who have scoffed at other religions are Christians, the kind of Christians that always seem to think that they are right and anyone who believes differently is wrong. And the religion they seem to scoff at the most is Wicca.   The most annoying part about this is that most of these  people don't know shit about Wicca. For instance, they have no idea what the Wiccan Creed is ("An it harm none, do what ye will"). And yet they insist that Wicca isn't a religion. HellO? That doesn't seem right to me.  On to the second part of my rant- this one is about being Homophobic as a part of a religion. Now, there is a verse in the bible- I honestly wish i could remember which one- that says that homosexuals are evil because they "worship the creature, not the creator". And yet it's not against Catholicism for a man to be in love with a woman, although that should probably constitute as worshipping the creature rather than the creator. I personally believe that this is just another way for the Catholic Church to justify not having sex for reasons other than reproduction. Think about it, they don't allow birth control either. It just goes along with the one rule that pretty much covers Catholicism- "if it feels good, stop". Thats what a lot of hardcore Catholics need to learn- they don't have to live in misery just to be happy in the afterlife. In closing, i also want to mention that the Bible was both written and translated many times over by humans. Now if humans are flawed, what keeps a lot of the stuff in the bible from being slanted information and mistranslations?  Mood- angry at the world Music- A Global Threat
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now for a ramble on Fred Phelps and his church.  Words cannot express how angry I am at this guy and everyone like him. I have NOTHING against Christians. I am, to a certain extent, a Christian myself. But these guys are just crazy. For instance, they are fucking homophobes, which i have absolutely zero tolerance for. Second, on their website (which happens to be UTTER BULLSHIT) they state that "The only true Nazis in this world are fags." Excuse moi, but how are homosexuals nazis? Most of them don't try to force homosexuality upon other people, they just want to be accepted. Also, when Hitler discovered that his right hand man was homosexual, he immediately shot him point blank. Nazis' hate homosexuals.   Also they say "Thank God for 9/11". The part about the homophobia made me feel angry, made me feel like throwing up, but this, in addition to their disgusting and hateful message, made me come close to tears. My cousin would have DIED in that attack if he didn't call in sick with a sore throat. He would have fucking died along with 3,000 other innocent people, and they're saying THANK GOD FOR 9/11???? These guys (and girls) are fucking sickos. They're one of the things that makes me truly angry. The kind of anger that biulds up in my heart and makes me see red. The kind of anger that makes me want to scream and cry. The kind of anger that hurts so much that I have no idea what to do about it. The anger that inspires me to write rambles such as this one. You know, I might go to Hell (if there is a hell), as much as i pray that i don't. But when 666 Satan Lane is occupied by this Fred Phelps and his fucked up buddies, they'll realize what I've known all along: they're wrong. Period.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You know, the other day I was listening to "911 for Peace" by Anti-Flag and I almost cried. Usually I don't cry when I'm listening to music, especially political music, but I felt like crying my little eyeballs out. And it took me a second to figure out why, but then it dawned on me. I was scared.   I was scared because I was suddenly fully aware that I don't have a lot of control over what the government does. I'm just a kid, and Dubya has the power to blow us up. He's a fucking moron, and usually I laugh at morons. But this moron has an immense amount of POWER over so many lives, including mine, to a certain extent. And I'm scared. What if he get's elected this year, or, like in 2000, he's appointed by the Supreme Court again? Then there's another four years of being scared shitless. Another four years of this moron destroying Iraq, another four years of the PATRIOT Act making it possible for him and&nbsp;his little minions&nbsp;to tap my conversations and take things out of context, possibly making me seem like a terrorist, another four years of no (rich) child being left behind. That's why I was scared.   But I've been doing a lot of thinking since them. I'm still scared, no doubt, but I have some hope. Alone, I have very little power over the government. But there are others who agree with me, and if I contribute to their cause, then maybe we can make a difference. But that means I can't be the little 14 year old who types in a blog that no one will ever see. I have to really get out and try to make a difference. I have to team up with people who agree with me on these issues, I have to protest, whether through letter writing or through hitting the streets (although I live in a hick town, so it's not very likely that I'll be able to get to any protests until I have my driver's liscense). I have to spread information, get into debates with people, and practice writing this shit and talking about it so I don't seem like a complete moron. Because alone I don't make much of a difference, but, as those Anti-Flag dudes say, "The people, united, will never be defeated."    That's my ramble for today folks. If I'm feeling particularly angry later,&nbsp; maybe I'll write another.    &nbsp;  Soundtrack- From Autumn to Ashes, Senses Fail, Poison the Well  
     

    
</post>


<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to tell you about my science class today!! Now, keep in mind, this is a class full of 9th graders, and we are known to have a habit of reacting to the most perverse meaning of a phrase, and also to be victims of contageous(sp?) giggling- i.e. if everyone's laughing about something and we only think it's a little bit funny, its really hard for us to not laugh. At least thats how a lot of us are. Anyway, in our unit on simple machines, our teacher- let's just call him Mr. Arbuckle (!!garfield!! lol) in order to protect his identity- was giving us notes on levers, pulleys, wedges, inclined planes, and screws. Well, we get to the notes on screws and he starts talking about a company he once worked for who put together dashboards for hummers for military use, and they kept falling apart. He goes on and on about it- i was only 1/2 paying attention- and says something about how the screw that held the speedometer in place was held in place by a nut. Now a few of the more immature of us (not including me) started giggling a bit at the fact that he had said "screw" and "nut" in the same scentence. Now i have to interrupt myself to tell you that these 3 guys in the class have a habit of saying "lubrication!" and "power lube!" randomly in the middle of class in a mock deep voice that immitates one of the geography teachers. Well, Mr. Arbuckle says "Now, the people who were manufacturing the screws and the nuts were putting this lubrication on the nuts and screws..." and at this point virtually everyone in the class- including me- starts giggling, because he said screw, nuts, and lubrication all in the same scentence. He gives us a wierd look but keeps on talking, and all of a sudden a look of "i suddenly realized what they're laughing about and its really perverse!" crosses his face and he goes "Aw, JESUS!" and everyone starts cracking up, it was great. He tries to gain control over the class and goes ", LISTEN! LISTEN! Lubrication is used for things other than sex!" It made my day, it was sooo funny.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok 2 posts in one day, but i dont give a shit. I just got home about 1/2 an hour ago from babysitting. Now, i was home for 5 minutes, and i put on a song by Much the Same (don't know if you've heard of them, but they're a really great band). Anyway, i get to the chorus of the song (it's called "Wish") and my dad walks in and says "Turn that off, I don't want to hear that PUNK ROCK MUSIC in my house." Well, isn't that a nice greeting! Haven't seen the guy all fucking day, and the first thing he does is yell at me about wanting to listen to some music and vent a little about my day. Maybe if he let me listen to the stereo in my basement during the week, i could go down there and listen to music and not disturb him, but nooooo. Then i go to the living room to watch the "Rock Against Bush Vol. 1" Bonus DVD, and he comes in to start yelling at my brother because apparently he's not supposed to be watching tv anymore. For one, i was watching it, not him. Second, I was home for about 15 minutes and all he's done is yell, yell, yell. Then he comes back a few minutes later, and starts lecturing us about how hard he's trying to run a household, make a living, etc. as if we don't try hard with what we have to do! When the mother of the kid i babysit for was all depressed and fucked up, i worked until 9 every night, while she was sick and right in the next room, and her 11-year-old (in my opinion, that's old enough to be home alone) and i had to make her food, keep the house clean, etc. Now, I never complained once to my dad about that, not once. He doesn't even know about it, as far as i know. But he has to lecture us every time he gets stressed, and take whatever it is thats pissing him off out on us for not doing our chores and wanting to have fun? Last time i checked, most kids ignore their chores and have fun instead, so why does dad feel obligated to make me feel like the worst person alive and like all his problems are my fault? Then he makes my dreams- everything i want to do with my life- of being a bass guitarist, singer, and lyricist in a band, seem like worthless bullshit. He tells me acedemics are my main priority now, and then puts all the chores he tells me to do ahead of that- maybe its because he knows that if i get all A's and B's this quarter he has to get me a bass guitar, which he promised to do, and he's trying to keep me from succeeding. You know, if he is doing that, then it's probably subconcious, and he doesnt even know he's doing it.   Anyway, back to that song I mentioned: "Wish" by Much the Same- it fits the theme of this entry pretty well, so here it is.    WISH Well You're in control and I know it 'cause I'm miserable again -- I don't understand how any of this makes me a better man -- You know I always run to You for some help with my life -- You know I always come to You for a little wise advice -- And all I get is pain -- Okay, so I'm exaggerating, I'm just saying that's how it seems to me -- If all good things come to an end, then what about the bad? -- Am I cursed to never see the fruits of the life I wish I had? -- And can I try, one more time, to be pleasing to You? -- My futile efforts never seem to make my wish come true -- What can I do? -- I'll follow through with all these claims I never cease to make -- A promise to myself is one I promise to break -- But when I have You by my side then I can do what's right -- I'll become the co-pilot and You control this flight -- Then everything will be alright -- This song's for me -- A reminder of how I intend my life to be -- Every word I sing -- Is an anthem against my own hypocrisy -- Let me be free     urlLink  click here   to check out Much the Same, and  urlLink  here   to check out the record company they're signed to and some of the other bands signed to the same company (A-F Records)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... but i never got around to it. Mostly, i guess i didn't know what words to put it in. But my english teacher read this poem to us today, called "The Dash" and doggoneit! (the southerner in me, lol) it gone done inspired me to write about last thursday.  So there was a mock car crash at my school, right? of course right. And afterwards we went to the gym to hear these people talk- all of them had sons (one was a friend of one of the sons) who died in drunk driving accidents all within 11 days and 25 miles of eachother. My aunt Maura died in a drunk driving crash also. I felt like such a mean person for only crying for about 5 minutes total when the moms were talking. I had that crying feeling in my stomach, but not many tears. Anyways, here's that poem that my teacher read. It seems insanely cheesy, but it's really true.    "The Dash" I read of a man who stood to speak at the funeral of a friend. He referred to the dates on her tombstone from the beginning...to the end.  He noted that first came the date of her birth and spoke of the following date with tears, but he said what mattered most of all was the dash between those years.  For that dash represents all the time that she spent alive on earth... and now only those who loved her know what that little line is worth.  For it matters not, how much we own; the cars....the house...the cash. What matters is how we live and love and how we spend our dash.  So think about this long and hard... are there things you'd like to change? For you never know how much time is left. (You could be at "dash mid-range.")  If we could just slow down enough to consider what's true and real, and always try to understand the way other people feel.  And be less quick to anger, and show appreciation more and love the people in our lives like we've never loved before.  If we treat each other with respect, and more often wear a smile... remembering that this special dash might only last a little while.  So, when your eulogy's being read with your life's actions to rehash... would you be proud of the things they say about how you spend your dash?    
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so fucking stressed out here. I decided to do this Model UN thing for school, right? Originally, I was working with 2 friends and I was representing Germany, right? Well, now I’m working alone on Nigeria. The crisis is the Question of Palestine, which Nigeria doesn’t really have an opinion on. I decided to go with Palestine, because3 50% of Nigeria is Muslim, and they have some similarities- i.e., both were taken over by the British and removed from parts of their homeland. But I’m never, ever doing anything like this again, it’s wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-ay too stressful. Did i mention that the conference is going to be one day this week, and they don't tell us what day exactly? arrrgh!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in fact, they don't just own, they Pwn, with a capital "P" (check out the avenged message board if you don't know what i'm talking about, http://www.avengedsevenfold.com, then click the "board" link.  anyway, here's a link to" an interview they had w/ Quinn from The Used, a favorite band of mine...  urlLink  click here     anyway, go veg*n... (vegetarian or vegan, for those of you that don't know what veg*n means) and watch that interview.   So what else have i to tell you? I have piano lessons in about an hour. Listening to Rock Against Bush Vol. 1.  Now I must bid you adieu and goodbye, as i must go post the link to the interview elsewhere.    mood- juuuust peachy music- Rock Against Bush Vol. 1- Currently "To the World" by Strike Anywhere
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, today was a pretty normal monday. Guy i   Other than that, not much i have to tell you. Got a new project in French, have done almost none of my homework tonight. Goodnight, i'll post again some other time.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually, school got out yesterday, but i was too lazy to post. Now I'm sitting here being bored, and i thought "HOLY SHIT I HAVENT UPDATED MY BLOGS!!!" So now I am. I  got these new sunglasses yesterday- they have clear lenses, but there's UV protection-  urlLink click here  for a pic if you still don't get it. Anyway, because of these glasses, my dad has decided that i am having an identity crisis and believe that i am Buddy Holly. Haha now that Weezer song comes to mind: "Oh wee-oo I look just like Buddy Holly..." etc, etc. Damn I have a habit of rambling about really stupid shit. I really gotta stop that. So what else has happened since yesterday... I decided to try to pierce my own ears. Um, no. Not fun. I succeeded only in creating a small indent in my right ear and causing a lot of unnescessary pain in my ear. I really should really get someone else to pierce them for me, but i don't want to go to that stupid Claire's place (i swear its so stupid in there i can't BREATHE) and my parents would never take me to Flat's Tattooing and Piercing. Fuck. I wish i had friends who knew how to do piercings. Fuck fuckety fuck fuck fuck. Anyway, Now ER is on tv, and I'm still bored. Goodbye.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting here at my mom's computer, drinking blackberry flavored carbonated water, and half-watching "Mucha Lucha" (which my brothers are currently watching.) And i have pretty much nothing to write about. I'm bored, I'm tired, I hate school, I'm glad I don't have piano lessons tomorrow, because i haven't practiced, I miss my dog (she's at my house now) I miss my other dog (he's at my house too). I GOT MY A7x BOARD MEMBERS DVD TODAY AND THAT MAKES ME VERY VERY VERY VERY VERY VERY HAPPY BECAUSE IT'S AWESOME!!! I like Shadows' voice- his singing voice is amazing, but i mean his talking voice. It's kind of stressed sounding, you can tell he puts a lot into his voice when he's singing/screaming. I wish Zacky and Johnny got to talk more though. :'( 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...is watching me type right now, so i'm not going to post much. just that i'm trying to figure out this new Hello thing by Picasa to post pictures in my blogs. so my next few posts might get royally fucked up by some random pictures. peace out. btw my name on that Hello thing is:  veggieXcore  seeing as i'm a vegetarian going vegan.   peace out again. for real this time.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So guess what I'm sitting here being really bored, contemplating the idea of starting a new website on animal rights or polotics, so i decided to post a few of my ideas in here in case i forget.  1. An animal rights website that has different sections about the various topics that come up in discussions on animal rights: the meat industry, hunting and fishing, animal testing, circuses, spaying and neutering, what to eat and wear, etc. and a section with links to various interviews (text audio and video) with different bands, actors, etc. that are involved with animal rights  2. A links database on various activism things- animal rights, anti-war, anti-police brutality, anti-racism, anti-sweatshop, etc. etc. this would be easier to maintain, because i already have one website that I'm working on ( urlLink http://www.myeyelinertears.xnapster.com  , it's a Good Chalrotte fansite)and I don't really feel like working on 2 extensive websites alone, especially once school starts.  But enough about that, it's time to talk about MY NEW BASS GUITAR!! That's right folks, I finally got it! It needs some work, and a few new things like a gig bag and a strap, but I'm so glad i finally have it! It's a left handed, pale yellow fender prescision (sp?) bass. YAY!!!!  Anyway, before i go i will leave you with 2 video interviews that Anti-Flag did with Peta2. The first one is their singer, Justin Sane, talking about the alley cat he recently adopted (or at least it was recently when the interview was done i don't know exactly when that was) and the 2nd is the whole band.   urlLink  Justin alone     urlLink  The Whole Band    Peace, Love, Unity, Caitlin  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>