<Blog>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you suppose I can put pictures on here?  I've never really looked at all my options, I still don't know if other people can publish on this site, but seeing all the other people who have posted, I"m gonna have to say 'no'.  What did I do today?  I'll tell me, and you perhaps.  I went to Selah for a double header against the 9-0 team.  Let's just say, it wasn't pretty.  We got up early, and at one point, had a 6-2 lead.  Then, out of nowhere, all went to hell.  Errors, walks, extra base hits, you name it, it all happened to us.  We ended up losing 6-16.  Second game: we get up 3-0 in the first, only to fall apart again, losing 6-13.  Again, the whole universe seemed to be Selah fans, at one point, there was a sharply hit grounder down the first base line.  Nik was behind the ball and ready to field it, but in a freak coincidence, it hit the base and popped way over his head.  But all's well that ends well, and in this case, it ended with me going to Minors.  I got the Jerry special (Bacon burger, medium fries and a medium Oreo shake).  Then I went home.  I didn't get a chance to call megan :-(sorry)-:  But tomorrow, wait, today is Easter and I'm going to sleep.    Here comes peter cottontail, hopping down the bunny trail, hippitty hoppitty Easter's on it's way... 
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it's been a few days.  Ashlee, I'm very sorry for the inconvenience that this has caused you.  But I'm back, and a lot has happened.  Wednesday, I went down to the DMV (aka: hell, but with a longer waiting line).  I took my driving test and passed with a 92.  I ended up taking it with a really nice lady.  She marked me off four points for parallel parking and another four for backing around a corner.  Oh well, I did everything else perfectly (Except I almost ran a red light, but I don't think she noticed).  So then they gave me a pamphlet about all the rules of the intermediate license, which I threw away on my way to pick up Tricia.  I went to Nates, where I learned that I don't know how to throw a football anymore!  Then some people came over (9 to be exact) and consumed 3 large pizzas!  By the way, Derek eats like a madman.  That day, I saw him inhale 3 hamburgers, some cake, and three slices of pizza within a 5 hour period.  I guess all that soccer really makes him hungry.  And all that food is put to good use.  I went to the soccer game on Thursday (3-0 over Sunnyside) and I was very impressed by Dereks perfomance.  He plays middle defense, so he doesn't do much scoring, but wow, he's good.  Thursday night was uneventful, but today was crazy.  I woke up at 9:15 to go to baseball, and I was there until 12:30.  At which point, I went out to try to get people to give me money for baseball (Highly unsuccessful).  I was out doing that until 3:00, when I had to go talk to our insurance provider.  He gave me a talk that lasted an hour, but I can sum it up for you in a few words: Screw up and it will cost you.  Then I got to go to Zanes for some BP.  Good times.  Then my dad and I went to Garts where he bought me a very nice bat.  Oh, how I love spring break.
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ouch.  Today we were delt a 9-15 loss to West Valley.  In the beginning we gave up 7 un-answered runs, but by the top of the 4th, we had closed the gap to 5-7.  Bottom of the 4th, we give up four walks in a row to start the inning.  We ended up giving up 7 in that inning.  Then, I expected the 10 run rule to take place the next inning (if one team is losing by 10 or more runs in the 5th inning or later, the game is over).  But we teetered on the edge for long enough to finish the game, which is good and bad.  On one hand we saved face, on the other hand, I missed my date with Megan.  Then I went out for pizza and when I got home it was too late to call :-(sorry Megan)-:  So there goes my day.  Tomorrow might be a big day for me, but I won't tell you why until tomorrow, maybe not even then.  Enough baseball.  Can other people post on this site?  Hmmmm... I bet that there is somewhere where I can find that out.  So tomorrow (Wednesday, April 7) there will be a movie and pizza at my house, talk to me and I will tell you the details (If you are reading  this, you're most likely invited).  What pissed me off today?  Not a whole lot.  That was a good day, now I'm going to cap it off with some good sleep.
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude.  Not too much to type here.  You know, more people drink than I previously thought.  Not that I was naive before, it's just..Wow.  Oh well.  It's like I've never really ever felt a really strong temptation to drink.  I hope it stays that way.  By the way, for all those concerned, I probably will not be going to the air force academy as once planned.  Why? Cadets in a military academy get two (2 (II)) weeks off a year, TWO (2 (II))!  OUT!  OUT DAMN POP UP!  It's a constant struggle with those pop-ups, because if I get too many, my computer freezes, and the pop-ups have won.  It's like they all get together, in football huddle fashion, and say, (A porn advertisement): "Ok, I'm going to pop up, and as soon as he tries to x me out, Webcam will pop up, so he accidentally clicks on his advertisement.  In the mean time, Erectile Disfuntion and Home Loan will pop under.  Ready? BREAK!"  They're out to get me I swear.  I have heard the new Maroon 5 son 'This Love' about a million times today.  Finally, I had to download it, so I will NEVER not be listening to it, and thus, I will complete the process of driving myself crazy!  HAHAHAHAHAHA!  Although, judging by this little rant of mine, it won't be a very long drive.
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Coming to a Road Near You I am shocked I began this paper with an intention to whine and complain about how ‘Sport Utility Vehicles’ or SUVs were pushy, overgrown minivans that were filling up parking spaces two at a time.  I could have gone on for hours on end talking about my hatred for the SUV, starting with their monumental magnitude and ending with their sonorous sound, stopping only briefly on their relentless gas guzzling.  Then, in the middle of looking for a few small facts to fill the holes in my essay, I came across some starling statistics. SUVs have an unquenchable thirst for petroleum.  SUVs are allowed to operate at 20.7 mpg.  That’s 6.8 mpg worse than standard passenger cars are forced to maintain.  The bigger SUVs, weighing over 8,500 lbs, are completely exempt from even the most lax of fuel efficiency standards. Scientists estimate that it took some 200 million years to form all of the oil beneath the surface of the earth, but only 200 years to for today’s machines to drain half that supply. At the current rate of fuel consumption, the conventional oil that remains will be used up in about 40 years.  Of course that would not be the end of fossil fuels all together.  There are vast amounts of unconventional fossil fuels, such as coal, shale oil, tar sands, and natural gas trapped in ice beneath the ocean, but with current technology, it would cost more to retrieve it than it is worth.  	Of course, not everyone is concerned with the environment, but most people are concerned with money.  Assuming that you drive 15,000 miles annually and fuel costs $1.50/gal, a 40 mpg vehicle will cost you $562 less each year in gasoline than the owner of a 20 mpg vehicle.  If you own your car for 4 years, the 40-mpg vehicle will save $2250.  In these times of fuel crisis and economic recession, it really doesn’t make sense to be driving an SUV.  The question then becomes which is more important to you?  Your environment?  Your money?  Your Children?  Or having the biggest car on the block.  
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      “Spong Monkeys” Are Not the Worst Problem on TV  Ever since I can remember, there has been as much hype about commercials that air during the Super Bowl as the game itself.  Companies pay millions upon millions of dollars so that they might grab or attention for 15 seconds of time.  So naturally, most people are pleased with the quality of the commercials.  That is, of course, with the exception of a couple of “Spong Monkeys” that appeared this year.     You may have seen the Quiznos Subs commercials featuring a couple of frightening looking rodents in funny hats singing off key.  I did, and I instantly assumed the fetal position on the ground and I shook uncontrollably for minutes on end.  I loved the little “Spong Monkeys” and their silly song they sing.  I actually memorized both versions of the commercial and can sing them verbatim on command.  My friends, for the most part, loved it too.  We were all singing and laughing and growing a bit hungry for a submarine sandwich.  Along with the commercial being hysterically funny, I think it is a brilliant marketing ploy based on four principle facts: 1.	The “Spong Monkeys” are ridiculous. 2.	Teenage boys love that kind of ridiculous humor. 3.	Teenage boys are responsible for 90% of the food consumption in the world.  In addition, even the people who hate the ad can’t stop thinking about it.  Now, anyone who thinks of submarine sandwiches automatically thinks of that annoying commercial and thus, Quiznos Subs.  Which brings me to my next point.  People are very angry about this whole thing.  They want it off the air and fast.  My question to them is, why, in a world with “Bob the Caterpillar,” the Arbys “Oven mitt” and “Check into Cash” did you choose to attack the innocent little rodents with such violent tenacity that made headlines?  Are there not more violating characters on commercials?  Does it not make you cringe when the toilet paper bear wipes his rear?  Or when the Dulcolax Stool Softener makes that lady so happy?  If nothing else, wouldn’t you like to see fewer commercials about erectile dysfunction?  I believe that many people think the way that I do about commercials today.  It just so happens that the little monkeys were the straw the broke the camel’s back, the victim of an advertising witch-hunt.  So take away one of my favorite commercials of all time if you must, but next time you’re watching TV, just remember to think about what you have just killed.  It is the laughter that used to reside in my heart. 
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow.  First entry.  So.  Where do we begin.  My ACL is still weak form the January surgery, but the doctor say of all the patients he's ever treated for torn ACL's, only one other has recovered as fast as I have.  Which is very good, because I'm sick and tired of not playing baseball.  He also says I'm good to go as soon as mid June.  So it'll all work out in the end.  In the mean time, I'm still working hard at my recovery, and praying hard for the patience to continue.  Our baseball season had just officially gotten underway with a pair of wins today in our doubleheader against Ellensburg.  We won the first 4-2 and the second 6-5.  That puts us atop the mid-valley league standings for now :-P.  For those who don't know, I've been dating the lovely Megan now for a little less than 6 months!  That makes my longest relationship ever.  I am very excited about the new Weezer DVD "Video Capture Device" and the new tribute to the blue album.  They both came out March 25, but I've been too lazy to get them so far.  What else can I possibly talk about here... Oh yeah... SPRING BREAK!!!!!  Too bad two of my best friends are out of town, not to mention the only two with licenses.  Oh, well, I shall survive to see another day.
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been having a great deal of fun at ebaumsworld.com and g-shack.com as well as my friend James' site whiiif.com and I highly reccomend checking the out for yourselves.  It's just a way for me to waste time wile not doing homework, but it's gotten me to thinking of starting a real website.  And that has got me to thinking, how do I go about getting a good URL?  Any ideas?  Write me at Fredchicken101@hotmail.com or on AIM at Weezfan12988.
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't feel like writing, but what else is new?  So  here are some "The Smiths" quotes that made me cripplingly idealistic about love.   "And if a double decker,crashes into us, to die by you side, is such a heavenly way to die, and if a ten ton truck, kills the both of us, to die by your side, well, the pleasure, the privlige, is mine"  "Send me your pillow, the one that you dream on, and I'll send you mine."  "And though I walk home alone, I might walk hom alone, but my faith in love is still devout"    And some that made me cripplingly pessimistic about love.    "If you're wondering why, all the love that you long for eludes you, and people are rude and cruel to you, I'll tell you why, you just haven't earned it yet baby"  "Last night I dreamt, that somebody loved me.  No hope no harm, just another false alarm"  You gave me somthing that I won't forget too soon, but I can't believe that you'd ever care, and this is why you'll never care."   "Give in to lust, give in to lust, heaven knows we'll soon be dust."  "Say goodbye, please stay with your own kind, and I'll stay with mine."  "This world is full, so full of crashing bores, and I must be one, because no one ever turns to me to say, 'Take me in your arms and love me.'"    Taken from Spin Magazine  
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sooooooooooooo long since that last post.  Over a month.  I'm sure a lot of people have simply stopped coming to this site thinking that I would never update.  Whatever.  Our Baseball season ended tragicly, losing 11-0 to West Valley in the opening round.  Oh well.  Flames baseball is fast approaching and I will finally be able to play!  June 1st should be about the time that my doctor says that I'm ready to go.  I'm still dating Megan (nut-meg).  Over 7 months.  Horray for us!  Weezer reportedly just wrapped up recording for their newest album.  I will cry with delight when it is released.  Right now I'm taking a break from homework, and I need to get back to it.  It may be another month, but whatever.
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       AT THE BEACH 18th-22nd    LOVE YOU NUTMEG   
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Making me Smile Today  She's coming home.  Tonight.  There was a rumor that she was already in town, and I got a mysterious call on my cell phone.  It showed up on the caller ID as "Unknown" which is how Megans number shows up.   Jerry Fact  I hate the sound of fingernails scratching on a chalkboard.  I think everybody hates that noise, but whenever I think about it, my whole body tenses up and I can feel the vibration of the chalkboard on my fingernails.  This paragraph has taken me ten minutes to write because I can't get that stupid noise out of my head.   Making my smile about the Jerry Fact  Nothing makes me smile about the Jerry fact.   Currently listening to  Ben Folds Five, "Still Fighting it"   Quote  "Man is free at the moment he wishes to be"          -Voltaire
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't post yesterday and I apologize to all of my one readers.  In the words of the late Jonathan Larson, "I'm trying, I'm not lying, no one's perfect I've got baggage."  I really did try to post, in fact I had written a whole post, and then my computer decided that It wanted to go to sleep, so I followed it's example.  I'm going to try to recreate yesterday's post right now.   Revelation of the Day  I told my friend to go to my site yesterday, he then proceeded to read it aloud to me.  As he read it, I realized just how negative this site is.  So from now on, instead of "Pissing me off today" it's going to be...   Making me Smile Today  She misses me.  She told me so.   Jerry Fact  Weezer is my favorite band of all time.  I think everyone who knows me could tell you that.  What most people don't know is that when I bought my first Weezer CD, I knew their music about as well as Jessica Simpson knows tuna.   Making me Smile About the Jerry Fact  Weezer is, as I said, my favorite band.  I listen to them all of the time and I never get tired of them.  It think it's really cool that I just happened to see the CD and give it a try.  It was the best $15 I've ever spent.   Currently listening to  Pink Floyd "Wish You were Here"   Quote  If there ever comes a day When we can't be together, keep me in your heart, I'll stay there forever.        -Winnie the Pooh
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Pissing me off today  I got a comment on yesterday's post.  That Doesn't piss me off.  What pisses me off is that it was the first comment I've ever received from anyone other than myself.  COMMENT PEOPLE.  Tell me how much you love me, tell me how much you hate me,  tell me anything.  JUST SAY SOMETHING.  (Andrea, thank you for your comment, It made me feel better about this whole situation.)   Jerry Fact  I've never had a job other than paper boy and mowing lawns.  Every time I have to write a resume for school or whatever, I write down that I was an "Independent Landscaper" and a "Tri-city Herald Product distributor."  But now I need to make some money, so I went around today and picked up applications for Gart Sports and Big 5 Sports.   Pissing me off about the Jerry Fact  I don't even know if the will hire me because I can only work for about a month.   Currently listening to  Live with Regis and Kelly    Quote  "The one constant through all the years has been baseball. America has rolled by like an army of steamrollers. It's been erased like a blackboard, rebuilt, and erased again. But baseball has marked the time. This field, this game, is a part of our past. It reminds us of all that once was good, and what could be again."          -James Earl Jones in Field of Dreams
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Pissing me off Today  I did really bad at baseball.  But that's pretty normal for this year I guess.   Jerry Fact  I hate second place worse than anything in the world.  I would rather be last than second.  Here is my reasoning: If you're last, then you know that you are not as good as the first place team, so you don't worry about it and you try to find other strengths.  If you're second, then  you start to think about the what-ifs.  "What if I had practiced harder?" you think, "What if this had gone our way?"  But you'll never know, because that's the end of that.  I keep all of my second place medals on my headboard right above my head as a constant reminder to go all out all of the time, because I remember how much it hurt to lose.   Pissing me off about the Jerry Fact  Every time I lay down, or roll over, those stupid metals always clang against the headboard.  The sound of my failure...   Today  Ryan, Nate and I went out to some trails in South Richland.  I made sure we got thoroughly lost.  Then we spent some time crawling around trees trying to find our way back.  It was pretty sweet.   Currently Listening To  Nothing soothes my soul like a little Frank Sinatra.   Quote  To my Nutmeg: "I miss you, and I wonder how you feel about me too.  Do you miss the way we would play?  And waste out time away?  Suddenly, we're apart and I can't see you every day, driving by you place every night, I used to feel alright, Oh Girlfriend...I'm lost without you love, oh love."            -Rivers Como (Weezer)
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Pissing me off today  Damn Blisters! I have a giant blood blister on my palm from baseball.  Very very sore.   Jerry Fact  I almost always go to Church at 5:00PM on Sundays.  I went today (Saturday) at 5:00PM (aka "The old people mass") because I'll be in Wenatchee tomorrow for a baseball game.   Pissing me off about the Jerry fact.  There was more gray hair in that building than on CBS.   Currently listening to  Nothing.  I tried to listen to Ben Folds but It was too much for my computer.   Yesterday  I went boating.  I was really bad at intertubing at first, but by the end, Poseidon himself could not have knocked me off that tube.   Quote  "It is not those who believed in me, but those who didn't that made me who I am today."                -(I forget who said it, for all I know, I made it up)
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       One more thing that pisses me off  My profile says that I was born in the year of the rabbit, but I'm a DRAGON!  A DRAGON I TELL YOU!
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to start keeping up with this again, but with a new format.  I will be writing less than before, but in a more interesting fashion.  I will make titles and under them, short explanations.  This site will serve as a vent for my anger as well as things I find very funny about my life.   Pissing me off today  My girlfriend is out of town, and my hygiene has suffered because of it.  I used to have a reason to shower and brush my teeth several times a day.  But they've both dropped to about 1 per day.   Jerry Fact  I am painting my room, so I took all of the staples out of my wall.  From just the one wall I've done so far I pulled out 87 staples.  Eighty-Seven!  Now there is so much patching compound on my wall, you'd think I was painting my wall piss-brown>   Pissing me off about the Jerry Fact  Nothing makes me sick faster than the smell of that stupid patching compound.   Currently listening to  "Army", Ben Folds Five   Quote for today  "My apartment is infested with Koala Bears.  It's the cutest infestation ever.  Way better than cockroaches.  When I turn on the light, a bunch of Koala bears scatter, and I don't want them to, you know.  It's like, "Hey fellas', hold on.  Let me hold one of you, and feed you a leaf."                                  -Mitch Hedberg
    
</post>


</Blog>