<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dang its been a while. ight well last night i spent the night with like my best friend...ummm named....Mary. We had a great time! her boyfriend and his friend came over. his friend is a freshman....in college. and yeah. mary and her bf were all makin out and the freshman...think think, named Caleb was all like kinda flirting with me. icky. the guy is sweet but he's kinda wierd. but yeah caleb and i had fun like pillow fighting and thumb wrestlin. he wants to be in the marines so he was all like "touch my muscles" or not. they left around midnight. then mary sis and her friends came home around 1, only to find me and mary raiding the pantry for pop-tarts. we finally got to bed around like 2:30. we had softball yesterday. i should have "kept my f***ing mouth shut" according to mary's sis about being catcher. i hate it, and especially during the summer doesnt look like much fun. i went to target today. i love target, but not nearly as much as WALLY WORLD. walmart rocks for real. i'm getting some of my pix developed from canada. i gotta finish my other roll. but a.g. called last night and said she's gonna send me some pix of me and her. something to look forward to. gah, i gotta go to school tomarrow and take some exams. i think i'll take 5 tomarrow and then 3 the next day. i will be so damn happy when exams are done. the whole universe is already out of school. it'll be wierd, me being the only kid at school with all the teachers. oh well. basktball starts like  sunday. i'm overly enthusiastic. probably too enthusiastic considering i'll probably just sit on the bench anyways. B said she wants me to jump ball, thatd be cool. but i just cant shoot, hopefully that will be fixed this summer. i really wanna go on vacation. i need to get away from my family. i never get along with my father but gah, i cant stand it. alrighty, i gotta go and talk to some of my peeps! love to everyone!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! back from canada! gah it was great! i love canada! i think it is so cool! i had the greatest time! like yeah, here comes the summary... friday!-@ the airport by 5 in the MORNING!! went to atlanta and then to montreal! we took a bus to ottowa. greatness! i sat by lauren on bus! the little kids went swimmin and me and mrs. cindy stayed and talked!  saturday!- we did a ton of touring stuff. we went to the Canadian Museum of Civilization...which by the way was not nearly as boring as it sounds. i found it neat! then we went to parliament! which is like the canadian white house. cran was sayin how when she was in 8th grade she went there, it was funny, she was sooo excited! we were supposed to go to the museum of nature, but we were sooo sick of museums that we skipped it! we went to the byward market instead! i got a henna tattoo. it was funny cuz mrs. jacobs and mrs. procter were the ones that told me to do it! sunday!- we did 2 church services @ rideau park church. well really 1 and a half. then we went to the tulip festival! its kinda like city fest. and we sang and then got embarrased because the group that went behind us whooped our booties. and i met a guy...in a giant lemon! he was sooo cute and we talked for a while, oh yeah, he was in the lemon cuz he was sellin lemonade. he was wearing a cowboy hat and he had really pretty teeth. so yeah we talked for a while and took pix!  monday!- we drove back to montreal. the bus was fun, sat with lauren. we went to the biodome. which was 4 different habitats. it was boring until we got the the marine thing! omga it was so cool. mrs. cindy was like dang u kno a lot about the sea creatures. then we went to st. joseph's oratory. that was huge and really pretty. it was my last performance in choir it was sad :(  tuesday!- went to the airport . i sat with mrs. cindy and a.g. it was fun. a.g. said she wanted me as her sister. but yeah it was so hard when we got back to birminghan. i had to say good-bye to people. it was really difficult to hold back tears. when i said bye to leslie @ montreal, she cried. i was so ready for choir to be done with, and as the plane landed in b'ham lauren and i didnt wanna get off, we had to say goodbye.  it was great and i love EVERYONE at choir, and i am gonna miss each and every one of yall!  i have a few quotes from hootie  Let her cry if the tears fall down like rain  Let her sing if it eases all her pain  Let her go let her walk right out on me  And if the sun comes up tomorrow  Let her be let her be.   'Cause tomorrow's just another day  And I don't believe in time   Lying down in Charleston under the Carolina sky  You see I'm tired of feeling this pain  I'm tired of living my own little lie   And now my days are short an my nights are long  I lay down with memories of you keep that keep me going on, going on  It makes me wonder as I sit and stare  Will I see your face again  Tell me, do you care   I don't want to live to see the day we say goodbye  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey! i'm gettin ready to go to lucies. well first i gotta stop by crans house to pick somethin up. so then i'll spend the night with lucie. i have to get up @ like 3 to go to canada. i'll be back tuesday night. so yeah! i'll see yall then!!! i love each and everyone one of u
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! today was up and down. i think its really amusing that cooper and mercedes are trying to find wayz to piss me off. cedes has been talking shit about me forever. and she even did it to my brother! so then after lunch i got bombarded with people asking me if cooper and i were going out last week....ummm no! oh yeah did i mention that like all of the seventh grade girls think that me and clare are gay together. ummmmm, not! i was so pissed off when i heard. so clare and i went in there and we were like "look, we're not gay"!! clare has a damn boyfriend! so yeah. i hate some of the people at our school. but after school was great fun. i went to see cran and then i went to the gym and played basketball with bp, cuse, nick, melv and some otha peoples. it was cool, except the fact that i suck! i havent played in probably 10 months. hopefully i'll get better. its just like depressing to see brit and cuse be so good. but i'm not really depressed, i just think that its cool. later 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey! yesterday was honors day. i only got 2 awards. so in my dad's eyes i'm officially a failure. so i had to go to lucies to study since she got 7 awards. (congrats to her). so yea. then i had our last choir rehearsal before canada. and i just contributed to what everyones thinking about how i'm not responsible. i forgot my head choirister ribbon/medal thingy. and i felt so bad u have no idea. and i really dont wanna screw up so crap. hilen and i got along! yayyyyy! i cant wait for canada. i was thinking this is my last weekend of choir and my last tour. i would loooove to have no fights with anyone and to have a great time....of course my head choristerness thing comes first. i really dont wanna screw up this time. i'm having a major debate about what to do with this person named "ross". yeah those of u that know me well probably know who that is....but i dont care. so yeah. btw. this website is MY JOURNAL. i write what i want, so no hard feelings ok. this is how i feel, dont like it....live with it! later! Jen
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! this site is STRICTLY for my friends. this crap isnt to be repeated got it?!!? damn, well yeah if i gave this to you, please please please dont share it with anyone or repeat anything. ok well my reasons are obvious to anyone who attends HSCHS and knows about all the drama lately. ok bye
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lets see....yesterday i talked to cindy for 45 minutes! i love her! shes the most awesome person ever! i have a huge amount of respect for her! today i talked to her again for about 10 minutes. I had a softball game today. coach made me play catcher again. mary emily pitched which was good, but she got kinda down on herself and so yeah. she pitched okay. then clare came in, but unfortunately couldnt do it and we lost...our first game...10-14. it sucked. but yeah. me and clare had to pee and it was a double header, the bathrooms were locked so we went over to kristen's house and used her bathroom! and then when we got back they were like the game's cancelled. so yeah! we went to coldstone, had some talks with the peeps bout our school. we have one more double header on thursday! and then tournaments the next week, but i'll be in CALIFORNIA!! wow! yay! i love yall 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! i love the rain! i love sitting there just watching it and thinking about stuff. i end up thinking about people i love or have loved and it makes me kinda sad though. so today i have a softball game, i dont really want to go. but i really wanna see clare and mary emily. so if it dont rain out i'll go.  oh yeah. yesterday was horrible. my mom had another seizure. it was great...not. so no driving for another 6 months, which means basketball is in jeopardy again. she's at the place right now gettin blood drawn and crap, this really isnt good at all. but yeah. and my dad was in his first car accident the other day so he's at the chiropractor right now so. another thing to add. and all this has happened since my brother has been gone, so i'm kinda scared what might happen while i'm gone. so yeah. i'm gonna go talk to my great friend brook! and then call my boyfriend...maybe! :) jk!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! wow its been a really long time...kidna. my cable went out so i didnt have the internet! but yeah. yesterday i went to Troy and met my fam from tallahassee. we gave them my brother...who will be gone for 2 weeks! yay! and then i babysat for the sully's. thats always fun. the little 2 year old is the cutest thing on the planet. so i'll babysit some more for em this week. but oh yeah. i got another outrageous cell phone bill again. its like $220. i dont know what the hell i did. but yesterday on the way home from troy we stopped at this place so i got a new north face! its pretty cool. but it looks a lot like my friend's mom's but its all good. my mom wanted one too so we could match....negative! my dad was like i aint buying both of yall one! so i win! oh yeah, a couple of days ago i went shopping! soooo much fun. i bought 6 cute shirts at aeropostale and then we went to cycle path to hang out...like old times! i ended up gettin 2 shirts and tevas! i was very excited! the guyz there are really sweet and since theyre moving the store like there was no one in there but us cuz it was empty! their new store is pimp tight. i'm gonna go hang out there i think on tuesday! i got a softball game tomarrow @ hillcrest if yall wanna come out! oh yeah....maybe my boy friend will come...but i dont really know, he's kinda acting different so. but yeh i gotta go not bc its rainin and i love the rain! so i will check this thing out tomarrow!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      001. What is your name? Jen 002. Spell your name backwards: Nej 003. Date of birth: September25 1989 004. Male or female? Female 005. Astrological sign: ummm, i think the lion one! :) 006. Nicknames: JEN 007. Occupation? student 008. Height: about 5'7...5'8 010. Hair color: brown 011. Eye color: brown 012. Where were you born? NC 013. Where do you reside now? Tuscaloosa 014. Age: 1 015. Screen names: bmjen8 016. E-mail addy jendeci@comcast.net 017. What does your screen name stand for? ummmm, it was kinda a mistake but its wierd...cuz the first 2 letters are 2 of my bf's initials! 018. What is your lj name? whats that? 019. What does your Blurty name stand for? whats blurtyy? 020. Pets: a dog and a kid brother 021. Number of candles you blew out on your last birthday cake? ummm however many the lady put on it 022. Piercings/how many/where? noppers 023. Tattoo's/how many/where? nopeee 024. Shoe size: 10 or 11 025. Righty or lefty? south paw! 026. Wearing: red cycle path shirt, yellow soffees, and my tevas 027. Hearing: "pieces of me"--ashlee simpson 028. Feeling: the guitar 029. Eating/drinking: gum count?  ~Girls/Love/Kissing/And Other Stuff~ 061. Have you ever been in love? umm yeah...once and currently falling hard 062. How many people have you told "I love you"? lots 063. How many people have you been in love with? 1 114. Does someone in your family wear a toupee? no 115. Do you have any nieces or nephews? nope, not yet 116. Are your parents divorced? no 117. Do you have step parents? obviously not 118. Has your family ever disowned another member of your family? naw 119. If so for what? ?? 120. Did some of your family come to America from another country? im sure, but i dont know.  ~Music Stuff~ 121. What song do you swear was written about you or your life? my stupid mouth by john mayer 122. What's the most embarrasing cd you own? ummm probably some burned ones 123. What's the best cd you own? uh hootie and the blowfish and sheryl crow and my john mayer ones 125. Do you sing in the shower? yes  126. What song reminds you of that special someone? uhhh...pieces of me  ~Okay, I Name An Artist And You Give A Lyric From Any One Of Their Songs!~ 127. Pink: get the party started 128. Aerosmith: dont wanna miss a thing 129. Madonna: like a virigin 130. Hootie and the Blowfish: Not Even the Trees 131. Backstreet Boys: backstreets back 132. Sheryl Crow: Diamond Road 133. Simple Plan: God Must Hate Me 134. J.Lo: Love Dont Cost a Thang 135. *Nsync: bye bye bye 136. Limp Bizkit: In the End 137. Britney Spears: Everytime...dude that video freaks me out! 138. Creed: can you take me higer.. or something like that 139. Enrique Iglesias: i can be your hero baby 140. Good Charlotte: lifestyles of the rich and the famousss 141. Christina Aguilera: durtyyy 142. Eminem: Hi My Name is... 143. Eric clapton: tears in heaven 144. Kelly Clarkston: RESPECT and A MOMENT LIKE THIS 145. Kelly Osbourne: blah blah blah blah thats what it sounds like you said to me 146. Mandy Moore: ive got a CRUSH on youu 147. Eve: Let my Blow YA Mind 148. Aaliyah:i miss you 149. Nelly:its gettin hot in herre 150. Alicia Keys: Fallin 151. John Mayer: No Such Thing ~Favorites~ 152. Color: blue 153. Food: chicken and mac and cheese 154. Song: wayy too many 155. Show: real word 156. school subject: PE...i'm sorry but i love sports 157. Band/singer: too many..yet again 158. Animal: monkey 159. Outfit: soffees c.p shirt and .. tevas. 160. Radio station: 100.5, 94.1, and 98.1 161. Movie: day after tomarrow 162. Pair of shoes: Tevas or Wallerbees or shox 163. Cartoon: sponge bob biatch 164. Actor: SeXXy ashtonn 165. Actress: jen anniston 166. Potato chip: all kinds 167. Drink: dr. p 168. Alcholic drink: bud 169. Holiday: Christmas 170. Perfume/cologne: ahh coolwater on guys and axe 171. Pizza topping: cheese 172. Jello flavor: red 173. Lunch meat: turkey 174. Board game: LIFE 175. Video game: Super Mario 176. Website: pbteen 177. Book: walk to remember 178. Computer game: Sims 179. Number: 3 baby 180. Cereal: froot loops 181. Comedian: chappel 182. Dessert: Cheesecake 183. Disney character: nemo!!! 184. Clothing store: aeropostle! 185. Passtime: sleep, internet, televissle 186. Teacher: cranny!!! 187. Childhood toy: i was deprived...no toys for me! 188. Carnival game/ride: i hate that crao 189. Candy bar: if its food i love it 190. Magazine: teen people 191. Salad dressing: ranch 192. Thing to do on the weekend:same as weekdays.. party 193. Hot drink: mocha 194. Season: summer 195. Sport to watch: basketball 196. Person to talk to online: bp   ~Your Bedroom/Sleeping Habits~ 197. What color are your sheets? sesame street!!! 198. What color are your bedroom walls? green 199. Do you have posters on your wall? no but i have a wall covered with pictures 201. Do you have a tv in your bedroom? yeah...2 202. How many pillows are on your bed? i sleep with 2 but like 15 when its all made up 203. What do you normally sleep in? soffes and a tshirt 204. Describe your favorite pair of pajamas: sweat pants from bball and a tshirt 205. What size bed do you have? full or queen 206. Do you have a waterbed/bunkbed/daybed? regular 207. Do you have your own phone line in your bedroom? nope but i gotta a cell 208. Do you listen to music while trying to fall asleep? sometimes 209. Describe the last nightmare you had: when i went to the beach i dreamed that the whole basketball team had the same bathing suit....and it turned out that clare and erin have the same one fer real! 210. Do you sleep with stuffed animals? tigger and a frog that someone gave me...but just sometimes 211. How many people can comfortably sleep in your bed? three 212. Do you sleep in any unusual positions? would i know.. im asleep 213. Do you have to share your bedroom with a sibling? no 214. Do you snore? maybe? 215. How about drool? no 216. Do you have an alarm clock in your room? yeah 217. What color is the carpet in your room? white 218. What's under your bed? probably nothing ~This or that~ 219. beach/mountains: Beach 220. Donuts/bagels: donuts 221. Day/night: night 222. Wicked witch of the east/wicked witch of the west: east 223. Heaven/hell:...heaven  224. Make love/have sex: love?? 225. Coffee/tea: both 228. Britney/Christina: Britney 229. Swiss cheese/american cheese: swiss 230. Real World/Road Rules: Real World 231. Backstreet Boys/*Nsync: Nsync 232. Silver/gold: silver 233. Nike/Adidas: Nike 234. Taco Bell/ Taco Casa: TACA CASAA bitch! 235. Sweet/sour: both 236. Punk/emo: neither but if i had to choose.. punk 237. Hot/cold: depends 238. Winter/summer: summer 239. Spring/fall: fall 240. Operas/plays: both 241. Read/watch tv: watch.. duh 242. Cd's/tapes: cds 243. Dvd's/vhs: dvd 244. Old/new: depends 245. Shorts/skirts: shorts 246. Pink/red: both 247. Colored pictures/black and white photos: Black and white are so cute but color rock 248. Meat/vegetables: chicken 249. Mexican food/chinese food: mexican! but chinese sometimes 250. Commercials/infomercials: Infos are so damn funny 251. Scary movies/comedies: Comedies 252. Bikinis/one piece bathing suits: bikini 253. Sandals/tennis shoes: both biatch 254. Dogs/cats: dogs 255. Unicorns/fairies: unihorns...not unicorns!  256. Water/land: water 257. Sugar/spice: Sugar 258. Black/white: WHiTEEE 259. ribbons/bows: Ribbons 260. Chicken/beef: chicken 261. Colored christmas lights/regular white christmas lights: both 262. Cars/trucks: trucks.. ... sexyy brushgrauds.. wowww 263. Austin Powers/James Bond: bond baby 264. Popcorn/pretzels: popcorn 265. Hip/hop: hip 266. Passionate kiss/peck: both 267. WWE wrestling/real wrestling: they are both stupid. 268. Back rub/foot massage: back rub.. i hatee feet 269. Picture frames/photo albums: Frames 270. Pens/pencils: Pencils  ~What Is Your Opinion Of The Following~ 271. Eminem: funny 272. Virgins: fine with me i dont care 273. God: love em 274. The Osbournes: different! 275. Reality TV: gay 276. J.Lo: big ass 277. Religion: i hate catholics lol 278. Emo music: is that lke BOOM BOOM music? 279. Valentine's Day: sexy...but extremely boring for people like myself 280. Christina Aguilera's comeback: that was nice 281. Homosexuals: whatever floats ur boat 282. Abortion: ummm no 283. Inter-racial relationships: fine  284. Murder: wrong 285. Death: depressing 286. Obesity: no thoughts really. 287. Pre-marital sex: whatever...follow ur heart 288. Terrorism: kick em in the GRiLL 289. Pornography: sick  290. Fortune tellers: funny 291. Threesomes: fun.. or i hear 292. Prostitution: funny as hell. hey if it pays your bills..  293. Politics: i dont even worry about them 294. Country music: yeee haw 295. George W. Bush: sexy for an old guy 296. Cloning: scares me 297. Britney's boobs: fake as a 3 dollar bill 298. Gas prices in America: too high.. but ha i dont have to pay em  ~Name Game~ What Do You Think Of When You Hear These Common Names?.  299. Jack: ass 300. Tiffany: diamonds 301. Ben: funny 302. Maria: santa... cali 303. Jennifer: who me? 304. Nicole: old friend 305. Amy: from everwood 306. Adam: 's family 307. Richard: Richy rich 308. Justin: timberlake 309. Arnold: HEY ARNOLD 310. Tom: hill 311. Melissa: etheredge 312. Charlotte: Good Charlotte 313. Harold: that fat kid 314. John: uncle 315. Joel: billy 316. Vanessa: williams 317. Michelle: branch 318. Kevin: costner 319. Brent: little like 3 yr old i know 320. Jake: hott guy i kno 321. Billy: graham 322. Sarah:dup 323. Natalie: peeples 324. Christi: sounds sexy 325. Nick: lachey 326. Linda: steeves 327. Taylor: jack johnson 328. Jordan:michael 329. Jamie: softball bud 330. Adrian: oregano head  ~Have You Ever....~ 331. Mooned anyone? yea 332. Been on a diet? no 333. Been to a foreign country? kinda...canada doesnt really count but been there twice 334. Broken a bone? no 335. Swallowed a tooth/cap/filling?nope 336. Swear at a teacher? to one...just cran when talkin bout my father 337. Talked to a lj member via e-mails or instant messages? no? 338. Got in a fight? yes 339. Dated a teacher? hell no 340. Laughed so hard you peed your pants? haha hell yeah 341. Thought about killing your enemy? no 342. Gone skinny dipping?  yeah 343. Met another Blurty member in the flesh? what the mess is blurty? 344. Told a little white lie? oh yes 345. Told a secret you swore not to tell? yes 346. Stolen anything? once when i was like 4...;) 347. Misused a swear word and it sounded absolutely stupid? yeahh. haha 348. Been on TV? yeah 349. Been on the radio? once 350. Been in a mosh pit? yeah...with my bball team 2 years ago 351. Been to a concert? yeah 352. Dated one of your best friends? almost 353. Loved someone so much it makes you cry? yeah 354. Decieved somebody close to you? yes 355. Broken the law? probably 356. Been to a rodeo? yes  357. Been on a talk show? nope 358. Been on a game show? nope 359. Been on an airplane? yeahh 360. Got to ride on a firetruck? haha yea 361. Came close to dying? with cran and then B in bham 362. Cheated on a bf/gf? if i ever had one..this is my first in a whiule 363. Gave someone a piggy back ride? yes 364. Terrorized a babysitter? oh yes 365. Made a mud pie? omg duh 366. Had a dream that our falling off a cliff? yep 367. Snuck out of the house at night? holy shit yeah 368. Been so drunk you don't remember your name? not likely 369. Had an eating disorder? no 370. Felt like you didn't belong? yes 371. Felt like the 3rd wheel? yes 372. Smoked? no 373. Done drugs? no 374. Been arrested? not me 375. Had your tonsils removed? no 376. Gone to camp? yeah 377. Won a bet? yeah 378. Written a love letter? yep! 379. Gone out of your way to be with the one you love? yeh 380. Written a love poem? yes 381. Kissed in the rain? no 382.Slow danced with someone you love? yes 384. Faked an orgasm? ummm negative 385. Stolen a kiss? yes 386. Asked a friend for relationship advice? yes 387. Had a friend steal your bf/gf? yeah 388. Watched the sunset/rise with someone you love? nope 389. Gotten a speeding ticket? negative 390. Done jail time? no 391. Had to wear a uniform to work? well if Holy Spirit counted.. yes 392. Won a trophy? yeah 393. Thrown up in public? yeah 394. Bowled a perfect game? no way 395. Failed/got held back? no 396. Got perfect attendance in grade school? yeh 397. Roasted pumpkin seeds? yeah 398. Taken ballet lessons? no  399. Attempted suicide? no 400. Cut yourself? not on purpose  ~Childhood Stuff~ 401. Did you play with Barbies? hell no 402. Did you own Treasure Trolls? yes 403. Did you watch Beverly Hills 90210? no 404. Did you play Simon? yep 405. Did you watch Fraggle Rock? on hbo.. before my time 406. Did you wet the bed? im sure 407. Did you believe there were monsters in your closet or under your bed? omg yes 408. Did you wear the underwear with the days of the week on them? hah yeah sometimes.. 409. Were you shy? yes 410. Were you spoiled? always 11. Were you abused? well being abused to me when i was little was when my mommy wouldnt buy me someting 412. Did you go to the circus? yeah 413. Did you go to the zoo? yeah 414. Were you in a car accident? nope 415. Did you build snowmen? yeah 416. Did you cry when you scraped your knee? yea 417. Were your older cousins mean to you? haha yeah but i deserved it 418. Did you think slinkies were cool? yeah 419. Did you think the Ninja Turtles really lived in the sewer? yeah.. who didnt 420. Were you afraid of the dark? hell yeah 421. Did you have slumber parties? yeahhhh! 422. Did you have New Kids On The Block sheets, curtains, sleeping bags, dolls and pajamas? no.. before me 423. Did you tease your hair out like Tiffany? no 424. Did you believe in the Easter Bunny/Santa Claus/ and the Tooth Fairy? every single one..  ~Randomness~ 425. Do you believe in aliens? no 426. Name three things that are next to your computer: cell phone, gum, and scissors 427. Do you have any hidden talents? yes 428. Do you wish MTV would play music videos? yes 429. If you were to star in a movie, what kind of movie would it be? ill let u know when i become a star 430. What would your movie star name be? more than likely my name now 431. Do you play any sports? der! yeah i do 432. What's the scariest movie you've ever seen? the ring 433. What is the best movie you've seen in the theater or rented recently? chasing liberty and fer real i loved day after tomarrow 434. What is the dumbest movie you've ever seen? i dont remember 435. Do you drive? dont have the permit yet 436. What is your dream car? land rover or range rover  437. Do you think your good looking? pshh no 438. Do others think you are good looking? why dont you tell me if you think so 439. Would you ever sky dive? hell no 440. Do you believe in Bigfoot? no 441. How many rooms do you have in your house? 5 bedrooms 442. Are you afraid of roller coasters? yes...kinda 443. Do you believe in God? yes 444. Do you believe in Satan? yes 445. Do you believe there is a heaven? yes 446. Do you believe there is a hell? yes 447. Do you own a pooltable? no 448. Do you have a pool? yes 449. Do you have a dishwasher in your kitchen? yeah  450. Do you like chocolate? yeah 451. Who/what is on your 2004 calender? dont have one 452. How many U.S. states have you been to? a ton...all the east coast and yeah 453. Ever wished on a shooting star? yeah 454. Best Halloween costume you ever wore?um long time ago i was the yellow m&m 455. Do you carry any weapons on you? no 456. What is your weakness? boys 457. Name something you can't get enough of: love 458. Describe yourself in 3 adjectives: crazy, moody, and loud 459. How many kids do you want to have? we'll see after 1 460. Future daughters names: sydney 461. Future sons names: aubrey..i love it! 462. What is your ideal way to die? fast...but do i really have to 463. How do you release stress? basketball 464. Are you a trendy person? no 465. Are you an artisitic person? not really 466. Are you a realistic person? i doubt it seriously 467. Do you un-tie your shoes every time you take them off? never 468. Are you a strong person? mentally...kinda...physically...workin on it 469. Are you a strong willed person? yes 470. Who is the last person to e-mail you? savannah 471. Who is the last person to IM you? emma 472. Do you hate chain e-mails? yes 473. Are you a deep sleeper? yes 474. Are you a good story teller? yep.  475. What do you believe is your best quality? i dont have any  476. What is your greatest accomplishment? winnin a butt load of awards in 6th grade 477. Do you like to burn candles or incense? yeah 478. Do you do yoga? with clare :) 479. Do you have your own credit card? no.. that is asking for trouble 480. Let's say you win the lotto. werd 481. Do you have a check book? haha another problem 482. Do you like your driver? say what? 483. Do you tan easily? depends on how long i stay out thurr 484. What color is your hair naturally? brown 485. How many fillings do you have? lost count after 1 486. How many cavities did you have at your last dentist visit? 1 487. Worst feeling in the world? losing someone 488. Best feeling in the world? knowing that someone you love loves you back. 489. Is the glass half empty or half full? empty 490. Last thing you downloaded? somewhere over the rainbow 491. Do you catch yourself using online terms in your real life? no. thats gay when people go LOL in person.. wow 492. What do you think people think of you? i dont give a fart in space anymore 493. Are you a likeable person? to some people, i offend a lot. 494. Do you need therapy? hell yeah 495. Do you take medication for a chemical imbalance? nope  496. What the best way to be proposed to? like in sweet home alabama... 497. What kind of movie would you star in? one where i make out with a hott guy like 4 times 498. If Fed Ex and UPS were to merge, would they call it Fed UP? wow nifty 499. When are you moving? as soon as i move to hawaii with savannah! 500. What's your favorite phrase? "i'm up...i want a pop tart"
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ight. i have found a guy! he's really sweet and i think it might work out. he told me that he really wants to ask me out, but when i get back from cali. he says all the right things at the right time. we talked for 4 hours today. its amazing all of the things i found out. i also cleaned my closet today. if u've seen it you can probably figure that it took me more than  2 hours to do. so yeah. theres only one thing about this guy...i'm really really close with his sister. and it sucks...cuz shes gonna probably not like it too much. have any of yall ever read great expectations? its about a jazillion pages long and so far boring as mess. but i have to read it for school. i'm gonna read some other cool ones so its all good. i think since tomarrow is my parents anniversary, i might invite some people over while theyre out...and then theyre gone all day saturday. theyre doin the whole massage and facial thing and then goin to this restaurant in Bham that my friends dad owns. so whatever. i gotta go now! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey! my mother made me get up so friggin early this mornin. i had to go to this thing for vbs and it was @ 930 and i woke up at 9 so she was screamin my head off. but i went and linz was there. so i gave her the cd i made for her. yeah...nelly and lauren (not you!) were there. we had fun. then i came home...i think linz might come over and hang out later but now shes with her sweety! omga....2 weeks from now i will be in CALIFORNIA!!!!!! i'm goin to go out there to live with my cousin for a while! is that not awesome!?! all by myself!??! i have to change planes in Phoenix on the way and Las Vegas on the way home. i told my mom that i was gonna miss my plane in Vegas and be all like "VIVA LAS VEGAS" wow cant wait. but i'm kinda scared. i am goin surfing everyday....and B made me watch Jaws a few nights ago....she was like if god wants you to die by being eaten by a shark you will bc its your way to go. gee thanx b! but yeah. kinda nervous bout flying by myself and meeting new people and yeah. but savannah is the coolest person i know. shes kinda like me too. like all shy and quiet until you get to know us...then its like BAM! so yeah. i had more nemo quotes but i lost em...lets find us some different ones!  Once you can accept the universe as matter expanding into nothing that is something, wearing stripes with plaid comes easy.  --Albert Einstein   USA Today has come out with a new survey: Apparently three out of four people make up 75 percent of the population.  --David Letterman   Beginnings are scary. Endings are usually sad, but it's the middle that counts the most.  --Sandra Bullock  The trouble with real life is that there's no danger music.  --Jim Carrey  This is like deja vu all over again.  --Yogi Berra   thats all for now yall!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm back! yay! we had a great time at basketball camp. there were a few little things but its all good. wow we played friday night in this huge arena...like coleman kinda thing...stadium! we won too. then we went to o'charlies. i was sittin wif storm and bt and chic and then cuse and bp and sarah and kels called me over. we were quoting finding nemo...and this guy came and told us to be quiet. inside voices....these are our inside voices! so yea. saturday we played 6 games...do u know how many that is...a lot! then we went to carrabba's for dinner. good times...not really as fun as ocharlies.but whatever. then some of us went to marble slab...like coldstone. and then me and storm went to walmart! we bought flip flops, razors,pre-soaked spounges, gum, and these awesome paper plates. it was funny. this morning we played 2 games. then we drove home. it was soooooooo embarrassing! if u were there then u know what happened. we were almost at ryan's..where we ate lunch. gah i'm gonna be remembered for that til i'm like 80. i walked in to the bathroom and coach b was sitting in there talking to someone about it i was like grrrrer. gah, this afternoon bp tried to call me and she called my house. she was all like tell ur mom i'm sorry. my mom was like i didnt know who it was. i thought it was hillarious. oh yeah. a.g.'s brother brooks like might like me i was like hmmm, bc cuse and storm told him that i liked him when i wasnt there. i dont even know him. and b told me not to bc she was afraid i would squish him. haha. here's some awesome quotes from the most coolest movie ever created!  i'm H20 intolerant!  Fish are friends, not food  Yeah, we saw you and we were like "whoa", and you were like "whoa..." and we went like, "whoa..."   Dude. Mister Turtle is my father, the name's Crush.   Oh. Intro. Jelly-man offspring. Offspring, Jelly-man.   Yeah. Now go swim away my offspring. You know, you leave them on the beach to hatch on their own... and coo-coo-cachoo, they find their way back to the big old blue.   Just keep swimming. Just keep swimming. Just keep swimming, swimming, swimming. What do we do? We swim, swim.   Hey conscience, am I dead?  Dory, this is not "whale". You're speaking like "upset stomach".   Sharkbait! Hoo ha ha!  Uhhh... the sea monkeys have my money... yes, I'm a natural blue...   Wow. I wish I could speak whale...   Denial.  Hey. You guys made me ink  Bubbles. Bubbles. My bubbles.  I'm having fish tonight  Oh, look at me. I'm gonna touch the butt  Nemo, newcomer of orange and white, you have been called forth to the top of Mt. Wannahockaloogie to join in the fraternal bonds of... tankhood.   ....thats enough for tonight...i believe there will be more by tomarrow...its just such a great damn movie! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what is goin on peeps? gah, yesterday was a loooong day for some reason. i just laid around till 230 when chris came to pick me up, then i went to basketball practice...i suck majorly and everyone was mad at me...and then mary picked me up and took me to our softball game. coach made me play catcher, but by that point i was so exhausted that i was like who cares when i missed the pitch. so the last inning i asked coach if i could sit it out so yeah. mary did an awesome job pitchin. so yay. we won. undefeated! linz came home from NYC yesterday...didnt call like she said she would, but text messaged me for a while. so last night my mother told me something EXTREMELY exciting! but i cant tell yall till its fo sho...its like 95%. i'm so friggin happy. but know my parental units are all like we should be your favorite people...i was like not at 730 in the morning. but whatever. i'm fixin to leave for mobile. big storms coming to pick me up in a little bit. and i think i'll be back sunday or monday. i'm so confuzzled. i dont care though. you know what i really need to do is get my summer reading book things. cuz i gotta read at least 3 and do reports and my parents wont take me to books-a-million so i can get em. oh well, when i fail in the first week of high school...its their fault! but whatever. later  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what is going on?! wow today was long. and its only 8.30! i just laid around all morning and then round 230 my friend chris came and picked me up for basketball practice. wow that was so horrible. we didnt run that much, we just did drills, but i SUCK. damn, i am horrible at shootin. and then on defense i was ok, my long arms help but the girls were gettin pissed bc i kept packin em. but whatever. so then my coach came and picked me up for my softball game. we played hillcrest. it was a good team game but not a good game for me. i played 1st base for most and then catcher for 1 inning. i love defense but i stink like poo at batting. last game i batted like 7th but i got a great hit so he moved me to 3rd batter this game. i struck out TWICE?! i didnt even know that was possible. i was so mad at myself. i really need to go to the cages. but yeah i caught for mary. i love her so much but i think shes like mad at me...maybe. mary is the coolest person i know. oh yeah, i got my pix from canada and school and i put em on my picture wall. i think with one more roll of film itll cover the whole wall. for real it goes from the ceiling to almost the floor. i'm so thrilled. i cant wait for this weekend!! basketball camp is gonna be awesome for the first day. we leave friday afternoon and play 1 or 2 games that night and then saturday we play 8 games. we're gonna be so tired sunday. we're bringin our bathing suits but we all know we're gonna be friggin dead by sunday. one more thing. i saw one of my old choir friends @ the softball game i was like omga its "ken". but whatever yay for me. i'll talk to you later then! like tomarrow!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just got back from my retreat. it wasnt too bad linz went so it was kinda cool. we met these 2 awesome guyz, their nicknames were Shrek and Trunks. they were so cool!!!!! too bad they were like in their 20s. Trunks was more me and we meshed better or whatever and linz and Shrek were cooler. maybe cuz shreks old than trunks. but trunks is 21 i think. i dont know but it was so funny. he was telling me about how when he wakes up he bangs on the wall and says "i'm up and i want a pop-tart". its so funny the way he says it. hes all femine but thats cool. i also got close with these guys named Kenny and Adrian. they go to my school, but those arent their real names so have fun trying to look em up in the yearbook. while i was at a campfire last night linz called tim. i was like damn. so she was like jen says hey so we talked for the first time in 3 weeks. so today me and tim had a talk. i was like why were u spreadin crap about me and talkin behind my back. he completely denied it and then he was like oh yeah. so he said he was sorry which lasted all of 5 minutes. he doesnt know how badly he hurts me and its becoming a regular basis kinda thing. while i was on my retreat we were talking with the minister about giving people second chances. i came to realize...and i think i made her realize it too is that you can give people all of the chances in the world and they take them half-ass and it falls through. so i'm done with giving people 8 jazillion chances. yeah like people screw up...hell i'm the queen of that. but i dont have regrets. gah i love life. i was watchin chasing liberty and she said that sometimes the things we are most afraid of are the things more memorable. so i think thats kinda something cool. allright well more later
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey. i had this like book that i wrote. it took me 20 minutes on this damn thing and then it friggin deletd it. well only like 2 people read this anyway. oh well. i guess i'll tell you about it tomarrow or whenever.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      almost summer! gah i only have two more tests and then i'm freakin done! today was ok. i took literature and science. i made an 86 in science. but thats cool cuz i still have an A as my average for the year. so i talked to "bert" for about 2 1/2 hours. we had great fun. then coach b and i talked.....drum roll......she told me i was gonna play varsity basketball!!! not jv and v...just varsity. is that not the best news on the planet?? so yeah. tomarrow i'm takin my exams and then having a practice with my babe storm! and then stormy and i are goin to find me some more bathin suits. i might get 2 or 3 more. i want one for every day of the week u kno?? so yeah. part of me and "bert's" convo got to cooper. which i really really didnt wanna talk about but she made me. i was like fine so her and i chatted about that whole ordeal. i'm over that crap. its like it really bugs me but whatever. cran said that he should call and apologize i was like...he'll never do that. so yerp, she got me to thiniking about that again. but i love her. i'm gonna go now cuz i'm babysitting some kids. and i think the police are outside. damn! more tomarrow. love love love~
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hola my people! i had to go to school. ick ick. well i took 4 exams and i'll go back tom. and thurs and then i'll be done. i had some very interesting discussions with cran today. i'm supposed to be studying but i've been playing my guitar for 2 hours straight. i really dont care anymore. i have lit and sci tom. they aint hard for me its ss and math i gotta worry about. i have b's in those so either way i pass...unless i get like a two. i went to lucies today. we had fun playing life. we named our life people people from school. it was verrrry interesting. then i went over to austins house to get some caffine. i now have a stash in my room. gah hell week is next week. coach b called my house...not my cell. and my mother and her had a loverly convo. greaaat. but she told my mom that she wants me storm and sarah to play some varsity so we can be with our 9th, well now 10th grade buds. SCORE. well yeah. my team had a scrimmage today, i didnt go. i really really really dont wanna play catcher so i'm gonna talk to em bout it. mary's sis told me some concoction to keep me cool...it involves like lemon juice and ammonia so i'm hesitant. ight well i'm gonna go. but i'll leave you with a quote from train.  Can you imagine no love, pride, deep-fried chicken Your best friend always sticking up for you even when I know you're wrong Can you imagine no first dance, freeze dried romance five-hour phone conversation The best soy latte that you ever had . . . and me  this isnt train...  Sometimes it's hard when you're so deep inside To see all you can lose in a blink of an eye Dreams could be shattered You could be gone  Would you want me when I'm not myself? Wait it out while I am someone else?  Well these days I wish I was 6 again Oh make me a red cape I wanna be Superman  Don't try to tell me what to do, Dont try to tell me what to say, Your better off that way  thats enough for today!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yesterday lucie and gretchen came over. well actually lucie came over and gretchen and peggy went to the store together. but lucie has strep throat so she was all drugged up--very funny-- so we had a pretty good time. today i woke up early and went to drop my dog off at the kennel and then to target to copy pictures from cali and then to books-a-million and finally we went to subs-n-you again. but yes, my pictures came yesterday!! it made me sad and happy. i was sooo happy to see them and all but sad that i'm not still there. savannah and my aunt wrote me a sweet letter. i miss them more than anything. but then at b.a.m. i got 2 more of my summer reading books and the second lance armstrong book. i wanted to get the kelley slater book, but paul wouldnt buy it for me. oh well! at subs-n-you i played army men with john. john's mom owns it. oh yeah, you know the little diet we went on, well cindy and i came up with a good name for it...the fat daddy diet. is that not hilarious?!? paul is fat, so we all go on a diet. WHATEVER! i talked to alex today for a while. found out some very interesting things! she uses bubble gum smelling shampoo....icky!! she was like "it only smells like bubble gum till lunch time"...still nasty babe! ok well i'm going out of town for a week tomarrow so i wont be able to write! you can call/text my cell phone if you need me. i'll be back next sunday night....the day before school starts!! horrible. later my lovely! 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this morning started out horribly! i had to get up at 7. yes....in the morning. it was pyscho. so i went down to school to get all the papers and stuff bc i'm not going to registration and orientation. so then pixie took me to quincy's house!!! i walked in to the den and he didnt even acknowledge my presence for like 30 minutes....ummm odd. so i was like, does he think that we broke up? i was like this is gonna be a fun day...not. but then we went and shot water balloons, he has this awesome machine. then we went up to the school to help his mom set up her classroom. i was fun. quincy me and his sister played keep it up with a beach ball. we had the best time, like most people like to cuddle with their boyfriends, me i like to beat them at monkey in the middle or something....and dont make fun of that game, its awesome!! so yeah, quincy and them brought me home which was fun, he saw my house...even though the front is covered in plastic, he liked it. then my mom invited some of her friends over. they brought kids so we had a party. some people from cycle path came, but i cant remember who! tonight we went to the gym, i shot some hoops for about 45 minutes then i walked the track. i got bored of walking the track so i called alex to talk to her, she had a friend over but we still had fun, all 3 of us. alex could hear people talking in the background so i was like sorry i'll walk further behind and she was like no i wanna listen. it was pretty funny. then the second highlight of my day (Quincy the first) was that i got to go to COLDSTONE!! i had like the kid cup, but i got to eat ice cream...full of all the fat and carbs! it was delicious!! wow! i have never had a better oreo ice cream cup! mmmk, well i gotta go finish my workout so i'll write again later! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey yall. Today was a bummer. I had to go to the doc to get a shot. so my arm is pretty numb and they told me not to use it or whatever. so being me i swam and treaded water for 10 minutes and just did a little lifting. usually i do about 50 bicep curls with a 15 and a couple other things with 15s and then i do 70 push-ups and depending on what i feel like, about 900 crunches. crunches are so much fun! thats like the one thing, besides running stairs (which i'm not allowed to do anymore for fear of hurting my other teammates) that i enjoy. but i can see the difference from before i started working out and now. oh yeah, i forgot to mention, umm last week my dad went to have his blood drawn and he found out that he has high cholesteral. so in turn, he puts our entire family on a diet. is that pycho or what. so now we have all low-fat, no carbs stuff. i swear it just doesnt fill you up, so like last night around midnight i ate an entire box of reduced fat wheat thins. its crazy, i weigh the least of anyone on my basketball team and i'm the only one on a diet. but whatever, so i've come to the conclusion that if i spend the night with people all the time then i dont really have to worry about it.  last week i lent lindsey some movies, cds, and magazines. she told me that she would bring them back on tuesday, well its now wednesday....8 days after tuesday!! and she still hasnt brought em back. so my mom is having a party here tomarrow and shes going to give her friend some movies and let her borrow my dvd player for africa, well there arent any movies here! i dont know what i'm gonna do without my dvd player for over a month....maybe i'll be forced to read or play board games or excercise...damn america. just kidding!! ight well i'm out!  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i babysat some little kids. there is one 18-month old who is adorable and then theres a 3rd grader and a 5th grader that annoy the crap out of me! but i made good money and i'm doin it again tomarrow! i was thinkin though that the 5th grader that&nbsp; annoys me is only a year younger than alex who is one of my best friends, really odd.  oh yeah, the worst has happened!&nbsp; i lost my cell phone! well kind of. i found it already but. i left it at the babysitting peoples house and i was leaving for the gym and i couldnt find it so we kept calling it and we were all walking around the house when i was like well i'll call the babysitting peeps to see if they have it. i called and the dad answered and my phone was going off in the background. i was like...ANSWER IT!!!!!! gah, its not that difficult of a concept, and my phone has caller id for moses' sake. he could see it was us calling, but whatever! so tonight i went to phelps to work out. when i got there all the courts were taken and there was a group of girls playing so i just lifted and stuff till there was a court open. i got my brother to come down and play bump with me, which fortunately i creamed him 21-4. so this girl walks up to me and asks if i wanna play. ummm yeah! so i found out that it was my friend's cousin. she kept telling me i was good, she was awesome at outside shots. so then her boyfriend brennan came over to play. he's a senior at my school and a starter for varsity! him and i went at it pretty well. i was all on him at defense; my offense is pretty horrible though. i find it amazing that i can make a reverse lay-up double-teamed but i cant make a wide open bank shot. its crazy. so the next time i go to play ash and brennan i'm gonna get quincy to come. even though brennan could squash quincy in size, i think he'll have a run for his money otherwise.&nbsp; but that was one of the best workouts i've had all summer.  so saturday i leave for our mountain house. i really dont want to go. it'll be boring as mess, i can see it coming. but i have a lot of summer reading to finish so i'll get that done. i'm three-quarters of the way done with my steinbeck book and i havent even started my last book. but my dad finally picked up the drivers book thingy so that only distracts me further. the little book is really really boring until chapter 5, then you get the pictures and the stuff you actually care about. like for instance the first chapter is on ways to get your liscence revoked or whatever. i was thinking about it and i came to this conclusion...if your 75-81, turkish, and pick your nose while driving under the influence, then your screwed! but oh well! i must go now! bubye! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just love the days where i get to sit around, i really do. but yesterday, i was watching this show and they had this special on mavericks! and it had interviews with danielle beck (roxy team manager and host of mtv surf girls) and sarah garhardt (first, and only woman so far, to surf mavericks). my cousin not only knows these people, but surfs with them sometimes. it was really cool to see them on tv. it made me realize how proud i am of my cousin, she is an incredible person for real. i was reading through some results of her recent competitions and i saw that almost every commentator labled her a "local favorite" and "on her way to a solid career". now i'm not very close with my family, in fact we dont usually talk unless theres a family reunion, once a year or sometimes every other year. but i've never had someone in my family to be proud of or to relate to. i have so many assholes in my family, its incredible. but i have some very very intelligent people. my cousin savannah's dad has 7 patents and was on the cover of software development magazine. my other uncles own computer companies or music recording studios. i have an aunt who is a micro-biologist. but that kinda stuff doesnt really hit home and make me proud, but seeing savannah doing something she believes in and working so much harder at it than anyone i've ever seen really makes me realize&nbsp;how proud i am. so yeah, lucie came over the other day with her mom. i hadnt seen them in over a month. it was pretty fun. i really really miss quincy. i havent quite had a boyfriend like him before. its a rather odd relationship we have. i guess thats what i shouldve expected, seeing as i'm friends with his sister. so its a big awkward mess. but it's all good. i've been reading this book, travels with charley. and this book makes you really think about things, it's kind of a slow book, but it has some really awesome quotes in it. but ok, i'm gonna go now. laterness!  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;this week is going great! yesterday i babysat and i got home and i was thinking about calling my awesome friend "alex". and so i was gonna read my book and then call her. but i sit down and the phone rings! she invited me to go out to dinner and then suprised me and we went putt puttin too! oh yeah, well we went to K-Mart, that place is wierd. cindy and i were like, they dont have walkie talkies like at wal-mart, they just yell for whoever they need! but yes putt putt was good until i told alex that i would give her 10 bucks to fall into the pond, cindy didnt think that was cool and then alex got really mad. but we fixed it and went to la fiesta. oh yeah, i went to see their house, its the cutest thing! i love their house! but they brought me home and we talked outside for like 20 minutes and alex got to see my dog. but yeah, last night i couldnt fall asleep, its really ironic, i couldnt stop thinking about a person from my past. this person was my best friend for like 4 years and we just mutually decided not to talk anymore and like i have no desire to talk to her or whatever, but i couldnt stop last night. they were there for me through thick and thin and i cant really say the same. i helped them through a little but not nearly as much as they gave to me. this person was there for me when no one else was, when i&nbsp;went to see my mom in the hospital, who was there crying with me...she was. and its a wierd thing, but i cant stop loving her. there are just those people that leave permanent marks in your heart, in your life.  so linz was supposed to come over, but she had a crisis. dont ask. but i dont know, she might come over later tonight. i told her that she wasnt allowed to drive her big hoopdie ghetto car in the top driveway. she just laughed, her car is old as moses for real! but i'm gonna go now because bo is barking! bubye!  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey. so sunday night i went to calvary! it was awesome, i saw so many people from choir school there. it was this like little musical/play thingy! lets see, i saw:emily, allie grace, jed, michael, katy, and mary grace. it was cool! they all did an awesome job! so yeah! i finally met quincy's dad! he's really really nice. they act a lot alike, theyre both very goofy kinda. but yeah, yesterday! we had our championship softball game. hillcrest beat the other tuscaloosa team, so we had to play hillcrest. it was awesome! mary emily pitched incredibly! and i caught the first 3 innings. omga! i must tell about 3 awesome plays! okay, the first one was a grounder hit to clare at second, she completely missed it. this girl emily playing center picks it up and chucks it toward home. i was like dear jesus what is she thinking. so i see the girl comin straight at me, but the throw was awesome and i caught it and slammed the girl out at home! it was SICK!! then this girl hit a foul ball towards third. mary emily and i both go for it, she dives face first and i skid on my knees. it was OFF THE HOOK! she caught it! ok, and then the last one was a grounder hit to clare again at second, and she bobbles it and makes a (sorry clare) bad throw to first. estes goes to get it and throws home, and i got the girl at home again! we won the game 7-2! it was great! i even got a knarly little scrape on my leg. it was funny because mary emily and i both got cut up when we dove for the ball. so we didnt have any band-aids, so i gave my team a lesson on being resourcefull. i've learned from experience that you can take a piece of paper and just wipe the cut a couple of times and it stops, and it doesnt scar as bad as shoving dirt in it. good times! so today quincy had surgery ::tear:: it sounded very painful, they had to put him to sleep! icky! but he sounded good when i talked to him, just a little silly from the meds still, he was watching cartoons and eating jello and he couldnt hold his head up. it was kind of sad! ok well that should be enough for today, but i'll leave you with some quotes! &nbsp; I went sky diving I went Rocky Mountain climbing I went 2.7 seconds on a bull named BluManchu and I loved deeper and I spoke sweeter and I gave forgiveness Id been denying and he said someday I hope you get the chance to live like you were dying. &nbsp; So dont make me cry Cuz this love dont feel so right You cant push a river You cant make me fall But you can make me unreachable &nbsp; Fall... Sometimes I fall so fast Well, I hit that bottom Crash, you're all I have &nbsp; My love, look at what you've done to me For someone who has felt so strong It's amazing I'm completely gone &nbsp; ight! i'm out! &nbsp; &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow its been a while! yesterday was a good day! i went to the mall, and got my hair washed. it was like $14 just to get your hair washed, but my mom wanted me to and she paid so whatever. then i went to books a million, that was different. then i went to darin....and laurens....house. we had an awesome pool party. like 15 people showed up and we had an awesome time so yeah. i'm going to miss andrew very very very much! oh yeah, i found out that stormy lied to me yesterday, that doesnt feel so great but thats life eh? so today we didnt go to church, for like the 7th week in&nbsp; a row. something bout my mom and no sleep or something. but linz is coming over at like noon and then cindy is coming to get me at 4. i cannot wait! we're going to go to&nbsp;baptist church! i have no clue why, but this excites me! so i'll go now, but i'll probably write later if my internet is still on. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hola! lets see! yesterday was a pretty good day! i had to clean my house for three hours...that STUNK! and then lauren came to get me and we went to softball. she's so funny. we were driving down the road and she was like whats chevy mean and then she goes, how much does perfume cost. it was the funniest thing i've heard in a while! it was really wierd though, our team practiced with the other tuscaloosa team that we're playing in the championship. is that not odd?! but so linz called, she's been in florida for a week, but she comes home tomarrow so we can talk about some stuff. quincy called...that didnt go so great, my mom answered because he called my house phone, it was all downhill from there. but yeah. so then last night a.g. called, we had fun talking! we played guess who on the phone, we kept ending up with the wrong people; we had different versions of the game! oh yeah, i talked to nick yesterday! he wanted to know if my cousin was hott. it was kinda funny, the only picture i had to show him was a group pic, so you couldnt really tell! but yeah i have to go now because i'm gonna call savannah! later  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hey people! wow, i'm still living on california time! i told savannah that i was gonna live on cali time until the next time i go out there! today and yesterday stunk! we had to watch these kids that are my mom's friend's or something. it was so horrible! i cannot believe how annoying they were! they finally left like an hour ago! phew! so yeah! quincy's at camp this week! and i'm missing him soo much! it was so funny though, the other night he called me and i was in the hot tub, and he kept saying he was the mexican hotline or something! and then he sang me a song....poor it! but it was very....er sweet? just kidding! he's awesome! but today i talked to stormy for the first time in a month! dang! her and zach have been going out for like almost exactly 4 months longer than me and quincy! great eh? but yeah! my cousin gave me like 50 stickers from her sponsors and contests and stuff, i just dont know where to put them. cindy suggested on the back of my door. my mom said no so i then threatened to put them on my guitars, i think i persuaded her to accept the door idea! but yes, i'm gonna go now! love love love! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! i JUST got in from b-e-a-u-tiful california! i had the most awesome time of my life! so monday i woke up early and my dad took me to the airport. that stunk, but yeah i sat next to this black guy on the plane, and he turned out to be a music producer in LA and he told me to look him up when i'm in LA. he works with kc and jojo and like some other people! ok but phoenix the switch was easy and so then i flew in to san jose! i was walking to baggage claim and i see this like bright shiny thing...its my cousin's bleach blonde hair! its soooo pretty! so yeah it was soooo awkward! but i got home and i had to try on the wetsuit so that broke the ice a little. savannah took me to the lighthouse and we walked and talked for a while, i guess we walked all the way to 2nd peak, or jacks house. so yeah went to bed! the next morning i went to junior guards with savannah. we did a     r-s-r or run-swim-run. it was physco! the water was like 57 degrees......CRAZY! so yeah, i finished and all the guyz were talking about how knarly it was...a girl from alabama doin the r-s-r! but yeah, then i had my surfing lesson. savannah and i went on the beach for like 30 seconds, she was like this is how to do a pop up and then we went. it was funny as mess. my first wave was like 2 seconds cuz i spazed, i went for the wave and i hear savannah squeal so i fell. but the next one she tried to jump on my board...but its all good! wednesday we surfed, i dont know, this is getting kinda tiring! but yeah i went surfing like everyday and to the wharf and the redwoods. i had an awesome time meeting savannahs friends especially : lexi, duke, denise, halie, sierra, austin, gabe, nikki, laura, vanessa, tyson, steve, miles, shelby, shannon, and a ton of others! yall are all great and i hope to hang out with you again next time! when i was in california, quincy called which was always fun. a.g. called a couple of times and cindy called a ton. i talked to clare and catherine too! very exciting! i was stoked to come home but i miss the beach already. i love surfing so much and i also love savannah tons! later guyz
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! i'm in california! the flight was ok. sat next to some music producer guy...but yeah. got here yesterday. stayin with savannah and them. this morning we went to junior guards...it was soooo cold! we did RSR...run swim run. we ran half a mile and then swam 2 buoys (the water was 50 degrees!) and then ran half a mile!  but then savannah and i went surfing! it was awesome, i caught like 5 waves! horray! ok well i'll write again whenever!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! i'm in california! the flight was ok. sat next to some music producer guy...but yeah. got here yesterday. stayin with savannah and them. this morning we went to junior guards...it was soooo cold! we did RSR...run swim run. we ran half a mile and then swam 2 buoys (the water was 50 degrees!) and then ran half a mile!  but then savannah and i went surfing! it was awesome, i caught like 5 waves! horray! ok well i'll write again whenever!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! i'm in california! the flight was ok. sat next to some music producer guy...but yeah. got here yesterday. stayin with savannah and them. this morning we went to junior guards...it was soooo cold! we did RSR...run swim run. we ran half a mile and then swam 2 buoys (the water was 50 degrees!) and then ran half a mile!  but then savannah and i went surfing! it was awesome, i caught like 5 waves! horray! ok well i'll write again whenever!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! i'm in california! the flight was ok. sat next to some music producer guy...but yeah. got here yesterday. stayin with savannah and them. this morning we went to junior guards...it was soooo cold! we did RSR...run swim run. we ran half a mile and then swam 2 buoys (the water was 50 degrees!) and then ran half a mile!  but then savannah and i went surfing! it was awesome, i caught like 5 waves! horray! ok well i'll write again whenever!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so last night was wierd. i talked with several people...including some that i havent talked to in a while. i had a really funny conversation with lauren...well both my lauren friends. then i got a text message from hilen....very very unpredictable, i havent talked to her since canada. so we talked for a while, trying to be nice, i think it went fine. but yeah, i hate how small this town is. word travels so friggin fast. like people at hillcrest know that i'm goin out with ummmm Quincy (not his real name). i was like oh thats great. i mean its cool but like even lauren w knows i was like wow. its just really funny to me. oh yeh but then in a wierd turn of events, this morning i was a target and as we were pulling out of the parking lot hilen and her mother were pulling in. very wierd. but yeah, i gotta pack all my stuff today. its kinda ironic, like since i've been goin out with quincy and have so many great friends i'm really just looking forward to comin home. that sounds kinda like i'm not grateful or whatever but i am. i'm sure that once i get there things will be awesome and i wont want to come home but i've already made some great plans for when i get home. i'm goin to see brook and quincy and cindy and lauren and allie grace! like and those are just the people that i've made like concrete plans with. i just really wanna hang out with them. i guess another thing is not getting to see quincy for so long. i mean he went out of town a couple of days ago but he'll be back before me so. i think we decided that like the day i come home i'm goin to his house or something but yeah. oh funnyness! when we were at target my parents bought some like furniture thingys that are really cool but theyre all like you can use these when u go to college! what the hell? but i just sat there and i was like fine. but yeh i'm gonna go watch the tour de france! i think lance might pull off a 6th! he came out so strong yesterday at the time trial!!! yay! and he's dating sheryl crow how awesome!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow! bored! my boyfriend went out of town this morning. i will miss him so much! then cindy left for the beach, i'm so very bored. i dont know what to do, i dont feel like callin anyone so ive just been vegging out. i went to the mall and got a manicure/pedicure. and got some more bathing suits but thats it. i really miss everyone. i rented some movies from blockbuster tonight. i got perfect score, along came polly, and the mooseport one. i didnt like the polly movie but oh well! u know what i think i'm gonna call my boyfriend and then cindy and then yeah....i'm gonna go use my free nights and weekends!! ight later~ only 2 days till i go to california!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall! so its been a while. ummm lets see. last night i had a double header against hillcrest. we took both of them. cindy came so that was fun. mary emily and i bonded. she is soooo cool. when i get back we're gonna do something! so yeah, tonight i'm goin to dinner with one of my friends, ashley. yeah we're goin to ben kei or whatever. but thatll be fun. i'm really excited bc one of my best friends comes home today! and i have sooo much to tell her. but yeah this weekends gonna be crazy, but then i'll be in cali!!! i cant wait, but mary emily got me thinkin bout sharks...gee thanks girl! chocolate is as chocolate does...we're so stupid! but yeah. i'm really bummed that i havent seen linz in a while, but shes doing her thing with her man so more power to her i guess. i think i'm goin over to nicks this weekend to watch some movies and hang out, he made me some cds for my trip! i love him....but hes just a friend! later!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>