<Blog>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah I have updated my personal website, my little playroom in the reality of the internet. My cornerstone in the uprising storm :-p  So you can enjoy it here if you want it...I've prepared and added some great pics.   urlLink Psychopath.nl 
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will start with pointing out a few good websites I know!  For instance.. tshirthell.com great tshirts wich..umm.. ensure you have a great workout! Just go there and see it for yourself.   urlLink T-Shirt Hell: Funny t-shirts, Funny shirts, cool t-shirts, Cool shirts   Another great website is my favourite Newspaper   urlLink The Union - Your Finest News Source   Ah what shall I say... life can be pretty interresting not?
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah my first message on This Blog, lets see..mmm, it seems to work pretty good!  Well isn't that a usefull fact, in such case lets try if this works good enough!
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sigh, ya know computers do have their own life... this one truly acts strange at times...  Just had to re-fit the heatsink on my videocard..again..it's sad... I think I should have the "right" to be able to have it working for longer as 2 months before I need to refit it...not?   Ah well, some nice things are coming here but not now yet! Ya shall see!
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Therians... yup... therians... what is up with therians....    I dunno, some say there are problems between the vampire community and the therian/were community.     What problems... I never saw those problems... what problems...     So I have chosen that it's time to ask the therians..and the where ones... to see WHAT the problem precise is.  A little bit of research..and maybe a first step into a ...better working together.    Oh well, we shall see...    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I updated my profile and released information about me. After all I am trying to make this my blogspot, though... I am not a person to give much out. I am inter-operatable ( chaotix ) but in combination WITH others.    Paper or Blogs are so... one way in their function.    I always hated them, I can't write much good... I can't draw.. I can't paint. .. Atleast I can inspire others to do so and get others in their optimum.    Ah yes, that is a part of my chaotic nature. I am born with a "wall of silence" around me, limiting communications and it's hard for me to understand "normal social levels". Basicly I can't see at the same level as most people work in their social constructs.    I am as a spider, living in the webworld of another humans webframe of reality. It allows me though something special, to look from the outside at what happens. I am basicly "incompatible" with basic human social networks, so even though the bad side is that "making myself compatible" uses allot of energy, it allows me to percieve things in alternative ways.    In old times I would be fully accepted and a use would be found for my special capabilities, but in this society where everybody works 40 hours a week for whole of their life, 9 till 5 ...    In this western world, your systems are like a prison to me...    Adjusting takes time and valuable energy, happily I am allowed to be "defunct" ... in certain times. It takes those like me to get things done... it takes some eyes from the outside.    And for chaos, ah since I am wired with her lady chaos blessing I have been every month more capable into seeing things different. I know, lady chaos "resides" in me... probably it's just a part of me, long prisoned within silence coming out.    But the label Lady Chaos makes me feel good... ..it's a strange reality that drives me!  
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Send this email to 10 friends       Ah yes, the all original "send this email to 10 friends"      Many of these are hoaxes, or the people mentions have never existed, or  the thing is not build to happen (  Like hotmail closing hoaxes )       Lets do math, you send "this" email to 10 friends and each friends send it also to 10 friends... shall we?       So in two days it reaches 10x10 = 100 people.   In 5 days it reaches 10x10x10x10x10 = 100.000 people.   In 30 days it reaches.... right 10 in the 30th power!       And that only if it has a perfect run! Means send around every time by JUST AND ONLY JUST 10 people.       Generally some friends don't send it ( hey they are smart ) and others  send it to their whole hotmail address list! ( and end up in my  blacklist >:-p )       What matters is how much pressure this causes on the internet...  already we have problems with SPAM... and we are fighting spam... and  we are getting succes.. on some level.  But this kind of emails  are worse them spam... because it comes mainly of friends in our  address list out mailblockers let it through.... meaning we have to  spend yet again 4 minutes writing a reply WHY those 10x sending mails  don't work!       4 minutes we could do allot more then such unworthy something!      The biggest problem is for the providers... those having mailservers...  as your mailchain letter might have caused a overhaul amount of mail  together.... by all your friends of friends of friends of friends...      Do you understand how much datatransfer that costs? Guess what, the  ISP's do know that... and they make YOU pay for it ...every paying  customer pays a bit in the services after all!       So what is the damage of such a mailchain letter....      A - wasting time of people   B - wasting data transfer   C - making the bill for ISP's rise and thus the bills for customers   D - Showing the world how stupid humanity is      Well I guess that is it... so next time you get such a letter.. think again!       
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Online Communities versus Offline Communities   Ah yes, the vampire community. In the early days there was no internet, or it was so expensive that it was limited usable.  But nowadays with the fast/cheap internet the vampire community has "infected" it with their activities.  Yet, there are some things you can't have in online communities. It doesn't fills the need for us to meet face to face. To talk to eachother for instance by phone.   It might look that we get closer over the internet but .. there is a limit in how close we can get.   And on certain times and moments you migt need to think about crossing the bounderies and meet face to face.   And yes, then we can get into a shock.. our Inner being can be very different from our Outer Shell. And also people can emulate being nice while being assholes who wish to abuse you.  Such are the dangers, yet this "weakness" touches every area where the online meets the offline.  The Internet in the End is merily a tool to connect things... and in humanity the final cause is to communicate! 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wonder oh wonder, my struggling 9800 Pro is an R360.. a 9800XT chip. So today I prepared an XT bios with 9800NP speeds and flashed it.. it works..for now.  What it does is to relax some timings and up some voltages..so basicly things ought to run hotter but it should keep it more stabile.  Lets hope it does...lets hope it does.  I lost one of my rats... Pirate, a very strong female but you can't will all times..  Pirate was about 1 year old when she first had cancer, at that time easily removed... about 11 months later ( yes almost 2 years old by then ) it was back.. it could be removed..but also the milkglands where removed. Prognosis... it will return one day.  And this week ... that day had come... and this time it was totally internal..and had stopped the liver/kidney from functioning perfect. Basicly she was poisoning her own blood with every meal! 3rd strike cancer and broken liver/kidney functions... then you know it's just to late... ah.. and quality of life goes above quantity... so she left.  Now I have to split up my time between 1 male and 1 female rat... mmm... possible... 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Birthday business and alike  Well yes, I had my birthday, friday I became a wooping 24 and saturday I cooked a 4 star meal for my parents.  And yes only parents, see I like my birthdays being very small and silent. Maybe next year I pull of a bigger gig... but not now.  One of my rats now has stare, I guess I told earlier about that... but now it's truly there... full stare ahead. Grinzz.. I am sure he still lives on for months this way....  LC wishes to be back in the Vampire Corner, ..and monday morning ( for them sunday night ) I have spoken with the council. And we agreed he can't be trusted! And that we ought to prepare a new group with US in command. And get the active people moving over.  Yup, I said before this would happen... but now it finally does  The Vampire Corner Zine is postphoned untill such all is done. Ah nothing bad with that...  I still have to do closure on the Camp Courant for the vacation I have been on. And that should in the end be all, :-) yup... still going good here. 
    
</post>


</Blog>