<Blog>


<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SICKENING THINGS HAPPEN IN COMMON PLACES I was watching oprah this morning and what it was about was really heart wrenching and disguistingly sadistic. This old man (a millionaire) had a dungeon 4 ft below ground under his house where he kidnapped women and put them there, and rape them all day... it was really shocking because his victims were kept there spanning from 2 and a half months to 2 and a half YEARS. sadistic old fart. he let them go and you know what happen when they try to tell the authorities? they couldnt do squat. and they admit to dropping the ball. it really sickens me that paedophiles can be everywhere, even in the suburban areas like this one..and how no one believes what the victims say, its demeaning a factor that is so important which is trust. if you cant trust, you cant do anything, because of people like that man...
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heylo, Izzy here, using blog spot and a default layout for now till i find a good host, cuz its all abt the blogging. You'd have to be living under a rock in year 10 if ur not spooked abt the upcoming mock exams, im going through the bbc bite size site for help and revision. I cant seem to remember what homeostasis is, and its gona be hard remembering the equations for physics, dont get me started with english =p.  anyway, i hope u all are doing fine,  ciao
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      now its tomorrow, dont mind that much. eh you know on astro, the advert showing nothing but girls and all the guys are missing? one of the girls in it is so hot man hahahha the one using the blow torch hahahha, nice man.. you know we got until the 23rd of august?&nbsp; wat to do in that time man..bored oredi ryte now. i went to gadong today and got some clothes for my driver, his birthday tomorrow, hes family to us. i wanna know this, do you guys have like jokes that only you and ur relatives (brothers, sisters, cousins, etc.) understand? like with me, me and my brothers did some stupid stuff like i put on&nbsp; these stupid shades when i was younger ryte, on camera, then i turn around and walk and i hit my face on a chair hahahahh, then i cried. my brothers like to bring stuff like that up, stuff we did in the past, just wanna know if u guys have stuff like that.. 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im going to singapore on tuesday, till saturday. nothing much else to say.... 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im flying on sunday morning at around 10 or 11.. staying there till thursday =] im bringing my maths and art homework along with me, i dunno why but i like doing homework overseas cuz its more fun, oso i can take photos of streets in singapore for my art coursework thingie... deepskye check lvl:40 job lvl:30 money: around 50 something k saving up for stuff  its been easier to lvl up recently because they increased the drop rate and exp, shibby..  hope u all are okay..and have done ur holiday homework T_T better start soon if u havent bye 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Deepskye status lvl 36 11k doing just fine &nbsp; hi all, its been really boring up till now, nothing much happening, just watched boston public, if you're not already hooked on it you should be =]  im trying to get my chemistry done and out of the way, so next week i can do maths and art. hope you all are doing well, chao! 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi again, yeah i know, this is another try at blogging, i hope to continue with this one... you like the pic up there? made it myself ^_^ took me only a few hours because there isnt much tonal work to do... anywayz in this blog i'll also be giving info on my character in ragnarok online, deepskye. apart from that i'll also be talking about the latest happenings that i consider of interest and also my thoughts on stuff, basically ill write about stuff, any kinda stuff... hope you like =) 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i play the guitar, im into technology, computers, computer graphics, islam, music; heavy metal, alternate rock, dj music, blues, jazz, football, i do add math (lol), i like manga, anime, comics, transformers, game magazines, computer magazines, i dont go for the car magazines that have models on them, i like sushi with some wasabi, i sleep on a matrass when i have 2 perfectly good beds, i dont like crowds, i get nervous around people (especially girls but thats normal i guess), and its hard to get along with me at first... wth am i? hahaaaa... im oso immature at times and weird 24/7, i have no classification... hehe 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont like being around crowded areas, firstly because i feel discomforted and you can get your stuff stolen in crowds. oso i dont like it when the crowd is chatty, cuz it makes me nervous for some reason...dunno why 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi, back from singapore  day 1 arrived at the airport, went to the hotel, got our rooms, one normal and one suite hehe. too bad it was on a smoking floor, smoking is bad, dont smoke we then went to funan centre, the all time techno geeks heaven, spent so long there getting my brother's laptop, oso we bought some games there too. went back to the hotel and slept oh yeah, free mini bar haha  day 2 had a buffet in the hotel, yummy hehe we went to wheelock, borders book store, bought all the computer graphics magz i could find went to funan yet again, this time my brother decided on his laptop nothing much else happened cuz we spent most of the day there  day 3 went to takashimaya, bought loads of manga etc. at kinokuniya, oh yeah, do you know a model person called jacelyn tay? we saw her in person there, she was doing a function  day 4 forgot what we did the whole day, oh yeah, we went to taka again and killed my legs over buying clothes and stuff haha that night we went to far east plaza and ate with loads of family, altogether 16 attendees including us after that most of the family went back to the hotel with us to get tea or coffee cuz starbucks was full hehe talked to my cousin, he was telling us stories about national service, heh so tough man, 5 days in borneo jungle surviving off the land, oso if u take the ranger course you have a MONTH there, trying to get out of the jungle, and all the army does is give u chicken once a week. dam tough, wish i could still do it, wud toughen me up alot eh? after that went up to the room and watched some anime, gundam seed. then was too tired so i went to bed  day 5 had buffet, then slept till around 10 30 in the morning from around 9 something on a seat. went to the airport, had some trouble with seatings but it got done, made it just in time to the gate heh, my mum's name was mentioned on the announcement for being late for the flight lol the flight home was really crap, leg room was non existent, so cramped, the tray was crap, falling unbalanced so we had to balance the food with pillows under the tray. finally got home =)  oh yeah, while i was at kinokuniya, a cute singapore girl in school uniform smile at me, and like she was walking by and still smiling when she was walking past, usually people turn around, she didnt.. so yeah, that rocked hahaa...  and here i am 
    
</post>


</Blog>