<Blog>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was kinda interesting. On the way back from lunch at school I was signing my friend Caroline's yearbook, when some guy came up to me(He sits with Colby during lunch.) and kept saying "hey this is Colby's girlfriend"(he was pointing  at me).Caroline and Meagan started laughing and I was like umm.... Anyway, Sunday after church, I'm going shopping to get a swimsuit for Cassy's party. Fun..Fun..My mom yelled at me earlier(well not really yelled) because she has to pay like $26.00 because I'm going to take the ACT, and now she has to give me money for a swimsuit.Oh well, she got over it. I really need to get a job. I'm looking, but can't find one that I'm really interested in. There is no way I am working in a fast food restuarant. I might be going to apply for a job at The Christian Book Warehouse. I really want to work at PacSun. That is a great store. I practically live in that store. Okay I think that's all you need to know for now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well...Cassy's party is May 29th...how ironic... Colby's birthday is  May 29th. I need to go shopping to get a swimsuit, since I can't wear my string bikini. G-rated...ha!...that's funny.lol! Well anyway, I went to Cassy's house today(picked her up), then we went to Ashley's house. We all decided we were going to follow Ashley's brother, Blaine, to Wendy's. He is a really fast driver(he was going like 60mph on this one road when the speed limit was 35).We got these really small frosty's, I mean they were really small. So much fun....cough cough! jk...ok I'm going to go now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Colbmister: i'm just playin i think your real purty  *Thanks Colby*  Just for the record....I think your hot, but you should already know that.;)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well....today was a pretty good day for me. I laughed a lot today, I'm not saying why. I have a lot of homework to do, well not a lot, but a pretty good amount of it. I did only 100 crunches today( I know that's not a lot, I usually do 250 and 150 situps, but today is Monday and it's a lazy, but slow day).Ashley if your reading this...you don't have a big nose....don't listen to what Blaine says. He is a loser...lol! And don't listen to Dusty Smith...your not ugly...he's a loser too....:)  ROCCATCHER: i think ur pretty   *Thanks Michael*  That's all I am saying for now.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Not much happened today. I got pushed into the snack machine at school by a certain someone. lol! I have nothing to do this weekened. Saturday my mom is going to the Shania Twain concert and I am stuck home babysitting. My mom said I could have a friend over, but everyone has something to do. That really sucks! I don't want to babysit, oh well. I don't have a choice. Gosh! I really wish that really hot guy would get online. I am so freakin bored. I am at my friend, Carolines, house right now. John Jones keeps calling her. Gosh! He wants to date her. lol! What a ditz! j/k....I really don't have anything else to say. So I am going to go. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Cassy you are my best friend in the whole world, even if we get into arguments over stupid stuff. We have been friends since kindergarten, we will not stop being friends, and whenever I get married, which will be when I am like 24 or 25, you will be my maid of honor(promise), even if I have to hunt you down, lol.I don't know what I am going to do when you move. I will miss ya! I will be very sad, but hey I got my license so I can come see you anytime. We should go shopping again sometime soon, except this time I will make sure I have money...lol! Love ya lots! Lylas! B.F.F
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My mom just got home. She had an interview for a job. She said she might get the job. I hope she does, she deserves. Yea!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm....well nothing really happened today. I don't have much to say, so I'm going to go now. Cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ~*Cassy if your reading this....heart ya!*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a pretty good day for me. My best friend Cassy called me and said she was sorry for what she said to me(you dont need to know what she said), then we decided to go shopping, so I drove to her house and picked her up and we went to Hammers to see Josh, then Walmart, Goody's. I had fun. I going to go now. Cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So far nothing has really happened today. I got to drive MY CAR to church. It was great, well except for when I was driving home the traffic was horrible. It is so freakin hot outside. That's all I am going to post for now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ~*Colby, if you are reading this...Sorry I didn't talk much tonight at the baseball game, I had a lot on my mind. I got in an argument with my dad.*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm....well...lets see here...spring break is almost over. Pretty much all I have done this spring break is help people out, it's not a bad thing, I am not complaining. I like helping people out, especially if they are my friends. What have I done...I have somewhat helped out Ash and Dustin(good luck Dustin)..hope everything goes well. WOW! this year is almost over. Time sure does fly by when your having a good time. This year has been great for me. I have had my bad days, but doesn't everyone. I think this has been one of my best years in high school, so far. Hopefully it will get even better. Oh yeah...can't forget about that date I went on with that really hot guy:)..yup...that was great...that made my day. Okay....I'm done posting for today. I'm tired..yaun! Cya!  ~*Ashley if your reading this.... I heart you!*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WOW! Today was great. My mom took me to get my license, I passed!:) Later on tonight I went on a date with a really hot guy. I had alot of fun. It took him awhile to hold my hand, but it was worth the wait. He is so cute. I really like him. Well that's all you need to know. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is going to be a busy day for me. My mom is taking me to go get my license:). I hope I pass. Later tonight I am going on a big date with this really hot guy. :) That's all I am going to say for now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I heard my favortie song, Take My Breath Away. I love that song. That made my day. My day had lots of anger in it. A couple of my friends keep getting into an argument(I'm not in it), it's getting old. I wish it would all stop. I might be going to go get my license tomorrow. My mom said if we don't tomorrow, then she will take me Thursday or Friday. I can't wait. I want my license so bad. My sister found an apartment. I get to move in with her and her husband. He is getting shipped off for 2 years. That's sad! The apartment is in Seymour. It has a football, soccer, baseball field and a fitness center. I'm excited! I'm going to have a party, my sister doesn't know it yet. She won't care anyway. When the time comes I will ask her. That's all I am going to say for now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Not much happened today. I was supposed to go get my license, but it rained. The lady at the dmv said they don't give driving test when it rains. I really wanted to get my license, but oh well. My mom said she might take me some other time this week, hopefully. :) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      SCHSsoccergurl: i want to go to the circus SCHSsoccergurl: lol idrinkdrpeppers: lol idrinkdrpeppers: I'm scared of clowns SCHSsoccergurl: lol SCHSsoccergurl: y idrinkdrpeppers: Because I went to the circus once and a clown came up behind me and said, "BOO" SCHSsoccergurl: lol idrinkdrpeppers: and I have been scared of them ever since SCHSsoccergurl: hehe SCHSsoccergurl: nobody is on SCHSsoccergurl: eerrggg idrinkdrpeppers: OH SO I'M NOT ENOUGH FOR YOU SCHSsoccergurl: except u and me and some other peeps idrinkdrpeppers: IS THAT IT SCHSsoccergurl: lol idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: oh no your plenty SCHSsoccergurl: lol idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: so SCHSsoccergurl: what do you like to do idrinkdrpeppers: hmm..  SCHSsoccergurl: beside get cassy pregnant idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: gettin* idrinkdrpeppers: crap.. what else is there idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: lol idrinkdrpeppers: well, I like sasuage balls idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: lol SCHSsoccergurl: i like cheese balls idrinkdrpeppers: well, I'm gonna go SCHSsoccergurl: ok SCHSsoccergurl: bye idrinkdrpeppers: Bye idrinkdrpeppers: love you idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: freak SCHSsoccergurl: lol SCHSsoccergurl: jk idrinkdrpeppers: lol SCHSsoccergurl: ttyl SCHSsoccergurl: bye idrinkdrpeppers: bye  ~*Josh you have a girlfriend, who happens to be my best friend. I know I'm hot, but I can't help it. I like someone else. lol!  Josh what a joke! lol!*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So...this is my first post. This is exciten..not really, but oh well. I talked to Mogill today and she said she went to the beach and is a little tan. I don't believe her. I don't think she can get a tan, I just think she will come back from Florida with a really bad sunburn. Josh Williams thinks Dustin Gamza likes me. I don't think he does, but Josh was like he talks about you all the time...and I was like uh huh. Josh, what a joke! lol! j/k!               "I like big pickles and I cannot lie, you otha brothas can't deny when a guy walks in with a really big pickle..."   -That is my song, no more posting it in your blogs..Cassy & Ashley.-:)  ~*That's all I am going to say for now. Lata!*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well today was funny. For starters, I'm never using a credit card to pay for gas again. My mom wanted me to go to Krogers for her, so I went to Krogers to get some stuff that she needed, and of course I got something for myself. Anyway, I needed to get gas too, so I went to the Krogers gas sation and I had my moms Kroger plus card and her credit card. The thing asked me if I was a member or whatever you want to call it, and I said yes and it said slide your Kroger plus card, and I slid it and it said remove it so I did. It told me to do that 3 freakin times, so I did it 3 times. The lady at the cashregister had to come out and show me how to do it. I was sliding it in the wrong thing. Lol! Then, some other lady came up to me and she said it took her 5 minutes to do it. I was like ok. I saw Andrew Hillard and Larry there. Andrew had like 5 people in his car. Ok whatever, I'm going to go now. I feel really stupid. lol!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Guess what! I got a new swimsuit. Yea! My dad picked me up this morning at 8AM. I'm a little tired, but anywho...I'm going to Cassy's party, fun stuff! There are a lot of birthdays today. Wow!I'm hungry, so I'm going to go eat breakfast. MMMMMmmmm.....food!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think I might have led someone into thinking that I like him the way he likes me, but I really don't. I'm really sorry. I don't know what was going through my head. I was just upset about something and I was trying to forget about it. I feel really bad about it. Okay...well, I'm going to go now. toodaloo!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Good news! My grandma is getting out of the hospital soon. She is doing a little better. I'm happy. I have been in a really good mood lately, but I feel like something is missing, but oh well. Anyway,I finally got all my stuff moved into my sister's apartment. It's so pretty there. I love it! This is exciten stuff, well except for the fact that I need a freakin shower curtain in my bathroom.lol! Notice how I said MY BATHROOM. lol! I'm mad now. Unger just signed off during a conversation. I hate when he does that. Sheesh! I am going to go now. I have to get up early. I'm going to my little brother's field day tomorrow at good ole' Northview Elemtary. Cassy and Dustin are going. fun stuff! Good night! Sweet dreamz! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was my last day of school. Summer vacation is here. I'm kinda happy but also sad. My best friend in the whole world is moving to Maryville, you know who I'm talking about. Anyway, we have not had a class together in high school, which sadens me :(. Oh well.....I'm really bored right now. I have almost moved all my stuff into my sister's apartment. It's so pretty...I love it there. It's a two story apartment. I get my own room, which I have had before, but what I haven't had before is my own bathroom, which I get over there. Yea! I can't wait. Soccer starts soon, well camp and practice. Soccer conditioning is July 21-23. Camp is after that, and after camp we start to practice. It's not a stay the night camp. It last a week from 8AM-4PM. Killer, I know. You get used to it after awhile. Hmm....running from 8AM-4PM...fun stuff. Camp is actually a lot of fun. We work hard but also play some games. Are lunch time is great! It last for an hour, we go into the team room and sit on the couches and watch a movie(on our big screen tv). Some people sleep...fun stuff. Last year we watched top gun. Well I'm going to go figure out what I'm going to do the rest of the day. I think I might go run or kick a soccer ball around. Oh shoot! I have to finish packing. I have one box left to take over to my sisters. I'm probably going to go over her house and set up my new room. Did I mention I'm in a pretty darn good mood, well except for not being able to see some people for a whole freakin summer. Lata Gata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay....lets get one thing straight, I am a really good driver. Blaine you wouldn't even know, you have never been in the car with me when I was driving, and Colby I was joking around with you that one time you were with me. Ok?....you can ask kayla, cassy, caroline, and ashley...im a good driver.sheesh!:)  7. Am I a good driver?(tricky question...hehe) toto said: Heck no!...you hit my mailbox!   7. Am I a good driver?(tricky question...hehe) Blaine said: Heck no!...you hit my mailbox!  7. Am I a good driver?(tricky question...hehe) bob said: Heck no!...you hit my mailbox! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well...I'm so bored...I thought I would make another quiz.      urlLink You think you know, but you have know idea!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Cassy and I are not arguing any more. Yea!! ok I'm going to go eat now.MMMM....food!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am feeling better. I haven't heard anything about my grandma. Well...here in a minute I need to go get ready for church. I am so bored right now. Take this quiz:    urlLink Take my FriendTest   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At 3:30 PM, Cassy said…  I've told you this before, get over it. You just want attention. You're not the only person in the world who has problems. If you want to go to your brother's feild day fine, but I'm not going if Josh is gonna be mad at me. I understand it's the law, but you never suggested any other way for me and Josh to get there. You're just jumping to conclusions and you need to get over it.  ~Yes, that is exactly what I want. I want attention(sarcasm). I know I'm not the only person in the world who has problems. You must think I'm stupid if you don't think I don't know that. Josh shouldn't be mad at you for that, that is stupid. Your not being a very good friend. Friends are supposed to help each other out with their problems. All you ever say is get over it. It gets old after awhile. Right now all I need is a friend to comfort me, since my grandma is dyeing. Is that so wrong. That's all I'm asking for. I'm sorry if Josh is going to be mad at you for that. I feel better after talking to my mom about this whole thing. My mom helps me out a lot. She told me that you tend to loose your friends once you get into a relationship. I understand that now. She said that happened to my sister and her. My sister hangs out with her friends every now and then, but not like she used to. That's one problem off my shoulder. Well, I'm going to go and call my dad to figure out what is going on with my grandma.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well...so far today has sucked. My dad called me to tell me he can't pick me up because he is going to Virginia to see my grandma. She is in the hospital and is dyeing. So my life is going down hill, again. My best friend, Cassy, and I were going to go to my little brothers field day. Dustin wanted to go so I told him he could. Then, Cassy tells me she isn't going without Josh. I can't have that many people in the car. My mom won't let me and it's the freakin law. So now she isn't going. How would you feel if that happened to you? Not to mention what happened with, well ya know. Ya, well I feel like crap right now. I have no one to talk to right now. I can't talk to my mom because she is with my little brother somewhere. So I am home alone, my grandma is in Virginia dyeing. Yup this summer is going to suck. I really don't know what to do anymore. I feel like I don't matter to anyone. Well, I am going to go cry some more. That's what I have been doing for a week now, almost a week and a half. That's the longest I have cried in my whole life.   ~*Cassy if you are reading this, we might be mad at each other, but no matter what we will always be best friends.*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well...lets see here....what did I do today. I went to school(fun stuff), went to the smokies game with caroline and kayla, and that's about it. I had fun. The smokies games are actually fun when your not alone. I have been to 3 smokies games(fun stuff). I'm so tired right now. I'm trying to talk my mom into letting me drive to school Monday and Tuesday. Tuesday is my last day. I don't have any exams to take. Yea! Anywho....I was going to go to graduation today, but I decided to go to the game instead. This weekened my dad is going to give me money to get a swimsuit for Cassy's party. Can you believe that!?! A G-rated swimsuit! Please....me....g-rated.....ha!lol!...I'm feeling better. I'm starting to get over,well ya know....I think. I need to go get a job. I will have a job this summer. I want to go to the movies this summer, but I dont really have any one to go with, so I think I might go with a couple of my best friends, ya know for the heck of it. I'm going to go to bed now. I am tired! I have to finish packing tomorrow( I'm moving in with my sister). This weekened is Shawns(my sisters husband) last weekened here. He is getting shipped off to Iraq, and he will be gone for 2 years. That's really sad. I will be praying for him. Okay, now I'm really going to bed this time. Goodnight....sweet dreams.....toodaloo.....cya.....lata!...ok...im done...lol!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ROCCATCHER: she accidentally touched it one day  ~*Haha! I think you know what we're talking about...lol!*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm...well...I am an unloved person...I don't know what to do. I am so bored right now. I have no one to talk to and nothing to do. I could go driving, but I have nowhere to go, so whats the use...sigh....I have another headache.I really think I'm going to make a C in Algebra 2. I have been doing good in that class until this six weeks. I have had a lot of stress on me. Gosh!....this is drivin me crazy. I found something out yesterday that really depressed me. So I have been sad since then...I haven't really eaten much(I haven't been hungry). I'm not sure what I did for this to happen. I'm trying to forget about it, but ya now how that goes. I have a freakin research paper to type...fun stuff. Today Jeff Sims sat on me. His pants are pink and really tight....lol!  He is really weird, but funny. Anywho....I guess all there is to do is to think about what the heck I'm going to do this summer besides tryin to forget about....well ya know...Have you ever liked someone so much? I know I have. Don't you hate when they get your hopes up and then tell your best friend that they don't want to date you. Well that's what happened to me. Yeah it sucks big ones, but I guess I'm going to have to deal with it. I mean do I have a choice? It's really hard for me not to think about it because I see him everyday. I'm really not sure what happened, but oh well....hmm....what to do...what to do...It really sucks....I really liked him.....hmm....well....yup......so....sigh...Some of my friends really aren't helping me get through this. All they say is get over it. Thanks for the help...you really know how to make someone feel better. Well now I'm getting all emotional again, so I'm going to go outside and think some more. :(
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well....guys suck....Guys are so confusing. I just don't get it. I wish everyone would stop asking me what happened with me and colby. SHEESH!!! It's driving me crazy. I have a freakin headache now. I just got rid of the one I had yesterday now I have another. Life is full of stress. My best friend is moving, my brother-in-law is getting shipped off to Iraq, and then well ya know. This year has been so hard for me. It will get better when soccer starts. Soccer is my life....pretty much. I have soccer conditioning July 21-23. Then I have camp after that. I can't wait. Camp is so much fun, but lots of hard work and running(can't forget running). You get used to it after awhile. I actually love running, well I don't love it but I don't mind it(sometimes). It depends on how I feel. Like right now I'm not in the mood to run. Well..that's all I feel like saying for now. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I feel better. I took a shower and now I smell really good. I am so bored right now. I was supposed to go to my dads this weekened and then go shopping, but I forgot about my sister's wedding shower, which is tomorrow, so I had to cancel my plans. Shoot! I have a lot of makeup work for Algebra 2. I'm going to go do most of my homework and fix my mom a sandwich because she is too lazy to make one herself,lol. I have teacher's aide Monday so I will do the rest of my Algebra 2 homework then. Cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow! I feel really gross right now. I put tanning oil on me. Then, I went outside and cleaned the inside of my car, ran, and did crunches. I am so sweaty right now and I probably stink really bad too.lol! I'm going to go take a shower right now. I really need one. I am so hyper right now. I think before I go take a shower I am going to go run again. Toodaloo! Yea Soccer!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am so stressed out right now. Life is so confusing. Who invented money anyway? All it does is bring hate to the world. Trust me on this, I know. Why are the gas prices so high priced? I don't understand. I wish they would lower the gas prices. I wish I had a job. I applied for a job at the Christian Book Warehouse the other day. The lady there said she would call me. I hope she does, I really want that job. I need that job so bad. I thought having my drivers license would be great. I thought my life would have less stress, that I wouldn't have to worry about finding a ride to places I want to go to, but there's this thing called money, which you have to have so you can get gas to get to the places you want to go to. I don't have that, which means I can't go to the places I want to go. When I get a job, sure I will have money, but I still won't be able to go to the places I want to go, because I will be too busy working. What is up with that? Oh well...hopefully I will have a good day tomorrow. I sure didn't today. First, my stomach started to hurt. Then, I forgot my money for lunch(yeah I know I said I didn't have money, but I had some for lunch). Then, when I got home, I looked in my bag and I couldn't find my house key, so I was locked out for about an hour(it sucked). I was supposed to come straight home then leave again to go get my physical for soccer. Luckily my stepdad got home at 5:15pm and I made it in time to get my physical. It's going on 10pm, I'm tired and I have had a long day. I'm going to go to bed now. Crap! I have a freakin outline to do for Honors English 2. Oh well...I have teacher's aide tomorrow, I'll just do it then. I feel so much better getting this off my chest. Goodnight! :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I got really sick at school. I was in so much pain. I slept during most of 3rd period. I at the begining of lunch. When I got home I went straight to bed. I slept from 1-5:45pm. I had such a great dream, but I'm not going to talk about it. Even though I was sick, I was still in the best mood. That's unusual for me. I have been in the best mood for almost 2 weeks now. That will change soon. I am going to be so sad when Cassy moves. We have been friends since kindergarten. I thought we would graduate high school together, but I guess her mom isn't going to allow that. She is moving to Maryville. I don't know what I am going to do next year. School will be so boring with out. Just to let you know Cassy, you will be missed a lot. Okay I'm going to stop talking about this right now before I start crying. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, ya know that guy I told you about, he talked to me today. I feel better now. I am in the best mood. "I'm so happy, so happy..."-Cassy
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow! I have been in the best moods lately, but I have also been kinda sad. I'm trying to talk to this guy I really like(ya know, the hot guy I talked about earlier in my blog), but now he isn't really talking to me as much as he used to. I'm so confused right now. I feel like I have done something wrong, and I don't know what to do. I have never felt this way about a guy. He makes me smile, and he is so cute(especially in his camy pants). I know it sounds stupid, but I really like him. That's all I'm going to say for now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Don't you hate it when it rains. It seems to cancel what you have planned. Anyway, I'm not going shopping today,unfortunately. My mom wouldn't give me any money(she told me she would some other time before Cassy's party). I might go next weekened, if I have nothing else to do. I am so bored right now. Hmm.....what have I done today....I went to church this morning, talked to Dustin and Cassy.....that's about it. I think I might do some more crunches later before the evening service at church. I hope we(as in a bunch of people from church) go out to eat after church. We usually go to Crackel Barrel on 66. I have been there so many times. Well.....I guess I'm going to go now. Lata!:)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Life has been pretty good for me lately I suppose. I have an interview tomorrow at Rue 21. I have applied for about 7 jobs. I might be working at the smokies stadium with Tiffany and possibly Caroline(if she gets a job there). I will have two jobs...lol!..oh well...anywho,  If I get hired at Rue 21 I will be working there probably about 2 days during the week and on the weekeneds. If I get hired at the smokies stadium I will be working whenever they need me. I will have to work out a schedule for that. Soccer starts soon. Practices are from 9am-12pm, conditioning is July 21-23. Oh boy! I can't wait!....:/....I went running today with Kayla. I need to get her in shape. I think I'm going to make her run with me everyday. Some people are really mean, especially when you have known them forever. I'm not going to say anything else about that because she will just think I want people to feel sorry for me, but I don't care anymore. I'm fed up with it. Happy happy happy! I really do hope  I get a job at Rue 21. They have awesome clothes and flip flops. My mom took the internet away. My stepbrother was only supposed to be on this neopet website and my mom caught him looking at a bunch of dragon stuff. So I won't be online for awhile. She is bringing the computer to my(if you don't know, which you should by now, I live with my sister)house. My sister is going to get the internet sometime in July.hopefully. I was waiting to see if somebody would get online...oh well. I'm going to go. Love ya! Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a sad day. I had 20 minutes of sleep, woke up at 3:00AM, went to the guards to say goodbye to Shawn(my brother-in-law), I cried of course, but then again everybody was crying. There were a lot of people there. Well....anywho....at like 2:00 in the morning some guy starts banging on my neighbors door yelling for some girl named Claudia and he said that she had sex with him and gave him head. Then, my neighbor walks outside and starts pushing him. It was funny! I was about to go outside and tell him to shut up. Anywho....Last Wednesday I went job searching and applied for 4 jobs....fun stuff! It's raining right now. I hate when it rains, you can't do anything. I was going to lay out in the sun, but the sun isn't out. Oh well....I suppose I have nothing to do. I guess I will do some crunches later. I'm going to go now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I made it to my dentist appointment and back home alive. When I left to go to my appointment it was rainging really hard. It's hard to drive in the rain, especially on the interstate. I don't like driving in the rain. I could barely see. The only hard part about driving on the interstate(well it's not actually on the interstate) is getting on it. Anywho, I'm still at my moms house. My sister  is on the way here to pick me up so I can finally go home. I'm happy but not, because I have nothing really to do there. My brother-in-law, Shawn, leaves Friday morning to go to Mississippi for I don't know how long and from there he goes to California and then Iraq, I believe(or maybe it's Turkey and then Iraq, heck I don't know). He is going to be gone for 2 years, possibly longer. It's sad, but he is going to fight for our counrty. I hope he returns home alive and unhurt. Keep him and Ashley's brother(he got shot in the leg) in your prayers(I know I will). I hope they both return home alive. Okay well I'm going to go get my stuff together. I don't know when I will be back online. I might be online tomorrow after church. Okay, as Dustin says....I'm out!....lol!...Lata! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not bored anymore. I found some home videos of my birthday parties when I was young. They're quite hilarious. The things Cassy, Tiffany A., Caroline, Kayla, Ashley, Christy, and I did. We danced to Baby Got Back, Hokie Pokie(lol!), and The Macarena, so many times. One of these days I need to invite all them back over to watch them. Okay well I'm going to go now. It's starting to storm. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm still at my moms house. For the first time I'm going to be driving on the interstate to my dentist by myself. Wowa! Anywho, I'm still bored out of my mind. I'm talking to Ashley's 13 year old kid cousin. Yeah thats how bored I am. MMMMmmm! A cappicino blast sounds good....sorry just saw that commercial. I went to Cassy's blog and read some comments that were posted on there. Interesting....well heres one of the comments: ------------------------------------------------------------------  Comments: At 12:02 AM, Daniel said...  Man Jenna, it sounds like you smell really bad, how long did it take to get that smelly? Oh yeah, and I like Dustin's little thing at the end of his audio post, where he always says "Im Out"  ------------------------------------------------------------------ ~*You spelt my name wrong, Daniel. It's only one 'n'. I smell really good. Okay well I'm going to go now. Lata!*~ 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm still at my moms house...bored out of my mind...nothing to do...nobody is online...I want to go out and do something, but it's to freakin late. I would only have like an hour to do something. Hmm...I don't know what to do. I want to go home. I'm kinda bored with the computer now, but I have nothing better to do so I'm stuck on the computer. Lalala...I'm bored...okay I'm done for now. I guess I will talk to Michael Unger. I'm out!...:/....Lata!  Go blow a banana~Cassy...lol
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just woke up. I had a lot of fun yesterday at the lock-in. Cassy and I shot some pool and then Meagan Huffaker and Suzanna Sauls wanted to play so we picked teams. I was on Suzanna's team. We were winning until Suzanna was going to try to hit are last ball, but instead she hit the 8-ball. I'm actually pretty good at pool and volleyball. Maybe I should try-out for volleyball my senior year. I would this year, but they already had try-outs. Soccer is coming up. I'm kinda excited, but not really, because of the conditioning. That is pretty much just running. That's not really a bad thing. Oh well, it's only a 3 day conditioning, I'll live. Cassy is taking a shower right now(she really needs to...lol!). Anywho, Ashley finally got her permit. It's about time! Cassy still doesn't have hers yet and she is fixing to turn 16. You'll get it someday. Yesterday on the way back from the lock-in(on the church van) I gave Chris Hutton a massage...fun stuff...lol...and Blaine touched my leg. What a horndog! Anywho, Cassy is out of the shower now. She smells a lot better. Yesterday before the lock-in my mom and I went shopping. I had fun. I got a pink skirt(it's prettyful)and a shirt to go with it,of course. I also got 3 pairs of soffe shorts(gray,black, lightish blue), a tank top, 2 shirts, and 2 pairs of flip flops. Okay well anywho, I'm going to go now. Love ya bunches! Peace out!..lol! Lata Gata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HEY!!!! THIS IS CASSY!! ok here's Jena....Cassy is such a skank. Gosh! gotta love me! lol! Anyway, we all know she is my best friend, so I am allowed to call her a skank. Anywho...I'm going to a lock-in today at 8pm-3am. Yup...some fun stuff! this is cassy again.. everyone needs to go to Dustingamza.blogspot.com... because it is like THE best website there is... NOT! His audio posts are silly... Jena's dawg keeps looking at me... OH GOD IT'S COMING OVER HERE!! AAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH... lol "anywho" ... Jena bought a really short skirt today and she looks really... SEX-AY.. not she's a skank.. but anywho.. I almost lost the $110 braclet Josh got me today.. it fell off my arm and Jena saw it on the ground. That thing is UNSAFE. Maybe it fell off because it's TOO BIG!! well.. I am really bored. I have such boring friends.. jk Ashley is buying me soffe's. She's my best friend in the whoooooole world. lol JK...Jena is my bestest friend in the world. Okay Jena here...I'm gonna keel that cassy girl. Who does she think she is, posting stuff on my blog, the  nerve of that woman. My dog is raping cassy right now...too bad for you josh. this is cassy again.. Jena is a skank... She made her dawg rape me.Ya know what I think I'm done talking for now. I'm gonna go keel that skankho cassy. What a skank! She is wearing really short shorts right now. Who wears short shorts~Cassy. lol! Anywho, you people(Cassy) need to stop saying my word "anywho." Ketcha Lata Gata! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been awhile since I have posted something. Well anyway, life has been great for me. You might know why ;). Monday I went to Dollywood with a bunch of people. It was quite funny at the begining because Meagan Huffaker tripped and almost fell on her face. It was funny> This lady on the tram was laughing really hard. We(as in a bunch of people from church) couldn't stop laughing for about 10 minutes. You had to have been there. I had fun. Friday I'm going to a lock-in with my church youth group. I have been looking forward to it. Fun stuff! Okay well I have to go now. Lata!         ~*Jena*~ 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was funny! First Grady called me and Shawn answered the phone, but I'm not going to tell you what happened because it's too long. Later on in the day, I called Cassy and we decided to call Grady, that same time my little sister was listening to the macarina song, and Cassy was like hey macarina, and I guess it was Gradys mom who answered the phone and she heard Cassy say that and she was like hey whats up. We just started craking up laughing. It was funny(you had to have been there). Yesterday I went to Dollywood with Cassy, Ashley, Tracy and Dustin, we were going to meet Grady and a couple of his friends. I finally got to see what Grady looked like. He's hot! I had fun. This summer has been getting better and better everyday. Well except for tomorrow. I have to take the ACT at 8AM. It's 3 freakin hours long. Then, I have a soccer banquet to go to for the team I coached. That's at 11AM. I might go to the movies later on that night(hopefully). Okay, I'm done typing now...lol! Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Heeeey ya!!!! lol! Okay, I really don't have anything to say. Toodaloo!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't do much today. One of my best friends(Caroline) spent the night with me last night. We went swimming today. I had fun. I'm at my moms house right now. For everyone who doesn't know, I am finally moved into my sisters apartment. It's so pretty! I love it there. I Just got back in from running, playing soccer, and some basketball(Well, I didn't really play basketball, just shot some hoops). I love playing soccer so much. It is so much fun. I don't know how anyone could hate it or not understand it. I don't think I could ever get sick of playing soccer. I mean I have been playing for about 11-12 years now. That's a long time. Well, my life is going good. I feel so happy! I know what your thinking....the guy I like talked to me or asked me out. Yeah right! I don't think so. The guy I sort of like, I talk to all the time. No biggy! I'm just in a really good mood, that's all. I'm over the whole, well ya know, thing. It feels good to be over it. I'm so happy, so happy....(Cassy)..lol! Well, anyway..I'm not sure how long it's going to be before I get online or post something. I don't have to babysit my little siblings anymore. I might be back online on Wed. Oh heck! I don't know. I like having a blog. It feels good to get things off your chest. I think I might go back outside in a minute and run again or play some more soccer or basketball. Did I ever tell you where I live now has a football, soccer, softball field, a pool, gym(workout place), tennis court, volleyball net, and a  mile long trail. It's great! Wow! I am in the best mood. It could probably be better, but oh well. I'm going to go now. I am so hyper right now! Lalalala! Lata!             ~*Jena*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Life is crazy! There is too much drama in life right now. Crazy Crazy Crazy! Okay, well I'm tired now. It's going on 12(midnight, duh!) Good night! Sweet dreamz! Love ya bunches!   ~Dustin, if your reading this, Ashley wants you to read her blog.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, guess what! I'm in a really good mood. Heck! I'm in a great mood. My mom is freakin out right now because of a storm(she does that all the time, but one of these days her being afraid of storms is going to save my life). Anywho, well I need some new words. I'm getting tired of 'skankho'. It's gettin old. I'm so over that one guy I keep talkin about. I'm actually starting to like someone else, but I'm not going to tell anyone who it is. I might end up telling my best friend, but not till I know for sure I like him. Well, I'm going to do something now. I'm bored, but really hyper. I had a chocolate milkshake from mcdonalds earlier. It was really good. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nothing really happened today. I felt kinda sick earlier, but I feel better now. I made a new quiz, so take it.    urlLink Take this darn quiz!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well.....I was just kidding about the $200. I'm not sure what to do about something in my life. I have been really busy lately and I just don't think I have time for this one thing. I need to talk to one of my friends about it. Anywho....I'm really tan now. I got a new hair straightener. It's awesome! Soccer camp has been going pretty darn good for me. I'm on varsity....obviously.....lol!.....okay well I'm going to go home now. I'm fixing to get the internet at my house. Woo! lalalala! OKay ! Lata!      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;      Jena        &nbsp;    PAYDAY IS FRIDAY AGAIN!!!!!!! WOOHOO!!       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Finally!!!! Tomorrow I get my first paycheck! Yea!!!! I'm excited. It's supposed to be like about $200. I think I'm going to call that Vicky lady and work at the smokies stadium too.   I'm not working many days at Rue 21. I work like 2-3 days a week. Caroline works at the smokies stadium and she is off all next week because next week is all away games.  I can handle working at Rue 21 and the Smokies Stadium. Tiffany and I think they're desperate. Vicky keeps calling and surprisingly Tiffany hasn't got fired..... lol!....Anywho....I got my car finally and I got a cell phone! Wow! I have been getting a lot of stuff lately. I like it! lol! Before school starts I'm going to get my hair layered and all fixed up so that way I can finally wear it down.   There is a reason why I wear it up. No I'm not balded in some spots...there is really nothing wrong with my hair except I have these little hairs on the side of my head(I know everyone has them but not like me.    Mine are really bad, if ya know what I mean.) I'm so happy so happy so happy...... hmm... well... what is there to say. I am so sore right now. Soccer started yesterday.    I have conditioning wed-fri. Next week I have soccer camp Mon-Fri from 8am-4pm. Camp really isnt all that bad. Conditioning is the worst. All that is, is running.... fun stuff..  ....Ashley comes back from Florida soon.&nbsp; Okay well I'm going to go now. It will probably be another week or so before I post something else. Cassy If you are reading this thanks for the colorful idea. Yours looked better though. Lata!     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;      Jena      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sadly this will be my last post for awhile. My mom is fixing the computer. Hopefully my sister will get the internet soon.I won't have time for the internet in about a week anyway. Soccer starts in a week and 2 days. How exciten!....lol!....mmm....fun stuff! I need to run some more, but I can't right now. I'm fixing to go out on a boat with a couple of my friends(Kayla, Tiffany A., and Caroline). I have to go help Kayla finish cleaning the boat. Love ya!             ~*Jena*~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Jesus Rally was so much fun. I didn't get home till 11pm, but that's okay. I'm probably going to go today too. I enjoyed it. The guy there was really funny. There was this one song(he said it was a love song) about a girl he met at the flea market named Bernie. It was funny. Okay, well my summer is going pretty darn good if you ask me. I thought my summer was going to suck. I have had a lot of fun. This summer has actually been quite interesting. Sunday, I'm going on Kayla's boat for her birthday and then the Sunday after that I'm going with her to her rich uncle's house. She is having 2 parties. We are going swimming at her uncle's house. That's awesome...okay well I'm going to go wake up Kayla. That lazy butt needs to get in shape for soccer. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was fun. I went to the mall with Kayla. She was trying on a pair of shoes and didn't have the right size so the lady that works there went in the back to get her the right size, so while we were waiting Kayla was playing with the shoe sizer thing and some guy walks over to us and said that was the childrens one and he asked if we needed the womens one. She was so embarrassed. It was funny(one of those things where you had to have been there).Well I have to go. I'm fixing to go to a Jesus Rally. That's exciten! ttyl!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can tell today is going to suck. Cassy just IMed me saying if I would have taken her to the movies her and Josh wouldn't have got into a fight and broke up. Well a little news flash for you Cassy, I'm not made out of money, gas cost money. Don't go blaming me for you and Josh braking up. It's not my fault. This year we have got into so many fights. Every fight you blame something on me or it always has to do with Josh. The last fight we got into you started saying I never invite you to do anything, that's a bunch of bull. I ask you to do stuff with me all the time. When I do you're doing something with Josh. That doesn't bother me. You think it does, but it doesn't. Then you said that was the advantage of having a boyfriend. I'm really getting tired of this. I have other friends that I would like to do stuff with. Your not my only friend, so stop thinking you are. I have known you longer than all my other friends. I'm really tired of these stupid fights. I'm going to go now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm.....lets see here....what is there to say...um....I got the job at Rue 21. The manager is going to call me to set up my schedule. Ashley if you're reading this don't get mad, get glad. Hmm....I'm so bored...I was going to go to the movies with Cassy, Josh, and Kurt, but I didn't want to go see white chicks again. A little advice, don't go see it. It's so stupid. Well, I'm going to go now. There really isn't anything to say. Matt and Miike are outside shooting fireworks so I think I might go say hi. It's been awhile since I talked to Matt. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm.....lets see here....what is there to say...um....I got the job at Rue 21. The manager is going to call me to set up my schedule. Ashley if you're reading this don't get mad, get glad. Hmm....I'm so bored...I was going to go to the movies with Cassy, Josh, and Kurt, but I didn't want to go see white chicks again. A little advice, don't go see it. It's so stupid. Well, I'm going to go now. There really isn't anything to say. Matt and Miike are outside shooting fireworks so I think I might go say hi. It's been awhile since I talked to Matt. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back from Mississippi. I had the worst 4th of July ever. Friday it rained all day. Saturday I went to the beach and a jellyfish stung my arm. It hurt really bad, but I got over it. It got all bubbly and red. It's better now. I'm really bored and everyone is telling me to hurry up and get of the computer so that's what I'm going to do now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well....hmm.....yup....ok....I'm leaving tomorrow morning to go visit my brother-in-law in Mississippi. I will be back on Monday. Rue 21 is so unorganized. They have me going all over the place. It's crazy, crazy, crazy! Anywho....um...not much to say. I'm tryin to figure something out with my life. I hope it all turns out good. I'm gonna go now. Lata!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well....what is there to say....umm....my summer is over, soccer has started, and umm....I don't have time for a relationship(unless it's with a guy I go to the same school with because I would actually see him). The guy I was talking to likes someone else(from what I have heard). Oh well...that happens a lot, but that's okay. Anywho,I got my hair layered. It's so prettyful...lol! I went to Wally World the other day and my car broke down on me(I just got that car too). Something in the transmission messed up, so I had it towed to my dads work. I have my car back now. It's fixed! Yea! Anywho, how is everyone? I'm doing pretty good I guess. I have a scrimmage next Tuesday at 10am against Seymour. Should be a piece of cake. They aren't all that good(lol). It's a home scrimmage. So come and support me. My first real game is the 17th. That's against Pigeon Forge and it's an away game(@ Pigeon Forge). We beat them every year. Well....I'm really bored and tired. Tomorrow I get to run a lot(joy!). Fun stuff! I saw Colby last week. He was at the soccer complex doing therapy. He's still pretty darn hot. Okay well I'm going to go now. Toodaloo!        Jena   
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>