<Blog>


<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A new changed layout  I completely did a new makeover on the site (hopefully for the better...) i added a few things, switched a few things around. I will have daily updates on the blog now which makes it cool. Anyways, hope you like the layout, email me and tell me what you think!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Frankly..   Things today weren't too bad for my first day at centerville junior, i've gotta say the kids there are awesome and most of them were extremely kind. Today actually went way better then i would have expected, i was "escourted" around the school by my friend Jamie Olsen which was a big help. In answer to some questions about yesterdays post, yes, the title was from an Oingo Boingo song ;).   CJH is definitely a big school, the halls are sorted by letters which kind of messed me up a few times today, im really not used to it and i like the layout of FJH a ton better just because FJH was my home.   I remember when i first went into FJH, i had came to register for 7th grade because my family built a new house in Farmington so i came from Woods Cross Elementry with absolutely no friends. I was so nervous, i could remember walking in and saying "holy crap, this is huge" because coming from a small elementry school and going into a massive Junior High can cause someone to go into a coma with fear.   My first day of school at FJH was scary as sin, i only knew the people that were in my ward and that was about it. One of my first friends was probably Adam Stewart in 5th period Gym - Coach Down's class. It was crazy and fun... it was also kinda stupid, but i got used to it.  Theres nowhere else i'd rather be than FJH, unfortunately, theres not much i can do about that.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       In The News  if any of you have been watching the news lately you have probably heard about the student at Oquirrh Hills Middle school who inappropriately touched students at the school. Im a student myself and i know that if i were the principal and knew this was going on, i would have definitely stopped it sooner. I know that that kid is probably sitting in the detention center thinking that his life is going to be ruined and he will never be able to move on, but i also know that after he has gone through this, his life will be changed forever and he will look at life in a different way... always. Hes going to learn to appreciate it more, hes going to miss his friends, hes going to go through more emotional rollercoasters than he can possibly imagine, but i know that in the end, after anyone has gone through something so severe, they will come out a better person no matter how much media attention he gets.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       we close our eyes   Most of you by now know that i have been having some problems in my life because of a poor choice that i made. And its starting to seem like no matter what i do I cant get away from this. A few days ago i went to court for what i did and i remember walking into the courtroom ready to face what i did wrong with the judge. After being in the courtroom for about 5 minutes i found out that judge wasnt as .. lets say.. "kind" as i would have thought, but hey, what are taxes for.   As far as posting on my website i hope that my free speech rights are still enforced, you can go to the top left hand link on my website to visit the free speech online campaign which I back 100%. http://www.eff.org/br/  The free speech campaign doesnt mean that i believe that people can say bad and mean things to people on the internet and get away with it, what it means is that i shouldnt be persecuted for writing my feelings on my own website domain which i purchased with my own money.  Okay - Back to what i was writing about. It seems that i can never escape what i did and that it will never leave me alone, just when i thought that the punishment was almost over it starts back up again. Theres just one thing that i want to say to anyone who is reading this, and i hope you listen - never, ever mess with the law.    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       dream big   heres a pretty cool song i found on the net, its not rock music but i still think it owns.   urlLink Dream Big 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       fixed.. and...stuff...   well the government page is fixed, it appears it was broke 10 minutes after it went up. Thank you MASSIVE visitors!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Announcements Announcements Annnnoouuuccceeeemmeennnttss!    Well i added a new "STUPID GOVERNMENT" Page, its under the funny as sin productions. That should hold you over for awhile until i can get some other stuff going.   Peace Out 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       staying alive  Im sorry, i just had to make the title of this post "staying alive" because that song 0wned J00! Sorry about that. Its the caffeine. This is once again Zack, i guess im just going to update whenever i can get the chance. Centerville is an okay school, when i say okay that means that "Zack likes farmington more and he wishes he could be back", that kind of okay.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       thanks!  this is just a quick post to thank everyone who reads the site and supports it, because what you get on this site is the true, uncut, unsensored, and... "non-shoutouty" website straight from the shutt. No JR.High shout outs here, only true blue through and through.  Peace
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Good for nothing script kiddies  My man Wil Wheaton is having major problems with script kiddies over at his site, www.wilwheaton.net, i cant stand it when they do this to Wil.  He writes:   I am done dealing with childish attention-whore script kiddie crapflooders...  ... I am offering $1000 for information that leads to the arrest and successful prosecution of anyone involved in the crapflooding of this website. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       how can things play out like this   for those of you that dont know whats been happening during the past few months heres a play-by-play, I threatened 2 girls because i delt with my anger in a bad way. After that, i wasnt accepted back into my home school and was sent to davis junior high to be evaluated (in which i passed with flying colors.) This was obviously a bad decision on my part to say those things, i had never had any kind of history in the past and i had never even gone on a trip to the office. After i got out of Davis Junior, it was a battle to get me back into my home school but we succeeded. After being at school for 3 weeks things were going great, i was having a great time with school and anxiously waiting for summer vacation like everyone else. Until at the beginning of my 4th week, i was going to court for what i did, it wasnt really any big deal because my lawyer breifed me on what the outcome would suppossidly be so i wasn't too worried.        After walking into the courtroom and talkiing with the judge things werent going too bad, but they werent going too great either. The judge decided that in the victim's defense (the "victims" were not present at the hearing) she would remove me from my school, we had a meeting with the victims before i went back into the school where they agreed at me going back to my school. So after working so hard and doing everything that was expected of me, somehow i still came up short, now i have to try and fit in with a school of totally new people. I had talked to one of my friends at my old school who has connections to a few people at my new school, she commented that everyone over there thought i was a "weirdo."   Right now im at a loss, and dont know what on earth to do, or what im doing.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        written by zack shutt       whos got my back now?  another day at cjh.. the days at school keep growing longer and more untolerable, i cant stand it, i miss my friends, i miss my school, i miss everything and its ruining me. I worked so hard to get back to FJH and now its all taken away from me? This makes no sense.. life shouldnt be like this  welcome to this blessed nation..
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Post Written by: Zack D. Shutt         The past week hasnt been too horrible, but i really miss FJH and everyone there, it was awesome. CJH is a big school, full of people that i dont know and probably never will. Its really dumb not to know anyone because you kinda of just stand there like a loser and watch everyone there thats been friends since 7th grade, but i guess i dont get that 'priviledge' because i got booted out of my school by the "system", but hey what can you do?        I dont know when people are finally going to realize that im sorry for what i did, yes! you read that right! Zack Shutt is sorry for what he did, and if you didnt already know that then shame on you. I dont know what they see in me that is so dangerous, i recently was ordered to get a psychological evaluation, no problem, i went through it and the psychatrist said "why are you here?!" I cant be crazy, but people just dont care.   And life goes on...  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       shutt's trip to russia   I've been wanting to blog about this the day i found out back in January, but i couldn't because i was sworn to secrecy by my parents. So here it is: In June me and my family are going to Russia to adopt a 8 month old baby girl.   I've been so excited about this, i've always wanted another sibling to replace my current sister since i think she was a lemon of a sister. haha just kidding, anyways we are going there about the 3-4th week of june for 2 weeks, im going to take pictures and we are shooting video there about the whole thing, its goin national and its hosted by yours truely.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       a blogging revolution?   I have lots of friends that own blogs, their all over the country blogging on their websites, i was talking with my friend Alex who owns a website and we have come up with the idea of a nationally syndicated blog with many different writers, kind of like a newspaper. We're basicly brainstorming now but we need a good name for the website, Alex says "Scattered Brain" would be a cool name, but send me and email with your suggestions.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       fixing up the old site  well im fixing the site, updating some of this and some of that. I made it so my online auctions actually work now! Yay! Today looks like another boring day, but i've somewhat talked my parents into letting me take an early vacation because of school and how much i "dislike" it right now. Farmington sweet farmington eh? Well on the last day of school im going to try and go over across the street from farmington and sign yearbooks since im not allowed on the school's premesis.  Things dont look like their really getting any better in my life, so taking an early vacation to get my mind off everything can't be too bad for the body. I'll update the blog while im in blanding as much as i possibly can, i wont be leaving for about a week so until then.   Shutt out.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Blanding sweet blanding   Everyone has a place to get away, as for me, my place is little old Blanding Utah. Its a small town in southern utah, it holds tons of some of my favorite childhood memories.. i remember riding horses with my grandad it was great. And more recently, i remember sitting on the beach of a small lake they have, teaching canoeing at a boyscout camp, this is one of my favorite things to do, i love working with the scouts. I remember when one of my friends at the camp came running down to the waterfront to tell EVERYONE he just got his mission call, it was probably one of the most exciting things that happend that summer. I can also remember the camp director warning the staff about bears, and right after he finished talking about how dangerous they are, we heard a big loud bear roar in the background, good times. The reason i've been thinking about this place so much is because school is ending soon, and i cant stand my new school, plus there is no place i would rather be than in blanding, its my ultimate #1 place i would ever want to be. Theres not lots of malls. Theres not lots of people. But... thats Blanding, i love every minute of it.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       my new hair  heres a link to my much hated new hair color.  urlLink New Hair 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       is this the "cool thing" to do now?  heres a link to a story on KSL's website,. urlLink LINK , its about a kid who threatened to shoot everyone at his high school and when police searched his home they found drugs. Police found violent plots, pictures, drugs, and other stuff that would make him out to be a dangerous person. But theres one thing that is extremely familiar with their case and what i did, they both got charged with the same felony charges as i did.  Theres one thing i want everyone to consider when they hear about this case, before saying to yourselves "jeez, this kid is an IDIOT, i cant believe that! he deserves the death penalty", before doing that i want you to think about his family and how they are feeling. Also think about the kid himself, the kid is 15 and hes already on the news! How damaging is that going to be for him? After hes gone to all of his anger management classes etc., whos going to go to the prom with him? Whos going to be his friend? Just consider it. Because sometimes the media can make things seem different than they actually are, trust me they can. Update: People seem to misunderstand what im saying, im NOT saying hes innocent, im saying that once hes paid for what hes done where does he go from there? And will his punishment ever stop?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       new and insane drawing  got bored again, check out my pretty picture  urlLink here 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       the wheat thins box   I've just noticed something crucial to the survival and well being of this country, the original wheat thins box looks like the crackers are growing mold. Dont believe me! Look for yourself! The crackers have a tint of green and its the most disguisting thing i will ever witness. Nabisco can kiss my butt.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Mr T.'s as guest   
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       boredom is an art   heres a picture i drew, i think its refridgerator worthy.  urlLink My little drawing 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       if you get 1 thing out of this   Well its practially summer vacation for me, so dont be suprised if you see the blogging increase becuase of my increased amount of time i cant spend writing. Im also going to spend alot of time working on my business, right now i have a wholesale pallet bid on 81 shelter tents to sell on eBay, hopefully that works out. Thanks for reading this site, i know its been crappy sometimes and my life has been up and down the past little while but i appreciate everyone that reads it. If theres 1 person that gets something out of my blog then thats all i care about, i could care less if i get 200 visitors a day or even 1,000 a day. The blog is more for me than anyone else, so if you get anything out of it then great job!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Blogging is fuuuunnn  
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       all is good, back to kentucky in a wagon   Turns out Eccles didnt mean to diss me at all, thanks Zac Clark for the wonderful speech on how eccles is trying to ruin me, sure helped things. Anyways all is cool and, aside from all that. Im a right leaning libertarian =). If your not a politics person stop reading here. Okay, now that your with me, go to http://www.lp.org/, i think these people actually know whats going on! Ever wanted to find out what political party you belong in? Go here to check it out! http://www.lp.org/quiz/  For those Al Franken haters, get together with me after school sometime and we can throw oranges and grapefruit at his house ;).    Heres what i scored on the politics quiz:  According to your answers, your political philosophy is centrist.   Centrist  Centrists favor selective government intervention and emphasize practical solutions to current problems. They tend to keep an open mind on new issues. Many centrists feel that government serves as a check on excessive liberty. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Blog from the land down under  
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       wendys frys and left  over pizza   dont even ask me where i got the title, i just got bored.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just made a cool movie, check it out. urlLink My Movie  Please allow enough time to load.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink  Shrek 2 LIVE 
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      float on man..  urlLink Listen  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i've always been extremely proud of my website. I put a lot of time into it and i hope you people as readers enjoy it also. Its awesome to see people make blogs and websites, I just went through lots of my old material that i wrote back in 2002 when i was in 6th grade and owned the site. Its amazing to see how people evolve from that point, its awesome. One of my friends from Davis Junior decided to make a blog, that is so cool (http://monicaquire.blogspot.com/), having a blog is like my "motivation" because if it were just in a journal i would never write in it because nobody would read it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will tell you what utah is and why i have a big problem with it. Those of you that love Utah to death, its probably because you fit into the category of the judgemental people that own the stupid state.   Welcome to the Utah State of mind.    1. If you arent mormon. Your not my Friend.   2. If your momon and you screw up, i will gossip about you until the day your caskette is placed into the ground and sacrament hymns are sang around your grave. While they sing. I spit.   3. Got a problem in your life? No REAL Utahn ever has problems and shows it, naturally, so im going to talk to  everyone  around me and tell them about your problems and my view on it. This makes an awesome discussion.   4. If you dont cruise in a bentley or your making $120,000+ a year, your automatically pig trash and deserve to be fed to donkeys and sent to a zoo to live with alligators.   5. if  I  think theres something wrong with your family, instead of being nice and helping you, im going to make it seem like all you do is leech off other people and demand support.   6. Need gas for the lawn mower? WELL GOSH DARN NEIGHBOR, GO AHEAD AND TAKE MY GAS CAN, INFACT, DRAIN THE GAS FROM MY CAR, I TRUST YOU WITH ANYTHING BABY.   7. If you arent like me, and if you dont act like everyone else, your automatically weird and i dont want to be seen with you.  You know, traveling out of Utah you see what your missing out on. Neighbors that arent closed minded, people who genuinely care about you without the fake love bull crap. People here maybe will learn not to be so closed minded and  maybe  stop judging before they even know the person.  For instance the guys at davis junior high, those guys ROCK. Their awesome people but its intimidating at first when you meet them... why? Because of what everyone tells you. Because of all the gossip. Because people cant learn to treat these kids like human beings, and i've gotta tell you, thats the worst thing of all.  Do me a BIG favor please, if you know someone that acts like this then GET AND ENVLOPE. STICK THIS LETTER IN THERE. AND PUT IT IN THEIR MAILBOX. Infact im going to make it easier for you. go to  urlLink Here  and you can print off a copy of this to pin up in your room, and maybe even give to someone who could use it. Lets change Utah because its seriously bugging the heck out of me. Now dont get me wrong, some utahns are nice and dont act this way, but if your offended by this, then your probably one of them that is. KINDEST REGARDS Zack D. Shutt
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      how is fjh treating everyone? I know this is a random question to ask but i've heard some rather negative stuff about this last bit of school from different people. I've also heard TONS of complaining about the officers for next year, more than i heard when the elections were over, whats going on over there?
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Anything BUT School   Today was probably the most interesting day ive had for awhile. I was at my dads work walking around outside the building when a bird fell out of its nest. So naturally i went over and assimilated it as my own, it now resides at my dads work. Its kind of funny, i actually got it to eat bread and drink my coca-cola. Im going to take care of it until it gets better, so theres going to be daily "Bird Progess Posts" on the photo-blog.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink  You Can Tell Im Tired 
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       updates at zackshutt dot com   I added a cool feature called the "photo blog" which basicly means zack gets to be annoying and carry his digital camera everywhere while snaping shots of interesting things. I literally carry it around and i take pictures of things i find interesting on that day, its located on the right side of this page. You should check it out, I will also have daily updates. And hey! i got a NEW Guestbook! I've been looking for a new one with a simple setup, i finally found it. So go ahead and post a comment.  Peace
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I just finished watching a really awesome movie. Its called "conspiracy" and its about the nazi's and their plan to destroy all jews using gas chambers. Check it out. It owned.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was awesome. I spent too much money at lagoon buying my season pass and renting a locker (which i forget to get my towell and swimming suit out of before 8:00 so i couldnt get the stuff out of the locker). I went with Kensley and Amy which was tons of fun, but my passport photo looks like complete crap, im going to upload it to the website tomorrow so you guys can see exactly how dorky i look (HAT HAIR!).  I've been listening to a lot of emeinem lately because it seems to help my frustration with the people around me.. because lately i've been really struggling with people who are so enthused about trying to make my life a living.. well you know what comes next.  Line of the day: I am one of Satan's minions, but in more of a ceremonial  role
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey i just noticed something, there are things called Jelly Bracelets that have colors referring to different acts, some say it is just a stupid urban legend that no one paid attention to, until Biddy Nation got wind of it, and then said that these bits of plastic were wrong to have. So, of course kids now wear them. I want to buy them, too, just (and only) so I can piss off Biddy Nation. The rebellion through Jelly Bracelets has begun!  P.S. Im starting the "line of the day", personally thought up by myself.  Line Of The Day:  I hope in the future Americans are thought of as vicious, warlike people. That way, high schools could use ‘The American’ as their mascot
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well thanks to everyone that came through for me and signed my yearbook! It was great to be able to have that happen, i really liked having seeing you guys for one last time (maybe?). I really hope that i can come back to fjh next year, being there today made me realize that school OWNS. It really does. I went to CJH for awhile and to be completely honest i like FJH a whole lot more. The people, the staff, the assemblies, everything about fjh is great.  But you dont realize that until your out.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      COME ONE, COME ALL TO THE SIDEWALK ACROSS FROM FJH TOMORROW AFTER THE ASSEMBLY IT WILL BE THE LAST TIME THIS YEAR TO SEE THE MAN, THE MYTH, THE LEGEND ZACK SHUTT! HE WILL BE SIGNING YOUR YEARBOOKS, ABSOLUTLY FREE!!! COME JOIN THE THRILLS, THE CHILLS, AND THE SPILLS OF WHAT IS SURE TO BE ONE CRAPLOAD OF A PARTY!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i found out im leaving for blanding the middle of next week. Its gonna be great. Just to get away from all this for a few weeks. I  will  still do daily Aud-Blog updates so you can listen to me in my virtual paradise tell you whats goin on with 'da shutt.' Im not quite sure if im going to be able to do "written" posts from there, i'll have to see what im allowed to do.   I will see everyone across the street from FJH on Friday. I hope to see you guys there! Its gonna be a great way to end the year with all the crap thats been going on.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does anyone have cats? Or want a cat? I have 1 homeless baby kitten who is extremely adorable and needs a good home. My friend Monica is trying to find it a cool place to live, so c'mon man... let it chill with you... please?   -Thanks Guys Zack Shutt
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heres my book! :  urlLink MY BOOK 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Virgins can get STDs, too. This is from a Salt Lake Tribune article, where teens who pledge to abstain can get diseases just as often as kids who have sex. Very interesting. Im not going to supply my opinion on this, not because its inappropriate, but because i want to hear your opinions first.  urlLink Link To Article 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Therapy is expensive. Bubble wrap is cheap. You choose.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hope everyones having a good holiday. Im going on a hike up Davis Creek in just a little bit, but not before stopping by some fast food restuarant and getting breakfast, im way to lazy to make my own. I might post an audio-blog from my hike if my phone gets good enough reception, so check it out.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey, i made a new movie, this one is kinda big so give it a second to load. Thanks.  urlLink New Movie 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from a quick walk to get ready to go on a hike tomorrow for memorial day. Theres something i have been meaning to write about for awhile. My dad and I were driving around in Salt Lake and i looked at a store that had floor mats for sale. and in the front they had a doormat that was the american flag, what? This false patriotism crap has gone way too far, Im glad that everyone wants to let everyonelse know how their with us and not against us. And i think its terrific that everyone wants to express their patriotism but THE AMERICAN FLAG AS A DOORMAT? Whats wrong with you people? Why would anyone even make that? You know its bad enough that they make american flag boxers and bathing suites, but a doormat? That you wipe your freakin feet on? Why is this okay?
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well right now im listening to "Summer In The City By CCR" which is a great classic summer song. I have my plans for going down to southern utah all done. Tomorrow im leaving at about 1:00 to head down there with someone that works for their school district (my uncle is incharge of all the transportation in that district) so that should be interesting, riding 6 and a half hours with someone i dont even know. I know. It does sound like a party!  Expect Audblog updates everyday up until Sunday the 13th, because that day i will be leaving to go to the scout camp. And during that whole week i wont have any access to phones so obviously the audblog wont be updated for about 1 week.   Then after that week is over, i come home for Saturday and Sunday but leave again on Monday. So expect audblog updates (long ones) on that Saturday and Sunday. Then ANOTHER week of scout camp starts so no blog updates again.  After those two weeks the daily updates will start streaming in from Audblog. So dont worry. I've got ya covered.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey i found out me and Will are *distant* relatives. Which is cool. Who would have thought? Anyway i thought that was kind of an interesting discovery and everyone should bow down to me and kiss my feet because .. well i dont know.. im just really tired and i cant think of anything else better to talk about.  UPDATE: I Updated the about me page, okay it was really late and i was totally wasted. Leave me alone. Creamed corn.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Summer the days get longer, the pants get shorter as with Winter the days get shorter and the pants get longer! Hmmmmm think about that one!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I thought of the absolute randomist(is that a word) thing ever! Cinnamon Raisin bagels in a toaster covered in Philadelphia Cream Chesse and Welch's Grape Jelly. I wanna see a Star Trek 11, let's go Wil Wheaton you could captain your own ship. The U.S.S. Wheatonator. muhhahahaha with me a commander we could eliminate the galaxy of Klingons and Romulans. Until next time this is Clark saying mmmmmmm where's the hairy-pitted French chicks!?  -Clark
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shutt here seems Clark has opened his own Blog. I thought I give you the link to it just to check it out. Here it is http://clarkschillhut.blogspot.com/  Check it and drop him emails to tell him what to improve on!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that everybody knows someone from Blanding, UT. A load of my family lives down there and so does Shutt's grandparents. So if you know someone from Blanding will you email cause most likely I know who it is and I will respond to you. Props to the readers!-Clark
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Clark here, I was sent this email from Zack! It seems that his computer that he is using in Blanding won't let him onto blogger so I'll be posting his emails from time to time. Enjoy!  Okay well its been an overall good time here in Blanding, between the late night 11:00-12:00 driving around with a bunch of guys in the Expedition making stupid jokes about irish people (seriously, jokes about the irish). And chillin' with all the teens in the town just outside of "Mel's Video Store" the one and only run down shack that the citizens of Blanding affectionately call a "video store."  The only real downside to being down here is not being able to see Kensley and my friends, thats not the best, but just being down here has done exactly what i expected it to do: get my mind off things back in Farmington and just.. get away.  I had two weeks of scout camp which i can really say was an awesome thing to be a part of (i will have pics of the camp and the guys that worked with me as soon as I get back). I taught canoeing and helped out a little bit with rowing, it was really cool. I had the opportunity to help a disabled kid get his canoeing merit badge which i am really proud of, in all honesty, I think he deserved the merit badge more than half the kids that got it.  Anyways, i will try to update at least 1-2 times a week, i'll see what i can do.   Peace out Farmington.  -Shutt
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Clark here, I talked to Shutt on Saturday and it sounds like he should be home about the 1st of August. Then we all can party like there's no tomorrow. Enjoy this post from Shutt. Peace  Well hello to everyone, from out here in Blanding Utah! Im starting to get a little bored here... thats probably how Blanding got its nickname... “bland”...  For those of you who have a vocabulary of about 14.5 words, “Bland” means boring or plain. Just a little helper for yah.  Tomorrow i head off to the allmighty gas station to grab a phone card so i can once again make phone calls to my close friends such as clark and kens. I’ve gone through 1 disposable camera and im looking to snap through a new one. Im waiting for my dad to send me some more cash so i can get busy on all these money consuming tasks that i, sadly, have to do.  Its been a lot of fun riding fourwheelers and chasing people around Monticello with 15 people crowded into a Ford Expedition driven by a crazy 16 year old. But hey, it all works.   Shutt is still crazy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its quiet.. deception lurks everywhere  unsuspecting is its victim  it launches, confirms suspicions  shatters lives, ruins trust  something built supposidly so strong collapses and leaves nothing  nothing left to have. nothing left to hold onto.   As life gets worse.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello everyone out there in farmingtown land. This is your favorite Zack D. Shutt finally posting on the website. This computer lets me use blogger so expect Shutt on MSN AND posting on the website. Holy cow. Awesomeness.   Blanding is the coolest. Lots of nice people who arent judgemental (yay! it feels like Pakistan!) but overall things are nice.  See you all on the 21st or the 22nd. Until then....  Shutt out
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>


<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Shot Of The River! YES!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If something isn't in her mouth to suck on; well thats another story..&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Way too interested in other things than pictures!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The plane Dale And Reesalee took&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just lookin' out the window&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This one is for everyone who wondered what a Russian wall looks like ;)&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>


<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    If you cant see the display words, double click on the image, it says "S To The Hutt"&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I just bought this dvd, its really awesome. But really graphic =)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I **heart** my coke&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    its sad satan my bird!, i wrapped it in the only thing around, a dirty towell on the ground outside my dads work&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this should be my first car&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    find it baby&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    thirsty?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    EWWW&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i had to visit cjh to get my homework. I'll always be a visitor at that school.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is a little hard to read, but its the custom sticker that i put on all the computers i assemble.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my ultimate favorite place to go at my whole house. i friggen love my waterfall.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    12:29 on a sunday night, PSH BEDTIME!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    cocentrate dad.. concentrate&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    YOU SUPRISED ME!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    isnt this so true?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    if there ever was a conflict with 2 pictures, this would be it. Freedom mixed with communism. Wonderful&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    its a workspace of my own!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    how does that girl live with me...?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>