<Blog>




<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      smells like teen spirit. such a great song.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sorry, sira nanaman ang freindster. ayaw magsend ng message. im sorry, now at least you know the events on april 24. ewan ko ba. baliw ako sa iyo. and frankly speaking, i dont even know where i stand. iyon lang ang gusto kong malaman. im just so lost in you and... and.. nawala na sa isip ko yung paulitulit na sinasabi ko sa sarili ko kanina. basta. im in love with you. and i just dont know.. wla na.. ewan ko.. in love ako sa iyo. period. and i dont  know what to do. and.. it just sucks to be this way. that i might never get to know you. naalala mo ba nung nag videoke tayo kay paolo. i felt you were someone i could really spend my life with. someone who is real and, true, and happy, and great and beautiful and, and, and then reality hit me, na hindi mo ako gusto, pero ewan ko, i just want to hear it from you, ayokong sa iba nangagaling. sorry. pero i need to. and want to know where i stand. kung ano ako sa iyo. sabihin mo, dont be polite, just tell it to me, blunt, frank. ano ako sayo?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I want to dedicate this song to you, "thet". you will be loved. you are loved. by me. and you are missed. i miss you, a lot. come to think of it, i never really got to know you.   She will be loved  Beauty queen of only eighteen She had some trouble with herself He was always there to help her She always belonged to someone else  I drove for miles and miles And wound up at your door I've had you so many times but somehow I want more  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved And she will be loved  Tap on my window, knock on my door I want to make you feel beautiful I know I tend to get so insecure It doesn't matter anymore  It's not always rainbows and butterflies It's compromise that moves us along My heart is full and my door's always open You can come anytime you want  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved And she will be loved And she will be loved  And she will be loved  I know where you hide Alone in your car Know all of the things that make you who you are I know that goodbye means nothing at all Comes back and begs me to catch her every time she falls  Tap on my window, knock on my door I want to make you feel beautiful  I don't mind spending every day Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved And she will be loved And she will be loved And she will be loved  Please don't try so hard to say goodbye Please don't try so hard to say goodbye  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain  Please don't try to hard to say goodbye     
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       i am still in love with her. god, why is it hard to stop lovingsomeone that you've loved for thepast three years. i loved her before i even knew i did. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      id always imagine myself with her. that we'd slow dance to "balisong" by rivermaya.  she's just so perfect.. so perfect.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Patay  Ilang beses na akong humiling sa Diyos na gumawa siya ng paraan na patayin ako. Ayokong mag-suicide, masyadong maraming nagsusuicide ngayon, masyadong common. Gusto ko iba naman.  Okay lang sa akin ang mamatay, wala naming mawawala sa akin, wala naman akong mahalagang gamit, wala rin namn sigurong purpose ang buhay ko, kung mayroon man, sigurado akong isa itong purpose na kahit sino ayang ganapin.   Naawa lang nga ako sa mga iiwan ko, mapupuyat sila, magagastos.  Medyo gusto ko pa ngang mamatay eh, at least malalaman ko kung may diyos nga talaga, kung may satanas, impyerno, langit at purgatoryo, kung wala naman ang lahat ng iyon, walang diyos, walang satanas, walang afterlife, okay rin. Sana naman, at least, may reincarnation, or buddha or allah or something else. Ayoko lang talagamng paniwalaan na pagkamatay ng isang tao’y tapos na ang lahat.  Madalas kong iniisip kung  ano kaya ang pakiramdam ng patay, yung katulad pa rin ba ng dati? O pag sakalign walang diyos, empty lang ang mararamdaman mo, tapos wala na.  Hindi ko pa alam, hindi pa kasi ako namamatay. Pero kung sakaling mamatay nga talaga ako, nasisiguro ko na hindi sa langit ang bagsak ko. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The Lost Soul    urlLink   What sign of the Black Zodiac are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
               urlLink   what will your band be?        name:         age:         sex:         do you lke cats?     yes  no  yes, with ketchup  i'm more of a dog person  i hate cats!!  i feel indifferent        you'll call your band:      newxwavexbattlecore        you will sound like:      pedro the lion        lyrics:      the steering wheel, rusted under her tears, became her sun              This   QuickKwiz   by  urlLink  cowboysbecamefolkheros   - Taken 569 Times.         
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
              urlLink   what will your band be?        name:         age:         sex:         do you lke cats?     yes  no  yes, with ketchup  i'm more of a dog person  i hate cats!!  i feel indifferent        you'll call your band:      newxwavexbattlecore        you will sound like:      pedro the lion        lyrics:      the steering wheel, rusted under her tears, became her sun              This   QuickKwiz   by  urlLink  cowboysbecamefolkheros   - Taken 569 Times.         
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       nobody made me feel this way before. shes all i ever wanted and more. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       in love with her. she makes me feel like no other person can. she brings me light when no other candle will. she gives me reason to live when there is totally none. im in love with you maria theresa mendiola. and though i may be too drunk, or STUPID to realize what im doing this very instant, know that what i feel for you is true. those four white flowers, they dont mean anything. at all. i prepared this long speech, about you, and love, and things like it, and who your are to me, but you took all the words away. i learned something, it's better to have loved and lost, than never to have loved AT ALL. im in love with you, the whole world and everyone else in it comes second to that. goodnight. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      may scroll down button po ag blog ko, just in case you couldn't see them.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      !@#@#$#@$^$%&%*^()  dsad:SAD"SA><>A"AS:{A}{AS?SA:687654321687qwpeipwqoyhsjxzbv,mxbklwehf!@$!~~~  Testing. 1" "! "2" "@" 3" "#"  abakadaboboka..
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Revamped my Blog
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Looks nice eh?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow. Gradweyt na ako. Pasado. Tapos na ang highschool. College na ako. ‘Steeg! Lupet! Sa wakas ay maiiwan ko na ang halos kasuklaman kong iskwela sa dami ng mga masasamang alaala na ibinigay nito sa akin.  Pero… Kahit papano’y mamimiss ko rin ito. Hindi ang iskwela mismo, kundi ang mga tao.  Mamimis ko ang pagising ko ng six o’clock para laman makapunta sa iskwela, mamimiss ko ang pag wawalis at pag-aayos ni migs sa classroom nila(na katabi ng classroom namin na katabi ng clasroom ng “love” ko na katabi naman ng clinic/faculty room/AVR [oo, isang room lang iyun]).  Mamimiss ko rin ang pagbati sa mga taong dumadating na kakilala ko tuwing naka-trip ako at hindi masyadong galit sa mundo at lahat ng laman nito.  Mamimiss ko ang pagtitig sa mga magagandang dilag ng aming paaralan. Wala lang, mamimiss ko lang talagang gawin iyon.  Mamimiss ko ang pagtawa sa mga “joke” ng mga komedyante sa IV-Newton.  Mamimiss ko ang mga teacher ko sa 4th year, sila ang pinakamatalinong set ng teacher ko, kaso wala lang talaga akong naalala sa mga tinuro nila (derivative of 1 is 0… ok… ok… kaya pa yan.).  Mamimiss ko ang pag “fuck you” ko kay Jimjim tuwing wala akong magawa dahil walang kwenta siyang tao (joke…).  Mamimiss ko ang pag-iwas ko kay Pating dahil may utang pa rin ako sa kanyang pera.  Mamimiss ko ang pagsuntok sa pinto ng Galilei dahil nababadtrip ako.  Mamimiss ko ang pagsunto sa poste ng building na nasa tapat ng pinto ng IV-Galilei dahil nababadtrip ako.  Mamimiss ko ang paglambitin sa tabingin crossbar sa tapat ng Galilei dahil wala akong magawa.  Mamimiss ko ang over-priced food sa canteen area. Hoy! Walang kwenta… Ang mamahal ng mga tinda niyoh!  Mamimiss ko ang Pag-tusok ng pishbol at squeedbol at kikiyam at pagsawsaw sa napakaduming sauce.  Mamimiss ko ang pag-sulat ng kung anu-anong bagay sa blackboard naming na wala naming koneksyon anu pa man sa pang araw araw na buhay ng IV-Galilei.  Mamimiss ko ang pakikipag-daldalan ko kay Ella at pag-tawag sa kanya ng “baluga” kahit alam namin na mas maitim ako sa kanya.  Mamimiss ko sina Shang Cai Chek, Mao Tze Tung, Gary Lising, Mika Immonen, Bernardo Bernardo, Standard, Boy Nigger, Krishna “the nonsense boy” lapitan, dara, cire, dada at wala nang iba. Mamimiss ko sila dahil naaalala ko na “star-studded ang IV-Galilei. Mamimiss ko ang Computer Lab ng ACNHS – SSC dahil sa dami ng games na available duun, daig pa ang Internet café.  Mamimiss ko rin ang Math Park, halos lahat ng kalokohan na ngayon ay pinagsisisihan ko nagyon ay dun naganap.  Mamimiss ko ang bread Stix building na binansagan ni Erin, Duon naganap ang confrontation ng mga fourth year sa Einstein at nagsigawan si Thet at Alfranzel at sumingit si cole para magmoderate at kumulo ang dugo ni Francis, Zhel, Patjo, Darwin kay Angelo Angeles. Walang kwenta. Ni hindi man lang ako nakasingit sa group hug. Pero at least nakakatawa, para silang mga batang nagbabangayan in an almost organized manner.  Dun din ginanap ang walang kwentang recollection namin. Bakit may Born Again? Akala ko ba pag public dapat walang religious Bias?! Punyeta. Tsaka baket may bacolaureate mass??? OYYY TAMA ANG SPELLING NG BACOLAUREATE MASS KOHH! Bakit may Pari? Kala ko ba Public. Ano yan? Christian Formation sa isang Public School?! Fuck that.  Oops… There goes my alumni membership.  Siguro magtataka na lang ako, baka minsan, pag naalala ko ang Highschool life ko, mapaiyak ako. Dahil sa sobrang walang kwenta.  Mamimiss ko talaga ang pag agaw ng tingin ko sa mga sobrang transparent na mata ni Ken (valedictorian namin), sa friendly na mata ni ainah, sa napaka cute na mata ni Jambol at sa napaka-apprehensive na tingin sa akin ni roms (bestfriend nung crush ko… yata.), mamimiss ko rin ang sobrang laking mata ni darwin santos(!@$#%@#$^# ang laking mata…), at sa wakas mamimiss ko talaga ang napaka warm na mata ni thet.  Mamimiss ko rin ang pagbigay ni Pocholo sa akin ng Dirty finger dahil naka trip yata siya. ..1,,   ..1,, 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok, so a couple of days ago, i was at national bookstore browsing through lyndon gregorio's beerkwatro book (really nice book, for college folks, buy it.).  so i was reading the book and having a few laughs when the saleslady comes up to me and says," pogi, bibilhin mo ba yannnn?" she gave me the mataray look and waited for a response.   holding the beerkwatro book (by lyndn gregorio) i had with me, i used my other hand, took out the 500peso (oo, may limangdaang piso ako. steeg, noon lang ako nakahawak ng 500 peso bill, yabang...) bill out of my wallet and flashed it in front of her, and then i took another beerkwatro book (by lyndon gregorio) from the shelves and said "politely","Miss, actually, dalawa eh, isa para sa akin, tapos isa para sa bodyguard ko, nakakatawa kasi oh.."  she walked away. left me.  of course, i never really planned to buy that book, nor do i have a "bodyguard". actually, natapos ko ang buong beerkwatro ni lyndon gregorio sa isang sulok sa national bookstore.  i just hated the fact that people treat other people according to thier physical appearance and clothing.  ie, i was wearing a white t-shirt(the kind i use as an undershirt for school) and voltes V shorts, the ones with the big ass letter "V".  sorry miss, naka trip lang ako.  did you know that beerkwatro was written/created/illustrated by uhmm sino kasi iyon?  thank you lyndon gregorio.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...ok, so its been in on the market for a couple of years now... great game... better than streetfighter...  i mean, its a hell of a lot funnier..  oh... hey, someone actually reads [insert karl's name here]'s shit.. cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      nasa pool kami ni pocholo henson yesterday, nag si swimming. medyo maingay kami, magulo, nagbabasaan nang bigalng sinigawan kami ng isang babae " PWEDE BA?! NABABASA AKO!!!"... adik. nice pocholo. this was taken from bob ong's latest book, ang paboritong libro ni hudas.  may kwento pa ako, bali may dalawang adik sa pool... hahahahahahahahhahahahahhahahhahaha!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yeah, after the swimming and the eating and the swimming and the talking, umuwi na kami, ang sarap mag closing party... even though only a fraction of our class attended, i buimped into an ex-classmate of my, genesis from phs-ssc, it was nice talking to that guy again, he told me stuff that happened after i switched schools... kirstine is mad at me for like, behaving irrationally... i think...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      after last night's karaoke bliss, i couldn't sleep, today, we are going to have our closing party. this sucks ass. everything sucks ass, my head hurts, my feet hurts, gawd, my whole body feels like a big chunk of uranium..
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      nag karaoke kami sa SM, bought more than 20 tokens worth 6 pesos each and brought with us lots and lots of pizza, pizza, rootbeer and karaoke with my former classmates, what you put in coffee even when there's milk around. hey, read my post ealier this morning... nice huh? i wrote that...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Unang Araw  -simula- 03/09/04 9:02:09 PM  Huling taon ko na, bukas ng umaga ang huling periodic test ko sa buhay ko, yung susunod, iba na yung tawag, “midterms” yata.   Nakakatamad, parang ayoko nang mag-aral, alam kong dapat akong mag-aral, pero, parang, wala nang gana. Gusto ko na lang makatapos.  Periodics na. Pagkatapos nito, halos tapos na ang lahat. Isa lang yung test ko bukas, ayoko nang mag-aral, gusto ko na lang matulog ng mahimbing at huwag isipin ang sandosenang requirements na kailangan kong i-pass.  Tatlong taon din akong nanatili sa paaralang ito. Ang pinaka-matagal ko sa isang paaralan. Madalas kasi, dalawa o isang taon pa lang, transfer kaagad, madalas kasi kaming lumipat ng bahay.  Nakakalungkot isipin na hindi na ako highschool, na maaring hindi ko na makita yung mga crush ko (sila ang dahilan kung bakit masaya akong pumapasok sa eskwelahan). Tatlong taon din ito ng buhay ko, sa tatlong taon na iyon, nasa loob ako ng pader ng classroom, nagaaral, minsan natututo, pero madalas, nakatunganga lang, kaya pagdating na ng test, “cramming”.  Pero sa pinakahuling pagsusulit ko sa paaralang iyon, walang cramming, walang kahit ano, itatype ko lang ito, at matutulog na ako, ayoko nang mag-aral. Pagod na rin kasi ako medyo pinapawisan pa. Hindi naman ako nagtrabaho, at konti lang naman ng inaral ko, pero parang pagod na pagod ako, parang buong araw akong nasa construction site. Hindi ko ba alam kung bakit, malamang ito yung “stress” na sinasabi nila. Bahala na. Simula na ng test ko bukas. Hindi ako nag-aral. “stressed” ako, matutulog na. Itutuloy ko na lang bukas.  -tapos- 03/09/04 9:28:04 PM 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmm... i really wish they'd let us add pictures in this blog for free....  that'd be really nice...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so.. hmm... oh happy days.. im with my former clasmates to day... so yeah, cool. damn.. they should allow us to upload picture for free or something..
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi, I'm Karl Sampang. This BlogSite is Under Construction. Check Again in like, 10 years or so. Something Actually might happen to my life.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      karlsampang.friendtest.com  is now online... not that you'd care
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      it's been quite a long while since i last sat in-front of a PC monitor..  very long..  sometimes, i wonderif anyone actually reads this shit.. sometimes.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      leyte...  i have been in leyte these past ten days. recapping my fucked up na screwed up na buhay. thank you, thet.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wow... astig..  kakatapos lang ng motorcade...  so deretso ako sa lib... and voila!  LINUX OS na computers?!  the best talaga ang UP...  so kakatapos nga lang ng motorcade... it rained... pero, that didn't dampen our bloc's spirit...  okay... shet ang galing... may functioning computer sa lib... sa SSC wala..
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haha... foundation week namin ngayon.. wheeee...  kasabay ko sa miss micks sa jeep kanina... yehey... wala lang.. ang ganda niyah... sobra..
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wow... someone actually reads this!  thanks paolo!  Tesa!  :)  okay..  wala pang masyadong nangyari ngayon... first time kaming nagkaroon ng classes sa PE! badminton! asteeg... masarap pala ang badminton...  daming tao!  nandoon sila lolita, jeannie, mga blocmates ko, psyche bloc B, other econ and BM students... masaya naman..  meron akong nakitang isang magandang babae... second year siya yun ang nalaman ko, pero hindi ko alam ang kanyang pangalan.. next week na lang siguro... ganda...  may nabasa ako sa internet:  "Things happen for a reason, its just that you can't understand other's reasons for doing some things."
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      oh great...napaparagnarok na naman ako... just great...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ohh... great.. tesa sent me this message... the message was crap.. but tesa's intentions weren't... thanks tesa... thanks a lot...  lagay ko picture mo sa site koh ha?
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      mass freshmen orientation sa UP clark... astig... ang daming tao.. noong pumask ako, black ang polo ko, ngayon, White na! white na! ano ba yannnn???  pero okay ang orientation...  it couldve been "more" organized, but it was good naman..
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Walang Title  Nakakaiyak isipin na kahit kailan man, hindi ako mamahalin ng babaeng tatlong taon ko nang minamahal. Ang babaeng sanhi ng daan-daang gabi ng hindi ko pagkatulog. Puyat. Pagod. DI makatulog. Puno ng adrenaline ang katawan. Mabilis ang tibok ng puso. Hindi makahinga. Walang ganang kumain. Walang maisip kundi siya. Iyan ang nararamdaman ko. Siya lang ang laman ng aking isipan. Tatlong taon iyon… Medyo mahabahaba rin…   Isa sa mga taong malapit na kaibigan ko, hinahangaan ko, inirerespeto ko ay may gusto sa babaeng pinakamamahal ko sa buong mundo. Mukhang nagkakaigihan na sila.  Nalulungkot akong isipin na ganito ang sitwasyon ko.   Miserable. Basura. Tae. Ako.  Lahat ng nabanggit ko sa itaas, halos magkapareho lang ang meaning; Miserable, Basura, Tae, Ako.  Pero ako, isang basura, tae, miserable, ay nagmamahal sa isang tulad nya. Parang lupa at langit. Siyempre, ako yung lupa, mukhang lupa, amoy lupa. Lintek. Basura.  Wow… Napaiyak ako kaninang nagbabalat ng sayote. Hindi dahil katabi kong nagbabalat ng sibuyas ang kapatid ko (pero factor na rin yun), kundi dahil inisip ko na kahit ayaw NYA (si kwan), at di nya ako type, at may kasama siyang iba (osmeone else) at kahit inaakbayan siya ng isa sa pinakasusuklaman tao ko sa buong planeta (yung kaklase ko) , susubukan ko pa ring iparating ang nararamdaman ko. Dahil alam ko na pag hindi ko ginawa ito, bubulabugin ako ng kunsensya ko habang nabubuhay ako. Mahal ko siya, at kahit sabihin niya na ayaw nya sa akin, “this time” okay lang baka ikasiya ko pa nga, dahil BAKA sakaling makalimutan ko siya, maalis siya sa background ng isip ko, kahit pansamantala lang. Pero siyempre, pipiliin at mas gugustuhin ko rin na sagutin niya ako, na magkasama kami, dahil, iyon naman talaga ang pangarap ko eh, kahit masaklap, gagawin ko pa rin, wala naming mawawala sa akin. Mahal ko naman siya.  Dahil na rin sa iniisip ko na isinayaw ko siya nung prom at minsan ding nakipag-kantahan sa kanya sa attic ni Paolo, mga masasayang alaala, mga alaalang di mabubura sa aking isipan kahit mabulok na ko si lilalim ng lupa.  Siguro, para sa iyo’s walang kwenta ang pinagsusulat ko…  Pero, umaasa akong maiintindihan mo dahil ito ang effect pag naiinlove ka sa taong alam mong malabong magkagusto sa iyo. Nasisira ang ulo ko(see: di makatulog, yung babae lang yung iniisip part sa bandang itaas.).   Siguro, para sa iyo, nag-sesenti lang ako ditto, nagsusulat, pero ako si Karl Sampang, kung hindi ako nakakatulog sa kaiiyak dahil sa mga problema ko, isinusulat ko lahat ito, para mailabas sa isipan ko, ito ang therapy ko.  Siguro, para sa iyo, isa lang akong tanga, na namamagasang mahalin din siya ng minamahal niya, may phrase para sa sitwasyon ko, at kung tama ang pagka-recall ko, “unrequited love” yata ang tawag.  Siguro, para sa iyo, isa ako sa mga lalaking torpe.  Nagkakamali ka, hindi ako torpe, may pagka-walanghiya pa nga ako eh. Natunaw yata siya sa hiya nuong 2nd year highschool kami, nung maglakad ako sa iskwela na may karatulang naglalaman ng nararamdaman ko para sa kanya. “I love you, Thet…” pa nga ang nakasulat, kung ‘di ako nagkakamali. Oo, gago ako, tanga ako… alam ko…  Siguro, para sa iyo, isa lang akong bata. Hindi pa alam ang tunay na ibig sabihin ng salitang, “mahal”, “I love you” at iba pa. Diyan ka nagkakamali.   Siguro nagsasawa ka na sa kakasabi ko ng salitang siguro. Pero alam mo, napagisip-isip ko na, siguro kung sineryoso ko lang ang buhay ko ng konti, mas mabuti ang sitwasyon ko ngayon. Gago kasi ako eh… Tanga, Bobo, Gago, Ungas, lahat-lahatin mo na.  Kahit na anong mangyari, mahal ko siya, at hindi ko ito isinusulat lamang, ito’y aking nararamdaman, kung hindi true love ‘tong nararamdaman ko, ewan ko na lang. (Jolina?) 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      can you say supercalifragilisticexpicalidotious?  i can't..  but that doesn't mean i won't...  ive met a lot of people this past week..  dami sobra.  si pebpeb, and tesa, and lucy, and kathleen dami..  and yung mga upperclassman ko..  and yung mga former classmates ko..  irevamped the site nga pala...  check nyo rin ang friendtest ko..  under "stuff" named : "kaibigan mo ba talaga ako?"  you should have some fun..  go out....  and visit ka na lang ulit next week  karlsampang.tk  para cute.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yehey!  karlsampang.tk  astig..  tell your friends about it..  para hindi ma-seize yung domain ko...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      im writing something....  random thoughts...  ill print it out for everyone to see... mebbe later..  "balisong" still is in my head... but in a cool uncaring sort of way.  i dont even know what that means...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      college na ako..  astig..
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The first one was called “[crush>”. She was 14 years old when I first met her. Short black hair, fair complexion, five foot five, as athletic as she was intelligent (she was in the “star section”), infinitely charming, and was a dead ringer for actress Pia Guanio, that was what she was to me. To me, she was the “end all, be all” of all the women in the world, nobody else compares. That was three years ago.  I first met her in second year high school. I was stupid, and obsessed with Magic™ cards, Counter-Strike™ and Ghost Recon™, among other things. I first met her in the grounds of our school’s “so-called” Math Park. It was a place where students share assignments, test questions, notes, play cards, and chat their idle time away. And like any other day, it was crawling with these idlers, students who cared little about their studies if in fact they cared AT ALL. I was actually one of these idlers.  I was a transferee that year. I was new, two weeks old, I was fodder for the upperclassmen and I was looked upon as a bumbling ass by my fellow sophomores (of course, I didn’t know that back then). And so, naturally, I was again, for the nth time, in my then 13-year lifetime, I was alone. I was used to that, and frankly, I enjoyed being alone, nobody pesters you with his or her stupid algebra questions or their personal problems, nobody bothers you, it was peaceful; it was nice.  It was at that moment that she, and a couple of her classmates came up to me. I saw her face. There were no words to express for what I felt. I wish there was, but I haven’t found anything yet. They told me their names. There were three of them. I asked her to repeat hers, and she did. I still remember their names just the way they said it. ‘I won’t forget her name’, I told myself. And I wouldn’t, I didn’t want to. What I didn’t know was that her name would haunt me for the remainder of my highschool life.   I was trying to memorize her face. Just so I wouldn’t forget her. She was so beautiful that everyone else, to me, paled in comparison. And what I kept saying to myself that day was that “I found her… I found her…” just kept telling myself that ‘til I got home, and the day after that, and the day after next.  Fast-forward to the day that I really, really, screwed up; fast-forward to the day that I made this “super-fatal” mistake.  It was just like any other Tuesday school day. We started classes by seven, got dismissed by four. The day was very uneventful. IT was supposed to become a day that like many others would rot in the back of my mind. Forgotten, lost, never to be recovered. But it wasn’t, it didn’t become that. I should have done the smart thing, I should have headed straight home. But no, I didn’t do that. What I did was I lingered. Like a bad perfume, I lingered. Walked around the school with my bag. BIG MISTAKE.  	The next thing I did, would haunt me for the rest of my high school adolescent life. Out of— I dunno, sheer STUPIDITY and boredom, I took a broken arm of an armchair that was lying around, took a piece of chalk and wrote on the armchair arm thingie:   “I LOVE YOU, [crush>”   	But that isn’t the worst part. I laughed at my handiwork, and my friend Erin, who was at the scene of the crime, nodded. Erin was always the radical sort, loved surprising people with this unconventional way of living life. I guess it rubbed on to me. But that doesn’t matter right now. Then, I took my wooden “placard”, and walked around the school campus. I saw her, she saw me, she saw the “placard”, she read the “placard”, and then she turned away. It was at that point that I realized how stupid I was. I dropped the “placard”, and it landed on my foot. Very painful, but my pain wouldn’t even compare to the amount of “shrink” bills I would have to pay for after what I did to her. Good thing we weren’t in the US.  I stood there, in the hallway, frozen, dumb, stupid, whatever. One of her friends came up to me; he told me that she was crying. She was crying, I was stupid and ashamed for what I did. Not one of us was happy. Until then, I figured that loved was a really, really good thing. In my case, it isn’t.  	And with that, and a heavy heart, I went home. Straight to bed, hated myself for doing that, and cried myself to sleep.  	She was great, but way out of my league, the truth of the matter is that EVERY girl that I’ve ever liked is WAYYY out of my league; I don’t even know who’s in “my league”.  	But for the next three years I was haunted by another two words:   “What if?”   	What if she liked me back? What if she IS in my league? WHAT IF? I wanted to know her better. But that was impossible now, not after the stupid “I LOVE YOU, [crush>” placard mistake. No. Her friends were always around here, like bodyguards, only, they don’t have guns, they had vindictive stares that turned men into stone and kept idiots like me at bay. Especially her closer friends, by the way they looked at me, I was afraid that they’d skin me alive and feed my insides to the dogs.          I still am bothered by those two words. "What if?" I’ve found the answer though, “She doesn’t like you”. So now, every time my gut asks me “What if?” and it concerns a girl, I’d tell myself, “She doesn’t like you.”
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      “You know what your problem is? You’re in love with this girl and you keep telling yourself that you aren’t!”  Those words struck me like a steel chair on Chris Benoit’s back. Those words are the painful truth that has bothered me for so many years now.  I’ve been convincing myself that “No, she doesn’t like me” and “No, I don’t have a chance against whoever her “other” suitors may be.  And then, I find myself listening to Wheatus’ “Teenage Dirtbag”.  And Duncan Shiek’s “Half-Life”, and Third Eye Blind’s “Deep Inside of You”.  Really pathetic.   I’m just a guy, who’s in love with a girl, who’s way out of his league, and doesn’t have enough guts to even try to ask her out for “dinner and a movie”. No… I’m less than that. I’m just a guy, who’s IQ is so incredibly high that he walks around the school carrying a huge arm chair arm that read:    “I LOVE YOU, [Insert name of my crush here>”   Some people told me that it was awfully romantic. I agree with the “awful” part.  I thought I was in-love with her. But now, I don’t even know what love is. Is it that weird feeling in your stomach you get whenever you see this one person that makes your heart jump and your butt, clench? ‘Cause I get that all the time, and I can’t find a way to distinguish love from a stomach cramp.   Old people, they say that when you fall in love, you’ll feel it, in your stomach, in your whole body, they say that the moment you see that special person, your heart will skip a beat, you’ll feel like there were butterflies in your stomach, you’ll feel like you’re floating.   I couldn’t remember whether or not my heart skipped a beat, or if I felt like I was floating. But there was this one thing, whenever I was around her, just near her (I consider the radius of 5 meters near), my heart pounds on my chest like a ~, my brain stops functioning properly, I go into “stupid mode” and I cease to receive nerve impulses from my ears.  Stupid mode? Yes, Stupid mode. During “stupid mode”, my vocabulary will be temporarily reduced to these following phrases:  Ahhh… Hi! O! Kumusta ka na? Ok ka lang? May gagawin ka ba? / Busy ka ba? Sino kasama mo? Ehhh… Kumusta school? Ganon? Wahehehehehe… Kumusta ka na? (yes, I really repeat this…) Kumain ka na ba? Gusto mong ahh­— Kumusta ka na? Wahahahahaha… Sige… Ingat ka palagi ah…  Stupid... Stupid me...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am hurting.. My head feels like a rock on my shoulders, my eyes have involuntary tears falling out of them, my nose, wet and icky and runny, my hands, utterly disoriented, i am miserable.  Have a nice day...  And oh... Check out my Tagboard...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Maddox's Site = www.maddox.xmission.com or just look at this links part of my navbar   This guy OWNZ! Bad humor for other people... but some people i know will like this site because it is "THE BEST PAGE IN THE UNIVERSE".  Greeat site.  Poch, Pao, GUys! better read this, take a look! really hilarious...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The truth hit me during Mr. E. Escultura's Natural Science 1 class. The truth... is that I'm cannibalizing my life for this site... Not that there much to cannibalize, I guess there'd be no point in stopping now... So I'm not going to stop doing this... No... I still have a lot of "Fuck You" left, if you know what I mean. I'm still going to write, still going to update, about this sad, sorry, pathetic excuse for a life.  You know what?  This is MY sad, sorry, pathetic excuse for a life. And I'm enjoying it!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      “Sweet like candy tooo my soul, sweet you rock and sweet you roll, lost for you I‘m sooo lost for you…”  She was like candy to my soul. Sweet she rocks and sweet she rolls. I was so lost for her. Lost in her. I even lost myself.  Strange that I’d pick a Dave Matthews song to describe what I felt for her, a song that has so much “improper” sexual innuendo in it’s lyrics. A little green, yes, but those lines say so much about something I wouldn’t even dare speak of.  She used to be the only thing in my mind. That was about two years back. She was just so great… the embodiment of everything I’ve ever asked for in a woman, lady, girl, you get the idea. I was so lost for her. I was so lost for her in fact that I even lost myself. Came every single school day NOT to learn algebra, or physics or biology or chemistry, but to see her face, to watch her smile.  You should see her smile… When she smiles, she smiles with her whole body… And her eyes are so sincere, not a hint of sarcasm of “untruth” in them.  But there’s another song. “Balisong” by Rivermaya…  “Never in my life, have I been more sure, so come on up to me and close the door, nobody’s made me feel this way befooore, you’re everything I wanted and more…”  I know… These lines have cliché written all over them. I don’t care. Sometimes, I think of her and everything just “feels” better, ever when they’re not. She’s probably everything I ever wanted but I’m stupid enough not to realize that.  “She ‘sez that love is for fools that fall behind, and I’m somewhere between, never really know a killer from a saviour…”  Shimmer by Fuel. Well… I guess I’m just one of those fools that fell behind…
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Minsan  Minsan nakatitig lang ako sa monitor ng PC… Walang ginagawa. Walang magawa. Kaya kadalasa’y ino-open ang file ko na may picture niya. Sabay titig… Mangangarap na sana’y nagging “kami” andami sana naming pwedeng gawin, sine, tambay, nood ng TV, mag-share ng kanya-kanyang kuro-kuro at taste sa mga bagay-bagay, interes, arcade, videoke, asa pa ako... Hanggang dito lang talaga, aasa, mangangarap, maghihintay ng kahit na anong pasabi o bagay na magpapakita ng isang “ray of hope” na nagsasabing “may chance ako sa kanya”… Pero wala, kaya hanggang dito na lang. Walang naiisip kundi siya.  Minsan naman, inuumpog ang ulo at hinahampas ang sarili sa pader ng aking kwarto dahil nagsisisi, dahil naaasar, dahil nagagalit at naiinggit, “Sana man lang, nakilala ko siya ng personal…”.  Minsan naman, magtataka kung bakit padalas at padalas na ang iyong pagkausap sa sarili habang nasa harap ng isang computer.  Minsan naman, makikinig ka sa tape ng Nirvana… tapos, nakangiti ka lang. Kasi mayroon kang bagay na narerealize na ni hindi mo maiisip kung nakinig ka sa kanta ng A1, Backstreet Boys at Westlife (Boy bands=sheiit).  Minsan nakahiga lang, nakatitig sa uhh… ceiling, iniisip ang mga bagay na hindi kailan man magiging, mga bagay na hindi kailan man naging, at iniisip mo na rin ung dapat bang kinakain ang garnish ng isang potahe.  Minsan naman, magpapaikot-ikot ako sa aking kama kapag gabi hanggang mapagod at ako at makatulog para lang makahanap ng paraan para.. uh.. matulog.  Minsan naman nakatitig lang ako sa pagkain, almusal, tanghalian, merienda at hapunan, walang gana, mapapagalitan pa ako ng tatay ko. Pero pag gabi na, hahaluhugin ang ref, makakita lang ng ilang pirasong Chocnut™ at Maxx Honey Lemon™ na pinapapak habang nakatitig sa PC monitor at pinagmamasdan ang patalbogtalbog na bolang screensaver na makulay na di-maiwasang maihalintulad sa patalbog-talbog ngunit walang kalatoy-latoy kong buhay.  Walang ganang kumain, pero may ganang mang-raid ng ref habang tulog pa ang buong bahay.  Minsan naman, maglalakad lang sa kalye, walang pakialam kung sinong mabangga.. Parang may sarili kang mundo.. Maibabalik mo lamang ang iyong sarili pag nahalata mo na na wala na ang wallet mo.  Minsan naman sa klase, habang recitation, nakatitig lang sa isang butas ng pako sa itaas ng blackboard na marahil binutas noong panahon pa ni Marcos habang pilit na inaalis sa utak ang mukha ng taong nagsisilbing dahilan kung bakit ka pumapasok sa iskwela. Pinapaalala sa iyong sarili na kaya ka pumapasok ay hindi para Makita ang iyong hinahangaan ngunit para matuto kung papaano kunin ang equilibrium constant ng isang reaction sa isang tren na papuntang City A na nakikipag-karera sa isang Kotse na tumatakbo ng 60 Km/Hr… Kung ganoon nga, ilan ang pasahero sa tren. Tapos, bigla ka na lamang tatawagin ng teacher, itatanong kung ilang sonnet ang isinulat ni Shakespeare. Patay ka… Hindi kasi nakikinig, samantalang kakasabi niya lamang.  Minsan naman maglalakad ka papauwi, bago tumawid ng kalye para sumakay ng dyip muntik kang masagasaan ng isang 100-wheeler truck na may dalang buhangin, pag tawid mo, maglalakad ka lamang, derederetso, parang may sariling mundo, di na bale kung masagasaan ako ng bus ng Philippine Rabbit™ o mahagip ng sportscar ng isang conio boy, basta nakatatak lang siya sa isipan mo.  Minsan mapagkakamalan ka pang nagwa-wan-two-tree sa dyip dahil sa  sobrang tahimik mo at hindi ka napansing magbayad ng driver, doble pamasahe ka pa… patay ka pag ganyan. O kaya nama’y sosobra ka sa iyong pagbababaan, kailangan pang maglakad ng napakalayo.  Minsan naman mananatili ka ng isang oras sa isang intersection dahil sa buhol-buhol na traffic. Late ka na naman sa Nat.Sci.1 mo. Patay ka.  Minsan naman kundi kadalasa’y, uupo ka sa harap ng computer at bara-barang itatayp ang mga bagay na nararamdaman mo. Wala kang pakialam, kung sinong makabasa, maging magulang mo pa o crush, o ang lola mo, o ang aso, walang pakialam dahil ito ang iyong nararamdaman…  Uninvited  For now, I would like to believe that I no longer think of her, that I no longer care or her, that I no longer feel anything for her; that I’m over her.  But that’s not true now, is it?  And then Ida told me that she would be going over to Paolo’s with Anne… I wanted to go with them… Not because I wanted to see Ida, or Anne, or Paolo, or Paolo’s attic, or someone who is not in any way related to me by blood, it was because she told me that Thet would be there… And I wanted to see her. Badly.  Why I wanted to see her? I dunno… I just wanted to. I just really, really wanted to. And I wanted to talk with her even… I wish I could do that.  Because I want to. But I don’t know what else might happen, or who else will drop by uninvited.  But I wanted to come.  But I couldn’t, I just couldn’t. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Pretty (daw)  wahehe...          Luci           Tesa           Peb Peb    Pretty, aren't they?  yeah... i know you're green with envy now...  Okay.. im a stop now.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      a thief by kimsampang  i am not a poet, am nothing but a thief, who steals the words, from poet's mouths, and make thier children weep,  i am not an artist, am nothing but a thief, i mar the canvass, with my strokes, of paint and coal, and dirt and cheep.  i am not a writer, am nothing but a thief, whose words of truth, are nothing more, than lies i write, i sell to eat.  i am not a saviour, am nothing but a thief, who steals your gold, by way of faith, and lies to you, for heaven's sake.  I am not a good man,  am nothing  but a thief, who writes some ryhmes, and draws some lines, and speaks of faith, just for me to eat.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Sees Through Me by: Karl Sampang  She sees through me, like cat's eyes, her piercing eyes, disarming smile, makes me believe, that i'm alive, im lost in her, so lost in her, ive lost myself, second time this week, she sees through me, those eyes of dark, see my soul, though im without, i have no money, im really broke, can't buy no food, no water,im stoked, can't buy her flowers, can't buy her sweets, can't buy her heart, won't win that soon, am i making sense? i think not. so why are you still reading this? now, bugger off...  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is MY PIECE OF REALITY.         This whole blog.  Is evidence that I'm real.  That I exist.  That I am not a figment of someone else's sick imagination.  This whole blog convinces me that I am real.  That I, with my cheap, worn-out, knock-off clothes exist.  This is proof.  This is MY REALITY. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            Meow...  Uneventful... i'm really looking forward to this weekend.  the upepp freshmen night is just around the corner... all the pretty girls are talking about NOT GOING.. so yeah... i'm having second thoughts about that...  Really really sad about that..  what's the cat all about? wala lang... it looks nice...  get a load of this one...                                     DARTH-MOTHER (DARTH VADER's MOM) Really...   Now that i've put that aside...  this is nice... finally, a break from my romantic fantasies...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Beauty queen of only eighteen/ she had trouble with herseeelf/ he was always there to help her/ but she/ always belonged to someone else..."  She was a beauty queen (well, she could be...), of almost eighteen, i don't think she ever had trouble with herself. I'll be always there to help her. But i figure she's way out of my league. AS always.  "The Second One" was named "Q". Q, for unknown. She was one of the most popular girls in school. Teh fashionista kind, the RICH fashionista kind, can easily be mistaken for an ice queen, yes. I did, but behind all that "ohhh-so-expensive" clothes and those dreamy eyes lies a princess like no other.(what in God's green earth am i saying...)  dreamy eyes.  disarming smile.  unfathomable charm.  how the hell did i mistake her for an "ice queen".  i have no idea.  although she has "POP" written all over her... chuck taylor sneaks, classic blue jeans, lots of jangling things stuck to her wrists... no, so much as i HATE POP, i also love her...  ahh.. great, she walked past me just a few seconds ago, and i wonder if she realizes that i'm actually writing about her right this second...  i am in the library, using the "official school computer" powered by linux... yaeey linux...  she's sitting right beside me right now.  and my heart is pounding like hell..  i can't feel my chest anymore.. gotta stop.. she might see this...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Revamping and fixing my blog, putting more stuff on my navbar thingie... Too lazy to move and do things that i ought to be doing, like studying and the like... My life is really coming back to what it was a couple of years ago... Just a crappy shadow of everybody else's. I've tried "rebuilding" my life just a couple of months ago, and for a time, i was "happy". I guess I got tired of all the hating and the "classifying of people as if they were music genres". Read Karina Pomaneg's Frontpage column just yesterday. Good luck with that drummer boy Karina.  Which reminds me of this significant other that i oft dreamed about back in highschool. She was a drummer in thier band, "A" student, volleyball player, former student council member, deadringer for Pia Guanio... What more could I ask, she was the "end all, be all" of all the women in the world to me... That was three years ago... She still is great... I mean, just plain... "great.  I'm Gonna write about her one of these days. (Maybe later) I have a copy of here picture, but i figured that i shouldn't show it for all the wordld to see, she'll hate me even more.  Still fantacizing about becoming a lead vocals/rythm guitarist of my own band. We'd be called "The Great Depression". Angsty, hateful, unconventional, bordering on gothic, but more on grunge. Yep! Just like Nirvana. (God, what am I talking about?)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just finished reading "The Sicilian" by Mario Puzo...  Tragic... Beautifully tragic, if there ever was a description like that...  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Prelims are over... Man, I'm glad they are... I did "nice" on my History 1... But pretty nervous about English 1 and Math 11... Really nervous... Got a copy of Mario Puzo's the Sicilian from the school library; Still looking for Machiavelli's "The Prince" though...     Utada Hikaru is sooo cute... And really talented too!!!               Ohhh... I saw this while surfing the web:                     Weird...       
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ang book of life ko. Na pinagawa sa akin ni Mrs. Pangilinan, ang English teacher ko.  Marahil, isa sa pinakaimportanteng proyekto na tinapos at ipinasa ko.  Kung sinu-sino na ang nakahiram ng book of life ko. Ewan ko na kung nakanino…  Kasama sa .doc na ito ang ilan sa piling artikulo ng librong iyon…  Sino ba naming nag-akala na maiinspire talaga ako na idocument ang aking mga naiisip/saloobin,/trip/kasalanan/buhay… Well, ako actually.  Kahit na sobrang Daming Grammatikal Erors. Ewan. Sabi nga ni Karl Sampang, “I write the way I speak”.  Ows? Talaga? 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      test tomorrow...  an essay test! wheeeeee!  but really... i'm going to learn html... really serius about this.. and im going to postpone my dreams of ragnarok online stardom... for now..
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haha... the pain..  three major tests. one whole week. need to report on conjuctions next week... should have learned about that in highschool... but nooo.... ramayana.... damn...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hindi na ako isang Highschool student… Tapos na ang mga araw na kailangan kong mag-uniform para lamang makapasok sa iskwela… Tapos na ang pagbili ko ng fishball at squidball sa mga overpricing na tindera. Tapos na ang pagsabay ko sa maraming tao tuwing pumapasok para hindi niya mapansin na wala akong I.D. Tapos na ang pag-“spoon feed” sa akin ng mga teacher ko. Tapos na ang paglabas ko sa campus tuwing lunch ng madalas hindi para bumili ng pagkain ngunit para mag-internet at mag-laro ng computer games. Tapos na ang mga araw na may definite seating arrangement sa klase. Alam kong wala akong mamimiss sa mga bagay na nabanggit ko, pero… Tapos na ang mga araw na nagsasaya ako, pa-easy-easy lang, hindi nag-aaral, ngayon kailangan nang magseryoso. Dahil tapos na ang mga araw na highschool ako. Estudyante na ako ng kolehiyo. Wala nang tutulong sa akin, mag-isa na lang ako ulit… Parang tulad ng dati? Teka… Parang highschool lang ah… Kaso kailangan na talagang mag-aral, at ang mga teacher dito, mukhang kumukuha sila ng kasiyahan sa pag bigay ng bagsak na marka sa mga estudyateng tinuturuan nila. Ito siguro ang tunay na mundo, hindi masaya, seryoso, at ngayo’y pinapatunayan ko ang isa sa mga teoryang aking binuo habang nagdidiscuss tungkol sa kabutihan ng tao ang Values Ed. Teacher ko. “Ang tao ay likas na masama. Ang Tao ay Hedonistic, iniiwasan ang sakit at lagging humahanap ng paraan para mapasaya, mapahusay ang buhay niya. Ang tao ay hindi likas na mabuti, dahil kung totoo iyon, wala tayong dapat nakikita na pinapatay, o ginagahasa, o nininikawan, o dinudukot… Tayo ang salot sa mundong ito… Parang napaka-corny samantalang sa atin ipinagkatiwala ang mundong ito. Tapos na ang lahat ng gusto kong isulat ukol sa parting ito ng buhay ko. Hindi na ako Highschool… At sa ikaapat na araw ng pagiging estudyante ng kolehiyo ko, napagisip-isip ko na mag-isa na naman muli ako…  Tulad ng dati… 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmmm... pathetic...  three days of pure boredom..  tatlong araw! you know what that can do to a man?!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh joy!  Oh pure sarcasm!  Oh SHIT!  This is just one of those days. Typical days when i just one to kick the living crap out of my pretentious classmates.  I hate them so much that i wrote something for them.  A prayer for my pretentious classmates.  Dear God, please forgive me for my sins, please help me forgive others for thier sins, please forgive me for planning to murder my pretentious classmates, please help me not to commit that sin again, please help me control myself from KICKING THIER OHH-SO-PRETENTIOUS ASSES to the fiery depths of hell...  AMEN  p.s.  If i am not able to stop myself, please please please save thier souls... they need it.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. WHAT IS YOUR MIDDLE NAME? - Alias  2. WHAT kind of PANTS ARE YoU WEARING?  - Im naked.  3. WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO RIGHT NOW? - MY pretentious classmates' voice singing Manilow's "mandy"  over and over again... is defiling the song... note DEFILE!  4. WHAT ARE THE LAST 4 DIGITS OF YOUR PHONE? - 5547  5. WHAT WAS THE LAST THING YOU ATE? - Juicy fruit and soda  6. IF YOU WERE A CRAYON, WHAT COLOR WOULD YOU BE? - Black, blue.  7. HOW IS THE WEATHER RIGHT NOW? - partly cloudy with scattered rainshowers  8. LAST PERSON YOU TALKED TO ON THE PHONE? - operator services  9. THE FIRST THING YOU NOTICE ABOUT THE OPPOSITE  - face, complexion...  10. DO YOU LIKE THE PERSON WHO SENT YOU THIS? - who?  11. HOW ARE YOU TODAY? - i am quite satisfied, i controlled myself from STRANGLING MY, guess what, PRETENTIOUS CLASSMATES!  12. FAVORITE DRINK? - extra joss, with water. or just water.  13. FAVORITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK? - VODKA... parang kampit kung gumuhit.  14. FAVORITE SPORTS? - [insert something here]ball  15. HAIR COLOR? - black  16. EYE COLOR? - brown.. yellow from hepatitis  17. DO YOU WEAR CONTACTS? -no  18. SIBLINGS AND THEIR AGES? - i forgot.  19. FAVORITE MONTH? - January, cold.  20. FAVORITE FOOD? - edible  21. LAST MOVIE YOU WATCHED? -THE BOURNE SUPREMACY  22. FAVORITE DAY Of ANY YEAR? - the day after tommorow.  23. ARE YOU TOO SHY TO ASK SOMEONE OUT? - im never shy, im just stupid...  24. DO YOU LIKE SCARY MOVIES OR HAPPY ENDING? - scary happy endings  25. SUMMER OR WINTER? - winter  26. HUGS OR KISSES? - or getting laid?! no... hugs..  27. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA? - chocolate 28. DO YOU WANT YOUR FRIENDS TO WRITE BACK? to what?!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. NAME? >> Karl  2. SINGLE OR ATTACHED? >> Single  3. ARE YOU IN LOVE? >> I don't know the difference between love and a stomach cramp.  4. DOES SOMEONE HAVE A CRUSH ON  YOU? >> i don't think so..  5. HAVE YOU EVER BEEN HEARTBROKEN? >> constantly  6. HOW MANY EX(ES)? >> is zero a number?  7. HOW LONG WAS YOUR LONGEST RELATIONSHIP? >> 16 years. a love love relationship between me and my parents  8. HOW SHORT WAS UR SHORTEST RELATIONSHIP? >> 2 1/2 hours, there was this girl once na nakasakay ko sa bus..  9. HAVE YOU CHEATED ON SOMEONE BEFORE? >> This is such a "relationship centered survey..."  10. HAVE YOU BEEN CHEATED / TWO- TIMED ON BEFORE? >> my patience is running thin...  11. IF YOU ARE SINGLE, DO YOU WANT TO FALL IN LOVE AND GET ATTACHED? >> no... i have too many preoccupations already...  12. IF YOU ARE ATTACHED, DO YOU LOVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND / BOYFRIEND? >> but i am not.  13. HAVE YOU EVER PLAYED WITH SOMEONE`S FEELINGS? >> what are feelings?  14. HAVE YOU EVER BEEN FORCED/DARED TO GO WITH SOMEONE? >> no...   15. HAVE YOU CRIED OVER SOMEONE YOU THOUGHT YOU LOVED/LIKED? >> 365 days a year.  16. HUGS OR KISSES? >> words.  17. DO YOU THINK IT IS ALRIGHT FOR PEOPLE OF THE SAME SEX TO LOVE EACH OTHER? >> sure why not... it's a free country..  18. HAS ANYONE EVER TOLD YOU THAT  YOU WERE 2 YOUNG FOR LOVE? >> i think that.  19. WHAT DO YOU THINK OF LONG  DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS? >> no chance of getting laid whatsoever...  20. WOULD YOU EVER GO WITH SOMEONE OVERSEAS? >> SDGSDFGDFGSDFGDFGSD  21. HAVE YOU THOUGHT YOU LOVED SOMEONE BUT THE FEELING WENT AWAY AFTER A FEW DAYS? >> i takes two days.  22. DO LOOKS MATTER TO YOU? >> yeah.  23. WHAT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING  IN A RELATIONSHIP? >> sex drugs and rock and roll..  24. FOR GIRLS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF  YOUR BOYFRIEND IS YOUNGER THAN YOU? >> im going to ignore this.  FOR GUYS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS OLDER THAN YOU? >> BRING IT ON.  25. FOR GIRLS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF  YOUR BOYFRIEND IS SHORTER THAN YOU? >>ignore.  26. for GUYS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS TALLER THAN YOU? >> are we talkign about an inch or a foot?  26. DO YOU TELL YOUR CRUSHES YOU  LIKE HIM / HER? >> yep... in a weird, idiotic, stalker-like manner.  27. ARE YOU ROMANTIC? >> i am an idiot.  28. WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ONE NIGHT STANDS? >> im going to quote VAn Wilder: "Don't be a fool, protect your tool."  29. WHAT DO YOU THINK OF COUPLES  WHO BREAK UP AND PATCH BACK AFTER A FEW DAYS? >>can't relate
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Still no word from Syeri… I’m beginning to doubt that she will be returning my jacket sometime this week. Gave her my number but I just really can’t see myself answering the phone with her voice on the other side of the line….  Really pathetic.  I’m listening to Nirvana right now, doesn’t matter which song…  Ahh something popped into my head just a few seconds ago.  I met a guy a few days back.  The turd talked endlessly about “Frida” and “Y tu mama tambien” and Tarantino and Coppola, and Lee like he was some kind of film critic ass. He was carrying with him this tall tumbler of note, STARBUCKS; he drankthe foamy starbucks latte thing inside the starbucks tumbler thing while rambling about his critiques. Like I cared…  I’m sorry, I don’t know much about coffee except the fact that it contains caffeine. And I don’t get people for buying coffee at Starbucks and Seattle’s Best or Coffee Overdose for that matter. It’s probably a cool, rich people thing. I intend to rant about that in a separate entry, watch out for that.  Okay, so there is this guy with a tumbler of whatever they serve at Starbucks, acting like he was some film critic ass. Note the way that I use the word ASS. That’s what he is, just some ass. There are some things I would like to cite, and might support my theory that he is a poser.  1.	I saw him in the Angeles city proper. That would mean that the closest Starbucks would be 17 kilometers away from where we were. The closest Starbucks outlet that I can think of is the one along the north expressway, and if there is one in SM Pampanga or Robinsons, which is still 17 kilometers away.  2.	I saw him at 9:15 am. It’s either he brought his coffee along with him from the expressway for a 50 minute ride, or he traveled at the speed of light to bend the time-spaceakljsfbailsdgfwjklbfd[SCIENTIFIC GIBBERISH HERE], to buy a “tall glass of whatever the hell flavor of Starbucks coffee” and drink it at a cheap-ass mall (NEPO MALL) just to show off.  3.	Or he made himself some coffee and put it in a Starbucks tumbler which he values so much and washes with dishwashing liquid in order to reuse it.  4.	Four? Oh sorry, I already puked because he has POSER written all over him.  5.	Like I didn’t notice his knock-off Girbaud sneakers, or his knock-off “pornstar/Am Blvd” T-shirt.  6.	He was talking about how the said movies were so great expressing so much meaning. He also said that the “Matrix: Reloaded” and the “Matrix: Revolutions” had so much meaning and deep philosophical content and tackled causality. Really?! Can you tell me what those movies meant?! Do you know what causality and existentialism means? Huh?! I didn’t think so. Dumbass!  I therefore conclude that this idiot is a POSER.  Now DIE!  (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab) (stab)  Idiot… 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. What is your complete name? Does it have a special meaning?  > Karl Isaac Mari A. Sampang. Yes, I think. Karl, maybe that was for “Karl Marx”, I think my grandfather really approved of that. Isaac, “Isagani from El Filibusterismo”? Mari, I am offered to mother Mary. “A” stands for Alias, my mom’s maiden name. And Sampang.  2.If your life had a soundtrack, what would be the songs and how would they be arranged?  >These are the songs, in autobiographical order:  About a Boy – Badly Drawn Boy  214 – Rivermaya Torpe – Hungry Young Poets  Be Like That – Three Doors Down There She Goes – Sixpence none the Richer Drops of Jupiter – Train Half-life - Duncan Shiek Sleep all Day - Jason Mraz Im on a High - Duncan Shiek Lonely - Rhett Miller  Fast Car – Tracy Chapman Everywhere – Michelle Branch Pare Ko – Eraserheads Tindahan ni Aling Nena – Eraserheads Bizzare Love Triangle – Frente Sway – Bic Runga  Yellow – Coldplay Blinded – Third Eye Blind Deep inside of you- Third Eye Blind The Scientist – Coldplay Androgyny – Garbage It’s Over Now – Neve How You Remind Me – Nickelback Crash into Me – Dave Matthews Band Shimmer – Fuel Gising Na – Parokya ni Edgar Sampip – Parokya ni Edgar Drive – Incubus Wish You Were Here – Incubus  Balisong – Rivermaya Burnout – Sugarfree I Disappear – Metallica  Here without You – Three Doors Down She will be Loved – Maroon5 Clubbed to Death – Kurayamino mix – By someone I don’t know  But if I were asked to pick only one song to describe my whole life, it would be:  You know you’re right - Nirvana  This masterlist is subject to change, I know I’m forgetting a lot of other great songs(but if they were great, I wouldn’t forget them, won’t I?). Songs will still be added.  3. DO you have a girlfriend? Why or why not?  > NO. Because of the following reasons:  They take too much of your time. The Hatid-Sundo Service. And, need I remind you of the PARENTS, most especially, HER DAD, the guy who would gladly rip your ass apart with his [insert anything he uses in his job here, i.e. monkey wrench, calculator, m16 rifle, shotgun, pencil].  They cost too much; you have to pay for their fare when you two go out, you have to pay for what you eat, and for everything else you might need money for, and you also have to buy the presents to assure them of your unwavering love.  I’m not a chauvinist, so please don’t mistake me for one. I’m just saying what every other man has in the back of his mind. These are the facts. These are the superficial facts.  As for why I don’t have a girlfriend, this would explain everything, this and the fact that I’m an idiot.  4. If there was one person in the world, living or dead, you could spend an hour with, who would it be? What will you do to him or her?  > God/Supreme being, I have many questions for Him.  In the sad event (read: sad, because NO GOD is a BAD THING), that there is no GOD, I would very much like to meet Jesus, he is the next best thing, I will ask him the questions that I would have asked GOD.  In the SAD SAD(read: SAD SAD) event that Jesus does not exist and the whole of Christianity is just a hoax to control the populace(which is a really sad thing), I would very much like to meet Ferdinand Magellan and do the following things to him in this exact order:  1. beat the living shit out of him, with my fists 2. beat the living shit out of him, with a 2x2 wooden stick 3. beat the living shit out of him, with a steel chair 4. cut off his fingers one by one 5. scrub all wounds with steel wool drenched in alcohol 6. get some gas and some matches and roast him until golden brown 7. poke his eyes out. 8. rip apart his abdomen and feed his insides to the dog 9. all of this beating is will be done while I pee/shit/spit on him and while insulting him.  I have that much respect for you, FM.  5. Name some people who you really think is intelligent/wise/whatever.  a.	MY DAD. NO EXPLANATION NEEDED.  These people are intelligent in a different level, in my opinion.  a.	Jefferson – His reason is very… reasonable… Napabayaan lang. b.	Marthyn – Matalino, napabayaan lang… c.	Erin – Unconventional but slightly reasonable reasoning ability. d.	Eric – Meaningful, yet utterly meaningless… Napabayaan lang e.	Pocholo – I am… at a loss of words… Napabayaan lang. f.	Jemmabel Viray and Laurence Gueco – The young and the wasted.  6. If there was one word in the dictionary that could describe you, what would it be?  >“Undescribable”   7.What are you doing at this very moment?  >I am a multitasker. These are the things that I’am currently doing.  -	beating the shit out of Magellan -	listening to nirvana -	reading Shakespeare -	answering this survey -	not having a girlfriend -	being broke -	trying to sew Magellan’s head back on -	and oh, beating the shit out of the guy who wrote this survey 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ext. Sa labas ng campus ng College. Makulimlim, medyo basa ang lupa, hindi pa gaanong maingay, alas nuebe ng umaga.  KARL: (bulong sa sarili) First day of classes, Karl, don’t screw up. (paulit ulit)  JAMES: O! Karl! Kumusta?! (nakangiti)  KARL: Okay lang… (mapapatingin sa paligid at makakapansin siya ng isang lalaking naka itim na jacket, asul na maong at sneakers)Sina Chino?  JAMES: May pasok na yata… Ewan ko. Sige, alis muna ako ah? May pasok na rin niyan ako… (tatakbong papalayo, papasok na sa lobby ng school)  KARL: Sige… Ingat. (maglalakad patungong lobby ng school)  Int. Sa lobby ng campus, nakaabang ang mga student council people para tumulong sa mga freshmen at mga transferee.  SOPHOMORE: (lalapit kay KARL) Course mo?  KARL: (nagulat, nagtataka kung bakit  nilapit siya ng estrangherong ito) Ah… Psych…  SOPHOMORE: Oh okay… Sama ka sa akin?  KARL: (nagaalinlangan) Bakit?  SOPHOMORE: Walk with me. (habang naglalakad na papalayo sa lobby at papasok sa isa sa mga hall)  KARL: (susunod)  SOPHOMORE: (babagalan ng konti ang lakad para makahabol si KARL, magsisindi ng isang stick ng sigarilyo, tuloy pa rin ang lakad) New blood?  KARL: (nagulat sa pag-ingles) Yep…  SOPHOMORE: You smoke? (sabay abot ng kaha ng yosi) kuha ka.  KARL: I don’t smoke.  SOPHOMORE: You don’t know how to.  KARL: It’s not that… It’s just that I don’t want to.  SOPHOMORE: Don’t worry, that’s what they all say, next time you see them, they’d be puffing smoke like a train. (exhales a cloud of smoke)  KARL: Not me.  SOPHOMORE: Not yet. (smiles) 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sa isang kalsada sa kalagitnaan ng siyudad ng Angeles (Malayo sa “Area”), may isang tineydyer na may labinganim na taong gulang na ang naglalakad.  Ang tineydyer ay nakasuot ng itim na jacket, nakasalaming may makapal na frame na kulay itim, may itim na buhok, nakamaong pants at sneakers. Siya si Karl.  “Putcha… bakit pa kasi nahulog yung singkwenta sentimos eh… AMP…” ang isip ng kawawang tineydyer.  Nagsimulang bumuhos ang ulan galing sa madilim na kalangitan.  “Buwiset… ano ‘to? Nawala pa naman din ang payong ko… Shet, shet, shet, shet, shet, shet…”, bulong niya sa sarili habang patalon talon at umiiwas sa mga malalim na lubak ng kalsada na napuno ng tubig-ulan.Lalong lumakas ang ulan at napilitang sumilong sa isang waiting shed na may nakasulat na malaking letrang kulay pula : “Bawal Umihe Dito” si Karl.  “May silbe pala itong mga pinapagawa ni Lazatin no… Walanghiya… Ang yaman na siguro ng bulugan na iyon…”  Kakatapos pa lang ng eleksyon at marami pa ring nakadikit na poster ng mga kandidato, ang iba ay may drowing na ng sungay at bigote sa mukha..  “Bagay pala ni Jamby ang may sungay..”, isip ni Karl habang pinakatitigan ang litrato ng kandidato.. “Huuss… kung hindi lang kay Juday, lampaso ka na naman…”  Lumakas pa lalo ang ulan at may nakisilong rin sa shed ng ating bida.  “Uy, babae…”  Basang basa ang babaeng bagong silong sa shed.  “Lamig noh?” sabi ni Karl, pilit na nagsisimula ng isang friendly conversation.  “Oo nga eh..” Sagot naman ng babae habang nagti-text sa kanyang cellphone.  “Uy.. Shet, chinita… ang puti, cute pa…” isip ni Karl habang pilit na ikinukubli ang kanyang ngiti.  “Wala ka rin bang payong?” hirit pa ulit ni Karl.  “Ah? Wala eh… Basang basa nga ako eh.. Nakakaasaaaar…”, angal ng cute na babae. “Inindian nga ako ng imi-meet ko eh… bahala siya…” naasar na tuloy nito.  “Boyfriend?” tahimik na itinanong ni Karl.. Habang nag-iisip “Nakuuuu delikado ‘to… may sabit pa yata…”  “Hindi no!”, ang natatawang sagot ng dalaga.  “Syeri…” tuloy pa niya.  “Huh?” nalilitong sagot ni Karl.  “Ako nga pala si Syeri.”  “Ahhh… okay… Karl naman.” Ang pa-cute na sagot ng ating bida, umaasang makaiskor. Medyo humihina na ang ulan, at habang ganoon nga ay pinagmasdan ni Karl si Syeri, nakanakaw ng tingin dahil sa ibang direksyon nakatingin ang dalaga.  “O heto…” ang bukambibig ni Karl habang inaalok ang kanyang jacket kay Syeri, “nakakaawa ka naman kasi eh… para kang basing ibon…” sabay tawa.  “Ganon? Sige… Salamat ah..” kanyang sabi habang isinusuot na ang jacket ni Karl.  “Putcha… buti na lang pala nag long-sleeve ako, at least kahit wala na ang jacket, maporma pa rin..” isip ni Karl “Lamig… Putcha… Makonsensiya ka… Isoli mo jacket ko…”  “Number mo?” tanong ni Syeri habang naghahandang pumindot ng kanyang keypad.  “Shet 7610… PAQ! Ang yaman nitoh..” ang isip ni Karl “09274135547 yung akin… ikaw?”  “Ahhh… sige, malalaman mo rin naman kung sakaling isoli ko pa ang jacket mo, ‘di ba?”  “Ganon?”  “Oo… ganon… sige, salamat sa jacket, Karl!” sabay ngiti at lusob sa patuloy na humihinang ulan.  “Ang cute niya… Sana isoli niya yung jacket ko… Ang mahal non…”  Pinagmasdan ni Karl si Siyeri na tumawid ng kalsada at biglang nagpara ng isang Ford F150..  “Hmm… 7210, chinita, weird tagalog accent, girbaud™ shoes, girbaud™ pants, really expensive looking beret, F150 na sundo… This means only one theeng… Anak mayamannnnnnnnnnnnn!!”  “Sinong kausap mo?” tanong ng cigarette vendor na kakasilong lamang sa shed ng ating bida.  “Hahahahahahaha… May Maxx™ Honey-Lemon™ po kayo?”  “Meron, tatlo dalawang piso”  “Pabili po ng six pesos..”  “Kuha ka. Philip™ gusto mo?”  “Hindi po ako nagsisigarilyo..”  “Matututo ka rin… Marlboro™?” sagot ng vendor.  “Ayaw ko nga pong matuto eh…”  “Yan din ang sinasabi nila… DJ Mix™?”  “Tenk yu na lang...” sambit ni Karl sabay alis at sakay sa pinakamalapit na Checkpoint – Holy na jeep na Makita niya..  “HOY!!! Bayad mo!!” ang papawalang sigaw ng vendor habang palayo na ng palayo ang jeep ng binata.Hindi na ito pinansin ni Karl, nagabot ng 4.50 piso sa drayber sabay, “Estudyante po. UP, University of the Philippines..”  "Yabang ko.." puna niya sa sarili, habang iniisip kung may kahihinatnan ang kanyang ginagawa...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      No words, can express, the way, im feeling, sad,lonely, scared shitless, although i'm, all without, regret my, life has, been a,  living hell, it seems, that i, really really, have to, stop doing, this because, it's messing, my life, and screwing, my head, but i can't, stop now, i've gone, too far, beyond what, is out, of line,  Some words,  might express,  what im,  feeling now,  screwed up,  scared, sad,  lonely, pathetic,  im what,  you can, call a,  perennial dipshit,  who hasn't,  got a,  freaking clue,  of what,  is really,  going on,  with my,  life and, i dont, know what,  it all,  means and,  i dont,  know what,  she means, to me,  but i,  wish i,  knew anyway.  Oh crap, im really,  lost now, my mind, is screwed, my heart, is beating rapidly, like a, big-ass drum, and whatever, some other,  things i,  really don't, know what, im feeling, for myself, for her, for everyone, im really,  lost don't, know what,  i want,  but i'll,  update as,  soon as,  i realize, what im,  really really, really really,  here for.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>