<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       swearing off the woman. swearing off the woman like swearing off the bottle, keeping time with a taptaptap with the tippiest of my toes. impatient to get things going, and feeling like the ground just turned to silt.  everytime i see her name my stomach gives a little; it gets pushed in and all stuck to my spine in the greasiest of places. this is a time that looks like it smells - musty and brooding, like angry forgotten things that molded.  i promised myself that i would be better than this. i promised each grade school picture that next year's would be perfect.  
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       i have a great idea! chris christophersen and maybe a little mood lighting. maybe a little moonlighting for all the daytimers inside.  i have a better idea! anita baker and maybe a little peppermint tea. maybe a little pepper spray to keep the Feds away.  
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       holy crap of everything. i can't believe that i'm blogging. i remember a time when 'to blog' was not an infinitive, and Destiny's Child was just a couple of beh-behs. maybe this is the  furss day of the ress of my life . maybe it's just the last day of something that got broken.  in either case, i'm excited to be an exhibitionist. (!) i mean, for serious -- i had the option of making this all private or letting people poke around. how come i want to make this public?  [pensive gazing out the window for 29 seconds]  i dunno. i donncare. it's raining out and my lunch just came. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
        drizzle to the trizzle.  woke up this morning with a chill and some sort of fire in my belly. first place in the one-person race.  i left work last night and headed to the improv class, banking on the prospect of laughing my ass off. class was hard work and it needed to be; get the insides all bouncing around, and get the blood to the brain parts. i'm figuring out that i need to make huge leaps of improvement in order to impress myself.   ooh, and this:   it's terrifying to sit back in a crowded room to realize that all of the friends that surround you have only known you for a matter of months. meeting new people is both exhilirating and taxing -- you've got to cough up your history and entrust it to a stranger, hoping he or she buys the story and wants to see the movie. sometimes it's nice to find yourself in a space where nothing is new at all and that everything is made from a favorite sweatshirt.  but i don't have that right now. i've found myself in a space that is squeezing and uneasy. when whitney houston asked me, "didn't we almost have it all?" i should have just told her the truth.    
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
         hellboy got a sister called cubicle.    
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
         this is a song i made. and i sing it all the time.   every morning when i rise inside my head i pretend i am the sky  and own the rain and trees and sun. i'm looking at clouds to find their rhythm and rhyme. - i got big ideas,  and they're bigger than the sound of world records breaking.  something's coming up so she'll lay it down. it seems like the only way of things;  living for the space and time. i've got my sights on and i'm planning a Great Escape. - i got big ideas, and they're bigger than the sound of world records breaking.  there was a reason to believe that i would make it here. i've got more than dreams of california and i'm never going back. i've got a job to make the grade. i'll never run out of love or time, i've got time.      
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       blogspot rhymes with blood clot, and there's never been anything more perfect to describe my mood. this blood clot of a day just happens to be all sunshiny and brady bunch. and i can't have that right now.  but what is happening on the horizon is deliverance from this doo-doo of a ding-ling. i'm moving out, moving up, and moving across 2 blocks to my very own shoe-box. i signed the lease a couple days ago, having trudged through a very un-welcoming jewish neighborhood to do some handshaking and check-writing at the realtor place. it costs 5 bucks a month just to have an air conditioner, and lead paint has been banned since 1978. these things are important enough to make me secure contracts and promise not to sublet to my sister.  my desk is covered with abused paper and bitten pens. i've got a bottle of water and a stapler posing as paper-weights, and who knew that i would start my very own Exotic Stamp collection?   evil eye, third eye, needle's eye, baby face.  chocolate bar, acne scar, jelly jar, microsoft word. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       everything everything all all all went to a store in the mall mall mall needed a dress for the ball ball ball everything everything everything all  everything everything all all all  waited all night for your call call call bang my head on the wall wall wall everything everything everything all  everything everything all all all your teeth so white but your mouth too small so i went to the party with Pope John Paul everything everything everything all  ev-er-y-thing-is-so-nice-and-neat-not-bus-ted-like-be-fore 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
        whoops, bowl of shit   gotta find the right corner the most acute of angles in a very dark place  in a very dark place the most acute of angles gotta find the right corner to hold the walls up  to hold the walls up the most acute of angles in a very dark place i kick it in the teeth and i kick it into gear and i'm a cog that is loose  and i'm a liability 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       did i make a mistake?  nope.   - got life by the guts and i prop 'em up with my bow and arrow, stiff against the garage door, quiet so nobody gets bothered.  life ain't afraid of me, though. life's a big brother bully. i sucker punch him when he's not expecting it and i run away like the dickens and scream without first breathing deep.  my coworker/friend came over to my cubicle on the way out of work to say goodnight. i was snacking on a fingernail and basically wallowing in my anxiety when she appeared over the divider, her coat awreddy snapped up and happy to be leaving out the door with her. she must've sensed the sickness before she even got over here, and i sipped the mug of tea that i made 9 hours ago and pretended not to be as overwhelmed as i really am.  but luckily for me, things look brighter when the night approaches. i've got that part all twisted up wrong in my eyes. i can imagine my rods and cones fighting over who goes where, so, as it stands right now, my dawn comes at 6pm.  big lies from brown thighs all the while, the hugest smile no surprise by my disguise i thought i knew you, too. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       i'm jealous of a place called "fire island" a lump of land with a lot to live up to already aflame when you utter its name i'm jealous of a place called "fire island"  i'm weary of a pace called "light speed" a clocking of space with a lot to live up to a threat'ning to blind all eyes left behind i'm weary of a pace called "light speed"  i'm fevered by a dream called "now" a pin-prick of time with a lot to live up to exploded and cradled and realized and fabled i'm fevered by a dream called "now" 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       mind-dribble because i'm allowed to.  staff meeting/staff infection: i'm holding my priorities hostage just so's i can keep the health benefits. truth be told, the daily grind isn't as severe before it gets written out like this, but making something dramatic is better than not making it anything at all.  things that i look forward to lately:    - the hour train ride home after work.  - remembering that i have tasty leftovers in the fridge.  - remembering that i can take a smoke break.  - remembering that there can be a Boy George. - remembering that i have a body.  today, at the staff meeting, my boss used the phrase, "Between You, Me and the Lamppost."  as a result, i've decided that there truly is a Santa Claus.    
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       cartoon thought bubble. inside, it reads "i'm a-fuck this shit up."  two weeks ago, the ceiling over my cubicle caved in, due to the fact that the cooling system for our office was draining in a retarded way. the water that wasn't draining properly had collected over time, and this juicy bile exploded all over my business and destroyed every file i had.  last night, this started to happen again. i was staying late in efforts to make up for lost time for the previous incident. it started raining juicy bile over my head, and, after lifting my soul up to the Lawd Jeezus, i cleared my desk and left work. i came in today to find the cooling system's guts all exposed, and there is a gaping hole over my desk that lets in doo-dooey air and lawd-knows-what-else. i'm in the corner cubicle now, the one that is reserved for the temps. the one that has the broken chair. the one that is also used at storage for all the files that haven't made it to the archives.   i'm twenny five years old, and the only thing i want is my mommy.  *************  in another brain about things, i wrote that poem for C last night. she interpreted to mean that i was jealous that she was going away for the weekend. oops. i just like how "fire island" sounds. i just want to be "fire island."  cocoa puff outta the biggest bong. things go wrong, so i make a song. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       egg and sperm, then the spark of life.   'my red smoke' came from a journal entry i made back in, like, 2000. or 1999. or some other awesome time before this un-awesome time. 'my red smoke' was this thing that i wished that i had. i wanted to trail a column of red smoke behind me wherever i went, like some Diva Wicked Witch of the Breast or something. i wanted people to know that i was there, and that what i left made you cough and also blinded in a colorful way. i have no qualms about admitting that my ego is prolly not the smallest. and i'm normally sad about failing at being the person i think i can. so, if i can't leave a trail of gold or chocolate behind me, it should be at least something that stinks and takes up space. because i'm evil like that.  so, right, how come the sadism? what's the deliciousness in it?   i'm trying to figger that one out with the help of psycho-analytic lovers and a dash of Oprah.  whistle blow, jump ball, sneaker untied, oops. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       .75 + .75 + .50 + .75 + .75 = $3.00  i just spent 3 bux in the vending maching in the staff cafeteria.  it is 6:51pm, and everybody went home except for the cleaning dude and the security guard. i am now on the verge of truly vomitting over my desk. and this is what it will look like: a chocolatey-almond covered swedish fish with a dusting of assorted chips and probably someone's wristwatch.  staying late, because i'm catholic, and catholics are professional guilt harborers. that's all. that's it.  eeny meeny miney moe. cut my foot off to spite my toe.   well, DUH! 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       can we make this great? can we make this a viable reason?  stream of boringness:  kitty litter pittance and good riddance father capricorn movie pocorn nickel bag, redhead bounding stallion 1992 vcr dandelion wine paperback  apathetic nuns rollerrink on sunday, too late to count hangnails like there is no tomorrow  that's all i've got right now. that and a bucket of sandcastling to do. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Sometimes, when I'm on the train or when I'm having a conversation that I don't care about, I invent songs.     &nbsp;     This one is just a little bit of a larger theme about C and needing to escape with her from this stupid place.    &nbsp;     you know, i've got big ideas  and, baby, you make the best desserts  so let's fly to a tropical island  and leave our bathing suits at home  on purpose      It's wikkid fun to sing.    I&nbsp;think&nbsp;I've&nbsp;been singing to myself a little bit too much lately. &nbsp;Talking to oneself is different -- that's either just flat out delusion, depression, absence of mind, or just habit. It can go the range from benign to pathologic. Either way, its symptomatic of  something . Singing to oneself is something completely different. And it's really different from singing out loud. Singing to oneself is more than trying to entertain yourself. It's more than being delusional, depressed, oblivious, or lonely. This bizzniss is about invention when there's no need to invent. A performance for the smallest audience. Leading lady, balcony heckler, backstage groupie, and stage manager all wrapped up in one. I feel like&nbsp;a freak, but not enough to stop doing it.    Not writing in a while makes me feel like rust. Consumed and dried out, red and tetanus-y. I steal this time from work, fully relishing the fact that someone somewhere is going to suffer for these 5 minutes that could've been spent on them or their paperwork or their lives. But I stole it, and I rushed home, and I opened up the package, and realized that it already  belonged to me.     What's the formula for a true Catholic?    2 parts homosexual, 19 parts guilt, 30 parts sadism. Or am I off?    I think I'm off.      &nbsp;    &nbsp;    
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       i can't take today. i can't leave today, either. so "take it, or leave it" sounds like a dead end idiom for a dead end dead head.  i'm tiptoeing around the office, trying to make like i'm diligently working for the good of the organization. this elbow grease is only oozing out of guilt of the fact that i know that i'm going to be quitting my job within the next few weeks. it's like i'm clearing a nice space to shit on and leave for my coworkers, who i actually really love. i don't think i'm the type of person that can leave my work at work. at least when i'm tendering people's visa sponsorship. that stuff is too much.   C's coming back. this is a dream that can only come true! 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>