<Blog>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. My name is Karla   2. I am a female   3. I am 26 years old   4. I live on capital hill in denver   5. I was born in Iowa   6. I have lived in iowa, alaska, florida, and colorado   7. I have blue eyes   8. I have light brown hair   9. I am a 9th year senior biology major.   10. I am a genius.. self proclaimed.. and thats all that matters   11. I have decapitated over 2000 baby rats in the name of science   12. My favorite song is "Into the Mystic" Van Morrison   13. My favorite color is pink   14. I am a procrastinator   15. It should not be taking me ten years to get my four year degree   16. I have a two black cats. Niles and Frasier.  17. If you have a good pet &amp; a good toy, you dont need a man.  (Not in any way implying the pet and toy are related or used in conjunction..)  (Shit.. i am already a crazy cat lady!)   18. I sing Borderline everytime I karyoke.   19. I have danced the mahkerena in a wheelchair at a star trek convention   20. My porn star name would be Molly B. Boulder (following the first pet + first street rule)   21. Born on August 1st a Leo   22. I am 5'6"   23. I am a righty   24. I am half Czech half mutt   25. The perfect pizza is dominos thin crust cheese   26. My goal is contentment   27. My fears are that there is no higher power and drowning   28. My weakness is mind altering distractions   29. My first waking thoughts are.. how late am I today?   30. Pepsi or Coke? Mountain Dew   31. Vanilla not chocolate   32. Chipotle not Qdoba   33. Peppermint mocha frappachino   34. Eggs: poached   35. Best sushi: Eel&amp;avacado roll   36. There is only one person I would trust with my life.   37.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  38.             
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. The white walls always appear green as I am falling asleep. I know they are white, but they look bright green.  &nbsp;  2. I have no conscience. I never really feel that bad or guilty when I have been wrong/bitch/evil/inconsiderate/etc. to someone. I know I should. I have noticed that I say sorry a lot.. and I am good at pretending I do... but I don't.  &nbsp;  3. &nbsp;I don't think i fear death.. I discovered this when I was in a car going 65 miles an hour doing donuts, completely out of control.. heading straight for another car head on... I thought.. well.. I am going to die now. I finally get to see whats next. I honestly at that moment didn't think there was an afterlife and I was just gonna be over.. and I didn't care.  &nbsp;  4. One of my best friends is nearly a klepto (part time job he says) &nbsp;and I think there is nothing wrong with this.  &nbsp;  5. One of my best friends is a cheater and it never crosses my mind that there is something wrong with this either.  &nbsp;  6. One of my best friends is basically a hooker and I see nothing wrong with this.  (I am realizing that I might attract these crazy friends because I am an enabler!)  &nbsp;  7.&nbsp;Despite all these things.. I have been called "sweet" by almost everyone I know.&nbsp;No one reaalllly knows.  &nbsp;  8. I decapitate live newborn rats (at work) and find amusement in their arms and legs still flailing on their headless bodies.  &nbsp;  9.&nbsp;&nbsp;Besides with the few people I care about, I usually feel completely insincere.  &nbsp;  10.&nbsp; I am a self proclaimed genius but use it mostly&nbsp;for&nbsp;evil covert ops&nbsp;not good.  &nbsp;  11. &nbsp; I have played poop dollar and thought it was hysterical.  &nbsp;  12.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>


<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I need a new job. I love my job. I love my coworkers. But I dreamed about it and now I need a new job.  I am a killer. I have decapitated 40 newborn rat babies almost every monday for a year. I cut off their heads with scissors and slice down their chests and pop out their hearts. (Research, knowledge, medicine, good cause, yada yada.) Their little arms and legs and tails are still moving in a pile of bodies with no heads.  This sight has actually even made me giggle. If I am robotically decapitating rats in my dreams, I think I need a new job.  If I believe in karma and reincarnation.. am I going to be reborn as a rat 2000 times and get my head chopped off before I open my eyes? Or no.. is something that is just equal to 2000 decapitations going to happen to me in this life? Not considering just these rats... have I already so karmicly fucked myself that I can say screw it? and stop worrying about my soul and karma and the afterlife.. because i have so many lifetimes of suffering and repayment and all that that i wont be getting to any nirvana anytime soon anyways? I can see myself starting to obsess in a circle here so I am just going to go to bed and have more bloody dreams.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Has anyone else noticed that little religious kids have much worse staring problems than heathen children? I went to church today with marge and chuck. (I am poor and they have cash, so I sold out.) Its been so long since I went to a church that I forgot how fun it is to make faces at all the little kids that stare at you when no one else is looking.  I kept feeling like it was my duty to tell them that there was no such thing as the devil, so their parents fear tactics wouldn't work anymore. But I guess they can figure that our for themselves someday.. or when they die. ha. This weekend was lame and I am lame. You know you have no life when you are looking forward to monday, to work. Shit. Tuesday this week. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have a new diet plan! And it seems to work! So I was at a friend's house last week going through her closet helping her throw out the ex's stuff since he seems to be gone for good this time. Jail does that. (Probably more on this later) We found some of his porn and decided to watch it since we all love porn right? The very first one we pop in turned out to be "fuck a fattie." The first porn I have ever found that I was appalled by! The kind of thing that is so disgusting that you cannot tear your eyes away from it... or turn it off. Now this was not just pleasantly plump girls, but girls with stretch marks an inch wide! Fucking skinny little greasers! We spent about twenty minutes demanding each other to turn it off with no luck. Finally her new boyfriend came in and rescued us and turned it off and threw it away. Oh.. this is the guy she has know for thirty three days.. moved into her place 32 days ago... and got her name tattooed on his arm from elbow to wrist in big black lettering 3 days ago. Fucking idiot! He will probably be moved out within a week. Shit, I keep getting distracted. OK. So I have a new diet plan and it seems to work. I have instructed all my people that whenever I am going to eat something bad to say "fuck a fatty!" This plan occurred to me shortly after the porn viewing when I wanted a nutty bar and the friend whom we will call Montana since that is her stripper stage name said, "oh really bizarla? do ya wannabeyafuckafattie?" This diet plan is so gonna work. I just know it!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah! I always wanted to be the imaginary pre-op member of  urlLink someones  posse! Check number 591 off things to do list.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you ever dreamed that you really had to piss? and then you did.. and it felt sooo good? and then you woke up.. and realized you weren't dreaming? Me neither.   Redonkulus  (adj.) half ridiculous, half a donkey's ass  Marge and Chuck are visiting. (Can't believe I was spawned from people named Marge and Chuck.) We had to go to the Applepee's for dinner. I mean supper. Because Marge is on the Weight Watchers and needs to know exactly how many "points" she is eating. Pee's actually lists the points on their menu. She is only allowed 21 a day. I find this makes both Marge and Pees redonkulus. Hmmm. After further consideration, skinny lady counting points, or fat girl making fun of skinny lady counting points.. hmm.. maybe I am the redonkulus one. Naaa.  And I am a girl and I like pink and I expect to recieve no shit for having a pink page. The fact that pink annoys many people makes me all the more happy to enjoy my pink page.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I went to the nerd ball at the trekkie convention. Just as T told me it would be, it  was like homecoming for geeks in costumes. From Gay-Vader to Gollum to Strawberry Shortcake. I got to ask a Klingon why they had foreskin on their forehead. Still no explanation on that. Anyways, never underestimate the joy of dancing the mahkerana (sp?) in a wheelchair wearing a bushy black wig, a rainbow propeller hat, glasses that make you look bug-eyed, and a tshirt that says "I'm with cripple." Sooo fun!  T ended up getting the hotel room comped because yellow liquid was pouring into the bathroom from the ceiling. What luck!   I am gonna try to figure out how to post pictures because words don't do the experience justice. Tired.. brain hurts.. more later.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I typed in my address wrong, flipped around two letters, and got this. Funny.   urlLink http://www.bizarlaritz.blogpsot.com/ 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OK So the movie Saved reminded me of some characters from my childhood.  Those fanatic born agains.  One of them, Nichole, I am still good friends with. She is a 2nd grade teacher at a bible school. She is so religious that she prays every time we talk on the phone before we can hang up. (I talk to her about once every three months.) I have to point out the difference between her and basically all of the other born agains I went to school with. She has tolerance. She doesnt judge. And she isn't fake. I believe that she actually feels it in her heart.  She's wrong of course! but she feels it.. and I respect that. Plus she finally stopped trying to convert me.  Anyways...  She is 27 years old and still a virgin. She is even a renewed kiss virgin. She will now not kiss anyone till she is married. Probably why she is 27 and still no prospects. I told her that she is going to die an old maid. She disputes this saying that Jesus will give her the desires of her heart.   So she was out to visit me awhile back and we had a discussion about masturbation. I wanted to make sure that if she isn't ever gonna have sex.. that she at least has that.   Nichole: Oh no.. I dont do that. Because lust is a sin and I would be lusting after a guy while doing that.  Me: Don't think about a guy!  think about yourself =) ..after the initial confusion I talked her into this not being lust so not sinful!  Nichole: wait.. i would be touching myself so i would be having sex with myself and premarital sex is wrong.  (Sheeesh!) Me: OK.. so don't touch yourself.. use water Nichole: huh? (again sheesh!) Me: the water coming out of the bathtub faucet .. short discussion of how this works and then she had to think and pray about it..  fast forward a couple months. I get a call from Nichole. She is crying.  Nichole: Now I have to tell my future husband that he isnt my first orgasm. (once more, Sheesh!) Me: (excited) It worked then?! Nichole: It worked. Me: Nichole.. if you say that to a guy.. he is gonna think you are crazy.. Nichole: not a godly man Me: I guarantee you will not be his first.. more like his 10,000th Nichole: more crying even louder   Gotta love her.  Hey.. i gotta have friends like Nichole to balance out friends like Montana.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      " urlLink Bush  is a  urlLink dangerous  right-wing ideologue who couples his political fanaticism with a neo-Christian blood cult."  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Will someone please donate 5K to my  urlLink cause  so I can become smooooth?!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink here   must  urlLink enter! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Interesting   Sweden exports lotsa weapons.   urlLink Funny   Guadeloupe has lotsa jehovah's.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been suggested that I share some stories of my stripper pals.  So since nothing happens in my boring life.. I will resort to telling stripper tales.  Fact.. all strippers AKA hookers have sugar daddies which I have renamed sponsors.. makes it sound more like a helping out kind of situation than a get paid lots of money to have some disgusting guy with a crap bag on his side lick your ass situation.  So dancers make excellent acquaintances, in small doses of course, for many reasons.  First of all.. they always have cash and insist on paying for everything...cover charges, drinks, movies, sushi (they love sushi), gas, and drugs.. (if one did drugs.. which drugs are bad.. dont do drugs) ...etc. I think most of them have some weird sort of codependecy disorder where they think they have to make you like them by buying you things. I won't complain about that! Secondly... they are severely fucked up in the head and make your.. or should i say my fuckedupness appear small in comparison. And finally.. this might be a bad thing more than a good thing... they are so dramatic and chaotic that there is always some sort of entertainment in my boring life.  Take for instance the taser gun episode.    Well, I should introduce you to the characters first. First of all, there is Montana; Small town girl turned hoochie in the city.  She will be the main character of most future stripper tales. Then there is the loser we will call Justin, because that is his real name and we could care less about protecting his privacy.  Justin (her one night stand that lasted for five days in Butte, Montucky) is the felon that Montana came to Denver for.. without his knowledge.. who was living with his girlfriend when Montana packed up, drove 16 hours, and knocked on his door.  Then there are Ivy (the older) and Diamond (the younger), bleach blond hair extension stripper sisters from O Canada.    So.. once upon a time... when our friendship was off.. too bad cause I so wish I could have witnessed this one.. oh yeah.. friendships with strippers are on and off kinds of friendships.. more on this later) This is a compilation story from both sides which no longer speak to each other. Anyways, Montana and the O Canada sisters were hanging out and scheming.  How to get Justin and Montana together despite her new boyfriend, the ankle monitor, and the restraining order keeping them apart (due to a mutually abusive relationship.)  Brilliant idea.. lets have him spend the night on his first all night pass at Ivy's house so his probation officer doesn't see him enter Montana's "zone."  They go out, and come home with even yet a new set of guys.. and Justin is waiting there for them. Duh.. forgot about him. Yelling and throwing things ensues.. and somehow Diamond and Montana begin fighting each other. No one knows exactly how this began.  But I suspect someone hit on someone elses guy.  Strippers are very jealous, paranoid, and quick tempered. Adding to the speedy escalation of all disagreements.  So they are still on the bed kicking punching and ripping out $3000 hair extensions.  Ivy begins to get pissed because they are trashing her house and all her expensive tacky belongings (another stripper hallmark.)  So she whips out the taser gun and begins to taser her little sis and Montana until they stop fighting each other and start chasing her.  Side note: most strippers have weapons that more often get used on them than protect them.  Somehow everyone settles down.  Ivy couldn't help herself because its too much fun and has to reach out and taser Montana once more on the back on her skin.  Montana claims to have taser burn marks on her ass from this.  She also admits to peeing her pants both times she was tasered. Ivy swears that she tasered Montana's "big disgusting love handle" not her ass.  This is amusing to me because I know that there are no love handles.. just skin and bones.  On her way out the door, Montana picks up a purple drink and flings it all over Ivy's white suede furniture and carpet.    Just now, I realized how I wish I could have videotaped this episode and set it to some fun music.  I really need to get a video camera!  Oh.. so now I am forbidden by Montana to be friends with the O Canadians or to babysit for them anymore. Yeah right! They pay me too well! Of course I still do it.  Which reminds me of another funny side story.  So Diamond asks me to bbsit for her.  On that day Montana calls- Montana: Whatcha doin tonight? Lets get choochee (sushi) Me: Oh.. um.. uh.. i am baby sitting  Montana: oh really? who? Me: (shit lie fast) um.. oooo.. just this lady from work's kid (now why i just didnt say who it really was and fuck off you are not the boss of me.. i don't know) Montana: Since when do you bbysit for people at work? what lady?  Me: I have before.. and her name is.. um.. uh.. angggeeeeellllla (OK so Diamond's nonstripper name is Angelique AKA Ang) what a dumbass I am.. i can't even think fast enough to lie well.. i say angela?! angela?! hello!) Montana: Really? (tone of voice that says you are so full of shit and I know it) Me: yeah Montana: karla are you bbsitting for ang? Me: Noooo.. see. thats why i didnt say the name before.. because I knew you would be weird.. its just a coincidence.. Montana: oh.. ok then.. talk to you later bye Then, about 15 minutes later I recieve a txt msg from her. (for some reason we often text song lyrics to each other) It reads:  I just called to say I love you and i mean it from the bottom of my heart. (not sure if she was trying to make me feel guilty or saying she didnt care anymore..) so i txt back: great green gobs of greasy grimy gopher guts.  And if anyone is still reading and made it this far.. i am impressed!  After reading the above.. I have to add one more thing. I have to say that dancers are not all bad. Its like they are half angelic half demonic. Sometimes senstive with big hearts, but sometimes destructive train wrecks. The word sucubus comes to mind. Ah! just like my sister! maybe thats why I continue the friendships.  I see where they came from and why they are the way they are.  So its hard to walk away. With that said... I will probably ususally just tell the stripper tales of chaos, drama, violence and the sort.. the good stories. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why do the walls which I know are white.. always look bright green as I am falling asleep?  I need to make a list of all the reasons I think I am insane...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Seven dollars  urlLink wellspent !  Saved  Hysterical satire about a Xstian girl who loses her virginity to her boyfriend who has been "stricken with the spiritually unfortunate condition" of "faggotry" to "save" him.. because "jesus told her to."   Also including a pep rally for jesus with a pastor who is down with christ!  and mandy moore on a mission to "save" the jewish girl.. who begins speaking in tongues about her pussy while ripping her shirt open at the rally...  The characters seem over the top judgmental and intolerant and fake.. but having personally suffered through religious school for 10 years of my life... these characters could have been taken right out of my childhood! oh.. and what the Xstians are  urlLink saying  about it. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whatever you do.. dont do the blue one with the  urlLink dolphin  on it!  not because it isnt good.. but because the two days afterward are hell..  and i know this because.. um.. someone told me so..   disclaimer: drugs are bad.. dont do drugs   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bush Manages a  urlLink Complete  Sentence  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Listening to the radio at work today... and playing our fun game of  urlLink lyrics ... spiritual or sexual?  "If you want to kiss the sky ... Better learn how to kneel... (on your kness boy!) " -U2   Achtung Baby 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hereby pronounce new official rules for Trivial Pursuit. (Because I can.)  Whosoever gets all their pies first is the winner.  Fuck being the first one back to the middle.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Baaaad  urlLink idea . Another way for women to further fuck up their hormones and make them more crazy.   Why the pill is bad- 1. Takes away sex drive 2. Makes you fatter 3. do we need any more?  Fun fact- Crushed up birth control pills make great plant food.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After doing one little tiny, stupid, airhead thing today.. and fucking up my whole week long experiment, I am reminded of my favorite quote to steal and use (w/o due credit).. when someone is being a dumbass.   "There are two kinds of things in this world Karla * or insert name of other dumbass here *. There's rocket science.. and there's everything else! and this aint rocket science!"   -originally stolen from cheesypoof after previous airhead work moment   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its sad that I have enough free time at work to find something like this. -Fun  urlLink picture  of the day.   "when you are insane your mechanism for being able to tell when you are insane is impaired." --Sylvia Does this mean that if you suspect you are insane... you must have this mechanism and therefore are not insane..?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What kind of test tells you that you are the movie Schindlers List?!  They must make you answer a bunch of questions for no reason..then just randomly pick a movie.. because I don't see how they got THIS movie out of MY answers! whateva...        urlLink What Classic Movie Are You?    urlLink personality tests by similarminds.com  
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      These  urlLink quizzes  can be addictive!  So I am somewhat borderline, schizotypal, and schizoid. OK. That explains everything.            Personality Disorder Test Results       urlLink Paranoid    ||||||||||||||   58%        urlLink Schizoid    ||||||||||||||||||   74%        urlLink Schizotypal    ||||||||||||||||   70%        urlLink Antisocial    ||||||||||||   46%        urlLink Borderline    ||||||||||||||||   70%        urlLink Histrionic    ||||||||||   34%        urlLink Narcissistic    ||||||   22%        urlLink Avoidant    ||||||||||||   50%        urlLink Dependent    ||||||||||||   42%        urlLink  Obsessive-Compulsive     ||||   18%      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       * your ass smells like sharp cheddar  urlLink cheese .  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well. Looks like I am a bitch.             Global Personality Test Results
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I saw Claude, my old gay stalker neighbor, stumbling across Colfax today with his sippies in hand.  (One sippy vodka and one sippy water.) He doesn't eat.. just trying to drink himself to death and not succeeding. He was a block away from my apartment building. He must use the same post office I do. Great. This is the crazy-drunk-yellow-haired-eskimo that I moved so I would never have to see again.. the one who left life-story never-ending voice mails on my phone almost daily even after I hadnt talked to him for months.. The one who has been married five times.. three men and two women. I took my voice off my voice mail message for over a month.. and had friends answer and say he had the wrong number enough times that he finally stopped calling. Unfortunately.. today.. he saw me too.. on my bike... and called my cell phone.. and heard my voice on it. What horrible fucking luck. =( ahhhh! I can't believe he is even still alive! I saw the medical photos of his innards full of cancer over a year ago. and just when I thought it was almost safe to go see my favorite drag show at  urlLink Charlie's  again... bammers
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh yeah. So I don't pay attention to the news as much as I should. Due in part to not having television at my apartment... due to being too lazy to go buy rabbit ears. Actually, I get most of my news from my boss or from reading blogs.   So.. I was taking my first drive this year across Rocky Mountain national park on Sunday. My favorite way is to drive up to Winter Park, Grandby, then Grand Lake.. then over Trail Ridge to Estes and down.  Anyways, I drove right into Grandby and unexpectedly, immediately saw a white Excel energy pick-up folded perfectly in half sticking into the wall of a the first building in town! Like someone literally plowed it straight into the building. Turns out..  urlLink they did ! Which I would have known had I watched any news. Then we saw many other buildings bulldozed through, a demolished bank, and town hall basically on its side! Of course, I went back and got a picture standing near the perfectly halved pickup.  Sometimes I have such good luck.. =) Oh, and I also find it very amusing that my ex-husband is from the same town that produced this bulldozer dumbass!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My poor  urlLink mom.   If anyone reads this... please send my mom your good energy.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      When I was little, I used to open my bedroom window at night and invite any nearby vampires to come in... because remember.. they can't come in without being invited. They never came.  Bammers! Maybe they only come to people who don't want them.. its more fun that way right?     urlLink Link  to awesome Denver author of novels with incestuous  urlLink vampires , and warm&fuzzy&lovable killer  urlLink mercenaries .  urlLink Fun!   Still anxiously awaiting the next one.   urlLink Link  to someone who handed me down my first and much enjoyed vampirotica porn comic book. More fun!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I did something really retarded.  While at a tattoo shop awhile back I let myself get talked into having what they called a dry run done on my arm.  I don't even want a tattoo. But for some stupid reason.. at the time.. really wanted to know what it felt like to get one.  I actually paid five bucks for this for the needle.  They used water instead of ink and told me to pick a word and where i wanted it. I chose to just have my initials on my arm.  Supposedly, I would get to see what it felt like but no ink would go in my skin.  I would be able to see the initials because it would be red from the needle.  After a couple weeks, it would heal and go away.  It has now been two weeks and the stupid thing is still there. Bright red as the day it happened.  And how could I not think about the fact that it might turn into a permanent scar? duhhhhh Well, the good news is.. it didnt hurt... mild discomfort.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My laziness had the brilliant idea recently to buy a bike and start riding to work and school.  I have a gym membership but the gym is so fucking boring, and of course I am too lazy to go.  I measured the mileage to work in my car. Its 2.3 miles one way, and in the car seemed fairly flat. Perfect. If I do this every day.. I will bike 23 miles a week. Measured the miles to school, ~3 hilly miles. Today I biked to work. Hills.. lots of hills. Muscles on fire.  Nixing the bike to school idea since I would certainly have a heart attack on those hills.  I am reminded of my previous belief that excercise sucks and starvation would be a much better diet plan. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yaaaah! My sister got out of alaska state prison. Hopefully she doesn't go back to living by her old motto that stupid people do drugs, smart people sell drugs.  (Love you sis!)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is the first day of my summer classes.  Why i signed up for summer torture, I dont know. And I already spent all the cash I had for books on baby stuff. I was woken up today by a phone call telling me that Rachel, a friend through a friend, just had a baby girl. Hello?! No one even knew that Rachel was pg.. supposedly not even Rachel. What?! I thought that only teenagers subconsciously denied pregnancy.. not twenty somethings! Knowing that this baby was probably born with drugs in its system and prolly has at least one syndrome.. and mom and dad have no money.. i spent my book money on baby stuff. I didnt even get to buy fun baby stuff.. just boring practical bottles, and diapers, and shit like that. hmph. Oh well. At least the baby is cute and has all its fingers and toes. Maybe this gives me an excuse not to take summer classes! Cant take the class if i dont have the book right?!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HM Department of Vague Paranoia  urlLink Welcome to the Preparing for Emergencies website  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Montana has been spending time with beater boy again.. but cheating on him as always of course.  She started this new bartending job and lots of the cute neighborhood boys like to drink there. Notice how I said "boys." Anyways... the bartender training her never ID'd this one particular boy.. so when she started on her own. .she didn't either. I took one look at him and said.. he ain't 21! But he said he just turned 21.. blah blah blah.. So montana proceeds to start to hook up with him.. a couple days later I walk in there after work and he is there. The sucubus has convinced him to visit her at work instead of "training." (kickboxing wannabe)  He says he has to ask me something.. Do I think she will break up with him if he is not quite as old as he said and lied. Ha! Break up!? you aren't even to that point yet  you silly little boy. anyways.. turns out he is 19. when is your birthday i ask? july... ah hahahahaha... he just turned 19. (Montana is almost 23.)  this makes my day!  don't tell her dont tell her he says! ok .. but you know i have to tell her... I convieniently wait to tell her until after she does him! oops! how was i supposed to know she was gonna do that?! hehehehe i feel so evil. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So as most birthday weeks seem to be for me.. this week sucked ass!  gross hairy sweaty shitty   cheddar   cheese smellin ass ..  all over the place   Work - got lectured.. Disappointed the boss man... blew off one experiment and fucked up the  other one...   School - can't afford fall tuition and am finally coming out of denial and not registering for the two lousy classes i need to graduate this fall.  Men - fuck them.. fuck them all.. literally and figuratively!! in the ass!!  Men side note - how can ex boyfriends somehow just knowwww when you are not doing good and feeling low enough to actually talk to them again!? why can't they call when all is well and i can tell them to fuck right off.. i don't need to talk to you right now or ever again!!!  how come they can be then be so cool and listen and ooo i am so there for you.. blah blah blah.. and then try to get a blow job.. no you ass! you have a fucking girlfriend!!!  Money - so my checks are going to be garnished.. 25%.. for a truck i bought my ex-husbag five years ago that i almost had paid off but he let get repoed when i left him and now i have a big bill, repo fee, lawyer fee, a judgement i never even heard about until this week... when payroll called me. my now measly 550 check every two weeks will be 412. fuck! i am going to be homeless. the only way to avoid/stop garnishments is to file bankruptcy.. which i was trying to avoid doing because i dont want to be one of "those" kind of people.. but fuck it.. i come from white trash.. maybe it is my destiny.. only problem is.. i can't even afford to file bankruptcy.. how do they think people who need to file.. are going to come up with 200 to file and a buttload more for the lawyer?! duh  health - no comment.. but not good.. oh.. and need to stop smoking when drinking.. bad.. very bad... oh.. and need to stop drinking.. also very bad...  oh.. and need to not smoke with strangers whose moldy mari jo anna makes me sick for two days!  friends - they all want something.. they all talk shit.. or they all move away.. one is on her spiritual high horse and won't come down enough to even talk too.. one is so caught up in hoochieville that even i am losing respect.. and that takes a lot! aaand they (this they being montana) live at my apt and make me crazy.. make my cats sleep in the living room and not with me.. b/c theyyyy are allergic.. fuck that.. no more.. montana. .you get the boot.. nile and frasier you get the bed... ok. i love my friends.. but sometimes.. sheeesh!  ok i feel better now.. i am going to leave work early and start celebrating my bday weekend right now! dirty martini.. here i come  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Quote of the week- Midgets should never start  urlLink trains !  I finally saw this movie and the first 20 minutes were hysterical and we found many politically incorrect things to say and laugh so hard about that i once again pissed my pants... (i am going to be incontinent by the time i am 30!)  the rest of the movie.. snore....  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. Drive around yard sailing 2. while driving around throw pop its out the window by/at all pedestrians, bikers, animals, and funny looking peeps in yards 3. Go to costume stores and try on funny wigs 4. Go to Blinky's on Broadway and see all the antique type things he is selling.. and yes its actually the real Blinky from the Clown show.. and if you ask him if he is blinky he will give you an autographed pic. My science geekness enjoyed the antique microscopes for sale. Must go here either way to see his newly aquired authenic antiquish nazi flag that he is selling for like $300 bucks.. ick! evil.. must wash hands after touching! Silly old man was actually sitting outside with it draped across a chair one day. He is either asking for it! or actually a nazi.. 5. Use all the monopoly money to play Texas Hold em... and go all in on a pair of twos!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The way to a girl's heart is kissing her best friend's arse... no matter what you really think of her...   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sweet! Someone found my blog while trying to look for  urlLink Pep Rally for Jesus . Ha! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      When you call someone on your cell phone and they don't answer.. and someone you are with (not by choice but tolerating them) says here let me call from my phone.. and the fucking person answers.&nbsp; And they arent doing anything and they weren't busy. So you were obviously dissed. Especially when you know you are way fucking cooler than the other person... stupid annoying bitch.. why would you do that?! Ok. Thats all. I feel better now. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Holy shit.. i am so computer challenged. I was determined tonite to figure out this&nbsp;adding photos to blogs&nbsp;thingy. It took way to fucking long.. and I will probably never try it again.&nbsp;It&nbsp;had to be&nbsp;by sheer luck that I even got one on there.&nbsp;&nbsp; I followed the directions.. it didnt work. I didnt follow the directions.. it worked. Typical. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Is  urlLink this  site psychic or what!?  I put in my old name.. and out comes  I now dub your ass: Ugly Crab Whacka&nbsp;  &nbsp; I did it again and out comes...&nbsp;  &nbsp; I now dub your ass: Loose Drug Smuggla&nbsp;  &nbsp; Do this, its a fun complete waste of time..&nbsp; That I happily stole from some  urlLink funny bitches !  &nbsp;  Yep. Stole this too.&nbsp;&nbsp;  urlLink I Just Want BANGBANGBANG &nbsp; (Make sure volume is on.. hehe)      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       and&nbsp;my inner dragon is a ....      Chaos Dragon     In the war between good and evil, your inner Dragon self is rotten with the stench of EVIL.When it comes to the powers of Chaos vs. those of Law and Order, your inner dragon is a risk taker and answers to no one.As far as magical tendancies, Your inner dragon has the ability to conquer the world of magic, but it will not be easy.During combat situations, whether by spells or by claw, your inner dragon will do whatever it takes to get the job done.     Dragon Description:  Chaos dragons are the unpredictable, violent dragons of the ever-changing plane of Limbo. They are an isolated branch of the lower planar dragons, being concerned with issues that no one has been able to understand.     Chaos dragons seem to exist just to perpetrate acts of chaos - destroying order where ever they find it. The chaos of the chaos dragons is colored by evil.     They are more than just chaotic; they are also violent, evil, and merciless. A chaos dragon rarely shows any emotion other than a wild, maniacal glee. In appearance, chaos dragons are unremarkable.Their scales are a dull gray color, and their eyes are a similar pale color. Of all the many types of dragons, they are one of the few without a magnificent appearance.     This Dragons favorite elements are: Mercury, Explosions, and Chaos     &nbsp;   dragon quiz   urlLink  here     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Imaginary Girlfriends  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No party ever sounded so dorky but ended up to be so much fun..  so tonite..  I went to a "polaroid" party.. after we all bbq'd and got  appropriately lit..  we got a list of scavenger hunt type things we had to get a photo of. Our group... travilous, john, and I won! we had the best pics! (once again.. i have to figure out how to scan and put some of them on here) so..  -there is a pic of me and travis in a random apartment building's swimming pool downtown.. after jumping the fence and getting in (without pants!) -we also had to get a pic of someone with a MOM tattoo.. so we went to a tattoo parlor and had a tattoo artist draw a mom tattoo with a heart around it in sharpee on my arm.. in the pic (me and the tattoo guy) it totally looks like a real hic mom tattoo.. soooo funny!   urlLink    Mom Tattoo  urlLink     -also.. we were supposed to get a pic of us in a convertible.. we stalked this black porsche boxster  in cherry creek for a few minutes.. but they were too pussy to let me jump in for a pic.. too worried about an alarm or something.. so we ended up finding an old convertible on broadway covered in a tarp that we jumped in it instead.. another funny! -then we were supposed to get a pic of a clown.. so we got the Herman's Hideaway bouncer to take a pic of us in front of a  Blinky the Clown poster in a window... (old denver perv clown in case anyone doesnt remember)   -alsoooo... we were supposed to get a pic of the dirtiest tshirt slogan.. so we went to Fascinations and got a pic with me wearing an "i fucked yer husband" tshirt , and a "my girlfriend sucks.. good dick" tshirt..  with a big penis head hat on! -then... we needed a bush lookalike pic... so we took a pic of a poster in a window downtown of Bush's head on a nudie girl with a big bush.. bush with a bush.. sweet!  there were some other funnies.. but i can't remember them all..  after looking back.. it kinda seems like we sorta cheated to get all our pics.. but oh well. .our's were funniest.. except for the team that got five people into a portapotty..but since i am a germaphobe.. i took one look at that one on the list and said no way!        
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Beautiful  urlLink justice !  &nbsp; (I stole this link from someone and forgot to write down their address to give them credit. Oops.) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I came out of a 2 hour meeting today and found three frantic, sobbing, hysterical&nbsp;voicemails on my phone. Montana has been sent home from flying floozie training.&nbsp; I must pick her up from the airport.&nbsp;&nbsp;  She has been drowning her sorrows in the airport bar for a few hours before I can get her.  Something that she already disclosed on her application a month and a half ago, is the reason she was sent home.&nbsp; Some sort of public disturbance when she was 18 years old.&nbsp; 35 of the 60 people in her training are being sent home. 15 of them just because they are 19 or 20 years old, and Mesa/United Express/America West&nbsp;Airlines decided today that that is too young and you have to be 21.&nbsp; After giving up her apartment, spending a lot of cash putting all her shit in storage, and making big life sacrifices to go take this job.. they sent her home with no money, no home, and no job.&nbsp; She is wrecked.&nbsp; After not dancing since February.. she will prolly have to go back.&nbsp; Sad.&nbsp;  Also sad that she will probably stay with me.. no one else can put up with her.. until she gets back on her feet.&nbsp; I love living alone.. I hate roommates.&nbsp; Hmph!  At least I am house/dogsitting this weekend. In the kind of house that is so big and full of everthing you need.. that you could hermitize in it for weeks! Seriously.. the bubbling bath tub is in a carpeted room bigger that my apartment!    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After reading  urlLink Pisser's  post on weebles... I was reminded of&nbsp;an uncle.&nbsp;  My  real live weeble.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Uncle Weeble.. actually uncle Roger.&nbsp; But I have called him my uncle weeble for years.  He is one of the members of the Jerry Springer side of my family.  &nbsp;  So, I have an alcoholic diabetic uncle somewhere in Georgia who sits, sortof, in a wheelchair and has had both arms and legs amputated.&nbsp; God bless him.. he has actually gotten someone pregnant in this condition.&nbsp; I am quite proud.  &nbsp;    &nbsp;   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have cheek swabbed and DNA tested 40 baby mice today. I love my job. But who really cares who the daddy is of a silly little mouse!?!   On a more fun work note.. Curlymo gets to name a new gene that she discovered and is characterizing. She is seriously going to name it the FSMN gene. The fa shizzle ma nizzle gene. Yes! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Montana blew me off Saturday night to go stay with evil, restraining order, ankle moniter-Justin at some other scary farm house in the middle of nowhere. She was gonna call sunday morning so I know she was alive, so I wouldn't feel bad about helping her find him.  No word yet.  For all I know she is broken, bruised, and tied up somewhere! Probably not, but she usually calls if she says she will.  I predict he makes sure she misses her flight to go to flight attendant training.  I just hope the grandma and the other monster uncles didn't find her there..    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On Saturday, I recieved five phone calls from the people I took Frasier from, as they were driving up and down my alley. Someone I thought was a friend actually told them where I live. Idiot!   Then, I was contacted by a police officer regarding the alleged stealing of the cat.  He basically said- how can we resolve this so I dont have to hear about this cat anymore. I told the police officer that as far as am concerned, I own two cats and unless anyone else can prove that they own one of them, I am not giving it up. He said that that was a very good point. I also told him the story of how it was neglected. How I did not break in, I was invited. How I told someone (tattoo boy) who I thought lived there that the cat could not live like this and I was taking it... and how that person said go ahead.. i dont care. I guess no one can prove ownership because I haven't heard from him since Saturday. Yeah =)  Oh and I told him to tell them to stop stalking by my apartment building, because I don't want crazy crackheads like that around me. He said he would tell them. I am surprised it was that easy, considering that I think I probably did break some law. Hehe.  About an hour after the call from the officer, I got a call from some guy who said he lives in the building that the cat was living in. That he himself found the cat a couple months ago by the dumpster and gave it to the crackheads because he already had two cats in his apartment. So it wasn't even their cat to begin with!! I told him my side of the story. He said he wouldnt have given it to them at the time if he had known them better, and that I should just keep it. Duh. I planned on it.  He also said that these were not rational people and they think with their fists and to beware. Great. I don't even know what the guy looks like, but I hear is a tiny wimpy little punk so I am not worried.   One last little part of the story. I just found out that its really the guy's girlfriend fueling his fire to be pissed off. And I found out that the girlfriend is little sister of angry girl who hates me from along time ago because I unknowingly stole some guy away from her who I didn't ever want anyway. Ha!   Anyways, Frasier is a very happy kitty now, and Niles has finally stopped chasing him into corners.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once upon a time there was a very dumb girl named bizarla.. for encouraging and enabling stupidity. One day, her friend Montana decided that since the most recent boyfriend is history.. she must revert to the old, beater, mindfucker, on an ankle monitor to keep him away from her boyfriend. Guy who has already been back to jail twice for breaking his restraining order at her insistence. This is the one whose family seriously reminds me of the texas chainsaw massacre family. Granny used to chain them up and beat them and lock them in closets for weeks. She created a bunch of little monsters that for some reason still think she is the goddess. She in return continues to put mortgages on her home for bail/lawyers for her little monsters. Anyways.. after seeing 75 year old granny and crazy uncle of this family.. drag Montana through the gravel while kicking her... I renamed them the Hewitts.  So, Montana decides at 130 in the morning that she must drive an hour to their creepy farmhouse and knock on his window because she just knows he wants to talk to her. I convinced her not to go alone so as to get chainsawed or worse. Somehow.. stupid me is the only one who will go with her. Everyone else is too afraid.. for good reason. So we go... the house is totally empty with a for sale sign in front. Granny went bankrupt and lost it! OK.. its the end of this.. I think. Since she is moving away to become a flight attendant in phoenix.. she must must must see him one last time. She has to trick the victim advocate into telling her when/where his PO appointment is. Actually, I gave her the idea to tell them she needs to know what time and where so she isnt in the area cuz she is afraid. It worked. OK.. it was today between 9 and 11. So we get up at 7am. Are camped out on capital hill near the office by 8am. We must split up to cover more territory.. the front and back of the block. How I got into this i don't know.. actually I do.. I was bribed.. So.... finally.... at noon. I convince her to let me call his grandma's cell phone.  I was not hanging out here any longer! He answers. After all these covert operations.. a telephone call works.. duh.  He has rescheduled his appointment for another day... I walk around the block throw my phone with him on it at Montana and drive us to Sushi..  My Payoff =)  I am a sucker for chuchi... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I stole a cat this weekend.  I am officially a crazy cat lady now. Over the past couple of months.. everytime I was in this certain apartment (roommate of a friend of a friend of a friend).. it smelled worse and worse.. and the litter was never changed. I even brought food with us one time because the cat was never fed. It was scorching hot and stinky and there was no food. This last time, the cat had broken into the cupboards and gotton into some people food, and his tail was covered with shit. This was the last straw for me. I already have a cat, Niles, and I really don't want two cats... but I  had  to bust him out of there! He is the sweetest most loving kitty I have ever met. Furry, and black with lazy green eyes. He doesn't bite or scratch and loves everyone. Niles was a pissed kitty at first, but they are slowly getting to know each other through the crack under the door of their rooms. I have to keep them separate or they will kill each other. When I first brought Frasier home he jumped out of my arms and they scuffled. Niles ended up with a mouth full of fur and Frasier ended up hiding in the corner behind the TV. Hopefully soon they will be pals. They can tolerate, sniff, and stare at each other for about an hour now before starting to fight.  The old owner actually cried to my friend about losing it. Hello, if you love it enough to cry over it.. the least you can do is feed it! I guess I am trying to find a good home for Frasier.. but I have a feeling that I will end up being the single girl who lives in a tiny apartment with two cats. Ikes.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So better late than never, the one who tattooed Montana's name on his arm.. is history! But only after kicking a lit fire work at a 12 year old, getting beat up and hog tied, later punching his arm through her brand new car's window, severing an artery, and getting life flighted from Nebraska to Denver... to keep the story short... Ahh... trailer trash on the fourth of july... always good times. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So my two best friends finally made peace. Finally!  The 2nd year medical student and the ex-stripper soon to be flight attendant... I always knew they would get along if they just gave each other a chance! They are actually very similar. Both scandalous with big hearts. I can't wait for us to all go out and see what trouble we find.  Amazing what one night of mind altering substances and another girls sangria night can accomplish.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Flash: Sloganator Bush Memorial  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      bout time
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Montana, Curlymo, and me  this weekend at Funky Buddha =) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      happy birthday to me happy birthday to me happy birthday to mee eee happy birthday to me   
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>