<Blog>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FINALLY, I made gala na!!! but heavens! i am soo tired.. even up to this moment..  whew! wehehehe, it's a FAMILY DAY for me today because me and my family went shopping!!! where else e di sa mall?!?! well, most of the things we bought was for my brother(jun-jun).. gosh! my parents bought him some really expensive rubber shoes, school shoes, sandals, and some nice slippers...well, as for myself, i bought a pair of nice slippers din and a pair of pants... yun, i tried to get a new bag na din sana.. but, there was no bag that suited my taste, maybe next time na nga lang... i also forgot to buy a new top.. waaah! because my younger sister(joana) was sleepy! shit! but still, at least i have bought some things for myself, yah know, i hate going to the mall when i'm not buying anything for myself.. i think it's super useless, waste of time and effort! dibah?! well, anyweiz, me and my bro ate French Baker.. which was our all-time favorite shems.. you know, hickory spareribs... that's what we eat there always.. so after our long tiring day, we went home... but mama told me that next time, we will be shopping naman daw to buy MY things... kasi nga, i'm not sure yet if i will be enrolling at makati med or UP manila.. damn! i hate it! i even can't decide... but of course, kailangan, bagay yung bag and shoes sa uniform(if ever) in my future school dibah!?!? i'm really looking forward o our next shopping session!!!.. Humanda sila!!!  well, i think i will not be staying in the net too long because i will be calling my bestbud, i will borrow from him a C.L. book, because my aunt needs it.. so yun... that's it for my day.. ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i guess you're wondrin' what this title is all about... well, i'll be telling you the story behind the title later.. the start of my day, was ok... i woke up at around 12 na... wahahaha.. shit! i'm really waking up late.. i mean, really late! i guess, i'm just savoring this goddamn vacation!ehehehe.. then we ate lunch na syempre! i mean, man, it's tanghali na! yahyah.. well, for today, i am a home buddy again.. then after our lunch, tierry called and we chatted for about an hour, she was asking kung tuloy ba daw yung get together namin, i said  "hindi ata..." it was like around 2:30 in the afternoon when mama served lots of super yummy ICE CREAM... there were many different flavors.. ube, chocolate, mango, and we had this half gallon ice cream that you can put the toppings of your choice like yum-yum mallows, sprinkles of fancy colors! ehehehe.. so yun, we ate and ate! Gosh, it's so refreshing! then i, mama and joana(my younger sister) took a nap.. afterwards, i watched the tv, and it was dinner na.. we prepared naman a mango shake! it was so yummy rin! whew! ehehe... so yun.. that's my day for today.. i hope in the coming days, i can make gala naman... ehehehe.. that's it! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yup! yup! i was alone and i did it! i had my schedule in my speech power classes today.. remember?! MIRACULOUSLY, i went home, ALONE! harharhar.... i'll tell you the whole story below.. hehehehe... diba, in my previous post, i told you that i HATE being ALONE... i feel helpless..lonely, i dunno why?! but today, i just did it... why am i so proud?! malay ko... let me tell you about my day..  First, i woke up at around 10 in the morning, an hour earlier than my usual bangon.. then i did nothing... i just watched the tv.. then ate, until nag 12:45 na and i took a bath na.. i told laurice that we're going to speech power at around 1:45 na lang because dati, we were quite early... but, laurice asked me to accompany her to Chrisjekar to buy a ballpen and a little notebook, and so, nagstart na kming mag biyahe at about 2:10.. Fortunately, we were not late again, i saw Ellen (one of my Chinita classmates) and we chatted a bit.. then, our class starts.. we had recitations and discussions for today, but we also had an activity, you have to choose a partner... it was a sort of informing, persuading and giving comments... me and laurice were not partners.. a girl, who i met in the first day chose me.. she is Simonette(a girl from UST), the newspaper i picked has a picture of a cellphone, so yun, i think we did it well naman.. we got a 10, a perfect score. well, actually, all of us got a 10(because my classmates are too generous or i think they're just afraid to speak out?!).. the instructor told us that we should only lessen the giggles and laughter... hehehe.. me pa, i always laugh! all the time! i can't help it! we will have our so-called "Reporting" next meeting, with a VTR!! i dunno what to do! we're imitating wazzup! wazzup! and me, Laurice and Sandra are assigned to the entertainment news! i wonder what am i be wearing?!?! so yun, after the class, we went to Robinsons Manila with our new friends..Sandra, who was beautiful and smart, and Nabel who was cute and friendly. The two ate at Sbarro's, but Laurice told me that she don't have enough money that's why, we ate at Popeye's and met her cousins...we left Robinsons without Laurice, Thank God i was hinatid in the fx terminal by my new found friends, even though i'm quite nervous, i have to commute by myself! and im proud to say... I DID IT! nga pala, while in the fx, my bestfriend txted me that he will drop by my place dahil kukunin nya daw yung feeding bottle ni shake(his pamangkin), and some of his vcd's that he left here...eh i was still in manila that time, i told him that i will txt him nalang if i'm home... so when i got home, i txted him nga..but he replied that he already went home and next time na nga lang daw.... i was quite disappointed, pero ok lang.. next time na nga lang... dahil it's gabi na.. so yun, that's my day for today...ay wait, my friends are planning to have a party here at home tomorrow, i dunno kung matutuloy.. but i told them na sila na lang ang magdala ng food.. i miss my buddies na! that's it for my day! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar!  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hell!!! he just confirmed that he was'nt my classmate! whoa! i am amazed that he was not.. but i swear, he really looked liked him! PLUS, they had the same names! shit! i dunno! hahahaha.. why am i so affected with this fuckin' man! hahaha.. well, thank goodness that he was not my classmate, because my classmate was far more better than him... well, speaking of that classmate, i lend him my ballpen (parker!) and gave him a piece of paper.. when he had none, that was in our class.... am i not good?! hahahaha! i think that man is funny... he had chinese breed too.. (parang aso!) and when i asked my chatmate if he was chinese, he said no naman... bahala nga cya! Hell with him! ngarrr! why am i galit... he just ignored my messages... hahahahaha! i'm going crazy again! so that's it.. i'm going to watch star circle quest pa.. "Where the magic continues"  hahahaha.. i hope Hero and Sandy does'nt get voted out.. same with Roxanne and Joross.. hahaha. i'm being showbiz again! eeiiiww! hehehehe.. so goodbye! that's it! Ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey.. i have a pahabol... i had this mysterious chatmate... and i'm chatting with him this very minute! omigod.. he has a picture and i viewed it... he looked like a classmate in my speech power classes.. and if he really is, well, i'm glad.. because that classmate of mine is very funny... not to mention he's cute too... hahaha.. but kung hindi sya yung classmate ko.. well, ok rin lang, but you're asking what's mysterious about it... is that they have the same FACE! my instincts tells me so... that they are just one person.. well, i dunno, pero i just feel like posting this story in my blog... by the way, he lives in rizal and he's 16... well, i think laurice will be reading my blog really soon, well, laurice, you told me that in our speech power lessons, there was this guy who makes the whole class fun.. i'm thinking that he's my chatmate... i dunno...  i'm VERY MUCH confused at the moment.. well, i invited him to read this post... i didn't asked him yet if he's my classmate.. by the way, he had seen my face in friendster.. i just hope he did'nt get scared!!! hahahaha! with this little devil... nah! just kidding! so.. mamaya na ako mag dadagdag.. i'll update you guys later.. see yah! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yah.. you're right.. i didn't go out of the house today.. i dunno why..  eh wla akong lakad, anong magagawa ko?! and i am quite bored again...well, i woke up at around 9:30 in the morning, i went to the dirty kitchen and saw my mom doing the laundry, i told her that i will help her... but i dunno for what reason that i became sleepy again! For heaven's sake?! i dunno why.. i woke up at around 11 na! hehehehe.. so yun.. then the phone rang, and it was for me, it was tebby on the line, she was asking if i will be coming to the funeral, unfortunately my parents did NOT allow me... huhuhuh... poor little me... they told me... "hindi ka pwedeng umabsent sa speech power, sayang ang bayad natin, 500 per session din yun" ... well, i felt a little disappointed.. i would really like to attend the funeral... plus, wala akong kasama sa speech power ko because i think laurice is attending the funeral... but on the other hand, they're right too.. and one thing more, tebby was inviting me to go to Tagaytay with them for just one day... of course, i hesitated agad, i knew it, my parents would NEVER ever allow me... haler?! sa mall nga lang, mahirap nang mag paalam eh.. Tagaytay pa kaya?! yup, yup.. that's my life, and then our conversation ended na... i helped mama in the laundry pa rin... and we ate lunch afterwards... in the afternoon, i prepared a shake, (chocolate) which was yummy! weehehehe, and i connected to the net and chatted for hours... fortunately, my friends were also connected, so we chat, but we encountered some problems in chatting and so we got disconnected! Hell with this chat!!! harharhar! i'm devilish again! that's for today.. i really hope that laurice comes with me tomorrow for speech power.. i dont want to go there alone.. i HATE being alone.. i really do.. i dunno why... i'm going to take a bath pa.. and then call my friends to inform them that i'm not going to the funeral with them, my bestfriend is first on my phone list.. hahahaha.. so see yah, that's it for today.. ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, this day, i had another speech power lesson..my schedule was tuesday, thursday, 3 to 5 pm... but let me first tell you what happened at the beginning of my day... i woke up at around 11 in the morning.. and helped my mom in some of the house chores... i applied floorwax in the bedroom of my mama and papa (where i am sleeping now) and then used the floor polisher after... i was also watching morning girls.. then i got ready para sa speech power lessons ko... i took a bath for about 30 minutes and off i went to laurice's place... when i got there, she was taking a bath pa... then i thought,  haaay, nako, ano pa nga ba.. eh nuno ng bagal to' mukhang mala-late kami... , our usapan is that we will go at around 1:30, but because of laurice's so-called "kabagalan" we left at already 2:00... i really thought that we're going to be late...   thank God that we arrived there 10 minutes earlier.. so, yun, we thought that speech power lessons are going on na or maybe our other classmates were there inside, so we got in.. unfortunately, that was another class which was not finished yet... so we went out.. then our time came... and the class starts.. i had laurice by my side and she was new.. we also had so many new classmates... but there are also my old classmates... so yun, we had activities, lots of fun.. tawanan and all.. there was one game, a whisper game... you have to pass the message by whispering, eh i was like at the bandang dulo na of the line, but i can actually hear what the people in front of me are whispering.. i was like laughing because it was a whispering game?!?!! and they actually had loud voices.. hehehehe... so that's it.. there was also an activity where me and laurice shared about our dream(or nightmare) about our past classmate who was dumped in the honor roll and got in again... it was funny coz our dream (or nightmare) came true... you know who iam talking about.. don't you. well , i'm not mentioning her name here.. so... our lessons had ended at nagpaalam nga kami sa instructor namin na we cant attend the thursday classes coz we're going to a funeral (Ma'am huele's bro.).. and afterwards, we went home na... in the fx i was sooo dizzy.. i dunno why and very much hungry... harharhar... when i got to our house, no one was there.. they were in my aunt's house.. and so i went there na rin... and right now, i'm in my aunt's house writing this post of mine... so yun ang updates sa araw ko ngayon... that's it.. ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WARNING: mahaba tong post na to.. i'm telling you... but it's worth reading!  lahat all in one day lang!!  Volume I:  whoa! this day is really a long day for me! first, me and laurice had plans to go to speech power early in the morning today.. she had decided to enrol there too.. i'm soo happy because i have a kasama na.. (syempre i used my super convincing powers), good thing she liked speech power too... so, as i woke up this early morning, i checked on my cel (my habit) if there was a messge. it said there,  '2 messages received'  so yun na nga.. i read it and i was surprised that i got a txt message from one of my teachers (i was close to) back in highschool... it was ma'am telly.. i read her message first knowing that the second message was from laurice and there was nothing surprising about her (laurice).. so i read ma'am telly's message... she said :  'Patay na ang bunso kong brother na c NEL. nalunod sya sat eve s batangas. Nkburol sya d2 chapel A (old chapel) garden of memories' ........ so that's it.. i was like.. Oh my God! i was shocked.. you know, really shocked. the first thought that came into my mind was our past adviser ma'am huele... yah.. i felt sad.. so i called up laurice first and my other friends so that we can drop by the cemetery and pray for her brother..  go for the continuation below........   THE ADVENTURES OF LAURICE, PATTY and JETTY   Volume II:  by the way, my lakad with laurice was quite delayed, it was supposed to be 10 o'clock but it was moved to 12 i guess... well, it was my fault.. i had to help mama in some chores because ate salie was not around (good daughter!) harharhar! so at around 12, me and laurice met.. she treated me to chowking.. thanks! because i really dont have money... (poor me...) yun nga, but chowking was full of people so we chose greenwich instead... we ate lasagna chicken plate (yum!).. patrick (laurice's boyfriend) followed... so after eating... sumakay na kami.. then habang nasa byahe.. IT RAIN... shit!!! this is so.... grr! we had no umbrellas! so yun, we had to made sugod the ulan... haler?!!! (my new expression.. means hello?!) we're going to the cemetery like this?!! gosh! so yun, awa ni God, we reached naman speech power quite wet... the girl who entertained us found out that laurice was named laurice, it was such a coincidence that her co-worker was named laurice too.. (not sure of the spelling..) she said in a very weird and hilarious voice..  "you're laurice and she's laurice... hehehe that's funny!  so i was like... what the hell is that! as if, there's nothing funny.. duh?! what's so funny about that anyways?!!! so well... that's it, she enrolled and i lend her 1000 coz she only brought 2000... good thing i got pocket money.. so it was still raining outside.. we made abang for a taxi, but there was none, so we made sugod to the rain... can u imagine?!! at long last we reached the jeepney stand at sumakay na nga kami.. we reached guada mall.. she made libre at godilocks, i just ate halo-halo and had some water.. because i felt dehydrated after the dreadful rain! i dunno why... so yun, i txted gladys and friends to go with us to the cemetery too.. so yun, on our way to the fx stand, we fortunately saw them.. but they said they will be taking the jeepneys instead... so we're on our way to the patio(our meeting place)...go for the continuation below........   THE MEANINGFUL REUNION....   Volume III:  So there in the patio, nagkita kita kami ng mga friends ko... chris was there, same with julius, ernest (who got their teeth broken), rocky, (our past classmate) who by the way, i dont know the reason behind his presence..., and got a boyfriend.. what the?!! well, i dont care... hehehe.., gladys, stephanie, rachel, rachelyn, oza, me, laurice, patrick, ervin, angela... sorry if i forgot anyone.. yun, we went to garden and decided to buy some flowers... we kissed ma'am vicky and ma'am telly and shared our condolences with them... that was really sad... yun, and i was very much surprised to see the 'Search for a Star' winner there.. Rachelle Ann Go... she was beautiful...yahyah... so yun na nga... i saw the pain in ma'am huele's face, specially in her eyes... we told her : "  Ma'am, namumugto na yang mata nyo, magpahinga naman po kayo...  that was a really sad scene for all of us... haaayyy.. but you know, maraming tao... it just proved that they had many friends, and they were good to others...  So after that, still in the cemetery, i decided to visit my Grandfather... i bought him some flowers which Ervin carried and 2 candles... gladly, all of my closest friends in this universe accompanied me... they surrounded the lot... and talked and chat endlessly, although, i, myself... didn't chat with them... i just uttered some prayers for my lolo.. who i love and miss... then, after a while, julius(my kababata).. noticed it... sinaway ny sila tierry. and said that i was praying and maybe if they could be just a little quiet... and my bestfriend noticed it too.. he asked if i was praying.. i just nodded... he told me..   "bakit di mo naman ako sinama?" .. well, i didnt know tahat you wanted to pray with me for my lolo.. but i was touched by the thought... then he said : "sabihin mo pag tapos kana..." .. i nodded again, i just wanted to pray for my lolo... i felt a little pain in my heart.. but.. tapos na yon eh.. then.. i finished my prayers... i didn't let him know that i was finished.. he just noticed.. sabi nya:  tapos kana?  then i nodded... then he said,  "sige ako naman..." .. you know, in my heart i was very thankful that of all the nine people who iam with, he, my bestfriend only had the thought of praying for my lolo.. well, now i know, i picked the right right Bestfriend.. i was thankful...  then, we decided to go home... we just prayed some prayers for ma'am huele's brother and off we went.. we said our goodbyes and told our teachers to be strong...just to console them... and we went home... that's it for my looong loong meaningful rainy day.... i hope you enjoyed... ciao!  Pahabol:  imagine?!! all these things in just ONE LOONG MONDAY... its past twelve na when i posted it kaya tuesday na ang nkalagay... ehehe.. ciao ulit!  from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay for my very bestfriend ervin! ... gosh! he's got a new cel! he told me that it was tito florante's (his father) graduation gift to him... how swerte! but i think he deserves it!!! very much! he graduated with honors!!!  FYI only !! harharhar! well actually, last friday pa yung cel nya... like ko lang na malaman nyo...para updated kayo... thank god at bumili na rin cya, because dati, the old bulok cel he was using was owned by his kuya...sabagay, he really need a cel for college, especially malayo sila.. Los Baños ba naman imagine?!?! good thing din at pwede ko n cyang itxt endlessly because dun sa bulok cel dati, he used to erase all my messages kasi nga it was not his naman... i'm so proud he had a new cel!!! so happy! take note! his new cel was a SAMSUNG!! omigod! like kay keanu in the commercial!! so nice.. colored, with camera and nice resolution too.. god! pinangatawanan niya na tlga ang pagiging keanu nya!... so nice naman na may communication pa rin kami even if he's in LB na.. i think i'm gonna miss him so much... well, he's one of my very best buddies... but, medyo matagl pa naman clang aalis ni julius... dont be shocked kung masyadong marami akong tsismis sa blog ko ha.. Likas lng tlaga akong Chismosa.. harharhar! congratulaions bestfriend!!-- for that new cel! hahahaha..   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omigod!!! i have a new blog na!!! yay for me! yes.... this blog is really mine!! i am so happy! thank goodness i will have something to write down my thoughts and feelings! harharhar! well, i named this "the weirdo's new diary" coz i am absolutely a weirdo.. i am crazy!! well, i think u will get to know me better if you'll read my blog... to start off i will create my first ever post:  god!!! it was a really hot day today! i got pissed off because it was so fuckin hot! nkaka inis ang sobrang init! plus the fact that i am so goddamn bored!!!! by the way, tierry called me up kanina... to my surprise, she was kasama pala to the outing-outingan laurice had.... at first i really felt bad.. because i thought they were my friends and they would invite me... but they didn't... well of course, it was the "lovers" outing pwera lang kay joeylouie na nandun... well, i just rationalized na alam naman nila na di rin me papayagan.. i think that's the reason behind it... well, i'm okay now... i'm not really galit to them or anything... kanina, we went to church, i was quite pissed.. i was nahihilo and all... i want to go to the mall, but nobody would accompany me... huh.... well... yun lng ang updates sa araw ko ngyon... i'm looking forward to my speech power lessons with my most likely "stupid" classmates.... yah know!! hehehe.. i'm being devilish again, but truthful.. harharhar... that's it for today! ciao!  from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yup! i just arrived from the two parties i have been this day... i'm tired! but, it's ok.. well, to start off, this morning, i got a txt msg from arizza, it says that she wants to go here and ask for some help... about the ayos of her hair in the  secret sagala..  because she does'nt want us to know eh, that's why it's secret.. hahaha! she's makiki-print daw.. eh unfortunately, our printer is not ayos at the moment...so that's it.. about two o'clock, i already left because me and my other friends are meeting at seven-eleven at Pateros... so it was about 2:30 when we went to taguig and we stopped over arvie's house because she is the one who knows joyce's house... so when we arrived at joyce's house.. we greeted her parents and relatives... and she invited us to eat na nga...by the way, we were only 8 coz elaine and rev did'nt come.. so there.. there were lots of food..uhmm, baked mac, pansit, chicken, litson, cake, ice cream...uhhmmm  yun lang ang na-remember ko... so i ate, baked mac and chicken lang, i can't eat ice cream because i have a sore throat or tonsilitis! waaah! ang sakit ng throat ko! then, after eating, israel and olinad arrived.. they ate tons! hahaha! i mean it! then, we chatted for a while and we left na, we thank joyce's parents and off we went to arvie's place... at arvie's house. her mom and bro recognized me kaaagad... at first, we were hesitant to eat.. coz, we were full pa.. but afterwards.. ayun..bumigay din.. they had foods like: carbonara, fried chicken (again), menudo, i forgot...yah, and the buko juice... yummy! so yun... we ate again! it's one whole day of damn eating!!! hahaha! so after watching star circle quest, we thanked them and went home... it was about 7:00 when we bid them goodbye... so before going home, i passed by V2 to get the pictures from our graduation... and because i am a good friend... i also picked my friends pictures too.. but they have to pay me...i made abono! (the honors only) because they have an extra picture when they received their medal.. and afterwards, i went home na.... so that's it for one whole day of eating, eating and eating! don't worry, i did'nt eat that much! i'm on a DIET! remember?!?!?! hahahaha! by the way, it's my uncle's birthday today!!! so HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!! so... that's it.. i'm tired.. ciao!  from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this day, was normal as usual, except for the fact that mama forced me to do some exercises this morning! hahaha! so i've got no choice but to follow her or else she'll start nagging at me about: me, not being accepted by Makati med! whew! so i did it with joana.. well, i was catching my breath when i finished the excercise! hahaha! i did the things we used to do in school, the half-knee, full-knee bend thing, the jogging in place, jumping jack, etcetera!so after that was already lunch time, i measured the rice i was going to eat! waaah! i'm going to a real serious diet now! hahahaha! i dunno if it's going to work! i hope!!! well, my mom left us here at home to arrange some business whatever... so i'm left here with joana because jun-jun is getting his notebooks at school, then arvie txted me, she said that i'm invited in joyce's(reyes) birthday bash...then, i called arvie up.. then she told me the details about it.. she's also inviting me for a party held at their house because they're celebrating her bro's graduation! a UP diliman grad! so tomorrow i'm going to 2 parties! i'm a party girl?!?! one at around 2 in the afternoon and the other at around 5! haahaha! i'm going with gladys, yumi, ava, jonas, alvin, rev, elaine, kei... those are the ones i remembered...i'm excited! hahahah! and this afternoon, ervin dropped by our house because he's returning the pamputol ng tiles he borrowed yesterday, we ate some merienda and chatted a bit, and he went home although joana won't let him! hahaha! he has lots of fans at this house! jun-jun and joana! they're always calling him at home and asking him to go here with shakee... uhhmmm, bahala sila.. then, that's it, i washed the dishes after... i'm looking forward to the parties tomorrow! that's it for my day! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! i'm here again, i've got lots of things to tell you about my day... to start, this is how the story goes.. laurice called me up last night and told me that she would not be able to attend Speech Power classes today due to her uncle's arrival from Ireland.. so Laurice, if you're reading this right now, you OWE me a bunch of pasalubong from your shopping!!! hahaha.. so, for short, i'm going to SP alone.. then, ervin called for the sleeping-session talk... you know.. and i told him that i would be going alone for my SP classes tom., i asked if he would like to accompany me... thank Goodness, he said Yes right away... and for him not to be bored while my SP classes are going on, i told him, he can get another kasama pa and they could hang out in Robinson's... so i said, invite jhing or julius... but jhing can't come... and it's too late in the evening to call julius.. it's about 11:15 at night for God's sake! so he told me if we could invite arizza to come, so i called aiza, but she refused! so, we've got no choice.. i told him that if he alone will be my kasama for my SP, i will treat him in everything he needs to pay.. from transpo upto the food.. see?!?! he's blessed! hahahaha!   so there..  then today, he txted me and asked what time we're going to meet.. i told him around 2:00(at the fx stand)...  we were quite naiba pa ng way coz the driver was a bit  "engers" .. so we need to ride a jeepney pa... at last, we arrived at SP.. then i told him to go to Robinson's muna... i'll txt him na lng if we're finished na... so in our class, we gave the criticisms about ourselves in the VTR... but we just wrote it on a piece of paper and the teacher goes to us... well, i wrote there  "i fix my hair"  and  "i giggle, a lot!" , when the teacher approached me, she told me that she also noticed that i was fixing my hair in front of the camera.. hahaha! and the giggling, it was alright coz the character i'm portraying required me to do so... and guess what?!?! she told me that i have a very NICE VOICE!!! and i could be a newscaster!! hahahaha! as in?! me.. huh?! uhmm..whatever.. then, we had an assignment, it's dramatization using idioms... and then the class ended, i txted ervin to come na, and he told me to wait for him.. so there, we went to Robinson's again and ate there... of course, as promised, i treated him... after eating i remembered that joana wants mcdo so i must buy her some... so me and ervin decided to stroll first coz we were full... and we bought Thumb's Up.. ice cream... it's so cute.. and very YUMMY! specially the cotton candy flavor! weee! we were laughing and laughing and chatting while eating the mini ice creams... and we went to mcdo na nga... so on our way home, we went to the fx stand and we found Jason dela Cruz there!!! haha! thank God, aiza didn't come with us! hahaha! and we chatted with him the whole trip.. ervin went with me hanggang bahay coz kukunin nya yung feeding bottle ni shakee.. and he's borrowing the pamputol ng tiles, whatever.. coz he's fixing their lababo daw...hahaha! so sipag... then he went home na din.. i forgot to thank him so i txted him na lang.. whew! what a day! i'm tired.. but happy... that's it! ciao!  from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha! i'm back... yup.. well, this day, as i have said is not so exciting.. coz i have done nothing!!! hahaha! i just laid in the bed and watched the tv the whole day.. chatted in the afternoon with jobelle, who by the way is in the states... we chatted just a bit.. then i went to watch tv again... then ervin txted me that joana is calling him at home.. hahaha! my devilish little sister.. he told me na  nagpapakwento ng cinderella  si joana... so, he is now a story-teller!! waaah! new career?!?! hehehe, so i called him nalang... then, nagkwentuhan kami but it was not that long... because he said that he wanted to take a bath and maybe we should continue the talking this evening kasi that's what makes him feel sleepy... waahahaha.. so in the latter part of the afternoon, i still watched tv and awaited for my turn in the computer because my bro was using it with my couz and his new found friend(our boarder)...so...after that, we ate dinner... and i watched the tv again!!! see?!?!?! see what i mean?!?! this day is hella boring! but tomorrow, is another speech power day.. i'm looking forward to it.. nga pala, we will be criticizing ourselves tom!?! uhhmm, so what?!?! i don't care! hahahaha! that's it for this not-so-exciting day... see yah.. ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      waaaaahh, i'm depressed that i'm only updating my blog now..which, i should've done yesterday pa... but my papa and my bro was watching dvd for about 4 hrs.!?!? hello?! is there such movie?! i really got pissed off... so before anything else... let me tell you first what happened to our most awaited VTR session... yesterday..  TUESDAY:    well, to start off, i was awaken by a text message from Keanu.. it says:  "Hoy kmusta mo nga pala ko sa mga klasmeyt mong magaganda at sexy na tulad mo! he! he!"  so i was like... what's wrong with this man again.. what came into his head to text me all of a sudden..  siguro alang magawa..  and then i asked him nga why?! he told me, he had nothing to do.. so, in short, he is disturbing me, ganun?!?!?! well, after our little kulitan.... i ate lunch and prepared for my speech power lessons because it is our vtr day!!! haler?! and i've got no news yet.. waaah... of course, bahala na there.. for sure my other classmates has no news din naman.. i bet!!! so when we got there, Nabel was asking if i had a newspaper... of course i had! but it was the entertainment section only.. and as i told you, there was no one who bought any newspapers.. inside the room, we changed the show  Wazzup Wazzup  to  Uzap! Uzap! ..we had one hour of practice... i had it with laurice and sandra.. (entertainment group).. our segment was named  "Showbiz Kacheapan" ?!?! hahaha... we can't think of any news... but because of our wicked minds.. hahahaha, nakaisip na rin kami! thanks to lolo chris and the malicious titles of movies he had been inventing back in highschool... that's where we got the idea.. it goes like this.. Sandra was the artist, and me and laurice will interview her.. she is Sandra Bulok.. and has two movies namely :  Tag-ulan ngayon, basa ang bukid...  and the more nasty one,  Halika Nene, Huwag po Lolo.. .. so that's it...well, all in all, i think we did good... ok naman yung vtr...and after the shoot, we watched it... then me and laurice went to robinson's to eat.. then afterwards, we went home...i had a stomach ache for no reason... these past few days.. i am having some stomach aches.. waaaaahh!!! what is happening to me??!?!?!? then we went to my tita and stayed there for a while and went home na... at home, i chatted on the phone with Ervin for about an hour of nonsense talk... kwentuhan, tawanan.. anything.. he told me that we'll talk again later.. waaah! see?!?! that is what we call: BOREDOM!!!  hahahaha.. i'm going to eat lunch first ok? that's it.. Ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whew! i had one heck of a night! you know what, i thought last night was another usual night for our family.. remember the card games?!? well, actually, NOT! My papa and mama had a petty arguement about the fucking card game! my papa keeps on blaming my mom for his pagkatalo sa game... my mom got a little pissed off and told him that it was not her fault.. well, it's like this... my dad asks my mom on which card is to discard...then my mom answers, but my dad refuses to, and makes his own decision on what is to discard... and then, he disards the wrong one.. meaning, he loses! so that's where the fight started.. my mom walks out and goes home, of course, i followed her, same with my sister.. if not,  eh, baka hindi ako makapasok ng bahay..  hehehe.. so that's it... we went home.. and me and mama had a very long talk.. we chatted for about 3 and a half hours...but first, we went upstairs because she needs to iron our clothes nga, so me and joana went up with her.. and there, she told me everything(i dunno), about our family.. i mean the big family,(aunts, uncles, cousins).. the constructive and destructive attitudes, stories and all... what i mean is everything about them, whether positive or not... Bullshit! i mean, there are so many things that i didn't know... hahaha, good thing i know them now.. like i had this aunt who i really don't like... i am pissed with her or something like that because she keeps on asking (or begging) for money, to my lola and other rich family members..but hell! her husband had a 6600! see?!?!?! and one of my cousins is pregnant! (you know...the pre-marital shit like that!) well, you know, they had a very good reputation...so i was like.. what the fuck is happening with this family?! too many secrets...  and there's another.. my other aunts aren't inviting our family and one family too, whenever they go out... you know, (bagiuo, tagaytay, outings, etc..) so what the hell is that?!?! well, i don't really fucking care! they can all go straight to hell! hahaha! and this is what i assure them! i swear, i will study hard and get rich! and we will go and have a trip around the world, just me and my own family!!! i SWEAR! hahaha!!!  itaga nila yan sa bato!!!   and i will NEVER EVER invite them either!!! i will also give money to my lola(mother's side) because they are the one who are hard-working!.. well, there are so many secrets unveiled.. and me and my mom's relationship is really BONDED! i have to end this post because i have to take a bath and buy some medicine for my mom... she has hemorrhoids again... my poor mom..i'll be going to mercury.. i'll update you guys later! so, that's it! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haaaay.. hehehe, it's sunday again, of course, we went to church...but inside the church i feel sooo sleepy.. Gosh?! so, what the hell is happening to me?!?!?! hahahaha... i dunno too... but after the mass, i wasn't sleepy at all!!! waaah... and then mama said that we will be eating our lunch at lola's place.. yup! yup! that's our every week routine... we use to go to our grandparents' house and visit them.. then we will stay there for about the whole day(and night?!)... and our parents, aunts and uncles are just playing card games!!!(tong-its to be exact..) that's it.. imagine that, for centuries we have been doing that!!! but it's just a family game..or should i say tradition!?! that's why our grandma always names their house the  "CASINO NACIONAL" .. hehehe, because even we, na mag pipinsan are also gambling.. ahaha. no we're just having fun... but without money at stake of course! and in the afternoon, still at our lola's place, i, arcie and rjay(my couzins) prepared mango shake!!(shit! is that all i'm gonna do this summer?!) i dunno too... pero lahat naman nasarapan! of course, me pa! so now, i'm in this goddamn internet shop na may nabubulok na keyboards na! not to mention the computers which are about to blow up!! Shit, you know, i have no other choice but to update my blog because when we get home, i will not be allowed to, besides, i'm tatamarin na rin... yah!yah! i'm out of here! i can't stand it anymore... i'm maarte, so what?! hahaha, you should see this place..(internet thingy shop) it sucks!!! there's no ar-con!! it's just that i haven't got any choice! so that's it for my whole day.. i dunno what time we will be going home... but, that's it.. Ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      grabe! i'm telling you, this day is sooo tiring for me! as what i have said in my previous post, there was a Brown-out here... i thought that i will be able to sleep, but hot hell, no! i slept at around 1:00 and i woke up at around 3:30 in the morning due to extreme HOTNESS! it was still brown-out at that time, i knew that i can't sleep with that hot condition, so i got out of my bed and looked for the emergency light, mama oo can't stand the heat so she also got up, we prepared the baons for papa and jun coz their outing is on this very day... mama and i also did some laundry... imagine?!?! me and mama, doing the laundry at 4:00 in the morning!! i hate it! waaah! it was sooo fucking hot! finally, papa and jun left... i called up meralco call center and they told me that electricity will be back at around 6.. so i slept coz i was sooo sleepy! but bullshit! when i woke up at around 9:30, still there was no electricity! waaaah! i was sooo... grrrr!i called meralco again and they said that it will be okay at 12:00 - 1:00.. so there... i called up my friends coz today is gladys' party... yipee! me and lourdes went together and ervin keeps on bugging me with his txt messages, i can't reply to him coz low-batt na ko... so there, we met at the patio at 2:00 and waited for the others to come... it was 3:00 when we set off to gladys' house.. we filled up one jeep! so there, at long last, i saw gladys' house...i haven't been there ever since.. so we ate her handa.. all were yummy! palabok, carbonara, pichi-pichi, pansit, lumpia, ice cream, cake... so we chatted for hours and kept teasing chris hich was our hobby, we were having so much fun... we were just laughing and chatting, but here comes the exciting part! gladys' dad brought out some red horse(beer) for the boys... so, as expected, they drank and so did tierry.. after one glass, ervin and jhing left for they will be attending mass.. so it was julius, ernest, chris and tierry left at the table for i and lourdes was chatting with rachy, oza and friends... we were forcing chris to drink some beer but he refused.. our group(me and oza and friends) drank gin orange..wehehehe... they told me na wala namang tama... so i drank, after all, it just tasted like orange juice, the rain poured so we decided to have some videoke, at the same time, the three(ernest, julius and tierry) were dizzy and drunk.... hahaha! ernest drank i think 3 bottles! we had so much fun at the videoke session because most of us were lasing na... i felt so htot and i'm pinag-papawisan na talaga! wehehehe... afterwards, we decided to go home because it was 7:30.. you should have seen ernest acting sooo WILD! he was  pagewang-gewang na...  i arrived here at home at exactly 8.. i had a little headache, but it was gone... so that's it! ang sarap ng day na toh! waaaaah! grabe! that's it, i think i should take a rest, you might think i'm drunk! hahahaha! Ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday, May 07, 2004  - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -   i woke up very early today.... as what i have said me and mama are going to makati med to have some measurements for my uniform... it was quite traffic because of the motorcade of the politicians... but, then again, we reached makati med just in time.. there were many students there, we went to the canteen section to fit some P.E. t-shirts and pants.. and ordered 4 pairs of uniform... we went upstairs to have my measurements taken.. i saw Jezrelle there, one of my previous classmates back in high school... but she was finished with the measuring thing...so there, after i finished, we went downstairs naman to submit the i.d. picture.. then, finished! mama and i went to glorietta to buy many things... hahaha! i bought another pair of pants and a bag... yipee! at last, i have a bag... and two shirts from anonymous... super nicey! yay! we bought clothes for jun and joana also... we three have a spongy bob shirt! yehey! hehehe... we also bought a gift for my newly wed couz... we bought too many things that we even can't carry them all... when we got home, me and mama have to cook lasagna for the little celebration that my couz prepared... so there... mama and i was sooo tired.. it was around 7:30 when we finally set off to the dinner party... i have already borrowed some books from my couz which i will be using at makati med... i'm telling you, man, she has TONS of BIG books! super! so that's it... when we got home it's already at around 11.. we have to sleep early coz jun and papa are having the outing remember?!?!  but, a shitty thing happened, BROWN-OUT!!!waaaah! so there, but because i woke up so early this morning, i can't help but to fall asleep... that's it for my day... but, there's a continuation above... hahaha.. by the way, it's gladys' birthday today! happy birthday gladah! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaha! have you seen the title??!?! that has a tagalog version pa :  "Nang ako ay malayt dahil sa aking kapayatan..."  waaaah! i'm going nuts! i can't think of any title so i asked ervin's help to think of a title for today's post... and because of his so... twisted whatsoever mind, he came up with this title..uhmm, yah! he accompanied me to speech power... i went to apex or "kanto" as what we call it, to have my picture taken for my i.d. at makati med, then i ate lunch at mister donut.. me and ervin met there, at the fx stand, there was no fx.. and we waited for about 15 minutes.. we started the trip at around 2:35.. i knew it, i was going to be late! and of course, i was late!!! i came at around 3:15 catching my breath as i entered the room... we had activities and discussions... and we are doing another VTR session next meeting! it's like a sort of a talkshow thing...about politics, we'll be imitating politicians..hahah! bahala na... so that's it, our class ended there and ervin was waiting outside...  so we went to Robinson's again.. we were walking and walking and walking, looking for a place to eat...   parang nalibot na namin ang buong Rob!   there was a sort of fashion show at the mall, which was nonsense...but again and again,  bumagsak din kami sa Popeyes!  we ate there AGAIN! hahaha! he told me that i was getting slimmer... hahaha! he said that it was just because we haven't seen each other... waaah! hahaha! that was funny....so afterwards, we strolled and we were looking for a coffee shop that sells iced mocha... shit! i'm like obsessed to that iced mocha whip thing! we were looking for it.. i mean, the cheap one, but unfortunately, the ones we found was for about 95 to 100+ pesos! it's so expensive!! waaaah! as we are strolling, we dropped by a petshop, well, not exactly coz it only sells fishes! heheh, we saw veryyy expensive fishes...we strolled again and we were like feeling a bit tired of walking, so i decided to buy the "big chill" na lang... it's a shake... hahaha! again?! and ervin bought some brownies for jhing...so there, we took the fx, but we first went to apex to get my picture.. and because of ervin's stupidity, we had to walk because he thought that the fx will be going to pateros, but it turned the other way around and went to apex... waaah! so we had to walk and my feet are really aching! we rode a tricycle and he went with me upto my house because he got jhing's pic.. he was nangungulit that he'll pay me his grad. pic... i said, it's ok and he does'nt need to, after all, he accompanied me naman to SP.. so we bid each other our goodbye's and thank you's.. and that's it... yah! tomorrow, me and mama are going to makati med to submit the i.d. picture and have some measurements for the uniform and shoes... and i have to wake up early!! i got a bit pissed because this post is my second post, my first was erased for no such reason! waaah! but, after all, this post is finished.. so that's it for my day.. thanks for droppipng by... Ciao!    from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, for my day, i woke up at around 9 and started cleaning the house... i also helped mama in the laundry and we finished at about 12:30.. i ate lunch first because i was soo hungry... i also prepared a shake.. wehehehe,, again?!?! hahaha.. nothing's new with me preparing shakes! well, i just watched tv.. and i've been in the internet for about 3 hrs.. wahaha.. uhmm, yah, i have decided to attend Gladys' party rather than to go to the outing.. why?? because i have my period! and that explains all! get it?! i'm catching my breath right this very moment because i rushed outside because my cousins told me that there was an eclipse... well, i think i'll just look at that later...i'll just finish this post... there... uhmm, whatelse, i just chatted with arvie this afternoon, ah! i must call ervin nga pala to invite him again to accompany me to SP tomorrow, remember?!? laurice can't come... so i'll just call him later.. for sure, if i tell him that i'm enrolled at makati med and not UP, he'll kill me!!! waaah! but, i have enrolled anyways... so, that's it for my day, i dunno what will happen at SP tomorrow after all the evaluations... i'll update you guys.. that's it... ciao!    from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday, May 04, 2004 - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -   waaaah! as in waaaaah! i have many things to tell you guys! i'm being crazy again! FINALLY,  I AM ENROLLED AND I HAVE A SCHOOL!!!  yup, you guessed it right, i'm now enrolled at Makati Med.. waaah! and Gladys is not my classmate! and oza will be enrolling next week! i guess, i will really be alone.... waaaah! Good bye UP!!! bhala na... i'll tell you later my schedule... let me tell you first what happened in my SP classes, at last laurice is back..but she will not be attending thursday classes because her mom is leaving on friday... so, in our SP classes, i got to meet 3 new friends again, Diether, Simonette and Ronel... we were laughing the whole session... Ronel was so makulit... we had so much fun.. but on the latter part, we had to evaluate our teacher, Mrs. Bek Cantillero, for me, she was a good teacher, it was the curriculum that i don't really liked.. i feel like i'm not learning anything!! i swear.. what i have there when i first stepped there is what i still got upto now! get it?!?! nothing has been added! it's just like we're playing.. dramatization, games! shit! i'm not gonna waste my 6,000 on nonsense lessons! well, i really liked my classmates and my teacher... it's the curriculum! well, i wish i could really learn how to speak english fluently, i mean, in public...not being ashamed because you know what you're saying.. grammar lessons, things like that... well, enough! i just hope that i will get to learn something out of that SP... next issuue: my couz has been married this day... and my parents are the godparents... well, congrats to you and best wishes!! another one, it's my tita nang's birthday!!! hahaha! happy birthday! i went to their house which was just at the end of our street.. we ate there and watched tv.. i got bored so i invited my tita nang and kuya eldie to play card games with me.. tong-its again of course! hahaha! it's just piso-piso lang naman! guess what?!?! I WON!!! hahaha! i won 50 pesos! yipee! i'm so galing! hahaha... they were natalo... so that's it, we went home at about 1:00 in the morning... and something shocked all of us... when mama is about to open the door through the keys, of course, it is unlocked!!! so everybody was worried, we thought we have been robbed or a thief is inside the house, whatever.. it was my stupid bro's fault... my parents became hysterical... nga pala, i was not able to see the eclipse... sayang! once in a lifetime lang yun! well, ang daming kwento... i would like to post my schedule at makati med coz i got it na...   SUBJECT    --------------------------    DAYS    -------------------------     TIME                  English I               ----------------------      Wednesday       ----------------------           1:00 - 4:00                 Pil I                       ----------------------      Wednesday       ----------------------           4:30 - 7:30                 Algebra                 ----------------------      Thursday           ----------------------           7:00 - 10:00                 Gen. Psychology   --------------------      Tuesday            ----------------           4:30 - 7:30                 Gen. Chemistry     --------------------      Tuesday            ---------------           7:00 - 10:00                 Gen. Chemistry     --------------------      Tuesday            ---------------          10:00 - 2:00 - Lab.                 Philo. Of Man         ---------------------      Monday              -----------------------           1:00 -  4:00                 PMSD I                  ----------------------       Monday            -----------------------          10:00 - 12:00                 P.E. I                     ----------------------      Monday             -----------------------           7:00 - 9:00   by the way, we got NO classes on Friday... yipee! i think i'm gonna die! this post will just make you say:     WAAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!     from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm sooo bothered.. i dunno.. waaaah!well, to start off... today, i woke up and polished the floor...i also cooked breakfast because my mom is quite tired with the house chores... so i fried some ham and prepared a chocolate shake... that's it.. my mom told me that she'll be going somewhere this afternoon, after i washed the dishes, i watched the tv... my mom took a bath and told me that she's goin to makati med.. i remembered that today was the first day of enrollment.... waaah... so does that mean that i will really be enrolling at makati med?!?! waaaaah! i dunno, but that's how it seems... i'm bothered!  SAYANG ang pagkapasa ko sa UP!   of course, that is a very great oppurtunity for me, but, on the other hand, i have'nt got my course there, and moreso, i can't shift to that course which is Nursing.. and in makati med, it's near lang, and my couz graduated from there... waaaaaah! help me pls! i pity my parents because the tuition in makati med is so damn expensive! it's 35,000 without any books pa!the P.E is worth 1,750.00 damn! and you'll just be getting a P.E. shirt and a manual... and another one is worth 3,500.00 and you'll only be getting 2 sets of school uniforms and a pair of school shoes!! damn it! i can't survive with only two uniforms!!! what will i do now?! that school is so mahal!! and in UP, it's only 7,000.00, compare it! i hate college! i swear, if i will be enrolled in makati med, i will apply for the dean's list! para ma-reduce naman ang expenses... waaaah! it's so hard.. by the way, i just chatted with two of my friends today, joyce villanueva and kei... i miss highschool! except for the director! haahahah! that's it.... ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's sooo hot today! uhmm, i can't think of anything to write...ting! (light bulb blinking!!)  well, of course, today is Sunday.. and i know you're guessing it... haha! we went to church! of course! uhmm, nothing extraordinary happened there naman.. except for joana throwing her tantrums and crying for no reason.... so after the mass, we went straight home naman... then, i fell asleep upon lying in the bed... then, i woke up, it was already lunch time... of course, i washed the dishes afterwards coz it's my turn to wash them naman talaga... then, all of us were gathered in the bedroom and watched tv while my papa was trying to sleep... we turned on the air-con because as what i have said.. it was soo HOT! and because of this hotness, one of my uncles asked me and my mama to prepare the my ever famous, most requested MANGO SHAKE! what else?!?! hahaha! yah! i think that's my new found profession this summer.. but on second thought, i don't want to be a mango shaker! hahaha! so, yun.. we prepared tons and tons of mango shake for them, i think we made four pitchers... and i got tired... whew! then, i watched the tv afterwards.... then i prepared chocolate shake naman and clubhouse sandwich for our merienda... yum! waaah! so yun lang.. i told myself that sandwich would be my dinner na rin... but, my bro bought some balut, and i wanted some too... but i did'nt eat the chick inside! whatever! so that's it... i dunno what else to say...ahh, by the way, Gladys is throwing a party because it's her birthday on May 7... but she's celebrating it on May 8.. she's inviting our barkada to come.. well, i'm not sure yet if i'm coming because on the same day, my father's legion group(church org.) will be having an outing, i think we're included there.. but it's up to my mama, she said that the pool's not big... i'm thinking of not coming with them.. well, if mama won't come, i won't come too... uhmm, i'm still thinking of it... so, that's it for my day! see yah! thanks for dropping by! ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bonsoir! i still don't feel good... waaaah! S'il vous plait! i want to get well! i think, i cough every minute! poor me.. this day, was another boring day.. as usual, nothing's new... we ate lunch and i washed the dishes.. they were tons! ang dami! as in! it seems that 10 people ate lunch here! afterwards, i watched the tv... mama left at around 4:00 and went to my aunt's house.. she said that we can go there if we want... papa and jun left and went there too, as for me, i stayed here at home and watched star circle quest first.. btw, errol is now out! wehehehe.. he was so young and not suited for scqt... after i have updated my blog, i'll be going also at my aunt's house.. i don't want to be left here alone noh! Jobelle, me too, i updated my blog when blogger had a new look.. well, what the hell's in this template anyways!?! no big deal for me.. i just love the way my blog looks today.. so, that's it for my day.. i'm still thinking of changing the URL of my blog... uhmmm, let's see... j'ai partir... that's it for my day.. Au revoir et a demain.. Salut!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bonjour! ... uhmm, Au secours! Je mauvaise mine! waaaaah! i'm learning how to speak french right now! uhmmm, this day, was not a very good day for me, i spent almost the whole day in bed.. i'm SICK! God! i'm not really feeling good! my cough and cold are getting worst... waaaaah! i mean worst! when i coughed this afternoon, it has a little blood.. i dunno if i have to say it here pa.. well, just a little.. i'm not bothered... it happened to me before and i eventually got well naman... i think i'll be well... i just don't know when, i really hope, soon... i'm thinking of vacuum-ing my lungs.. nyahahaha! well, i don't have anything to say about my day because i just watched tv the whole day... urgh! booorrring! tonight, a chinese chatted with me, i got really pissed off with him coz he was insulting filipinos, well, me?!?! shit! i don't have time listening to his nonsense talks and sermons.. i dumped him! nyahahaha! so there, i didn't talk to him and i bored him to death and what i did was to surf the net for a site that teaches french lessons... btw, what i said earlier meant : Hello! uhmm, Help! i look unhealthy! nyahahaha! i look unhealthy, well, actually it doesn't really show! harharhar, i just don't feel good...well,  i have to continue with my french lessons! i'm having fun! à la prochaine...et Bonne nuit.. Salut!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hiyah! well, uhmm, this day, was ok naman, i feel happy... wekekekek...i wasn't really feeling well today, but i managed the entire day quite well...i have cough and colds... waaaah! if you could just hear my voice right now, you will think that i had just risen up from bed.. wehehehehe... so at around 1:15, i took a bath and prepared to go to SP, i was expecting that laurice will be coming with me, but hell, no! at first i got a little pissed off because she didn't even inform me that she was'nt coming with me, i only knew it when i called their house and they said that she went on an outing... well, everything is finished and i can still manage to go to SP alone, though i hate being alone.. so there, i waited a bit long in the fx and i thought that i was going to be late, when i arrived, i think i was late for about 5 mins. only.. so there, when our group became complete, we praticed for the VTR shoot.. i can say that the script diether has made is quite serious... we also did a commercial, the mcdo one, where sharon was shouting... yah, and when we were in the actual shoot, we were the last ones to perform, i was seated beside diether and we were watching the first group, we were nearly suffocated because of laughing so hard... hahahah! the first goup was ridiculous! they haven't got any preparations so they just like messed up their whole performance... they had i think take 3's... well, on our group, we were also laughing because of joshua and, uhmmm, the sharon commercial too, which simonette portrayed.. after the class, sumabay ako with diether and simonette because their way was my way also... at long last, i got home, though i was alone, i can say that this day is full of laughter! wehehehe.. then, today, i was surprised by a guest in my blog! Contot! wekekekek! welcome, nyahahaha! grabe, sinurprise mo ko dun ahh.. yun lang, that's it for my day! Ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whew! i had one stressful day again... well, to start off the day, i woke up and ate breakfast with my family... my brother and i had a petty fight while eating, actually, it would not have been a fight if my brother did'nt make sumbong!! he was so sumbungero! grrrr... and because of that, mama lost her appetite and got angry... i was soo pissed off with my brother and so i did'nt talk to him.. he was watching the tv and so i decided to connect on the internet and also, i received a txt message from simonette saying that diether has already sent the email of our script for tomorrow's VTR session so i checked my email, i found out that i will be imitting Ms. Jamby Madrigal as Ms. Join ka na sa kin, uhmm, whatever, goodthing i only had few lines to sy there... wehehehe... as i logged on to ym, i quickly logged on to invisible mode, coz i don't feel like chatting, i checked on my new blog and surprisingly, alvin messaged me on ym.. he was asking if i was still angry to him.. i told him that i was not, and i was never angry to him, he told me that he thought i was angry and he poured his sentiments on his webpage...i visited his webpage and i read what he has written, well, he told me not to bother about it.. well, noting was said against me, and until now, i am so proud to say that alvin is one of my closest friends in this universe!!! well, i just want to post the things he wrote, hehehe, alvin,    panakaw muna sa site mo ha..  i'm not posing this for any other reason, well, uhmm, just a remembrance that once, our friendship was put to the test:      "THE WORST FEELING EVER... - i don't know how to feel toward this friend of mine. should i also be mad or just be patient and wait for the time to calm her hatred or unpleasant feeling to me.? i think this friend of mine is mad at me because of an unpleasant situation that has happened 2 days ago. i really didn't mean it to happen. the problem was already solved because the thing that i ACCIDENTALLY and DIDN'T mean to DELETE was finally retrieved back because i really did all i can to make this friend happy. i even called at their house to say that it was already back but still i feel that this friend of mine is still not in the mood confronting me. actually i think this friend is "making iwas" to me because after logging in at ym, this friend readily logged-off that made me feel that this friend doesn't want to chat w/ me even though i was in invisible mode. to tell the truth and no offense i really don't like very sensitive people (i'm not saying that this friend im referring to is a sensitive person. i just want to say how i feel about a sensitive kind of person...) because they get easily upset in an unwanted situation. to tell frankly, i'm also a sensitive person because like what i said, i easily get upset in an UNWANTED SITUATION but i'm getting over w/ it once i feel bad in a situation that i don't like to be involved. *sighs..... i really hope that everything will be back to normal because i love this friend of mine and one of my closest."  i was sooo touched by what he said, but, as i was "nagnanakaw" from his site, i found out that he had posted another post... this part of his site is where he posts his feelings, i haven't read the entire post yet, but surely, i will read it.. i would like to post it again here... i will be a thief again... ehehehe...   alvin said:  " FEELING GOOD... NEVER BEEN BETTER... - oh i'm so glad because everything is back to normal. it was just 15 mins ago when i wrote how i feel towards my friend and the situation we've got into but now i can't compare the happiness that i'm feeling because we're ok now. i didn't know that she was online all the time i was writing on how i feel. she pm so that's how i figured out that she was online. i was shocked that she pm me w/ a msg that seems nothing is wrong between us. i told her that i was really sorry about and she told me that everything was ok. that was the time that i really got off with the uncertain feeling. then i told her that if she reads the blog that i wrote, just regard it since everything was ok between us. then we chatted about it and we used the cry smiley as if we're crying!!! wahahaha!!! i really feel good now!!! thank god!!! i really couldn't afford to loose a very special friend..."   waaaaaah! that's it... that's what happened... uhmm, this post is too long, but i want to cry out loud that: "alvin is my friend and forever, he will be!" yipeeee! my old blog is back again, i bid goodbye to my new blog... it's better kapag orig! i had a nice day! hope you had one too! Ciao!    from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      waaaaaah! i am so damn Stressed!!! waaaah! as you can see, i've got a new template! and, i've got a new blog! see the address!?!! why?!?! because alvin accidentally DELETED my blog! waaaah! i was nearly in tears! but uhmm, because of my insanity and beauty.. i created a new one, hahaha! related ba yun? but don't you worry, all my previous posts are still here... wehehehe! yipee! at last.. i'm finished with this blog! all i did was to copy and paste! i'm so stressed out with what happened.. but don't worry alvin, i'm not pissed off with you or anything... i got my blog back and it's okay... one blog can't ruin one strong bond of friendship! dibah?!?! wehehehe! and yes, today is National election! uhmm, whatelse??.... news about the election is nagkakalat in different channels! mama left at around 1:00 to vote, i was watching the tv and saw many news about different happenings in the election, i hope this will one will turn out to be a successful one... today, i'm left alone here at home, but i'll follow mama and others at my aunt's house... nothing happened today.. i can't think of anything to say!!! waaaah! i'll just update you later.. okay?! by the way, blogger has a new look! yipee! wehehehe! that's it! ciao!    from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday, May, 09, 2004 - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -    yipee! it's mother's day today guys!! Happy mother's day mama! well, today is Sunday, we didn't attend mass in the morning so we attended mass in the afternoon.. well, my day, was okay... nothing much happened.. i just greeted my mama happy mother's day and kissed her.. we watched pacquiao's boxing match and i was very much disappointed with the result which was a draw.. well, we went to church nga this afternoon... i saw janking there and he was greeting me happy mother's day... wehehe.. we had a little chat and he greeted my mom happy mother's day too.. there was one altar server who kept on looking at me... wahaahaha! well, i don't care, and after the mass, he blocked my way! but he's cute..waaaaaah!but, i passed in front of him of course! then, i ordered a bouquet of roses for mama, after the mass, i picked it up...it was soo beautiful, it was a bunch of roses red and peach! it was wrapped in a fiber-like wrapper which made it look expensive! we ate at chowking afterwards and went to my grandparent's house, i greeted my aunts' happy mother's day.. and we stayed there not so long because papa is a member of the PPCRV for tomorrow's election.. that's it for my day! Ciao!   from the great weird mind of the pretty jetty! harharhar!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello! okay, this day was a busy day for all of us.. i woke up around 11:00 a.m and did some chores.. we ate lunch and after that mama left with her bestfriend to buy some ingredients for the foods that we will be preparing tomorrow.. we are having a sort of a celebration coz tomorrow is my brother's confirmation day... we're maghahanda ata.. so mama went to the mall and she intended to buy a polo shirt for my bro coz they are required to wear a white shirt.. but i found a ralph lauren polo shirt upstairs which i think, was new pa naman, i told mama not to buy anymore.. as for me, i was left here at home with my sister, in the afternoon, my parents' church friend called up, she was the president of a certain church org., she was inviting me to attend the audition for the lector-commentator organization in our parish, it seems to me that she was really forcing me, well, first of all, i really don't want to be a member of that organization, i was a member of that once, it was a group of juniors, since i was also young then, but, as time passes, it had conflicts on my schedule.. most of the time, whenever they assign me, i can't... i don't want to engage myself in a thing that i don't really like.. she kept on bugging me that dadap was there, hell with dadap! i don't care whether she's there or not! they are having auditions tonight at 7:30 and an interview follows after, i think our parish priest will be conducting the interview... they will also be having a seminar tom. at 8-5.. gosh! i don't have time, plus, i don't know anybody there! for sure, most of the people there are oldies! hello?!?! not me! heheheh..okay, so enough, i don't care if they wait for me or what! but i'm definitely not attending! okay, so enough with that crap.. tierry also called me, oh, i miss that wild girl... we chatted and laughed almost every minute, we talked for about 1 and 1/2 hours about anything and everything... so there, at around 7, mama arrived with her bestfriend, they bought tons of new things to embellish and decorate the house... throw pillows.. etc. they actually renovated the whole house, they're like interior designers, well, they did good naman, up to now, my mom's bestfriend is still here, same with her daughter and her nanny ata... so there, i dunno if i can update this blog tomorrow coz for sure, i'll be busy with the handaan and my bro will definitely play with the comp. with my cousins.. so there..that's it for my day, i dunno what will be papa's reaction to my refusal of joining the org, he's one of those people who's forcing me to join there! waaaaah! i hate it! that's it! au revoir!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haler! today is thursday that's why i had another SP session again.. my day was good and a bit cold.. uhmm, okay, so today, my mom's bestfriend went here at home and spent the whole day here.. she was with her youngest daughter so joana had a playmate... they ate lunch here and they also bought some ice cream and some snacks... i left a bit early for SP because it was raining, of course, automatically, when it rains, it's traffic.. i was right, because it was really traffic in manila.. good thing i just came on time, actually, i was 5 minutes earlier... so there, we had discussions and some role playing which was really fun.. we made no use of words, just non-verbal actions and gestures... then the others seating will guess what we were acting... so there, i think we will have another vtr session next meeting or if not, maybe on the next, next meeting... i dunno what's the vtr about, oh yes, uhmm, our group won the guessing game thing, actually, two groups won, the other one was sandra's group, the teacher said that on the last meeting, we will bring some snacks for the whole class because we were the winner.. i dunno if they are serious or not, but, for me, it's fine to treat my classmates, anyweiz, it's the last time that i'll be seeing them, but surely, i'll be missing them.. and when it was dismissal time, sandra told us that we will be having extra classes because of what we have written in the evaluations.. i think the supervisor will be giving that lesson... uhmm, good for us, at least, we can say that our payment was worth it..if it was?! i dunno, let's see on friday.. because the extra classes are offered on friday at 2-4 pm.. so, for sure, i'll be going there.. nga pala, i have a brand new closet in my bedroom, it was nice... actually, my parents were forced to buy that because a priest will be staying at our house these july... priests all around the country are having a sort of convention..so in our parish, each family is assigned to have one priest, to qualify for the "adopting priest family", your family must be complete with parents and children at home, they will sleep here and go to the convention in the morning and be back in the evening..so there.. i just hope that the priest that stays here at home will be good.. i think i'll be forced to stop with my little devilish acts first when he's around.. only when he's around! hahahaha! so there... that's it for my day... goodbye!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      waaaaaaah! uhmmm, hello! before i go nuts again about what happened last night, i would like to greet you first.. haaaaay.. i had a dreadful but fun night... okay, this is how the story goes.. i have told you that we went to my grandparent's house last night... but before that, i stayed here at home and ate dinner already.. then, i followed them there... me and my couz watched marina there and i decided to eat again because i felt a little bit hungry, or maybe, i just wanted to taste the adobo.. nyahahaha...  so as i was about to finish eating, mama suddenly noticed it.. because she didn't knew at all that i was eating.. papa frantically panicked and got the adobo! they told me that it has bubog.. waaaaah! i felt my heart skipped beating for a second, my parents became hysterical, but my aunts were defending me.. of course i was defending myself too.. i didn't know that it has bubog! haler?!? nobody told me.. so how would i know.. but, at least i'm not yet dead upto this very minute.. harharhar! let's see and wait for the effect.. heheheh! of course, i'm not that brainless and stupid if i didn't notice any bubog in my mouth naman.. but, there's nothing to worry, i'm not dead afterall, hahaha! afterwards, me and my cousins played card games and bonded a little bit as if nothing happened to me... we had fun naman..so today, my mama got angry with my bro.. he went to our boarder kasi without even eating breakfast and taking a bath.. my mother said that if he does that again, we'll be packing his clothes and let him stay there.. hehhehehe.. nice threat for him.. i updated my blog a bit early again, coz i might run out of load any minute now.. and my bro will be using the comp. later..  ah, yah, at long last, i and alvin chatted again... yipeee! i missed him.. so, that's it for my day.. actually, my day is not over yet, i'll update you guys tom. if there's any happening okay?! so.. bye!   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hiyah...whew! i had another SP session today... i went there alone, laurice finally confirmed to me that she would'nt be attending SP classes anymore.. if i haven't txted her, she wouldn't tell me again. i dunno how to feel or react about that.. nevertheless, it's their money and not mine..but, i can proudly say that i'm coping pretty well with SP alone.. i learned how to commute all by myself... good thing that i have kasabay on my way to the fx stand, (diether and simonette)... haaaaay.. well, today, nobody's home again.. they are all in my grandparent's house... i'm going there maybe, later... uhmm, for my SP classes.. we were laughing again.. endlessly.. we had a game there.. we were divided into groups of three, our leader, will be asked to go outside, same with the leader of the other groups.. the teacher will tell them a story, afterwards, they will call on the next member and relay the story to that person until the whole goup knows the story... then, the last person will relay the story at the whole class.. it was so funny because the story had a thousand and one versions! hahahaha! we were laughing because the story has completely changed... haaaaay.. so there... uhmm, i have to finish this post because i have to go and follow my family there.. but, i'll be watching SCQ first..  au revoir camarade!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haler! i'm here again.. i am updating my blog a little too early... well, today, nothing much happened again.. except that it rained today...oh, yah, the title of my blog is in french again... uhmm, wait, it means: "Chat Day with Friends..." tell you about that later... uhmmm, today, i helped in cleaning the house, i gathered up some information about ate salie..hehehe, parang investigator! should i say, some updates... mama told me that she is not in Bicol now... she left Bicol, first week of may pa, because she had voted already here in makati eh.. she's now in laguna accdg. to mama... i asked, when she will be coming back here, mama told me that she'll be coming back on june pa daw.. haaaaay, bahala nga siya...maybe she really wanted a break from work.. so, yun.. and, yes today, it rained! whew! thank goodness for that! at least, it's not so hot today.. my parents are not around, they went to CAP ata..they left joana at my grandma's house and jun-jun is out.. i'm alone here! i got bored so i logged on to the internet...luckily, arizza was online, i haven't talked to her for two weeks na ata..so we chatted quite long, about college and stuff, she also told me that they are now having some family problems.. haaaaay.. that's life.. but, suddenly, arizza told me an absurd and ridiculous thing, she told me that she was applying mayonaise on her hair to make it more shiny! i was nearly suffocated again because of laughing, i just can't stop laughing! i mean, mayo! eeeeiiiw.. i hate mayo.. it smells horrible! yuck!  then, later on, joyce pm-ed me... i invited them for a conference..the three of us were laughing and laughing about it... joyce visited my blog too, well, thanks for the visit, anyweiz, then jonas arrived too, he was in invisible mode so we did'nt notice him, but he pm-ed me... maricon arrived after a few minutes! whew! too bad, alvin wasn't online, same with jobelle, because these two persons are the ones who i often chat with.. btw, i read that jobelle is having a car! wow! yay! congrats! ehehehe! so that's it for my day.. i better log off now, i might run out of internet load! hey wait! as i was about to publish my post.. Juvy logged on! grabe na toh! ehehehe.. yun lang.. tama na nga...au revoir!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mabuhay! take note! hindi na yan french! oh ayan ah, my greeting is in tagalog na.. uhmm, hi.. i'm here again, blabbering about my day.. was that correct?! let's ask the grammar genius: Leslie! nyahahaha! yup. today is Sunday and we went to church, actually, i was acting a bit sluggish this morning because i was still soo sleepy.. imagine, i have slept at around 2:30! waaaah! insomia attack again, i think.. uhmm, but, we arrived here at home from my aunt's house at around 1:00 am... geee! i was telling hilarious stories to my couz about PCS.. the teachers, the projects... whew! i felt a bit happy, looking back on what happened in my highschool days.. my classmate's impersonating our teachers... nyahahaha.. those were really fantastic and wonderful memories.. i think, i'm mising highschool, but definitely not the director! ehehehe! bad... well, i dunno if i'm getting better or not.. i'm talking about my sickness.. i dunno if this is what you can call better huh?! waaaaah! so, uhhmm, this day, at the church, the mass started a bit late, because the parish priest came late..i think he was tired coz our parish held an outing yesterday... the sakristan was not there too... nyahahaha! uhmmm, it was so hot this morning! kelan ba naging malamig?!?! haler?! so, when we got home after the mass, i helped mama with the laundry because still, ate salie is not home yet! i dunno when will she come back or if she will still come back?! hahahaha.. i watched tv the whole afternoon and at around 5:00 my bro arrived and bought some of his friends here, so we prepared a snack for them.. that's it for my day... adieu!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haler! today, i woke up really early, uhmmm,7:30.. my papa and other siblings planned to swim at Villa Monica, they decided to come with jun coz he was having swimming lessons... i was awaken by their noise.. mama was going to Pasig to accompany her bestfriend and buy some stuff for us.. so, for short, i was left alone again... at around 8:30, i received a strange txt msg, from an unknown sender... it says:  "am i sending this message to ms. jessica nacional?" , so i was like.. huh?! so who the hell is this?! i don't like anyone playing jokes on me at this time, not this early... so i opted to reply also in english,  "Yup. hus dis pls?" , the reply said :  "Gez hu?"  i was kinda pissed by the reply so i said,  "i have no idea at all, i know too many persons, so just tell me hu u r, and don't waste my time on any guessing game.. k?" , that was what i replied, he finally revealed himself and said that he was julius! hehehehe... i told him that i was a bit harsh in replying coz i thought it was a speechpower agent or the maniac classmate of ours who used to stalk my other classmates, julius said that, i was so masungit to unknown persons... hehehehe! to summarize it all, all he meant was he got a new cel too! yay for him! and he was asking for ervin's no. i called ervin right away to report the good news, the phone was given to him, he sounded like he just woke up,and he really did, i was talking there, full of excitement and joy, while all he did was to 'moan'.. hehehe, i hanged up the phone and called lourdes, she answered the phone though she was taking a bath, again, i hanged up the phone... at about 10:30 ervin called and he was back to normal again... we chatted for about 2 hrs of nonsense things.. so there, after that, mama arrived followed by papa and jun and joana, they rested and took a nap... our aunt invited us to come over her house and play card games again... so, i'm now here updating my blog, i'm chatting with my friend jho tupaz right now... hi jho! hehehehe... that's it for my day, me and my cousins are playing card games too... we will be going home at morning again, i bet! hehehe, bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi! my day was very educational! i love it! my day, was fun... although, i am saddened by the thought that this is my last day in speechpower... i prepared a little early coz my classes are at 1.. i arrived there early too, i wasn't surprised that no one was there... i came 10 minutes earlier, i was directed to go to room D by the lady there, i was worried that only i would have attended the make-up class.. but, luckily, simonette, entered, followed by diether, ronel and joshua.. for short, we were only five, and sandra who was complaining all about the curriculum, wasn't present there.. so there, the class started at around 2:05.. the professor was great, i thought he was harsh and a bit stern coz he was the supervisor of SP, but no, he was good, actually, it's okay for us to chat while he's discussing, as long as we are speaking in english... at the start of the lesson, he was chatting to each of us about the infos. we have written on the info. sheet before we enrolled.. about our courses, schools, nicknames etc... heheheh, gosh, i learned too many things today, correct pronunciation of words i have been pronouncing all along.. like  "subpoena"  i often pronounce this is as   "sub-pina"  but he said that the correct pronunciation was  "sa-pina" .. imagine?!? hehhehe, he was good and really gave focus to each one of us... he taught us how to read the dictionary and the things written in there... he focused on each and every one's difficulty and weakness... he said that he studied linguistics..he was great and he also gave us some techniques on how to speak english fluently... and that was the lesson that i expected and always wanted... although it only lasted for three hours, and i can assert that, that was the worth of the 6,000 that we payed... well, there, the lesson ended and i walked with diether and simonette upto the fx stand, i bid farewell to my friends, i felt sad coz i don't know whether i'll be seeing them again or not, i told them that if ever they decided to have a review, they just txt me and i'll go with them.. so that is the end of my SPEECHPOWER adventure... i guess it's up to me now on how will i develop what i have learned there.. surely, i'll be missing my gala every tues. and thurs. and my classmates and friends that i met there. :( that's it for my last SP day... bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello! i am so baffled at this point in time! why?! because a person in the name of  drek  just tagged me at my msg board, and i have no fucking idea who this person is! i am like pissed or something, well, i don't know him and neither i don't know where he found a fucking link to my diary! hahahah! but shit i don't give a damn! these things make me think of changing the url of this blog... so, enough about that cr*p, let's talk about my day.. my day was fine, last night, we slept really late, like, 3:30 am... hahaha! so i woke up at around 12:00, i was alarmed that i only had one hour to eat lunch and do my stuff because at 1, i'll be preparing for my SP class... so there, we ate lunch and i prepared for SP... at the fx, i waited a bit long, then i was surprised when charles and his friend (jojo, i think) stepped into the fx.. we greeted each other, charles was a friend of mine since elementary, but, we had a gap due to some unpleasant incidents, we talked about lots of stuff in the trip.. he had enrolled in EAC(nursing) and stuff about israel, etcetera... he(or she) and his friend are   nagbabaklaan  in the fx... hehehe! what do you expect?!?!so there, i bid goodbye to them and i was late for my class, as i entered, my groupmates, who are also singing rainbow clapped as i entered and suggested that i, sing a solo number.. well, of course that was a joke! so there, we practiced and then, the vtr started.. we had fun watching  the dance number ronel, joyce and erma prepared.. and joshua had a dramatic poem, which i think is dedicated to jaimie.. hehehe.. ronel, did a solo number and sang  What a journey  by Lea Salonga.. then, we followed.. afterwards, we watched the video, and that was the end of the class, we evaluated again and the certificates are distributed... our teacher bid farewell and so did we.. i went home a bit early coz the classes ended at 4:30.. tomorrow will be the last of my SP life.. so there, at home, i slept for about 2 hours so i wasn't able to watch SCQ.. that's it for my day... i feel sad about a friend today or should i say i pity that friend :( bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haler! today, i woke up at around 11... mama and joana are going to pateros, arranging some business there, me and jun jun are left here at home, then as i was upstairs, the phone rang, it was papa on the other line.. he was telling me that he wants to have a family outing, just exclusive for the five of us... i said i had extension classes on friday! sayang! grrrr! i told him, it's fine with me to be absent there, anyweiz, there's no payment for that session and the certificates will be given on thursday.. but he refused right away... he said that he wants us to have an overnight swimming... waaaaah! but if ever, there's no choice, it'll be on friday after my classes, he's suggesting on sea breeze, i declined right away! i hate sea breeze! you're like swimming in a pool of chlorine! i suggested that we go on la vista pansol, it was nice there.. well, up to now, i'm still thinking of a nice place to go.. but we're on a tight budget due to the opening of classes... it's just that, our family has always been having a summer getaway every vacation.. sayang naman diba... so there, and this update is quite early coz me and my bro will be going to my grandparent's house coz our family's there... that's it.. ciao friends! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hai! i kinda feeling depressed right now because i only have 2 remaining SP days.. huhuhu.. before the drama, i'll tell you about my day, uhmmm, nothing much happened, my bro was scolded because he was being too tactless and he was talking endlessly about some chores that he does and that i am a sloth.. weheheh, i didn't react but mama defeded that i was doing more chores than him.. wehehehe... that's it.. then, we ate breakfast at 11:00!?! and i watched tv and prepared for SP at around 1:05.. when i arrived there, we waited for a while before we could enter, coz the clases aren't finished yet.. we had presentations and stuff, and next meeting we will be having our last vtr session, we will be having a variety show.. duh?! okay, i've got no choice and all of us needs to participate.. me, diether, simonette and aina are having a song number, of course, i decided to join them coz i don't have the guts to perform all by myself, joyce, ronel and erma are dancing.... and the others.. doing, uhmm, foolishness whatever! hehehe.. so there, we made some newspapers from our own creativity... of course, i did the lettering! our group was the first to finish and there, the class ended... on friday, the schedule for the extension class was reset and was made 2-5.. good thing that it was longer... so there, haaaaay, i think, i'm gonna miss my classmates there and my new-found friends :(  they are so fun to be with.. same with my teacher who is so kind and patient... haaaaaaay, so there, that's it for another SP day again... bye peeps! :(
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      halu! okay! this is for sunday and monday's post... i'm tinatamad na kasi.. so, i am still having a hang-over from saturday's celebration.. and so i woke up at around 12:00... i ate lunch and helped in cleaning the house coz my parents are doing the laundry.. so there, i watched the tv and my parents said that we will be attending the 6:00 pm mass, i got excited because my other crush was there! whew! i'm so... alipokpokin! hehehe! that's the term we used to call arizza! so, there, but i was a bit hesitant because i might see the leader of the church org. who was inviting me remember? she might be hunting me! hahahahah! so there, but, still, i went to church.. and i was so blessed coz my crush was there!! geeeeee... and the lady wasn't there! hahahaha! happy! shalalala! hehehe.. so there, we went to bigbest and bought some groceries... and when we got home, i only ate some snacks... and i watched piolo's concert at abs-cbn.. that's it for my sunday, and for my monday, i woke up at around 11 and cleaned the house, i also cooked breakfast for all of them.. after that, i watched tv.. and watched a dvd after.. me and my bro watched school of rock.. it was funny.. and now, i logged on to the internet! but, i was interrupted for a while because of my bro.. tebby called, nangungumusta lang.. and jezrelle surprised me too, she called me up, asking about our school... so there, i'm back and i'm chatting with tierry at this moment! so that's it for my day! au revoir! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haler!! okay! i haven't updated my blog for two days!!! waaaah! i hate it! i'm separating my post for saturday coz it's really long! this title is for saturday.. get it?!? and so, i'll be creating another post for sunday, but i would like to merge it with monday's post... okay, so i wanna start my saturday post..   i woke up very early.. i think, seven! yah, and i helped mama in cooking, well, i cooked the spag and the gelo! yay! we cooked too many different dishes, caesar's salad, hickory... yum yum! my mom's bestfriend also helped us in cooking.. at around 11, we were done with all the cooking and at that time, we expect the guests to arrive, but my father txted that the bishop was stranded at coastal road so the confirmtion started late.. nonetheless, they still arrived here, looking so hungry, because the confirmation was intended to start at 9, but bacause of the bishop, it started late... so, there, i changed my clothes coz, of course, i have to look nicey! waaah! my crush arrived pa here! geee! i have so many crushes! hehehe... uhmm, i didn't really have plans of inviting my friends over, i dunno why, but, by coincidence, tierry called up and said that she wanted to go here because she hates her grandpa, not knowing that there was a celebration going on here! so, i decided to let her go here and invite all of my other peers.. i invited ervin, lourdes, julius and chris... i considered inviting chris so that we could mock someone and laugh at.. harharhar! nah, that was a hobby! so there, julius and lourdes arrived here first, followed by chris and ervin.. i don't have load so i can't txt angela, i thought that ervin will txt her but, he doesn't have load too, they ate and we connected to the internet for a while, then, tierry arrived, and she surprised all of us coz she brought the videocam with her! so there, we chatted and we went upstairs to play card games, we decided to play mitsubishi, the memory game, it was sooo fun! we were mocking chris all the time and we were on cam, tierry recorded it and i told her to put it in a vcd for a remembrance.. hehehe, angela came at around 7, and she joined us, unfortunately, lourdes has to go home... we played and played and watched the video after.. it was so fun, i haven't laughed this much since vacation started! haaaay.. so they went home at around 9:45.. and tita claire called here and my mom chatted with her for an hour.. so there, i was so tired and i washed tons of dishes! at around 10:00, tierry called and updated me some gossips! but i can't post it here! scandalous!  ervin and i chatted from 11:00 until 1:00 am.. i slept at around 3:30 am coz i accompanied mama coz she was playing card games with my aunt and uncle... so there, i had a very tiring day! but definitely, an enjoyable one! that's it for my saturday! vavoosh!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uhuh! today is the big day! today, is the day that i waited for quite long! let me tell you about that later... today, i woke up early coz mama said we were going to leave early today.. at 9:30, i was already awake.. we ate our considered lunch at 10:30... mama got angry because she wanted us to attend mass(coz today is first friday), but she said that we were preparing very slowly and if we didn't catch the mass at 12, we will not be watching Harry Potter... of course i can't let that happen... she started nagging at me and said that i was the slowest.. i was very much annoyed by that nagging, but i got so used to it that i totally ignored it... nothing can ruin my good mood... :) so there, we went to greenbelt to attend mass and also, to meet our cousins there who will also be watching Harry Potter.. after the mass, we proceeded to glorietta and bought some tickets for the 2:15 slot... we didn't bought sure seats tickets, they bought free seats.. we decided to just enter the cinema earlier.. we still had time to eat and have snacks coz it's just 1:20... and my cousins hasn't eaten lunch yet.. so they ate at wendy's and i bought gigantic popcorns from Tater's.. we entered the cinema at 2:00.. the film started at 2:25... and as i have written in the title...  I AM COMPLETELY DISAPPOINTED AND UPSET!!! GRRRRRR....  the fucking director ruined the whole story! he was like changing the whole story and making up his own! he haven't even read the Book! i hate him! like, the whole setting was changed! imagine?! hogwarts seemed to be built at the top of a mountain! and to reach hagrid's house, you must like come down from large blocks of rocks! unlike on the previous movies that hagrid's hut is just footsteps away from the castle! grrrr! and the whomping willow isn't tamed by pressing a knot! Remus Lupin just flicked his wand and said:  "Immobilous"  dunno, if that was the spelling! i was completely annoyed while i was watching the movie! Cho Chang wasn't even there!!! and the firebolt, which in the book, they thought was jinxed and which was anonymously sent was received by Harry in the end of the movie! he received it after sirius and buckbeak has escaped! and Harry knew that Peter Pettigrew was alive through the Marauder's Map.. isn't it that Sirius and Lupin are the one's who will reveal that he is still alive! the actor which played Dumbledore was awful! it was very much different from the previous one! oh no! i don't know what to expect on Book 4! and, if you haven't read the book like my mom, you will not fully understand the story! it seems like it doen't have a story at all! maybe, the director assumed that te ones who will be watching are the ones who read the book! he was so stupid! i want columbus back! grrrr.. the film was uhhmmmm, horrible, if i may say.. sorry,if i'm acting too exagerated.. but, i expected so much from this film, i thought this was going to be great... but, no! so that's it... till next time, see yah! bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yipeee! today is my lolo's birthday... well, i prayed for his soul last night, well, actually, i do that every night.. weehehehe! last night, joana slept with me upstairs.. we were ordered to sleep there so that we can get used to sleeping and waking up early just like what we did when we had classes.. i was so sleepy but joana still wanted to chat with me... then, at long last, we both fell asleep.. we woke up at around 10:30... and we ate lunch, afterwards, we watched tv and they took a nap, at around 3:00 my mother told me to prepare coz we will be going to the cemetery to visit my lolo... so we reached garden at around 4:05.. we prayed the rosary and while we were saying our personal prayers for him my lola and my aunt sobbed.. i was nearly in tears but, i controlled it.. i said to myself that everything's finished and the only thing that i could do for him is to pray for his soul.. i get too emotional whenever it concerns anything about my family... i cry very easily! hehehehe! and i laugh easily too! don't you think i'm retarded?! yah! that's a world-known fact! hehehehe! kidding aside, after we have prayed the rosary, me and my bro played the games of the general.. then we went to mcdo to eat dinner there.. all of my cousins came except for earl.. so there, it rained a little bit, but we still managed... we went home right after going to mcdo... we stayed for a while at my lola's house and went here at home after... and yes! tomorrow is the big day! hahahahah! i will be seeing harry again! yipee! i'm so excited! so that's it... happy birthday lolo! love u! :) bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi! yup! ate salie, our helper has returned again... last night, she was back again to our residence! i was a bit shocked by her unexpected return, but i didn't pay too much attention on her arrival, same with mama who just continued on ironing the clothes.. joana was again bugging me and celebrating that ate salie was home.. i just ignored her.. i must admit, i didn't really wanted her to come back.. yah, at first, i found it hard, working on all this house chores and everything, but heavens! i have adjusted! we(mama,jun and me) have managed to clean the house, do the laundry and iron the clothes.. mama cooks our food, so why do we need to hire a helper!?! i just don't get it! imagine, we have managed all of this without her help, considering that it's vacation and all of us are stocked here at home and littering all over the place! yah! coz that's what mama always tell us, whenever we're around, (the three of us) the house would be stormed vastly, and that's for sure! so, when we're back to school, the house will be solemn again, and there's no thorough cleaning up needed anymore because we're not there, storming the place... and one more thing, ate salie is going to school, so, how would she be able to do her job if she's at school the whole day and return here at dusk, and seem like so tired and everything! i hate her! we have been like this for about 5 yrs.. we are paying her for just a liitle work every month, i really think she should rent her own place and just continue her studies there, we have helped her enough, 5 yrs, i think is enough, our family let her study from 1st yr. in highschool, and she is now in 2nd yr. college... isn't that enough, she really don't appear like a helper to me, somewhat, a boarder... we let her eat, study and sleep here for free! argh! and she's receiving 2,000 every month for doing very easy chores! waaaaah! shit! i can do those chores by myself! so, i must convince my parents to dodge her outta here... i just can't stand it when she's being paid for NOTHING! so enough with that! i know you got my point and blogging it in here's just no use! i just wanted you to know.. coz that's the purpose of my blog! so, tomorrow, is my lolo's birthday, well, he's dead. :( but, we will visit him in the cemetery, i just hope the weather copes with us... two days to go and off i will be at the cinema! yipee! and yup! i have finshed reading the book last night! yay! today, i'm going again to my aunt's house because they're there again! i'm returning the digicam too... and it's raining quite hard today.. maricon is influencing me to download the new YM... but i failed! but i'll try again later! ayt!that's it for my day! bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hiyah! i'm back... my mind's kinda empty right now and i've got nothing to share with you really, heheheh! coz i spent most of my day rereading Harry Potter Book 3.. i woke up at 10:30 today and the book was the first thing i took a grip on... i read for about an hour then i helped mama with the chores first coz i felt a bit guilty... then, at around 1:00, i grabbed the book again and stopped at 3:00, feeling hungry, i went to the kitchen and cooked some food, i felt hunger coz i haven't been able to eat lunch.. so there, after eating, i continued reading upto 6:00... i'm more than half-way through the book.. i think, i will be able to finish reading it tonight.. hehehehe! this is a record for me, the shortest time i have read a thick book... for just one day! well, i'm really getting excited more and more each day to watch harry potter on the big screen... that's all i've got to say coz that's all that i've done for the whole day, i was drowned by some potter pages and travelled from makati to hogwarts this day.. heheheh! there is this urge i'm feeling every time i grasp a Harry Potter book, just to continue reading it, i'm just lured by it.. maybe Rowling jinxed it to entice some readers... nyahahah! so that's it for my day... bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yah! i'm quite tired today... yup, we went to the mall today as what i have said yesterday, we bought so many things from national bookstore.. whew! the bill reached i think.. 3,800.00 hehehehe... school supplies shopping to the max talaga! i bought myself new notebooks, tons of ballpens, papers... i applied for a  "Laking National"  discount card too.. then after shopping at Glorietta, we went to Landmark and ate there, my mom promised to buy me a new jacket... good thing she kept her promise, we went to the second floor to look for some, i found many there, lee, jag, fila... i tried lee, but it doesn't fit me well, but the designs were great, we went to speedo and i found a nice jacket there, i bought it, though i think it was quite expensive, it cost, 3,500.00.... waaaaaah! that was really expensive, heheheheh! so there, we opted to go home coz we had too many baggages.. we lined up for the taxi stand, but only very few taxis are coming, good thing an fx going to pembo passed, so we were able to go home na... it's my aunt's birthday today.. tita aba... happy bday! and a sad thing happened, auntie del died... :( she used to massage our family... so sad.. so that's it for today... ah, yes, i think our schedule for watching HP3 will be moved to june 4, coz my couz will be watching on that day... the more, the merrier! heheheh! that's it! ciao! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi...today is sunday, but we didn't go to church this morning, because as what i have said yesterday, we stayed on my aunt's house till 3:30 in the morning, we slept at 4:00 and we couldn't manage to get up early due to lack of sleep so we decided to attend mass in the afternoon, ah, yes, i borrowed a digicam from my couz, that digicam was ate bamba's gift to her, at first i felt envious, but i said that i could buy lots of those when i fly to UK... nyahahaha!  so there, my couz lent it to me and so i brought the cam home and i also bought some 3a batteries.. i tried to connect it to our comp, but it said that it wasn't compatible, i didn't insist to install it, or else, the computer might run some errors and they will blame me again for that... so there, then in the afternoon, i felt sleepy, i tried to get some sleep but i can't.. a bit later, someone came, then, it was tierry and jhing, we chatted but not too long because we have to go to mass, they left and i told them to go back here later, but, they didn't.. i don't know why.. so there, and Harry Potter, chamber of secrets is being shown right now at HBO, Harry Potter, sorcerer's stone is shown on GMA too...  i'm re-reading HP3 now... i think we're going to the mall tomorrow and have some shopping! yipeeee! sana matuloy! we will also have some reservations for HP3 at greenbelt... or at G4.. i've got nothing more to say... that's it for my day... see yah again bukas! bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, this is for tues. and wed.'s post.. my papa's sick! and he has flu.. :( he was chilling last night.. well, the reason why i didn't update yesterday was because i have nothing to blabber about! i just stayed at home and did nothing... my usual stuff.. then, this wednesday, joana slept upstairs again, with me, of course, then, i woke up at 4 in the morning, joana was coughing and i found out that she had fever.. we went downstairs and found out that my parents were also awake.. good thing, so that they can attend to joana... i think, she's nahawa to my papa.... :( so, we have 2 sick patients here at home, i hope that i would be able to resist this viruses roaming around! i wasn't able to sleep until 6:00 am.. then i woke up at 1:00.. mama went to makati to buy a wedding present for a friend.. i just took care of joana the whole day coz she has high fever... i just hope they get well soon.. i'm supposed to go to the parlor today to have my hair done.. i want to trim it and give it a nice cut.. i'm thinking of having a hair relax, coz my last relax was 3 months ago.. but, i think i'll be having it on the next days.. before classes start.. i'm really sad that my summer vacation is about to end in 4 days.. :( i miss my classmates, i called arvie and chatted for her for about 2 hrs yesterday.. i miss them all... :( i'm really getting nervous about going to a new school and coping up with new classmates and making friends... i just hope it all goes well... my classmates are smart and witty... god, i must really strive... right now, i'm memorizing the periodic table again coz it's like blown off in my memory.. i'm getting crazy about this! please! so, i jut don't wanna be pressured, but i really promise to focus on my studies! i swear! so, i dunno when will i be able to return again here... so, bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omigod! i haven't been here for three days.. i think, this marks the start of my.. uhmm, anguish?? heheheh.. no, agony.. i haven't updated you guys about the happenings last monday and the orientation stuff... okay, i'll just sum it up in this post.. well, from this day on, i think, i won't be able to update daily.. :( my mom, has forbidden me to log on to the net, if i don't have serious stuff to do.. like, i would just log on if i would research on something.. gosh?!! so, i think, i'll be updating this blog, weekly.. but, that's better than not updating at all, isn't it?? so, let me tell you about the orientation...   the night before the orientation, i just couldn't sleep.. i dunno why, am i excited, anxious, worried! waaah! so, i went to bed at 10:30 and was able to sleep at 2:00! what the?! so, that's it, i woke up at 6:15 coz the orientation starts at 8.. then, when we arrived there, we registered, the students were so friendly and accommodating... they were also so polite.. so, at around 8:30, we were transferred to another building, the kalayaan building.. so the orientation started at 9:00... i saw jezrelle and she seated right beside me since we don't know anybody yet.. then, the orientation began, there was so much talking, explanations and all.. then a classmate entered, same with her parents.. i think they're arabians.. gee! then, there was one cute guy, named arvin who really looked like vaness wu of f4! i mean, god! waaaah! so, how did i know his name, well, we had name tags... the orientation was divided into two, first part was with the parents then the bonding time with your new classmates.. so, on the first part, they explained the grading system.. gosh, their passing score is 60% of the items! i mean, if you have a 10 item quiz, and you get a score of 5, you fail! duh! the reason behind this is because they have the finest students "DAW".. what the?!.. whatever! and then, they are super strict when it comes to absences and lates.. 2 lates is equivalent to 1 absence, and if you had 3 absences, you are "kicked-out", they don't want to use the term kick-out! they said that they'll just help you find another school.. i mean, they're not so RUDE aren't they?!!? so there, the first part ended, and we had a lunch break, the next time we return there, the second part of the orientation begins, that's the bondig time with your classmates... errr...  so, on the elevator, my mom, chatted with another parent and we have met their daughter, "ICE" was her name, she was friendly and pretty, she looked like Rachelle samson and is Arvie-like in her attitudes... hehehhe.. so, we bought lunch at Tropical, but didn't eat it.. i dunno why i didn't like to eat my lunch.. then, mama went home and left me there.. we went back to the building with the lunch that we haven't eaten, well, as for me, i just bought fries and burger.. jez and ice were with me.. they haven't eaten their lunch too..so, the peer councilor, ("peer councilors" - n , they are a member of an org. in school which aids students in their problems and stuff like that; they host the orientation.) told us to go inside the room coz the second part will begin shortly.. we were divided into teams, unfortunately, either one of them is my teammate... i'm in the white team, je is in the blue team, ice is in the yellow team and the other one is the red team... so, at first, we had two peer councilors per team.. we must think of a cheer for our group.. well, first, we introduced ourselves to our team members... the cheer we came up with was so nonsense coz my teammates were still shy.. the cheer goes something like this:  "Ito ang cheer ng team namin, yan ang cheer ng team ninyo, get's nio na? hindi pa.. gooooo... TEAM WHITE!"  err.. was that a cheer?! hehehe.. then we had games like charade, tao, bahay, bagyo, etc.. the tao, bahay, bagyo was like, open-the-basket... well, i had fun, the the peer councilor which is the host, was so hilarious, she seemed to work in a comedy bar! she's great! bentang-benta mga jokes nya sakin!! as in, then, we toured the whole place and the hospital as well, they showed us some VIP rooms where elite people are admitted like artists like Vandolf's case... it was so fun... then, we went home, me and ic were magkasabay, she even accompanied me to the terminal.. then, that's it, i went home.... that was for my monday... hehehe! i hope you enjoyed! bye! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi! i'm back, as promised.. this post is for today's update.. well, today, i woke up at seven.. then i went back to sleep at 8:30 and woke up again at 1:30! hahahaha! so sarap to sleep specially during cold rainy days! so there, my parents are not around, they are in a seminar for the "priest-adopting-family" thing.. so i stayed here at home with joana the whole day watching tv.. mama arrived at around 6:30.. then, i logged on to the internet... we had dinner afterwards.. then i called gladys to ask her some details about the orientation happening tomorrow! i'm really getting nervous about that stuff! i'll be meeting my classmates and teachers! i just hope they are good and friendly.. so, i'll just update tomorrow about the orientation... wish me luck! i have to sleep early today or else, my mom will start nagging again! oh no! hehehehe.. so that's it! my bro's bugging me and i'm annoyed! i'm outta here! bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi! sorry, i wasn't able to update yesterday coz i was so busy... this post is for yesterday.. so, yesterday, my mom was preparing foods for an affair to be held on the roofdeck of our church... it was a dinner for a cause.. they are soliciting money for a legionary who has a blood disease... i think.. i really dont know.. so there.. she prepared sandwiches, fried chix... her friends came over to help her to prepare... so, they said that we should attend the anticipated mass held before the affair... good thing my couz was there so i wasn't bored, we decided to watch the affair and go home at 9 to watch SCQ... heheheh.. my crush was there.. yipeee. but i was so hungry, so i can't wait for the food to be served, i went downstairs to buy a clubhouse sandwich and that was my dinner.. so at around 9, me and my couz went to my grandma's house to watch SCQ there, i told my parents that i'll be back at the affair after SCQ... so there, we watched there, then after 30 minutes, my aunt called and told us to go to their house and watch SCQ there and my parents will just drop by there to pick me up.. i was so aliw at sandara's performance, she looked stupid with the beads hanging on her hair... joross was good in breakdancing... and hero was sooo... cute! grabe! so there, then mama txted me that they already went home... i decided to go home before the announcement.. my parents arrived just minutes after me.. then, the winner was announced.. HERO!!! yipeeee.. so there, i went upstairs with joana and fell asleep..
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omigod!!! my first week in college is done!! i'm so very much tired! did you know that, before the first day, i catched flu too! i mean, i was chilling because of fever for 2 consecutive days, and now woofing with cough, i was so humiliated everytime i'll cough inside the classroom, imagine, it's so quiet then here i go, coughing mightily there, breaking the silence! gosh! well, for my first week, i feel so tired! evertime i arrive here at home, i just want to lay to bed and sleep, anyways, i only meet my subject once a week..and, i've got good news, the dean's list in RTRMS-MMC is out, all pcsians are in there! i mean, they were great! really! i'm impressed! in my first meetings with my new profs, well, it was okay, all we did was to have an orientation about the building and the rules and regulations of the school, discuss the handbook etc.. others have also started their discussions..our lessons in philo and psycho were a bit boring... well, i dont want to generalize first, were just starting anyways.. and i have to buy lots of books for my subjects coz i will be needing it... i have spent more than 1,000.00 but they are not yet completed. i was able to meet new friends too, ice, kat, mae, iesa and sarah, of course, jezrelle was with me too... one of my classmates was the son of our dean, so, he was so popular, but he's friendly...we only had 7 boys in the class, one looked like sir rod magalona, but he's quite weird, although he was cute! next week, i'm loaded with tons of quizzes and asignments, but i'll be managing it.. so, that's my update for now, and yes! i just got my hair relaxed! but, it's not very obvious now, one week has passed since i went to the parlor.. but my hair's shorter.. so, i got to go, i haven't eaten breakfast and i got tons of things to do! essays, research experiment papers! i'm dying! hehehehe! ayt!? i gotta go! or else, mom's nagging will start again, i'm typing really fast now, so, i'm outta here! bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omigod! good Lord help me puhleese! i need to get through college.. it's so fucking hard.. i mean, quizzes everyday, in every subject.. whew! long boring, sleepy psycho classes... terror and callous chem-lab teacher... oh yah! i can do it..  oh, so before i could post every protest of my life in here, i would just like to update you about what happened to my so.... happy, enjoyable, and stress-free life! argh!  uhmm, last weekend, ervin went back home, he txted me that he would drop by the house and have a photocopy of the S-V agreement coz they'll be needing it for English... so he went here at around 7 pm, he just attended mass, and we chatted, we also went to julius' place coz the xerox machines were not working here... he went home at around 9 pm.. well, i'm missing my friends.. sadly, we can't have fun with all these damned assignements, quizzes and annoying things around..  lets go to my RTRMS-MMC life.. i've had more friends, i mean i got to know everyone in the room now.. but i really LOATHED one of my classmates, well, tell yah bout that later..i had classmates who are weirdos! one looks like sir magalona, but roy b.-in attitude??!?! one looked like vaness, and the other one's the son of our dean! i mean.. OMIGOD! so... uhmm, everyday we got quizzes and assignments.. the P.E. teacher was great and looked like shan cai's mom in MG... hahaha.. PMSD and English classes who had the same teacher were my most fave subjects of all! She was so great... and my Philo. of man subj.. gee, i mean, the teacher was unpredictable and quite Banlag! hahaha, i thought that he was looking at the girl behind me, but then, it was my seatmate he was looking at! Psycho class is my most boring class, but the teacher's kind... i mean, the minute he enters the room, i can suddenly fall asleep! waaaah! My Chem-lecture teacher was so great, you wouldn't really hesitate to ask questions, she was so accommodating... unfortunately, my chem-lab teacher was her opposite, we had this assignment/experiment and she would criticize all our answers.. argh! but, her quizzes are quite easy though... heheheh! my filipino teacher was fine... and my Algebra teacher was great!  Galing magturo! super!  i love his way of teaching! well, that's all about my subjects.. well, they were so kind that they gave tons of assignment and of course, quizzes!  let me now tell you about my most LOATHED classmate... he (a boy, obviously) came from Rizal High (errr.. =).. ) well, i'm not mentioning his damned name for heaven's sake..so, at first i thought he was accommodating, respectful(to girls) and all that, i even voted him to be a member of the Peer group... but he's not handsome(frankly).. i'm telling you right now that he's not, so you won't link him to me.. i mean yuckerz! hahaha! he looks like blakdyak but the fatter version... nyehehehe.. so, here's the story:  it's our english class and we were grouped into 5 groups, he was my groupmate, same with jezrelle and mark a.s. (sir rod look-a-like) and we were given acetate and markers and we were assigned to present the communication process.. then he was so proud of his idea and he said:  "Ako, may idea, ganito, so, yung sender, tapos may medium tapos may channel, then yung receiver, taps ulit lang ulit yung process pag nag-reply na yung receiver.."  so, i thought, okay, then suddenly i remembered that the last part of the communication process was the feedback.. i learned that i speechpower of course! hahah! so i said:  "alam ko, sa dulo may feedback, yung sagutan, parang interaction na... yun ang alam ko..yun kasi napag-aralan ko sa speechpower.."  jezrelle agreed with me, then i was shocked when he said:  ah, hindi! tama yan, yan ang tama, basta walang mali dyan, eksakto na yan... wla nang idadagdag dyan.. tama yan!"  i was like.. F*ck! whatever you say.. "WISE BOY" !?!?! duh... so, when we presented, the teacher old us:  "there's no medium talaga in the process, what we have are the channels but the MOST IMPORTANT thing you LACK is the FEEDBACK..."  i was like.. "Have you heard that dumbass?! she said, we lack the FEEDBACK! the thing that i was trying to suggest to you, moron! so, after that, we had another activity, the role-playing part.. we were assigned to perform interpersonal communication (2 persons involved) so, once again, he was too excited of his so "great" idea he said:  "ganito, may isang grupo, tapos wla lang silang ginagawa.. taps kunyari ako, lalapit ako sa isang tao sa grupong yun tapos, may tatanong ako sa kanya, apos kunyari di ko magugustuhan yung sagot nya, tapos lilipat ako sa iba naman.."  wow! that's so "stupid of you", i thought... so, what,  nakatanga lang kaming lahat sayo at iintayin ka namin na lapitan kami!?! ano kami robot, pag kinalabit, tsaka gagalaw?!  duh? so i suggested another situation, the opening of classes... he looked like he didn't like suggestions and was insisting on his "brilliant" idea.. o was so fed up and so i came to the teacher and asked her if that idea was ok.. she said no, it was wrong and she even suggested us the right thing to do, like to have a survey... when i said o my groupmates that it's better to have a survey/interview thing, he said:  "kaya di tayo maayos eh, pabago-bago kayo, ang gulo gulo!"  i mean, if he doesn't like to be in the group, well, he might as well leave, anyways, nobody needs him.. so my plan was accepted and we proceeded and he had no choice.. hahaha! the last activity was the Guesstures/charade.. he again volunteered himself to be the group's representative, so there, we only got 14 pints because of his  pag-iinarte, pagpapacute at kabagalan!  i loath him! really! he's one big  E.P.A.L.!!! ... that's it... this post is so long, but then, i'm happy that i've shared it with you guys... i hope he gets to read this.. hahahaha! and yes, we're having overnight swimming tom. gee, i'm excited, but i have to bring my books with me noh! heehehe! so, there, bye and God Bless y'all! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaha, i have a pahabol, my papa's birthday is coming really soon, it's on JULY 1... so after classes, i decided to drop by National Bookstore to buy him a gift, coz i had money anyway. my grandma gave me 500.00 for being studious daw.. hahaha. it was father's day then, and they had a little affair at my grandma's house, i opted not to go coz i have to study and do my homeworks, to my surprise, when my parents got back, they handed me a 500 peso bill, my lola gave it to me, sort of a reward. well.....  so, yah, let's get back, i bought a Parker pen for my father, it was silver in color and cost 380+, and i also bought the refill which cost 85+, and i got it gift-wrapped in a very expensive looking way, so i spent 500+ just for my gift, well, i don't have any hesitations at all, he's my father and that gift would never amount to the sacrifices and things he has done for us... well, just thought of sharing it with you guys... so, Advance Happy birthday papa.. love yah.. gotta go, got work to do.. bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whoaaaaa! halu guys! it's tuesday and dismissal is early for today, i felt the urge to log on to the net.. though there are assignments and quizzes for tom., what's new about that anyway?!  let's talk about our swimming, which was so late by the way, summer's gone, but on second thought, it was much better to have outings coz nobody's there on the place, just us.. imagine?! privacy galore!!! so, we went to palm island chuva... i can't remember exactly the name, but it was nice, we had 4 pools, own house, tv, aircon, ref, rooms, everything! i wasn't sunburned or anything because we started swimming at 5:30 pm... and the water didn't have much chlorine.. i was so tired when we got home.. though i had tons of work to do, i opted to sleep.. hahaha. how responsible?! but, i managed to complete all of them the next day though.  yahahaha.. my RTRMS-MMC life? well, we had P.E. on mondays, yup, and of course, we had physical fitness test.. i'm so happy, i'm so proud because i had done 17 dreaded curl-ups.. yipee.. hahaha. which, in turn got my lower abdominal muscles hurting and same with my back and arms.. hahaha... next class was PMSD, we were actually assigned to draw a road map leading to your ultimate goal. when it was collected and checked (coz it was an assignment), to my surprise, my name got called and the teacher said that i did it very creatively and artistically.. i mean, me?! who only knows how to draw human sticks?! hahaha. i was called same with arvin and mark a.s.(sir rod look-a-like), because of our very nice work(daw), we were chosen to explain out work to the class.. i was shaking. hahaha. philo classes followed and the quiz was so damn hard! next is psycho, quizzes are fine, but a bit confusing.. of course, nothing's new, same old boring topics.. want updates about my most LOATHED classmate?!... well....  hahaha! how fast Karma comes back.. basically, after our P.E. class, most of us change clothes, this guy, i think didn't bring any clothes, but when classes resumed, he was wearing our school uniform, to my surprise, he was the only one wearing the uniform, coz we haven't got our new uniforms yet..and his uniform, in fact, HAS PENCIL DRAWINGS AND LININGS AT THE BACK!  sa sobrang excited, bsta na lang ata pinick-up at isinuot, baka may tailor's chalk pa yan..  well, i was making fun of him in my thoughts all day, hahahaaha. i enjoyed, by the way. and today, well, he was the apple of the eye of our chem-lecture teacher, he was, i think 10 times called, he was asked:   "Mr. --------, did you understand the lesson?" , so i thought, he was maybe a slow learner or something to be called too many times, but, the reason why is because he was not listening and the last time he was called the teacher got angry and made him sit in front of the class.. hahaha, that's what we call... KARMA! yah,yah, enough, i might receive karma next.. :D, well, i wish him good luck because life will be miserable for him now that i have come his way.. nyahahaha! well, that's it for today, i still have to do our Filipino assignment and study for the quiz... agrh! bye, God bless yah!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMIGOD!! it's been a lifetime since i last updated my beloved blog, well, i know you've been checking my blog every now and then but there are no updates, wondrin' why?! uhmmmm... yah know it na! hehehe.. well.. i'm learning to cope with school works and stress right now, SLEEP is the first thing i crave! gosh! the whole week, i would be studying by the time that i would arrive here at home then i would wake up very early around 2:00 a.m to review again! imagine,i'm not killing myself, so don't yah worry..   well, my efforts really pay off! my GOD!I always get the highest score in Chemistry hahaha, we just had a Quiz today,i got a perfect score while 3/4 of the class failed.. Thank God and Thanks to ma'am Munsod! i also was commended by my psycho prof because i had written a beautiful piece about ourreport, he asked me to read it in front of the class... :).. i don't wanna boast, but i'm just so happy about how college life really runs well for me..   ah and yes, one more reason why i wasn't able to update my blog coz recently our guest priest has arrived, but he went home na.. i was nearly into tears when he left.. he's Fr. Edwin Fontanilla from Vigan, he's just 31 but looks old though, because he's the spiritual director of a seminary there..(bongga!) he was so into kids, he loves kids so much! that's why he and joana got along well, joana even cried when he left.. i had this assignment in english to interview a professional, i haven't got anybody to interview, coincidentally, mama said that i would rather interview Fr. Edwin rather than papa coz parents would be so common... the next day, we were shocked that we would relay in class about our interview coz our topic was about speech and stuff.. when it was my turn, i really was feeling nervous.. but, it got off my nerves afterwards... i was again commended by my teacher and said  "That was nice Ms. Nacional.."  considering that our teacher was a Mormon.. not a catholic, but i told them stories of a priest.. God is sooo GREAT!   so, the day came that Fr. Edwin had to leave the house..it was Saturday when the Host family would be attending the Mass and concert at the World Trade Center.. i was deciding on not to come coz we had a practice, but i opted to go, since it was the last time i'd be seeing Fr. Edwin, i knew it would take a very long time before i would be able to see him again... there was a part of the mass that i really liked, btw, Archbishop Rosales presided the mass, and all of the 4,000 priest were wearing their 'sutanas', i have seen one of the most beautiful sights of my life, i can't really describe it, but it was dark all over, then all priests were holding lighted candles... OMG! it was so awesome to see that.. then the concert followed, Agot isidro was there and even Robin Padilla me and Joana even got to take solo shots with Robin and Agot was actually holding joana's hand! hahahaha! Robin was soo handsome! geee.. we also took pictures of ourselves with moslem children beside us.. they were cute in their clothes...  well, it had been a long tiring week again.. but,i'm improving, as what i have promised in highschool, "ihahataw ko na sa college"  due to the scam that happened, i used it as my inspiration.. that's why i'm getting all these high grades, it's the best feeling ever, to be admired by your classmates.. i'm in "HATAW" mode right now.. so, you guys, galingan nyo! i know you could do better than that! show them your best and show them that they're ain't no good enough to beat yah! that's the spirit! and yes, i would like to congartulate chris for acquiring a new cellphone,remember, when God closes a door, he opens a window! i miss yah all! that's it guys! byeeee! :p
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hi there you guys... i'm back again.. it seems like i've been updating my blog irregularly... honestly, i don't really have that much time as you all know.. i really miss updating my blog and i'm so fascinated and surprised about the new look blogger has again... it has now colors and uploads of pictures... i dunno if it works, i guess i have to see for myself...     &nbsp;   You're wondrin' about my title aren't you? Well, I have told almost everyone about it.. My mom has been rushed to the hospital last thursday... Actually this is what happened...      &nbsp;   "Rush to the Hospital..."      &nbsp;   Last Thursday... Me and Ezra(my partner in Chem. Lab)are planning to buy the materials needed for our chem lab-art project.. but first, i must fix the xerox copy of our philo. report&nbsp;that&nbsp;i have to give to my classmates as their reviewer..&nbsp; i finished distributing it at around 11:30... i was so hungry and i told Ezra that i think, we should go and eat at Glorietta.. D.A. was also with us... so off we went to Carolina's... Only a few minutes after we have entered.. my Phone rang.. it was my mother.. she told me:  "Anak, umuwi kna kaagad pagkatapos nyong bumili... Sumasakit na naman ang tiyan ko..."  Upon hearing that, i really rushed outside of Carolina's.. i told them.. maybe, we could buy some other time because my mom's sick... Ezra and D.A. understood so i rushed outside for a taxi.. Fortunately i found one immediately... on my way going home, i had mixed emotions.. i really feel like breaking down... i remembered, also this summer 2004, we rushed mama to the hospital due to her ulcer, he almost fainted here at home and she couldn't breath, good thing papa was around, we rushed her at around&nbsp;1:30 a.m.. i was so scared at that time.. now, everything's about to repeat, and who knows, i might have been more worse?&nbsp;As the taxi was fast approaching The Fort, i txted mama and told her that she should prepared herself and the things we needed to bring because i'll be rushing her to the hospital... mama never calls if she isn't really feeling too much pain.. i know her..  kung kaya nyang tiisin ang sakit, titiisin nya...  that's why i really rushed home.. when i arrived home, mama was waiting, i told the taxi to wait for a while coz we'll be going back at makati med... im a great big PANIKERA... for all you know.. mama was in excruciating pain while we're on our way to the hospital..     &nbsp;   when we reached the emergency, my heart was thumping so loud and fast... mama was placed in a wheelchair because she can hardly walk... while i, was interviewed by the nurse there... mama was rushed inside.. we separated.. what goes on my mind at that moment is: Are the doctors attending to her? Is she alright? Is the pain still there? What's happening?... The thing that added more pressure on me is that Papa is not around.. He's in Bataan for an operation there and he'll be going home in 3 days time pa... We were assigned at bed 7.. the last bed at the emergency.. the doctor immediately injected her a large amount of pain reliever.. i thought it would make her feel alright.. but no... she still cries for pain.. i know it was very painful.. she was moaning and calling out for my name in a very weak voice... i really don't wanna see my mama in that condition.. i guess no one does.. the pain she's sufferring is like stabbing me deeply..one by one.. every now and then, she would fall asleep, i thought she'd be fine coz she won't feel the pain when she's asleep, but after 10-15 mins.. she'd wake up.. we'll caht for about 5 mins or so, looking fine, but then all of a sudden, she&nbsp;suffers this excruciating pain again.. my heart melts... but i was not crying.. i must be strong.. i'm all alone..    we went back and forth to the x-ray station.. the doctors went also back and forth for her blood samples... i called up papa at bataan using my mama's phone and told him to go home.. he knew that mama was rushed to the hospital because mama txted him too.. papa txted one of our family friends, trita winnie to come to th hospital to look over us... she didn't stay too long, but thank God, she bought food from max's..remember, i was really really hungry.. that was around 5:00 p.m ...my last meal was at around 5:30 a.m!! then finally, the result came...the doctor said, she was diagnosed to have a stone in the tube of her urinary bladder that's why she find it difficult to urinate.. i was like.. "My Lord.. what i this?" then, the doctor asked if she wanted to be admited, she said yes..     &nbsp;   Papa arrived at around 7:30... i went home at around 8:30 to fix the things needed in the hospital...    joana, lola and kuya eldie came with me back to the hospital.. mama was admitted at room 536, 5th flr. we had a private room.. we arrived at the hospital at around 9:45 and went home at 12.. next morning, i'm planning to take papa's place and stay with mama at the hospital at noon... i found myself crying very hard, when i was txting all my friends to pray for my mom's fastrecovery and healing.. they replied and told me that they will... my emotions can't be held back.. i cried.     &nbsp;   At the hospital, joana came with me and same with one of my aunts.. we took care of mama, i even bought all my books there.. thinking of studying at night... but i wasn't able to because visitors flooded, at day and even at night.. tierry, ervin, laurice, and julius visited on the second night.. they arrived at 10:00 pm and went home at around 1:00.. i missed my buddies a lot, and we were all so noisy, sharing stories and chismis of our own... mama was happy to see them.. ervin and julius even bought 3 boxes of buko pie for her.. friends and relatives also visited my mom... luckily, we were    released on saturday, although the stone is not yet removed, the doctor gave her medications, hoping that she would be able to urinate the stone... we stayed in the hospital for 3 days.. and we payed for 30,000.00. the nurses were great and the services they render is really excellent...     &nbsp;   yah.. we went home, saturday afternoon.. all the time that we're in the hospital,&nbsp;all i did was to pray the rosary and take care of my mom.. i didn't care for quizzes or anything else.. just my mom.. then life ran normal again, although, there are times that pain strikes, but she says it's tolerable... i hope and pray that the stone be removed as soon as possible, mama and papa are going back to MMC after 15 days to check mama's condition.. haaaaaaay... that's it... i really dunno what i'm feeling right now... wehehehe.. i think i'm in ****.... yeeeheeee! hahaha.. i'm happy that's it.. i just hope you'll continue praying for my mom.. thanks guys.. and GODBLESS!    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>