<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm, Joanne just blocked me today. Lolz, can't believe it manz, I didn't shout or curse or swear at all when I was so worried over Merrill, Vernon and my bike and here is Joanne, calling me a senseless creature because I hit her accidentally. Well, it all happened today when Frederick wanted to squeeze my hand again, so being the sporting guy I am, I agreed. Hahaz, then as I was about to lose, I spotted my water bottle on the floor (Clumsy Alvin) and used that as an excuse to quit the squeeze(?!?!) But Frederick didn't want to let go so I had to pull my hand out. When I did that, I accidentally hit Joanne. Well, that stupid girl just stared at me as I returned to my seat. As if she was trying to give me a look of disgust. Hmmm, can't really stand that. I'd rather fight than continue taking it. So I can only just curse her silently.   Hahaz, I'm proud that i'm such a better person than her aniwaez. Still, can't get arrogant I guess. Yea Clara, Yea Carrie, I think i'm better than you. -Deleted- and stop discussing about me like i'm some sorta poor guinea pig. I hate it when people do that. I think i'll kill the next person who does that. People at school don't know me like people outside. Clara actually thinks i'm bad with adults? That's such a gross error. Then and again, no one really knows me. The school ppl see my bad side, the outside people see my good side but it's the strangers who I really confess my real self to. Hahaz, I don't claim to have that much experience, but let's just say that I have an interesting sexual history starting from 4 or 5. Furthurmore, I mix around with more people than they(Carrie and Clara) know. Carrie mixes with DJs, I mix with family counsellors. Bleahz, shouldn't have said that but i'll leave them. Just annoyed that they think i'm a total idiot. Heard Sharon and Ting Yan diss Byron's sister today.. "She's an airport strip". Hmmmm, Clara? Just wondering what is she.. Enemy or friend? I strongly believe in the reasoning that there are no grey areas in life. Clara is an enemy. 'cos she still has all these negative impressions of me even though she still talks to me. But that's only because she is depressed or something.  Dunno, I know i've had a bad reputation but i'm not going to let that get me down. I'll just kill anyone who gets in my way. Lolz, guess that's why i'm not good at project work, speakin of which IPW is totally screwed. But you know what? I'm digging my heels in. Everyone always wants me to be leader to be the scrapegoat. Enough! I shall decimate and annihilate all of YOU!!  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp; Manz, today was one screwed up day. Don't think I came home the same manz. Left the house at 7.20 which is like, uber late and true enough, I only made it halfway across the parade ground before I was grounded. Good thing Mrs. Ng didn't drag me to TAF club though. Yea, woke up&nbsp;with 5minutes&nbsp;to 7 and slept at 2am last night.  So blame me.  Aniwaez, listening to Revolution from the album Revolution by MIKE. Hahaz, bet you thought I was gonna say Revolution didn't ya? Lolz so aniwaex, it's kinda pumped up music with lots of screaming and stuff so i'm pumped up myself too, lolz. Bleahz, Yu Yu actually started getting heated up with me last night, lolz, like talking in one of those tones before you turn hysterical, yea.. Hahaz, she's pretty stressed, poor thing.. Wish I could help her the way she helped me. Yeapz. Today was wacked and whacked from end-to-end or rather, morning-to-evening since my dayu ended at about 6. Yea, slept half the time during school so nvm. Ken tried to.. well nvm but I jus felt kinda pissed so I was like "stfu!" hahaz, pronounced as stu-fu.&nbsp;Lessons weren't great but I lived. They seemed surprisingly shorter than usual!  Hmmm, what sucked is that I did the wrong comprehension, hiaz.. that's what you get for doing your homework at 11pm. Actually, I got around to it at 1am but wth. Lolz, Dickson got the same thing too. So aniwaez, I had my CGH appointment so I got to skip the English Common Test and go straight home. However, because of the installation of the sinks and stuff, the water was cut off( I&nbsp;hate it when that happens) so I gathered some clothes and headed to CGH. Damned, couldn't even make some instant noodles! Hahaz, acted kinda cool I guess, felt totally rebellious against my school uniform with my shoes and Cd player. Oh and that red bag too!&nbsp;The therapy was wierd, like the therapist hated me or something, lolz. 'Cos she just kept assigning me exercises&nbsp;as if she wanted to keep me busy so that she could attend to other patients. Haha but I guess it's okay, since&nbsp;I haven't reached the critical stage yet. Some wierd exercises included a funny machine with pedals that u moved with your hand,&nbsp;lying on a ball while lifting 1kg weights, doing exercises with a kind of&nbsp;rubber thing that's like a ballon, doing that same thing with weights and a pulley and lastly, doing some sorta exercises on this machine that's a cross between a pull up bar and one of those bars&nbsp;that have two horizontal poles side-by-side. Yea, wierd!! But what's wierder is that I decided to give Vernon the CD when I got back? Alot&nbsp;of&nbsp;miscommunication between his maid, grandma, him and me. Lolz, it was kinda irritating but funny all the same.&nbsp;Damned,&nbsp;Vernon made me this uber-chio girl who looked so O.o lala~. Haiz, speakin of which I accidentally swore using the F word when I was attempting to teach Ian that your head can actually be *******. Bleahz, why must I ALWAYS be right? Haha, dammit though, couldn't stop thinking dirty&nbsp;thoughts.. Must stop it sialz!   Okay okay, what's wierd later is&nbsp;that I actually&nbsp;MET CHARIS!?! Yea, I decided to give myself a treat to mashed potato at 7-11 and I actually met her and her mum? The cashier seems to know her pretty well and was talking to her about devloping this film that she was gonna put inside one of those photo boxes where they'll deliver the photos to your house. Her mum didn't seem to see me though, despite everything happening nearby. So, yea.. said hi and stuff, sad though.. we're no longer growing apart. We ARE apart. So, yea.. maybe it's God or something? Maybe he's trying to get me back in but I dunno, don't think I know her anymore. Oh and that Pepsi bottle in my yellow bicycle basket is finally gone, lolz. Although I have this nagging feeling that my Dad threw it away.   As a final note, my crystal growing is not doing too well, Mr. Lo doesn't want to add chromium but I guess that I gotta abide. Too lazy... or should I? Hahaz, nothing! Yea, aniwaez, it's reacting with the solution to form this milk-white thread like substance that's floating around. Kinda yucky! The crystal is growing layer over layer so we have crystals within crystals. But one end is horribly shaped. Yucks to look at! Doubt we can win this year.. 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wierd.. I dunno why but I feel like i'm in this golden age, the greatest time of my Secondary School life. However, elsewhere people seem to be doing horribly? Like NPCC is going to strike, NCC might be disbanded, Carrie's suspended and yadda yadda.. Hahaz, nahz.. can't be.. I'm sure not everyone is going through a bad time in their lives!
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh, some may call me wierd, some may call me different and some just say lame or extra. However, myself I call me unconventional. I often wonder, whether other people have see deep into Life as it is. Not just what we have around us, but the depths, where misery and poverty reign. Have you ever met an orphan? Or someone from a broken family? These days, we know more and more people who have had divorces and that's becoming common. However, to me... What I treasure most is a deep insight into the deepest, darkest of a human soul.. It's meaningful I guess and impacting too. I guess that's why some people are counselors and psychiatrist. The reason is because, when you fix a human, his life, like a machine, you have to take him apart, check everything over and repair or replace or introduce new parts. That's when you really gain an insight into life.  &nbsp;  Haha, Shuling&nbsp;says that I like extreme stuff... I dunno about that but i'd love to do paintballing and rockclimbing if&nbsp;I could. I don't really fancy musical stuff, but I&nbsp;like outdoor activities. Not sport, outdoor. You get to work hard but you don't need to compete, lolz.. I mean, all sports are competitive after all. Gymnast, Soccer, Rugby, I can't think of any which&nbsp;doesn't have the main objective of scoring more points than the other.&nbsp;Figure skating, even swimming!!&nbsp;Although often, outdoor activities and sport cross into each other, I still like outdoor activities. Lolz, or do I? Hmmm, not sure but i'd like my belief to be challenged. Speaking of which, I read an interesting 1939 book in the V.Hive&nbsp;furniture store my mother went to today. It was one of those silly gibberish books&nbsp;you find in the bookshelves.. This&nbsp;one talked about God though.. very scary!!! Even as I read it, I felt my beliefs being changed and shaped...&nbsp;The author was talking about Genesis, the creation of life, the creation of God. It was very scary&nbsp;as&nbsp;I realised I was being changed as I read one word after the other... He said that&nbsp;in the beginning, there was light and darkness. Within the light was thought and will and&nbsp;after eons, thought and&nbsp;will  grew closer and light grew brighter. Slowly, as they finally became united,&nbsp;light spread out everywhere and&nbsp;covered darkness. And they said thought-will was God. And that God created 12 beings. Then, one day he decided to make other beings and so he made the planets. Then, he chose one, Earth&nbsp;or rather, he knew Earth would be able to support&nbsp;life. So he sent those 12 beings there. They helped get ready the Earth and waited and waited.. then they grew impatient and asked why God was tarrying. Then. God said.. Those who have been impatient, come back because I do not want you to lead the new people. But they refused and tried to figure out life. God sent another warning. They did not listen, finally,&nbsp;when God said&nbsp;something about Darkness being limited, they decided to create life out of not&nbsp;Light, but Darkness. And so this Darkness came out and corrupted them and changed the entire planet.  Haiyo, you read already... Do you&nbsp;feel like something's changing? I dunno, but as I read all this over again, I feel it sinking in. Haiyo, no no no!! Must get it out!! Scary stuff man&nbsp;and it's just so addictive..&nbsp;make me want to read more but must resist. Thankfully my mum came by then. Hahaz, speaking of resisting, I managed to resist temptation today! Yea~!! Hahax, but cannot&nbsp;celebrate too soon because I know i'm still vulnerable.. Gtg back to my Chem Webquest now, wish me luck~!!&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Odd day huh? My parents are out to a wake now. But I just held the wake of two of my friends inside. Goodbye Byron and Charis. Maybe, one day, come judgement day you will be resurrected. But until then, I do not know you anymore.  &nbsp;  It's always hard for me to say goodbye, but our friendship has become like a dead branch and I need to cut it off.   
    
</post>



</Blog>