<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        las vegas   if the gods had not created vegas, what kind of person would i be?  vegas is my place of indulgement and fantasy.  i could do whatever i want in vegas.  i could sit at a buffet for three hours and keep eating.  i can gamble until i lose all my money.  i can drink alcohol for breakfast and not feel bad.  having said that, i am off to vegas bitches.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this bit of a dry spell is killing me.  so today i will be going to mexico and bringing home a wife.  i will lock her in my closet and only bring her out when my needs must be fulfilled.    okay, so maybe this is my fault.  i have been too lazy to drive anywhere which means i have not been going out and exposing myself to any one out there.  did you know that the present is the result of our past?  yeah i know, that statement is very logical.  but i have been thinking lately, i think i may have endangered my well-being by actually staying in a relationship for as long as I did.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       dear potential employers,  it has come to my attention that after many interviews with many companies, i cannot seem to find the perfect fit.  it's either you don't want to hire me because i don't match your ideal employee, or you don't offer me what i am worth and i turn and walk away, or i don't like your company, or you don't like me.  i have come to the conclusion that i will quit trying to find a perfect job and just never work again.  im going to become a hobo and blame it on the employers of america.  bastards.  see you in hell.    -ryan 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink bar's new friend  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the mail came early today.  have i ever told you i don't like getting the mail?  so i usually never make the trip to the mailbox.  that is left for the people i live with.  did i tell you i don't like to get the mail?  in all honesty, i'd rather receive mail in digital format.  it is quicker and has no waste whatsoever.  i really hate to get the mail.  all i receive are bills that i hate to pay and SPAM in paper format.  getting the mail sucks.  i went to the ER back in December.  i have no health insurance.  i thought they forgot to bill me.  i hate mail.  i received my bill today: $508.00.  that money goes to the nurse that took my temperature, the doctor who listened to my heart and lungs, and the 45 minute wait in the waiting room. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       since starting my own blogger, i have no clue what to write about.  i thought about current events, my daily grunts and rants, or maybe just about whatever was on my mind.  these are all great topics to write about, but whenever i want to post something, i go blank.  i don't know what to write about and when i do begin to type, it is so uninteresting, that i delete the whole thing.  dont worry, i'll get better at this...... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i cant believe kwame lost because of omarosa..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        pork rinds, alcohol, drunk neighbors, good times.   it all started at noon.  there is a knock at the door; it's sroy with a 30 pack of beer.  come 4 o'clock we have went through at least a 12 pack.  6 o'clock rolls around and the others begin to arrive.  6 beers later and I start drinking the crown.  come 9 o'clock the jungle juice arrives.  my neighbors come over and the older neighbor makes herself at home by turning into a raging lunatic.  she makes me fondle her 40 year boob old while i am trying to take a picture.  isn't there some kind of law against that?  mark does the most fantastic karaoke rendition i have ever seen in my entire life.  my mom went bonkers, she went papparazzi on him.  bruce decides to upchuck his burrito from earlier.  to top off the night, my mom hands out at least 10 bags of pork rinds.  the kids went nuts!  unusually fun backyard bbq.    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       calling off sick from work is one of the greatest pleasures in my life.  i relish in the fact that i dont have to do anything today.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       tomorrow will mark 26 years of uselessness.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink A rant and a rave: The wonderful agony of oral sex  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i wrote a sarcastic and not serious at-all "wanted ad" on craigslist.  now i am getting a ton of replies to it and i just had to share my post with everyone here.  looks like there are a lot of lonely hearts out there.  below is the ad i posted on craigslist.  New Girlfriend   -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Reply to: ryancasupanan@yahoo.com Date: 2004-05-27, 2:29PM PDT   I need a new girlfriend. I am trying to get my life back in order and the last time my life was in order was when I had a girlfriend.   Qualifications:  1. MUST BE A GIRL.  2. Must like to have sex.  3. Must act like a girl and dress like one.  4. Must be under 5'6".  5. Must have a personality.  6. Must have a job.  7. Must laugh at my jokes and funny faces.   Unqualified applicants need not apply. Being my girlfriend is contingent on our first meeting and how that fares.     this is in or around LA it's NOT ok to contact this poster with services or other commercial interests   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today i thought about the time when i was twenty two and i believed i had everything going right for me.  i had the dreamiest of dream girls.  i had a good job making good money.  i no longer lived at home.  i was going to school for my degree.  i was heading in the right direction i thought.    if you were to tell me four years ago that i'd be in a dead end situation at the age of 26, i would have laughed in your face and told you to fuck off.  that was my demeanor when i was that age.  confident and maybe even arrogant.  i thought i was on top of it all.    it seemed that over the last two years things started to tumble.  a domino effect is what they call it.  i quit my job, i lost my girlfriend, i moved back home, and now i am stuck in a shit hole of a job.    well i am not going to stand for it any longer.  i quit my job again and i am moving out again.  no need for a girlfriend though, plus i aint got no money to support the bitch anyway.  all apologies for the language, but bitches aint shit but hoes and tricks.    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        extremely upset   i made the mistake of co-signing for two different people.  the first time i ever did it, i got myself into a messy situation.  i vowed not to co-sign ever again.  years later i co-signed for a person who was special to me at the time.  co-sign mistake number 2.    it all happened in mid-2002.  this certain someone needed something and the only way to have it was for me to co-sign.  intuitively i knew this was a bad situation to get myself into; however, i gave in eventually because that's what suckers do: make bad decisions.  i fought it at first and it was a hard fought battle, but those puppy dog eyes are truly convincing.  everything i said to this certain someone about the consequences has come true.  now i have to live with it.  i am stuck in a legal situation with a collection company for MONEY I DIDN'T BORROW! i don't have enough to pay it off, so now what do i do?    i got screwed.  i got the bad end of the deal.  i got nothing out of this and two others gained something.  she has the last laugh, not i.    please people, never ever co-sign for other people.  it can turn into an aweful situation.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        corporate war   sad to know that this country is run by two-buddies backed by a corporation with more money than any of us will ever see.  our current vice president cheney is still collecting a compensation of over a million dollars from his old company halliburton.  for the un-informed, halliburton provides services to gas and oil companies.  halliburton also gets the rights (or at least is favored) to contracts in iraq.  one of the contracts is worth close to a billion dollars where they set up tent camps for our troops and are in charge of other logistical operations.    so are bush and cheney in this war to promote freedom and democracy in iraq?  or are there ulterior motives?  most probably the latter.    both bush and cheney come from an oil-rich background.  bush is from texas and has made ventures into the oil business and cheney was the chief executive officer of halliburton.  i wish i could elaborate more on the subject, but it would take me an extremely long time to research and write all of the details.  there are resources out there where you could learn about what's  really  going on.  i suggest you look it up.    our troops are getting killed because of greedy politicians and other high powered individuals.  please get out and vote this year and educate yourself on the backgrounds of our candidates.     
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "the west won the world not by the superiority of its ideas or values or religion but rather by its superiority in applying organized violence. westerners often forget this fact, non-westerners never do."  . samuel p. huntington . 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        i need a fax machine   if anyone is willing to donate or trade a working fax machine, i'd be most appreciative.  the fax machine doesn't even have to receive faxes, just send them.  i am willing to trade:  >two pairs of used socks >two AMC movie tickets >a fax machine that doesn't work at all >3 stamps  so if anyone is interested, please respond to this post.  thanks.    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    michelle and jane&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink I chased you for 12 years around the world, and I still can't find you  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       one of my newfound passions at the moment is taking pictures.  in the past, i never had any interest in taking pictures nor being in one.  now, i can't seem to take enough.  i need a camera for myself though.   the camera i currently use is not mine, and the one i bought a few years back was taken away to New York.  so if you could please paypal me some money at ryancasupanan@yahoo.com, i'll be most grateful.   advice for the day...never give your girlfriend a really expensive camera.  she might break up with you and take it with her.  on a better note, i went to the death cab for cutie show last night.  one of the most amazing shows i've seen; however, for the first 45 minutes, me and a friend could not see anything going on on stage.  that's what we get for being so short, it was not until we went up to the third tier that we were able to see the band.  towards the end of the set, my date leaned over and said she wanted to cry (she's never even heard of this band before, so that's how amazing this show was).  i've never wanted to cry  at a show, but the unity of this band combined with the captivating voice of ben gibbard, left me (along with many others) awestruck.     i don't want to mention any names, but I do want to thank you for such a great night.  if you read this, i hope you had a good time too.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
           death cab for cutie at the wiltern 5.21.04   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
            view of downtown los angeles off mulholland drive  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink | How To Build A Blog |   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       sorry i haven't posted anything in some time, but i haven't been in the mood, so too bad.  so what's the deal with people interested in watching the video of nick berg being decapitated? i received a few emails with a link to the video and not once did i even think of clicking that link.  someone being beheaded is not of entertainment value to me.  i know that some of you that have actually watched the video are traumatized with what you saw on that clip.    in other news...average gas prices around the U.S. have actually hit over the $2.00 mark.  so that means californians have been over the average for quite some time now.  well prepare for the worst ladies and gentlemen, its going to keep going up.   for those of you interested in knowing why, then keep reading, if not skip to the last paragraph.  as you should know, gas prices are controlled by a small but very powerful force.  these companies can control the price of gas because of the law of supply and demand (if you paid any attention in your economics class, then you know what that law means, if not, too bad).  regardless of supply, demand for gas/oil will always rise. this is because gas is used to power one of our most prized possessions: our cars.    some economic experts feel that these oil companies are holding back the supply of oil so the price will rise.  the oil companies say that they don't have enough refineries to produce the oil.  well, an oil refinery has not been built in california for more than 30 years.  in addition to that, the oil companies have shut down a few refineries and will be shutting one down in bakersfield in the near future.  so in addition to oil being a limited resource, we are limited to our refining capabilities.  smart move by the oil companies, but bad for us.  but it doesn't matter, because at the pace we are using oil, it will run out. imagine what we would be paying when there is only a small amount left.   so my friends, if the government decides to impose that 50 cent tax increase to gas, don't be afraid.  gas prices will continue to rise regardless.  the theory is that if we can't afford gas, we will look into alternatives.  hybrid, hydrogen/fuel cell, and electric.  when the demand increases for these alternative sources,  the car manufacturers will have to put more resources into research and development for these new vehicles.  that means more choices for the consumer.    one day oil will run out and we'll be kicking ourselves in the ass. if we can supress our use of it and increase its longevity, then i'm all game.  however, it is tough for us as consumers to purchase vehicles such as the prius or the honda civic hybrid.  like i said before, once our attraction towards alternative sources grow, so will the choices of alternative cars.    there is no quick fix for our gas crisis.  gas prices will continue to grow and boycotting gas for one day does NOT work!  we just buy more the day before or day after. the only thing we could do is look to hybrid, hydrogen, and electricity to power our future.  the virtues far outweigh the consquences.  hydrogen and electric equals a cleaner future.     
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        yeah, i know, i changed the name again...   i know this is quite ridiculous, but i ended up going to that myspace party.  yes, i know make fun of me, but i only went to see some friends from out of town.  real friends, not my space friends.  so to make up for my actions, john and i got stupid drunk.  then we took edna with us to eat at bossa novas.    i woke up this morning trying to remember how i got to my bed.  the last thing i remember was dropping edna off at her hotel.  i can't remember much after that.  even as the morning progresses, i can't seem to piece together my drive home.      
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       after such a dramatic ending to last nights laker game, i woke up this morning with a smile of victory.  it's over.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       if you're wondering about the constant title changes to this page, then keep wondering, because i am going to change it whenever i think of a new one, or until i come up with one that i truly love.  the newest one deals with exactly what it reads: instant reality.  it's like a self revelation at the most unexpected moment.  like the time i figured out that that i was not going to be a billionaire.     
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
                      free the rabbit!    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i still haven't figured out what i should do with myself.  i have been caught in a somewhat stagnant situation for months now and i feel that i must leave this nest of southern california.  i am not getting any younger and i figure to live until about 50, so that leaves me a little less than 24 more years to figure it out.    places considered (in no particular order): . las vegas . . philippines . . san francisco . . arizona (i heard the houses are really inexpensive) . . washington dc .  it's not that i don't love southern california, but if you read my frustrations below, then you will see why i would want to leave.  so let's start a countdown, if i don't find what i am looking for here in southern california within exactly a month from now, i am moving to one of the above locations.  this is the real deal people.  i am now completely committed, unless i decide to erase this post.    oh and by the way, check out either or both of the links below.  great sites i thought might interest my audience.     
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Where is Raed ?  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink stop student voter suppression!  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       never in my young adult life have i wanted or even craved anything that came from a mcdonald's kitchen.  after hearing about the time my friend evita found a worm in two different chicken mcnuggets in one day, i was completely grossed.  and then it happened to me, i bit into a chicken mcnugget and BAM, it's a lovely little worm looking thing.  from that point on i have despised mcdonalds.    up until today, mcdonalds launches the ultra trendy and somewhat friendly adult happy meal.  what great product marketing by mcdonalds.  who can resist not wanting an adult happy meal.  it even comes with a "stepometer."  it attaches to your belt and counts the number of steps you have taken.  this is great.  i mean, what a way to attract a much more health conscience america. what will they think of next? 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        hoo, hoo, hoo dat?   so i had a conversation with my good friends joel and russel.  russ told me about a time when he was talking with some guy from NY at pete's in downtown LA.  while russ was talking with that guy from NY, a homeless man walks up to them (they were in the patio area) and asks for money.  the guy from NY turned into a fury of madness and pretty much demoralized an already demoralized helpless homeless man.    when i can, i give what i have in my pocket.  i once gave a hungry person $20; it was all i had in my pocket.  but some of these homeless people can be quite demanding.  like the time i pulled out my wallet to grab a buck and the guy asks for the five.    so a lot of times i am very discretionary in who i give my money to.  yesterday a homeless lady with lips that looked like they were going to fall off from too much crack asked us for money, but at that time i had none and if i did, i probably wouldn't have given her any.  once we left pete's bar in downtown LA, another homeless man talks with us.  but this guy is different, he is a homeless comedian.  well, if i had any cash with me, i would have given him some, but i would have considered it to be a tip rather than just giving my money away.  my thinking is, at least he is working for some money.  i remember one time i was with jason and he told me he gives money to the guy that is usually at the santa monica exit off the 101.  reason being is that that guy juggles for money.  he also seems to like the entertainment.    i am all for homeless entertainers.  they are real and funny people.  i will still give my money when i can to people in need, but it so much easier to "tip" someone than to give away money.  so as to my title for this blog i leave you with a joke that the homeless comedian told us.    "what does a white owl say?" "hoo, hoo, hoo"  "what does an ebonics owl say? 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       long legged blonde girl at bar 4100, you have eluded me thus far, but only because your cheesy boyfriend was with you.  i will find you once again.  i couldn't help but want to bite your leg or even your arm.  yes, you were that hot.  even russell had admitted to wanting to bite you.  he never even had the urge to bite anyone before.    let's talk about biting.  its not really so much as to take a piece out of one's flesh, more like to just bite down with sensual force.  yes, try it, and you will thank me for mentioning it.  engage in a biting orgy for all i care.  all i can think about is you, miss blonde girl at bar 4100.  i will find you once again......  besides that, i haven't had a saturday night like that in some time.  i started off going to the LB with russ and joel, but had to re-route to downtown la.  once there, we went to pete's on main and 4th.  hung out, drank stella, smoked cigarettes, people watched, and talked about nothing.  after that we drove to silverlake where we got lost around the reservoir they call silverlake.  joel was dumbfounded to find out there actually was some kind of lake in silverlake, he thought it to be just a name.  finally we found our way to bar 4100.  we all couldnt help but notice the massive amount of women there.  but we had to leave because i just go directions to the next party. off to raymond roker's house.  hung out there for a quick minute and after all the fun and driving around, we made a trek up to eaglerock to make a run for rambo's tacos.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        born on 5.7.2004, my new niece sydney.     
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        what are we really fighting for?   i am deeply saddened and outraged that behind the scenes of the iraq war, we have a few dishonorable soldiers that continue to tarnish the world's perception of the US .  to see photos of  human beings  tortured and humiliated in the shadows of the war is truly shameful on our part.  are we running a post-nazi era internment camp over in iraq?  although i was completely against any type of war, i knew that it was inevitable.  knowing that, i had to support any actions taken by our government.  but we are supposed to be fighting for a new freedom; a new government.  we went into this war to end the sadam regime, not to start a new one.     we must not point fingers at race, religion, or culture for acts such as 9/11, columbine, or the madrid bombings.  rather, we must point the fingers at ourselves: human beings.  we can all be evil at times.....   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        las vegas   dear man-girl at ice,  you have ruined my weekend.  don't think it was just your balding head that gave you away too.  the ghastly site of you and your way too big of a friend sandwiching that poor little guy.  you have forever tarnished my mind with your horrific image.  please do yourself a favor and stay home.     regards, rc 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so i realize that i don't blog as much as i used to, but it's difficult to now that i have a job where i actually do work, thus limiting my internet surfing time.  so i apologize, i will probably only be posting once or twice a week.  then it will eventually die off to where i don't post in months and then never.  then one day i will remember my good ol' pal blogman and i will rise from the dead to tell you about my ever so boring life.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so i started my new job today at deloitte touche & tohmatsu.  im such a corporate buster.  i told myself a few years back that i would never work in such a huge corporate environment again, now look at me.  i am horrible.  oh well, it's a respectable organization and plus its kind of monumental in my career search.  meaning that its a starting point.    out of all the things to look forward to in starting a new job, the most exciting part was getting to meet the girls.  what a joke that was, i guess i am in the wrong department.  i've never met a beautiful computer geeky girl.  so i guess today was no different; however, lunchtime was like a feeding ground.  from now on i am going downstairs to waste my money on food chains that i dislike and starbucks just to see the girls.    anyway, other than that nothing too exciting.  since i am commuting to LA, i've added an extra 3 1/2 hours to my day just to get to work (via metrolink).  i give myself two more days and i'll get into my comfort zone and the real manimal in me will come out.  all hell is going to break loose.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i just saw that hbo movie "something the lord made."  i must tell you that it was one of the better movies i have seen in my life.  the film is based on a medical revolution in an era where segregation was still the norm.  dr. blalock, play by alan rickman, discovers a janitor, vivien thomas, with god-given intelligence for medicine.  the two pair up and the rest is history.    rickman has always captivated his audience by playing a character flawlessly; however, it was mos def's performance that really left an impression.  i've followed mos def's career both in music and acting.  i really enjoy any type of music that he makes, but his part in this movie should be considered monumental and so i tip my hat to mos def.  although subtle, he still conveys great conviction in this role and i hope to see more of him in the future.  let's hope he gets an emmy nod.    if you're interested in seeing the movie, check HBO for listings.  you will not only see a great movie, but you will probably be educated in something that the majority of us are unaware of.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Activists For Justice | Free Sherman Now  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       im so depressed.  how could we lose?  it was supposed to be destiny.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i woke up this morning to the joy of an extra 94 MB of space in my Yahoo! mail account. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i have only lived through 5 presidents in my lifetime.  Reagan being the first one i can remember.  i learned more about this great man today than i have learned in my entire lifetime.  like many others, i couldn't take my eyes off the tv during the ceremony, thinking to myself, how come i am so overcome by grief?    i am one of the lucky ones today that had the opportunity to witness a great moment in history.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so a few weeks ago i went out with someone.  we had a great time but we only talked once since, which was the day after.  she called me last thursday night but i was already sleeping so i didn't get to answer the call.  i called her back the next day and left a message but have yet to receive a call back.    i would have called her before she called me, but she her phone was disconnected for sometime so i never called.  plus i have been too caught up in things going on in my life that i didn't even want to talk to my friends or even family.  so now what?  should i call and ask what gives?  or leave it alone?      
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       don't you hate when you think you are prepared for a situation only to find out that after the ordeal you were no where near prepared?  that always happens to me.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this is my last week of work.  i quit my city job and now i dropped my accounts that i do on the side.  i stayed true to my word when i said that i am quitting.  now all i have to do is find a job or move away.  either one is okay with me.  i know i haven't written anthing in about a week, but i have nothing interesting to tell you.  i do recall having a conversation with a good ol' friend of mine.  we ran into eachother this weekend and she's doing real well in her career and i am making moves in my life to start my career path.  well we were talking about job respectability.  not that making tons of money is not a good thing, but do i have respect for what you do?  maybe, maybe not.  i know this is very generalized, but there are some jobs out there that make a ton of money and real quick too; however, we were both glad that neither of us fell into that.    on another note, i have two interviews this week (wish me luck), if nothing happens with either of the companies, i am leaving.  i don't know which one i want.  if i get offered a position at either of the companies, then i'll probably accept because they are both very respectable companies.  but it'll be a bittersweet because i still wanna get outta here.    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        is anybody out there....   when i'm alone in my room sometimes i stare at the wall and in the back of my mind i hear my conscience call telling me i need a girl who's as sweet as a dove  for the first time in my life, i see i need $*#)!@   ah, you thought.&nbsp;   so i ran into someone this weekend who i sorta forgot about.&nbsp; and now i can't seem to  take my mind off of her.&nbsp; she looked as beautiful as ever.&nbsp; and i can't stop kicking myself for not asking her out.&nbsp; i guess i didn't think about it since we had that falling out at the beginning of this year.&nbsp; so im on the way home and it occurs to me, why the hell didn't you say something cute, nice, funny, retarded you dumbfuck.&nbsp; geeze, am i totally oblivious to every opportunity that stares me in the face.&nbsp; that would have been the perfect time to, as joel would say, "put it in overdrive."&nbsp;   i always complain that the stars are never aligned for me.&nbsp; well the stars&nbsp;can't get more aligned than that.&nbsp; i lost my chance.&nbsp; fuck.&nbsp;    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        what not to do on the metro.....     &nbsp;   1. please don't fall asleep on my shoulder, it is not for strangers (this rule does not apply to cute girls)     &nbsp;   2.&nbsp; don't fall asleep and start to snore really loud, i will get up and leave.     &nbsp;   3.&nbsp; don't&nbsp;place&nbsp;your personal belongings&nbsp;up on the chair next to you on a full train.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   4.&nbsp; don't talk obnoxiously loud on your cell phone.&nbsp;     5.&nbsp; if we're riding&nbsp;a 4:30 - 6:00 am train please don't talk, im trying to sleep.&nbsp;   6.&nbsp; don't put your dirty shoes on the chair.  7.&nbsp; don't try to skip out on paying for a ticket and hide in the bathroom the whole trip.  8.&nbsp; don't floss during the trip, please do it at home or at the office.  9.&nbsp; don't take off your shoes so i have to deal with looking at your ugly feet or deal with that funky smell.  10.&nbsp; please please please don't cut your nails on the train or bite your nails and spit your waste on the floor.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       another bad move by that buss guy.  first he lets the best coach of the last two decades go and now he's trading our whiney but unstoppable gigantic center.  i tell ya, if we don't resign kobe, we're gonna be the clippers!  anyway, i was going to go to the dodger game yesterday, but looks like god had other plans for me.  i knew something was wrong with my car, so before i left for the game i planned to drive it over to the mechanic and leave it there.  i was less than a 1/4 of a mile there (i could actually see it) when ol' faithful decided to throw up the white flag.  she was good to me throughout all my years of mistreatment and neglect.  now it's time to start a new relationship with a new one....  on another note, i wanna fuck a tall whitegirl.  like 5'11" or so.  nice long legs that go on forever.  actually just legs that are so long and then just connect to her neck.  im infatuated with legs right now.  long legs and rad hair.  that's all you need whitegirls of the world.  so if you're looking for a normal 5'6" guy, then im your man.     
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so i am taking a crap today in the middle stall.  the guy to my left is quiet as a mouse.  the guy to my right is having a field day. he uses a barrage of courtesy flushes to cover up the sound of his excrutiating release.  what do i do? i start whistling.  why, because it just seemed appropriate at the time....i whistled my heart out.  like never before.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       “Our enemies are innovative and resourceful, and so are we,” Bush said. “They never stop thinking about new ways to harm our country and our people, and neither do we.”  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>