<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Check out this website www.coldplay.com register and click features click on nappies its very funny. It is a totally different sound all together too bad my player couldn't show Chris Martin wearing a wig and no shirt.Oh and they had to toot! his words too that's a first for Coldplay. Too bad i cudn't save it.   Oh ya today Ivan came to stand beside me. What did i do? i walked away. I have been kicking myself ever since. And my exam results stink its worse then rotten garbage even Al did better then me.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Argggg! This driving me crazy!! How the heck do i post pictures!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My mom hurt her toe cuz she dropped a keyboard on it. So well i guess the house is out of bounds until she gets better. Nuthin much happened other then tat i finished my book The incident about the dog in the night time its interesting about a boy who is a genius in maths but crap at telling apart people's feelings apart from happy and sad.   Its a emotionally detached book like he finds out his mom is not really dead but living with the husband of Mrs Shears the next door neighbour and his dad killed his neighbour's dog, Wellington but he doesn't go nuts he just lies on the floor and pukes. Next thing he does?  Go to London cuz he thinks his dad will kill him too.....he spends 5 hrs in the London train station cuz he is too scared to board the train we r talking about a 15 year old boy here. Totally screwed. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I am back from hibernation! my mom went to UK with my aunt so am staying with my cousins for two weeks hahahaha. Let's juz face it i got nuthin to say. oh ya i got the new avril Lavigne CD and those non fanns i dun care wat u say.  
       
    
    
</post>


<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am soo sick of trying to be perfect cuz i am not. And i look at those people who are perfect or at least act that way and feel sorry for them. Its ridiculous why the heck would they want to put on a mask its soo stupid and Britney is one such person. So what if i am dissing her? She wears pratically nothing and voice stinks too. Her penchant for kissing women is off putting. And she is still trying to mantain that perfect image. Watch it gal your mask is cracking.  Avril. peace out.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       oh god. My cousins are alking about farting and their experiances with it. Heck its a natural daily occurance jus hold ya breath shift ur chair and pretend sum one esle did it if it was super loud learn how to hypnotise others into beliving wat they heard was actually elephants passing by in a stampede. Plus throw in the made up facts that u are actually a star and stars dun fart they blow wind.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>