<Blog>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Had a dream last night. Not sure if it's the best start to a blog, but its real, its a catalyst, it has meaning, so here we go. I remember an old friend Shawn, who was my best friend from about 5th grade through 7th, was in my dream. So was Annabelle. I don't remember what happened exactly, but I know there was a good deal of betrayal, and when I eventually woke up it felt like I had been feeling it for a while. I remember seeing Annabelle and Shawn, heads leaned against each other speaking softly. It didn't make sense to me that my best friend would now have anything to do with her, so I asked them what was going on. Annabelle replied that "Well, you were arrested. You've been gone a long time." That's about the gist of the dream. So today I have a perspective on how things with Annabelle got as bad (and probably worse in many ways) than they ever did with Amber. Betrayal is a traumatic experience, especially when the person you trust repeats what she knew had hurt you before while insisting that she never would. Anyway, this blog is not about that, but a good starting point.   What's on the soundsystem?  Kanye West,  Jesus Walks 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hacker? Yes. Great one? No. Other charges? Funny. Maybe its your fugly fiance. You didn't realize he was spying on you all along? Where did you think he got my email address? Or logged my conversation with him? You have got to be the dumbest person I've ever met.  Who's hair is like straw and always falling out, stare is like she's dim-witted, humor is tiring and only appreciated by those that are humoring her, tits are 2 different sizes, ass is always out of shape and stinks, shits on people's floors when she's drunk, is an off-and-on junkie, has a thing for her brother, has a psycho sister, an ugly boyfriend, and can't accomplish anything for herself while she expects everyone around her to? Hmm...let's see... Feeling pretty good right now.   Realized that younger skate punks are almost all assholes. Seems like most people around here think that's all you can be. I also hate the SUV/Escalade crowd, who came into money by no hard-working means and park wherever the fuck they want to, regardless of the fact that they're almost causing several accidents. I understand how terrorism is so abundant in the world these days. People are bringing this shit on themselves.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, what do I really want to tell you all? hmm...sexy day it was, still reeling from it. My route today was awesome...didn't realize I could bring a hottie along, stop and go swimming, do other naughty things, and still get home at my usual time with a full evening for getting bitten by ants while rolling around at the airport. Oops! I guess it wasn't all perfect. Such is life, but dealing with it as it comes is the best way to attract everyone in life, so fuck it. I can't stop smiling...    What's on the Alpine?  Jay-Z,  99 Problems   If you havin girl problems I feel bad for you son I got 99 problems, but a bitch ain't one 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so things are coming together so beautifully it seems too good to be true. As that cute Adelphia chick would say, "Maybe my luck is changing." LOL! ...right after she shows off all the creeps she's dated. Well I've got too many good things going to count now, and its just a matter of juggling them and remaining crazily busy for the rest of the summer. I've discovered that being tired is a great thing though, it adds to my personality handsomely. I hiked Mount Ascutney with the most amazing young lady yesterday, and unlike with other girls, we actually went all the way! mwahahahaa. I didn't think I would settle down and commit to anything this summer, but I'm not committed to not-committing either. What has happened to me that makes me catch the hottest, previously seemingly unattainable ladies checking me out and then smiling at me and saying hi...everyday? Hahahahaha
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Did I mention that I love Amy Lee? I can't stop playing the acoustic version of  urlLink My Immortal . She kind of reminds me of  that girl , and the girl right before her, and maybe a couple of others. Actually, I think she reminds me of what I thought I was getting but wasn't with every relationship I've ever had. And she has an absolutely amazing, haunting, compassionate voice. I want to meet her sooo bad. No its not one of those silly crushes. She's the one for me. I can dream I guess....   What's on the soundsystem?  Evanescence,  My Immortal   i've tried so hard to tell myself that you're gone and though you're still with me i've been alone all along 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, its been a long time since I've posted to this thing. I've been so friggin busy recently. I'm exhausted right now, but in a very good way. My classes kick ass this term. I just had one today and I think I fell in love, and I don't mean with the class. Shannon had such a great idea about using AIM in class. This is gonna be a blast.  My Jetta's running great now, its badass  100% owning  a car that get so many looks like that thing does. Too bad my job makes me have to wash it all the time if I want to keep it pimpin'. Funny, though, that I'm refining my drive-like-a-maniac skills for as much money as I made at GDT. That's royally fuckin' hilarious. And I get to cruise all afternoon in better towns than we got here, even if you count all the scummy tourist ones.  There's so much more to say, but I'm soooo tired. I'm gonna pop open another beer....   What's on the Soundsystem?  Trick Daddy featuring Big Boi and Cee-Lo,  Dro in the Wind   Drop the top and let the sunshine in With the woodgrain, let the twenties spin Get you a glass, mix the Coke and the Hen' It's quite alright, with the 'dro in the wind, with the 'dro in the wind 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    anything's better than this p.o.s.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    okay so i lied...im probably getting this one :-P&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ...or this one&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    so i think i might be getting this car...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got back from seeing my girl. God do I have some feelings for her. She is so beautiful. The moment I try to tell her that she flips me off and says goodnight. Oh well--the lovin is good. Its been so long since I've been with someone who I could truly respect and admire. I don't feel like I even deserve her. Nothing is certain, but I think that's part of what makes everything great. And I think she truly admires me too. We have different lives and different paths to take, but I think our connection may last forever in one form or another. I sometimes wish I had more to hold onto, but I think she is teaching me that that is not what it is about. She is a wise young lady. I wish they all could be California girls...  ROFL!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm happy to see that the song I've been listening to since the beginning of April and never thought I'd even hear on the radio has become extremely popular on MTV and Launch. Its found its place in  urlLink my blog , as a video in my profile on  that site , and on one of my favorite mix CD's for my car. Speaking of cars, I may be getting a new one soon. Ahh, decisions decisions. I hope my friends can afford to join me in that house. A loft, hot tub, two-story whatchamacallit style living room, dining room, deck, lots-o-land, great swimming, trails, private...what more could I ask for? Well, I can think of a few things. Don't worry though, I'll have those too.     What's still everywhere I have speakers?   Kanye West,  Jesus Walks    God show me the way because the devil try'na break me down The only thing that I pray is that my feet don't fail me now And I don't think theres nothing I could do now to right my wrongs I wanna talk to God but I'm afraid cuz we aint spoke in so long...   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    my favorite...maybe cuz i took it...nah, that's not it at all&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I must be tall...yeah that's it&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    don't be hatin on me...i got backup!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    what can i say?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    hooray for jello!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    i think another angle is due >:-)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    tattooage&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    more croppage...its a disco in her pants!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just kidding. Good song though. I get bad vibes from people all the time. From the chick who added me to her friends on that social network cuz her friend told her she "had to" to that friend of the household saying that she thought I'd be more self-confident with my best friend as a roommate, people just have an amazing way with words sometimes. And the random people that add me to their messenger, talk for a while usually boring me more than i am them until they start to act weird. And the ugly white trailer trash that yell at me to slow down while i stare directly at them and continue unfazed. And the chick from my class that got a hold of me by messenger and i thought had a great convo with but didn't seem to close it sweetly enough for me to be sure. And all the random women in my life who act super-friendly one day and cold the next. Its ever-changing, imperfect, sometimes boring, sometimes insecure, but almost every one of these things works itself out with a cool head. Heck I'll probably end up dating most of the women that I've mentioned there. Meeting people, making friends, and attracting dating material has never been this easy.  Party frieday, and its gonna be grand! At least 3 awesome babes and a good friend of mine will be there, so it should be a blast. And my girl-friend (girlfriend?) will be back tomorrow as well, while I probably won't see her til later this weekend. Oh yeah...almost forgot...payday...sweet....    I've got a bad feeling about this....but its all okay with me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Boogah-woogah!   What's on the Alpine?  Murphy Lizzle ft. Nelly,  Hold Up   Just give me your information And I'll keep you in every rotation I wanna touch you where the sun don't shine I got a watch but I don't got time So if you wit it, then you wit it that's good Cuz if you not then I could simply take you back to the hood ...Cuz I love my hoes Pimpin' aint easy but it's under control I got a lot of shit in me but I'm not a commode Cell phone, area code overload 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    :drool: :-P&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    too bad...the rest of the picture is so beautiful too... :-( ...for my eyes only :-P&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    rawr-tarded&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    mmm...boobies&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    fuck you...no fuck you&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I know you you like to think your shit don't stank but lean a lil bit closer and you'll see that roses really smell like poopoo-oohoowho.  So anyway there's always something on the Dell of value for blog lyrics hehe. But the transition back to rock from exclusively hiphop continues. My best bud turns out to hold the matching pieces of the puzzle that I had only begun to explore while I can offer him the underground hiphop pieces. Isn't mutually beneficial synthesis grand?  I have no idea how I'm still running on such a small amount of sleep this weekend. A class, two routes, a party, a trip to Leb., a new networking/journal setup, a photoshoot, some music sharing, new pets, an excellent marinated tomato salad, a little beer-drinking, lots of iced-coffee's, girls, girls, girls, oh and cool guys too, can't forget not to be hating on them as much as I may have been known to in the past. But then again, they ain't exactly the same bros as before.  I guess you ain't heard that we swallow guys. Its too damn late to apologize. Its almost over now, almost over now.  So who to court first, and how to keep them all going until I can make up my mind is the task at hand. This work and school shit is getting pretty basic. And who to live with to keep as many balls in the air as possible without confusing anyone, including me. Mmm, I love my ladies...yes, I love my bros too...life is good. Ahh, how about a little old Offspring on the LaunchCAST?  Hey, man you talking back to me? take him out. gotta keep em separated. hey, man you disrespecting me? take him out. gotta keep em separated.  So am I going punk again? what these fake little bitches (girls like you are all a dime a dozen) don't realize is I was always more punk than their fake asses were all along. aggh, why do I even feel the need to defend myself against your petty voices and well-known-to-me opinions when I know that you're entirely full of shit? seems a common thing for people to do. Its a little like PTSD, or the parental tape bullshit. People just continue to defend themselves against perceived threats even after they're gone. I'm better than that though, and I always have been, whether I knew it or not. Those that have a hard time accepting me in their life are those that can't deal with someone who's not predictable. Even that I feel I have to defend somehow. Well guess what? Most of the predictions you ever made of me were wrong. And the ones that were right were self-fulfilling prophecies. I am whatever you say I am.   What's on [insert best friend's name here]'s Dell besides party pics of bis and I's?  Taking Back Sunday,  Cute Without The 'E'   (I stay jealous)  I stay wrecked and jealous for this,  for this simple reason  I just need to keep you in mind  as something larger than life  (she'll destroy us all before she's through  and find a way to blame somebody else) 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I feel remorse...but I shouldn't. Wronged once, wronged twice, how many times do I just take it? People aren't who they seem to be. Everyone has that to learn.  So I have this lull here. So much up and coming, just need to TCOB first. Opportunities don't last forever, and neither does youth. Even memories fade. Its about time. Haha.  I love that static energy, that connection, the unexplainable lust of a good lil group. Non-competitive collaboration makes beautiful things. Those words ain't as beautiful as the nymphs they insinuate. Life ain't always pretty, but it can be...just work and wait. We will see it again.  Fuck the past. Fuck you all. I know what I need and I know the life for me. Y'all's is fucked. Too bad for you. Everything alive is for me, no molding myself to another's life, no getting old too quick for me, no feeling dirty all the time for just being me. I am everything you could never be.   What's on the Dell?  Jay-Z,  Lucifer    Man i gotta get my soul right I gotta get these Devils out my life These cowards gonna make a nigga ride They won't be happy til somebody dies  Man i gotta get my soul right 'For i'm locked up for my whole life Evertime it seems it's all right Somebody want they soul to rise (I'll chase you off of this Earth)   Preach, Jigga.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I need to capture this moment. I am completely ecstatic right now. I just went to the fireworks with a friend and stopped by another friend's place (too bad nobody is privy to more than pronouns and such about my life on here). Anywho, I spent the whole evening stone cold sober flirting with a really horny bisexual vixen and one of her best friends and checking out pictures of their recent adventures in women. Nothing quite to that extent that you're thinking, but it was my first night with the pair and they're not that type of girl--more classy than that. ROFL-LMAO-LOL, no acronym to describe how fucking delighted I am with my life right now. I think I recently realized that I am some really hot shit and can get almost any girl I want and maybe her best friend while I'm at it. And it ain't no joke--one of these chicks I have had a crush on for years, but always thought her Jehovah's witness ass was too sweet to corrupt. Umm--btw this is too fucking good to be true! And if it doesn't work out, fuck it, I've got at least 2 others on deck.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Posting on my computer is so much easier than this. At least I can get on the internet for a few minutes. I've been waiting for the cable guy to hook up my powerlink at Will and I's apartment all week. So guess who I saw today? I was wondering who actually bought those things. Now I know. That's just way, way, way too funny. A friggin Jetta VR6 has more power than those "trucks." And doesn't look quite so gay. Even a chick just looks like a tomboy who doesn't quite get it. Especially while flicking her butt out the window. Every single friend I have now is an ex-smoker. Most run or bike several miles a day. I lift weights, rollerblade, and hike so I'm getting there too. So I guess I haven't bought a car yet, although I now own two '95 compacts. The best things in life  are  free. And I'm moving to Burlington with my girl/friend to finish college and make $1000/week at the same time. But I'll tell you about all that later. My life is extremely stable  and  I still have my identity.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>