<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    This is mainly to help Michael navigate his way in Malaysia. I will try my best to spell out the location of where the photos were taken. For starters, I am situated in Kuala Lumpur, the capital. The Husband is in Miri, East Malaysia, whereas my parents are in Johor Bahru and in-laws are in Kuantan.
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Ok... same scene. They gave us huge t-shirts, reaching to our knees. I might give mine to the Husband, but the shade of grey is such a yuckie colour.
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Waiting for the treasure hunt results to be announced. It was really one long wait. 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I know, this is so lame... I wanted to snap a picture of a site we needed to list down during the treasure hunt, but only managed to take a snap at the side view mirror. I know, I am not much of a shutterbug. You don't have to point it out. 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    A view of the Kuala Terengganu rooftops on an extremely cloudy day. You can't see much, really. These pictures were taken sometime in June, when the region was experiencing monsoon showers.
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Another one. The Husband was in Kuala Terengganu attending a course, but due to torrential rain, he was cooped up in his hotel room most of the time.
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The view of the beach from Primula Hotel, Kuala Terengganu on a very windy and cloudy day.
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Early morning yoga by the poolside. The picture was taken by the Husband who declined to join, but preferred to recline in bed.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    And here is the Cape Rachado Lighthouse.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    On the way down, a few of us discovered this fantastic looking bug. The Husband dubbed it the Cape Rachado bug. Unless you see it moving, I'd think it'd be a bit difficult to tell which end is head or tails.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    A triumphant looking lot who sweated it out to climb to the top. The guide tricked us, there was actually a paved road to get to the top. However, going through the forest was fun.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    It was quite freaky being up on the cliff, making our way to the lighthouse. But the view down below was fantastic.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Yeah... was supposed to post this eons ago but didn't quite manage. Sensei is front row, second from left.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The view from my previous 6th floor apartment. So cooling and refreshing. To get to the pink-roofed condominiums, you need to travel on a winding and narrow road uphill.
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's now or never. I have to start with these gloomy pictures, to get the ball rolling.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Right, the building there would be my object of desire. It's currently still under construction and all units have been sold out, so I am waiting for people to start selling. Keeping my ears and eyes open. 
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Yet another view showing the city... I need to put up more showing the greens.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    No, no, no, sorry to disappoint but that isn't our place. 
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The area has been well-planned; but a bit too many houses for my liking. Nevertheless, beggers can't be chooses, as I am often reminded by the Husband.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    You can see the minaret of the mosque from the balcony. The call for prayer is loud and clear; especially in the crisp morning air.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    This is the view we get from the balcony of the new apartment. On good days (without the haze) you'll be able to see KL Tower.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Whoa... grab on to what ever you can darling.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Me - in a state of loss and confusion; as always the case.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Trying my best to keep up.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    That's me sprawled on the floor. I don't feel too bad cause I see others are in the same predicament - though much more graceful at it.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I think the Husband is thrilled to see me being flung to the floor.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Ah... a little help from KB Sensei does the trick.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Err... quite unsure what's happening here really.
      
</post>



</Blog>