<Blog>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey!  Today I'm just going to mull over some random thoughts I've had floating around.  Little tidbits, like...  -If Mr. Right really is sitting right under my nose, then I wish he'd please stop staring up my nostrils and meet me eye to eye.  I'm a nice girl.  Not high-maintenance at all.  All I ask for is companionship.  -I really miss Jonesboro.  Some of you probably think that's crazy, but I don't.  It's a nice community that I grew attached to after all those Saturdays we spent there when I was younger.  Of course, Indian Mall isn't what it used to be...  -The little town in which I was raised is a strange Arkansas farming town.  Major identity issues.  Five miles from Missouri...close enough to get the TV station from Cape Girardeau, but also the ones from Memphis and Little Rock, even though they only covered stories in Corning when the trains derailed or the governor came to town for the 4th of July.  There's a topic...  -The Fourth of July in Corning.  They really know how to do that holiday up there.  Every business, including Wal-Mart and McDonald's, closes down for the parade and big homecoming picnic.  Everyone...and I mean EVERYONE in town goes to the picnic right after the parade, meets and greets, and then goes to their swimming pools or Current River and invites everyone they know for one huge day-long celebration, going back to the park for barbecue and to watch the pageants.  Drunk fireworks at my dad's usually begin about two hours before the city display...at which point I cower on the back porch with a bucket of water...just in case.  Then they draw for the Lincoln Town Car at midnight.  It's a fun day.  -If the Weather Channel comes to your town for vacation...be afraid.  -True leadership is not a title.  Just because you head up this or that doesn't mean you're a good leader.  It means your buddies wanted to make sure the power still lies with them.  -I don't understand why some people feel the need to stir up trouble.  It's like they live for it! My experiences in college showed me that one all too well...and the funny part is that the people who are causing the issues never EVER admit any part of it.  They just pass the blame to the next guy and tell everyone else to stop stirring up trouble.  Hypocrites are the worst.    -I hope I left a good impression at ASU.  With everyone I met.  I'd like to think I did.  Maybe one of these days I'll even get up the guts to ask just one question that's been bugging me for a looooong time...  -Common courtesy is not very common.  The same goes for just some common etiquette rules, like a good, firm handshake.  I have met more wimpy handshakes than I thought possible!  I was also always amazed at students who would treat their professors like dirt and demand to get respect in return.  -I need a marketable circus skill.  I could run off with the circus.  Maybe my little dance routines would work.  Maybe all those people who used to watch me through binoculars at the football games would write me a recommendation.  Today's Family Guy quote...from the Weather Center... "IT'S GONNA RAIN!"
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Before I begin...you may notice that my title has changed (all four of you).  If you can think of a better one...preferably not "Grant's Retaaaaaded Lil' Sis," I'd appreciate your input.  Family Guy is supposed to be coming back!  That's the best news I've heard since "Thank you, Miss Garland...we're forwarding this resume to the next guy."  I took some online quiz that is supposed to tell you which character you are on the show, but they said I was Peter!  How far off can you get?  He weighs at least three hundred pounds more than myself...and he's a freakin' alcoholic!    Let's take stock.  I really don't match ANY of the characters on the show.  I have the insecurities of Meg, but I'm much smaller.  I have some of Brian's intelligence, but I don't dig in the backyard.  I have the sensibilities of Lois, but I don't have kids or a fat husband.  I love my mom, which rules out Stewie completely.  He is funny, though.  Witty, in a biting way.  Chris, Quagmire, Cleveland, Loretta, Joe, Tom Tucker, Dianne Simmons, Asian reporter Trisha Takinawa...not even the freakin' AV nerd Neil matches me!    I watched what is probably my favorite episode last night.  Pawtucket Pat and the Patriot Brewery...complete with the piano competition.  I don't know how many of you have noticed that you can see Charlie and Grandpa Joe from "Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory" briefly in the brewery scenes.  It's a classic episode.  Very quotable too, I might add.    "Take a drink...and you'll sink...to a state of pure inebriation..." -Pawtucket Pat "Ooh...Ooh...play that sad walking away music from the Incredible Hulk!" -Stewie "When I was your age we had way better drinking games than this." -Peter and... Cop:  Aren't you a little old to be drinking illegally? Peter:  (turns to Lois) Lois!  Look over there!  (turns to cops) Run!  By the way...if they're inaccurate...let me know.  I hate to mess with pure genius.  We should thank our lucky stars that there is a Family Guy, immortalized in DVD. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You know, if life were really like our dreams, I'd have a fascinating life thus far.    All during sleep, I've flown without any type of aircraft, been married several times (but only engaged once), driven off the road a few times, played professional basketball, and dueled high notes with Maynard Ferguson...to name just a few.  (I knew that one was a dream.  My range isn't that great.)   Oh, yeah...some little elf ran through my room one night.  Don't know where I got that one.  And then there's the infamous dream within a dream within a dream within a...you get the point.  If I hadn't woken up, I would have also pushed up daisies a few times.  I don't remember my dream last night.  I do remember one in which I heard a completely original song...but I was in the sixth grade and it didn't occur to me to write it down.  It was pretty good, too, but I can't really remember it now.  I just remember it being good.  What's odd is, for all the years I spent in band, I never remember too many dreams about that.  Maybe I got enough of it in waking life.  I often saw my band friends, but I was never doing my cadence dances or anything in the stadium.  There is one good one I remember, though...from ASU...I couldn't remember ANY of the drill and I got in trouble for beating up an audience member who laughed at me.  Maybe I was punished because I stopped in the middle of the show to do it.  Or maybe it was because I answered my cell phone during the dreaded "washing machine."  (Once again...knew that was a dream because no one ever calls.)  Oh, well.  "Laughing Girl" was from high school, so I guess that was a pesky repressed feeling showing itself.      I did and still do have that one where you are running late for a final exam and never quite make it to the classroom...and I'm done with school!  It was never even a subject I took.  It was always a dead language or something.  One of those things that you take for personal fulfillment but really has no place on a resume.     I only wish some of them would come true.  I have, unfortunately, had some of those not-so-great revelation dreams that actually did happen.  Just once I'd like the happy one to happen.  I guess, to some measure, they have.  It's another beautiful day and I'm going to enjoy it!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ta Daa!  It is with little fanfare and even less anticipation that I present my blog to the public!    Please, hold your applause until the end of the entry.  Now, on with the show.  In my unemployment, I've become quite a television critic.  Don't get me wrong...I haven't started watching soaps or anything like that.  But I do catch myself yelling at the news anchors.  Just this morning I heard a gross mispronunciation of John Coltrane's name.  I ask you...how difficult does that one actually look?  Even if you had never heard his name or music (Heaven forbid) in your life, don't you imagine that you could at least sound it out?    I grew up in the "Electric Company" generation.  Apparently, Mom would sit me in front of the television and I would learn to sound out words with the two people's profiles.  (You may remember...c...at...cat.)  Anyway, I could read by the time I was two.  It really freaked everyone out when I read the dog's name out loud from Mom's handwriting.  No, the dog's name wasn't Fido or Spot.  His name was Hannibal.  I also used this little party trick on road signs...Batesville was a good one for kicks.    So, naturally I am a little bit short with someone who cannot pronounce "Coltrane."  Other than that, today has been delightfully boring.  At least the sun is shining today.  Nicely, I might add.  Perhaps I should go enjoy it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First of all, I hope everyone weathered last night's storms safely.  We had a few potentially scary moments, but we never saw the brunt of the activity; knock on wood.  Memorial Day weekend.  Lots of people use it as their excuse to come over here to the lake for the first time of the year.  I don't have much experience living in a tourist trap.  I grew up in the type of place that everyone left for the holiday weekend.  Now I know where they all went.    So...shall I define a Heber Springs tourist? The most common type is the Memphian.  Many Memphians have lake houses over here.  (If my friends in Tennessee wouldn't mind...tell me if there are any major lakes over there.  It has piqued my curiosity, since it is a three-hour trip between here and there.)  It's interesting to be landlocked in North Central Arkansas and see more license plates from Tennessee than Arkansas.  I think it's pretty neat...they've chosen to spend their time and money in Arkansas.  I can make a pretty good case for living in the Natural State by observing travel habits of out-of-towners.    Of course, locals typically do not try to get out on the water during peak holiday times.  They have the option of going out any time and typically prefer to avoid weekends and holidays, with the exception of Independence Day.  However, I assume going out at these times can also be a good way to meet different people.  Personally, I don't like to deal with the extra traffic.  No deep sentimental messages today.  I'm not feeling all that great and, consequently, cannot muster the energy to play philosopher.  If anyone can think of a good remedy for the resulting stomach ache from eating ham sandwiches six days in a row, please send it my way.  The only thing I could think to do was stop eating ham sandwiches! ;) 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm not sure if I should thank my brother or the top dogs at the WB for this one, but I am HOOKED on "Dawson's Creek."   Thanks, fellas.  You've opened up my inner psychologist, thesaurus and soft side.  This is quite possibly the reason I have developed some issues recently.  I have nothing but free time, and I have invited those characters into my life as part of it, to a not-quite-psycho extent.  What has happened here? I swore I would NEVER watch that show...out of principle.  Grant was watching it, Mom was watching it...I needed to be different...so I didn't watch it.  Then, TNT started over on their "ER" reruns, so I switched channels...I now have new best friends in fictional Capeside.  No worries...I still spend the ten o'clock hour yelling at "The Price is Right." However, I catch myself flipping stations between commercials and games and "come on down" and...yeah.  I'll stop now.  I don't quite know what I'm going to do until Monday...perhaps I'll dig into Grant's stash of recorded episodes.  (I hope they're still here!)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahh, spring.    The time of year when animals prance and frolic.  Sailboats romp on the lake.  Flowers bloom and trees leaf out in their glory.  Single people watch everyone else enjoy it that much more.   I'm headed to a wedding this weekend.  No...not my own...and if you even thought that for a second, I guess you don't know me at all! I'm very happy for them.  Not the least bit bitter about my own life.    Really.  I am.  And happy for the three million other people who've sent invitations in the last month.  Okay, I confess...I'm a little sad.  I'm still waiting for that prophecy that is supposed to be fulfilled for girls like me...you know it...the one that says, "Those college guys are gonna be all over you!"  Sigh.  I'm a college graduate, and, as for that saying, I've only been attractive to those "college guys" after they'd had a few too many.  Unfortunately, they're all drummers.  My dad told me never to date a drummer (He, and I, have known a few).  Some tend to drool on cue.  I've also been attractive to someone who apparently told half the campus that I was cute before I'd ever even seen him. (Shudder...)  I don't understand the problem! I have had this thought that perhaps all the good guys are threatened by a "smart chick." Maybe it has something to do with my nice set of... morals. (Heh...almost fooled you!)  Maybe there is someone great who's just too scared to tell me!  Well, guess what?!? I'm not a mean person! If you have something to say, just say it! PLEASE!  Here's where my self-imposed hypocrisy rears its ugly head.  I'd never, NEVER have the guts to do this. (Over-analysis.  Refer to "Wink and Smile.") Use this knowledge to your advantage.  Actually, I don't think it's so much having the nerve as it is my old-fashioned beliefs.    I'm rambling.  I know EVERYONE has heard this bit before, but when you have tons of time on your hands, it seems a worthy rant.  I'm allowed.  Good night!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, the euphoria of a few days away from this same set of walls has begun to fade slightly.  I really think it was new-found energy from the change of scenery, and saying hello to...well...everyone!  Maybe it's those fleeting moments and ideas about the near future that make everything bearable right now.  I know everything will work out, and I am learning patience in the process.  I know that is my heaven-sent lesson through all of this...patience.  I have been used to instant results and gratification for my efforts, but this is a way to stay in check.  I can remember when I was applying for colleges...seems like all I had to do was send in the application and I was offered more money than most credit cards can promise.    Wink and smile.    I'm trying my best to look at the silver lining.  It hasn't been easy, but I'm trying.  I shouldn't feel guilty about being a little bit happy right now.  No one can take my education from me.  I am very proud of that education, and it will go to work for me very soon.    However, I am often guilty of thinking too far ahead of myself and expecting certain things to happen at certain times.  It just doesn't work that way, and only seems to cause that dreaded personal anguish.  This is my heart-to-heart on life in general.    Wink and smile.    Basically, I have always thought too much.  If I allowed myself to quit analyzing for just a little while, I might be better off.  I should do something out of character for me.  I'm not talking about anything wild or crazy, just out of character.  Get rid of some of the shyness and chisel away some of the barriers.  Let the world really get to know me for a change.  I never understood how I could dance around like a moron in front of ten thousand people in Indian Stadium and still become nervous in front of one person...never quite know what to say...thinking so much about what to say that I inevitably flub it up...I guess I'm just good at showmanship at the surface.  I'm working on changing that every day.  I'm being a good student of life...using all this  extra given time wisely and working towards making changes.    Hope I haven't bored you...I guess, in a way, I've already opened up a bit more.  This entry was more for my benefit than anything.  I needed to prove to myself that I could be more in-depth and let others see it.  I'm a little nervous about pushing the button and publishing this! My goodness...how could I have been such a good writer all these years without really letting go of some of these inhibitions?  Wink and smile.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey everyone!   I'm making a kind of Peter Pan wish here, but I'd like everyone to think happy thoughts.  For me.  No, you won't fly when you do, but maybe I could feel like I'm going to if everything works out! I've had a few promising slight changes in fortune and I hope the wheel keeps on rolling.  E-mail me for more details.    It hit me like a Mack truck yesterday that my dad's birthday is coming up a week from Thursday and I don't have a clue on what to get him! Maybe I'll go up there and cook something...that ought to surprise him...his girl does have domestic skills...  I might have to make the family's famous spaghetti salad.  I have been told that it cures hangovers, although I've never tried it for that purpose...obviously.  For reasons of personal safety, I cannot reveal the ingredients of the recipe.  All I can do is say that you must try it sometime.  I know...come up for the Fourth of July! We have it every year.  (Actually, the big celebration is on the third this year...it's a Saturday...come on up for some fun, sun, food and fireworks!)  Today I'm watching my 80s movies.  I mentioned that I love my baseball movies, and my 80s movies have some good stories, too.  This afternoon's movie..."Lucas."    Keep thinking those happy thoughts...please! Catch you later!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Up until this morning, I could safely say I had never caused harm on any electronic device.  Unless you count two televisions struck by lightning, which I don't, because it is an act of God.  Today started out a typical lazy Saturday.  I watched some television, ate breakfast, then went upstairs to dress.  I just needed to touch up a pesky kink in my hair, so I plugged in my trusty old curling iron.  The one I've had for about three years.  There is a rip in the wire cover, but I took care of that (or so I thought) with some good old electrical tape.  After I plugged it in, I thought I'd untwist the cord, since for some reason I always get it twisted in the tightest way.  Big mistake.  Apparently, good old electrical tape was no match for shoddy wiring compounded with the untwisting motion.  I remember a flash of light...a pop...a scream...the lights went out...my hand covered in black soot...and then this smell...kind of like a sparkler...  I've blown fuses before.  Vinessa and I did once in the dorm when we both decided to run our hair dryers simultaneously.  THAT was a serious undertaking.  The dorm was built in 1964, and I don't think the fuse box had been opened since then...not to mention the fact that tracking down an RA was next to impossible at 10:00 p.m. in the sorority dorm.  The key didn't work, the box was stuck...it took a little while to remedy that situation.    But, alas, that was the college world.  This is reality, and now I have no good curling iron and a kink still left in my hair.  Thankfully, the fuse wasn't completely blown; the breaker had just been thrown.    The moral of this story:  A buzz cut is best.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't hear voices.  I've never hit the guts out of a baseball, and I've never played in a skirt.  But I love my baseball movies.  "Field of Dreams" is one of the best "baseball-as-a-way-of-life" stories I've ever experienced.  I've been on a "Field of Dreams" kick lately, and I even had a dream one night that picked up exactly where the movie ended.  Actually, it picked up on James Earl Jones' amazing monologue, with some interesting variations that were better suited to me.  Instead of his saying, "They'll come to Iowa," much to my amazement, he said, "They'll come to Arkansas."  (I woke up laughing at that one!)   Perhaps I should back up a bit.  My dad was the Ray character, and he built the baseball field in one of the fields in front of our home.  After the Terrence Mann speech, and after "Ray" plays catch with his dad, it gets very interesting.    I have been designated to take up the $20 tickets that all these people are buying to watch the games.  You know...the end of the movie...the lines and lines of cars coming to the field.  I also sell popcorn.  Unfortunately, we run out of tickets rather quickly and run into some interesting parking problems.  Those of you that have been to my dad's know that you don't park on the grass (a.k.a. mud) if you ever want to back your car up again.  Anyway, nothing quite goes as well as it should, and I wake up hearing that line..."People will come...they'll come to Arkansas..."  All of this aside, I remember seeing "A League of Their Own" in the Mansion Mall Theater in Poplar Bluff.  I was eleven.  I loved that one right off the bat, no pun intended.  I went home and wished I could be a baseball player.  I would try to re-enact scenes in the backyard, but I didn't have any baseballs...I had to use tennis balls instead.  It remains one of my favorite movies to this day.  Not my favorite-favorite-favorite, but it's a good one!  I was introduced to "The Natural" at a young age as well.  I never had a baseball bat with a name, though.  I would later have a fine arts theater class in college in which the professor claimed the movie was a bit too melodramatic for him...I didn't care...I loved it!  I'm also a big "Bull Durham" fan...along with "Major League"...I think you get the point.  Something about these movies just makes me feel good.  I don't know why; baseball movies usually have better storylines than some other sports movies.  Except for "Rudy."  There's a great football movie, even though I would argue that football is simply the catalyst...it shows his drive and ambition, and that's the central theme.  Anyway, I love my baseball movies.  Sidenote:  I feel very empowered here lately.  Almost giddy.  Just in the past few days, after my time back in my "homeland."  I have a lot of nice thoughts and notions and I sincerely hope they all work out quickly.  Keep me in your thoughts!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've spent the last few days up at my dad's playing paralegal in his office.  I really don't like going "home home"...I like going to his house and getting away, but I just don't like going back.  It takes me back to high school in 2.5 seconds flat as soon as I pass the population sign.  I lose all the confidence I've had for the last several years simply by crossing the city limits.  Unless I have friends with me.  Anyway...I ate at McDonald's way too many times, because my dad doesn't keep breakfast food around most of the time.  I ran into a former classmate who works there, and she informed me that my class is having a five-year reunion.    It's REUNION time?  Most of the class hasn't been un-united, so why get back together so soon? Those of us that left are all just finishing college and trying to get a life started! Those that stayed...well...I don't even want to go there.  I'll just say this...college was absolutely fantastically magically undeniably wonderful! I'm much more likely to go to every home football game on the ASU schedule than relive the agony that was high school.  I know what you're thinking...everyone thinks high school was terrible.  Well, give me a call sometime and we'll compare stories.  The people I knew from other high schools that I went to college with had no idea that I was semi-witty or outgoing until I got to know them very well in college.  Simply put, I was scared to death to say anything--funny or not--because of the way I was treated in high school.  Courtesy of my classmates.   Don't get me wrong...there are a few that I keep in touch with that were actually genuinely nice.  My goodness, though...if the rest of the group had taken the time to actually get to know me...  Here are a few of the quirky, unique little unwritten rules that existed in my class (for some reason): 1.  Don't carry a backpack.  It is an "elementary-school" thing to do and you are supposed to break your arms carrying books home unless you enjoy picking spitwads out of your hair. 2.  Don't show an interest in anything academic.  Unless you are the "right person." I never quite figured out what that was.   3.  Don't win too many awards.  It is a sign that you care about something.  Refer to rule 2. 4.  The coolest thing you can do is get a car and drive it in a circle.   5.  Don't talk to a teacher.  EVER.  Even if it's your mom.    Those are just a few.  I can think of more, but it's giving me a headache.  I seriously doubt I would want to go to that reunion.    And that's all I have to say about that.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As many of you know, I follow the political scene quite closely.  I want to be the most informed voter I possibly can.  I think it is our red, white and blue civic duty to go out and vote.   That being said, tomorrow is the Arkansas primary.  I'm not going to get into a discussion of my political preferences.  I'm simply going to encourage my Arkansas friends to go out and take a stand one way or the other.  I have a tremendous amount of respect for voters who make the most well-informed decision they can and stand by their convictions.  Especially young voters.  Some of you may know that I won a couple of awards with a research paper of mine about local opinions regarding negative political advertising.  I guess it was my way of taking my research course and doing something relevant and practical with it...especially since I wrote it during a particularly negative mid-term race.  People were actually interested in politics at the time!  If you're interested in reading it, leave me a comment and I'll see about sending a copy your way.  (I'm still learning some of this web stuff, and I will figure out the whole linking to e-mail thing soon...if you have advice, I PROMISE I'll listen!)   So...I'm headed home to vote.  I won't be making any entries for a few days, because my dad hasn't quite jumped on the Internet bandwagon yet.  I guess that's okay...I don't think he's any worse off for it.  Maybe I'll play the piano or help clean the pool or something...maybe head to Jonesboro for an afternoon.  The change of scenery will be nice.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A new and rather prevalent fad has taken shape on VH1...the list.  Anything that can be ranked is being ranked.  Obviously, with something as varied as the so-called "music" scene, some disagreements will take place.  However, their recent list on the 50 worst songs really bugged me.  Maybe it bothered me because I really liked some of the songs on the list and I was afraid they were right about them.  Maybe it bothered me because I really liked some of the songs on the list and I think they are wrong, but there's nothing I can do about it.  Any which way you go, I just didn't like most of it.    I was extremely relieved to see that rap made an appearance on the list many times.  I do like some rap, because some of it is very clever, but I will never, EVER refer to it as "music."  It's rap.    Rap.    Say it out loud.   Rap.  Not EVER...and I MEAN EVER...rap music.    They had the nerve to put Billy Joel on the list for one of my favorites of his.  I am also a die-hard Huey Lewis and the News fan, and they were on the list.  I'm not saying that Huey fronted the greatest band in history, but their music was just plain fun and they played their instruments.  That's more than anyone can say for J-Lo (who, regrettably, was only on the list once).    Another shocker...for me, anyway...Bobby McFerrin's "Don't Worry, Be Happy."  What's wrong with being optimistic? In this world of "cry-me-a-river-thrasher-metal-I-can't-play-a-tune-alternative-style-because-I'm-so-misunderstood" trash, a little peppy Caribbean flavor is in order.  The things that man can do with his voice are unbelievable...just listen to an entire CD of his and you will gain respect for him.  I'm not saying you have to like him, just give it a chance for what it's worth.  I was upset that the interviewees on the VH1 show said that any song without instruments sends up a red flag.    Folks, if you're going to criticize music, criticize it for something substantial, like the inability to carry a tune or making up words for the sake of creating the next incoherent teenage pop phrasing frenzy.  Give yourself some credibility.    Some of the songs on the list truly belonged there, and the logic that supported the decisions was right on the money.  Apply the same logic to everything, please!   Now, I'd like to hear from you on this one.  What do you think?  I think I'd like real music back, please.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am a small person.  Always have been, always will be.  It has been pre-established through family genetics that I would be small (with large and not-so-great teeth...go figure) for life.  I buy many of my fun clothes in the junior section, so conceivably I can stay trendy forever.  My business professional wear is best left to the petite section.  You know, the section for people like me...short, skinny, runt-like.  So...why on earth does the petite section have large sizes?  I can't even find clothes for myself in the petite section anymore! Last night I went shopping and found many suits labeled "large petite."  Does this not seem like a huge oxymoron to you? "Large" and "petite" go together like garlic and French toast.  Just doesn't work.    You know the old saying, "Just because it's in your size doesn't mean you should wear it"? I follow that one when it is dreadfully obvious that a certain outfit will not look good on me.  Many people don't have that kind of compassion for their fellow man.  Just watch "Cops" some afternoon.  I didn't ask to see your...well...everything.  I wouldn't feel comfortable in extremely revealing clothes.  It took me twenty years to get the courage to wear a two-piece bathing suit.  I'd like to thank the Britneys and Christinas of the world for bringing about many of our fashion problems.  Petite is petite, plain and simple.  There should be no provisions to make variations on this.  I've had a difficult enough time being the runt my whole life...at least let me have my clothing size! I'd love to be able to reclaim the petite section so that I might be able to wear something that doesn't have to go for alterations first.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Anyone who knows me knows that I get chicken-style scared of thunderstorms.  We just had a good one, too.  Thought the house was going to be struck by lightning since I was the only one home.  (Murphy's Law.  You get it.)  I don't know how it is that I can love the South as much as I do and hate storms.  It's not like I made a conscious choice to get scared out of my skin every time a front comes through.  It's just one of those things.  I turn into a jumpy, frantic cat-like individual.  I guess I should be thankful that I didn't grow up in Kansas or Oklahoma.  I wouldn't sleep from March to July if I lived there.  There are a few professions I do not envy, particularly in tornado season.  Given today's weather, I really would not want to be any kind of delivery person.  I've driven through the mother of all hailstorms before and I really don't feel like doing that again...scarred me for life.    I always thought I would love to be a meteorologist, but I don't think I would enjoy reporting from the studio for twelve straight hours and know that it was headed right my way.  It would be my luck that I would be the rookie they'd send to stand right in the middle of it and give live updates.  Storm chaser is definitely out of the question.  I doubt I'd make a good telephone operator or power company repair person during an electrical storm, either.    I wonder...is there much calling out there for a basement usher? Or perhaps a storm cellar inspector?   Whoops...it's getting dark again...have to go.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I, along with many others, have noticed how the advertisements on this page are tailored to the dominant topics.  Right now, it has to do with luck stuff, like charms...I guess the demographics information says this would be a good place to advertise them given my recent entry.  I wonder what happens with a totally random assortment of topics?   Tonight I am going to strive to be random.  Kind of like Mad Libs.  Ah, yes...let's watch the hilarity commence.  A warning...this will be goofy.  Some of it will make no sense, like door locks on a twenty-four hour convenience store.  (I feel like Doogie Howser every time I do this.  Entering the day's life lesson into a computer.)  Randomizing Schtuff...  You ever see the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man walking down Caraway? He must be looking for a good Chinese restaurant near the Sewanee River.  Or, perhaps he is going to Holland to buy a cuckoo clock.  I'm allergic to candlestick holders and cardboard boxes, but only on the second and third Tuesdays of the month.  And only when I'm driving at exactly 43 miles per hour in a truck while eating honeydew.  Off of a styrofoam plate.  (This is fun...it's a good escape!)  I know a dog whose pinky paw is longer than all its others.  By a whole three feet.  He sort of wobbles when he walks.  Unless, of course, he's running.  (I'm ready for my nervous breakdown, Mr. DeMille...)  Okay.  Enough of this.  I could seriously use some socialization time.  If anyone's looking to get away, think lake.  Lots of water.  Boats.  See ya!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I hope this is my good sign.  I found five four-leaf clovers in the front yard this evening.  Five.  I do believe I wished for the same thing on all of them.  Maybe one or two variations, but my big one, hopefully, will come true.  I think Forrest knows what it is, and I suppose he's putting in a good word with the man upstairs for me (as am I)!  I find it quite odd...I could never find those things as a kid and now I find them everywhere! Even when I step out of the car and see a small grassy area, I can usually manage to find one.  I found one the morning of my field commander audition two years ago, but there must have been a small oversight.  Or, perhaps it was lucky that I wasn't selected...after all, I don't know of many other places that super-flexible ankles are in the job description.  (If there's one thing in this life I could do well...the roll step is it.)  I hope that luck isn't all that turns the tide...I'm sure my father hopes so too, after paying for college! I'd like to think I have some desirable skills.  I know exactly where I want to use them, and anyone that knows me well would know where I really want to live.  I just hope it's a real option, and very soon.  After all, those little four-leaf clovers are curling up right this minute.  Symbolic, don't you think?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay! Thought of a topic!  I have not seen my original hair color, in full, in about five years.  I just can't stand the thought of going back to it.  It has something to do with the fact that I was not terribly happy in high school and I got it highlighted to sort of end that phase of my life.  I'm trying to be less drastic with the blonde now, but it doesn't ever turn out quite like I want.  I do not want it to be dark dark dark again, especially for summer, since it usually lightens somewhat due to my sunbathing habits.  My roots started showing noticeably about two and a half weeks ago.  I don't have the money right this minute to go have a professional job done, and I'm trying to let my hair grow before I do anything anyway, so Mom and I decided to get one of those new home color streaking kits to do some touching up.  Needless to say, I was quite nervous, thinking of some of the hair disasters I had the misfortune to witness and, at times, have a hand in with home kits.    I decided to go ahead and go for it.  You just mix up the chemicals, take a little brush and apply in a few areas.  Easy enough.  Then I had to sit practically motionless for thirty minutes and then rinse.    I was pleasantly surprised with the results! Once I dried my hair, it had kind of a honey glow to it.  Almost iridescent.  I turn one way, I have a strawberry-reddish color.  Another way, I have bright blondes.  Yet another view brings darker hues.  The overall look is shimmering and golden...looks very pleasing, if I say so myself.  Not too dramatic...very natural.  It also buys me some time.  I can let it grow a bit before visiting a salon.  So, if you're thinking about making a change and you don't want to go overboard, try one of those home kits with the streaking comb.  They're easy to use and have a natural result.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Howdy!  Took a little time away from the blog this weekend to help my brother move home and celebrate Mother's Day.  Now, I have to think of something to write about since I have developed slight writer's block.  That doesn't happen to me very often...there's usually something to write.  I'll write later and see what happens...:)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm staying in Heber Springs.  North Central Arkansas.  The Natural State.  And nature crosses our street every day.  The house is in a heavily wooded area just a few blocks from the lake.  Matter of fact, I can hear the boat motors humming right now.  Technically, it's in the city limits, but you wouldn't think it was.  I almost ran over a lizard while I was bringing my lunch home a few minutes ago.  Two nights ago, I had to stop dead in my tracks to let a slow-moving armadillo cross the road.  He was taking his sweet time, and I didn't want to hit one of the many hill critters we have, including the deer waiting in the wings.  We can have about six or seven deer running through our front yard at any time, not to mention the squirrels building nests in our attic and getting trapped in the walls on occasion.  There used to be a grey fox running around out here, and neighboring communities had reported seeing bears in the woods.  These hill critters sure are persistent.  And I would be remiss if I didn't mention the four neighborhood cats my poor little kitty has attracted.  One of them is absolutely adorable...and apparently all the boy cats thought so, too.  I just hope we don't inherit all her kittens.    This is a little different from growing up in the woods in Corning.  Delta critters...lots of snakes, skunks, mosquitoes and raccoons.  Once in a great while someone would see a deer or hear a coyote.  I was always a second too late.  I guess all the farming and the highway were a deterrent to the larger animals.  Still, I liked those woods, since we were able to have the swimming pool in the backyard (where I found many pet frogs) and all the room in the world to run around, ride bikes, and just have fun.  Until dark, when the Arkansas state bird came out.  After our house burned down in 1992, I remember my cat had taken off into the woods not to be seen again...or so we thought.  About six weeks later, we went out to the "house" and heard a puny noise...the cat was sitting about ten feet up in a charred tree.  Needless to say, she didn't hang around very long at our temporary home.  We did bring our own problem on ourselves once, buying an ill-tempered ferret as a family pet.  Wiggles was her name.  She liked to bite.  And she smelled funny.  She wound up being shuffled in a sort of foster situation...a trustworthy student of my mother's adopted her, then had to give her away like we did.  Goofy little weasel.  Wonder where she finally wound up...  Anyway, this is definitely a reflection of our state nickname.  Perhaps if I were Snow White the little animals would meander right up to me and sing or something.  It could happen...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I could tell today was going to be a winner from the second I rolled out of bed.  I forgot that my mom had partially burned up the toaster oven last night, so breakfast was an "in a hurry style" Mickey D's.  This is not before I turned on aforementioned toaster oven and watched smoke roll through the sides.  The Eggo tasted like rubber, so I threw it in the microwave to nuke the ice off of it.  Still tasted like rubber, so some small animal is probably picking at it now.  Then, it was off for an oil change, which went well.  Next on the agenda:  head to a job fair.  I met Forrest for lunch, which was the high point of my day.  I did, however, see my life flash before my eyes in when I drove past a gas station...the prices were:  $1.89 regular...$1.99 mid-grade...$2.09 SUPREME.  TWO DOLLARS AND NINE CENTS A GALLON?  I buy regular, but still!  I thought that only happened in really big cities, like Chicago!  This made me feel horrible, since I got a gas guzzler for graduation.  Now I'm really trapped.  So, I visited the job fair.  Afterwards, I paid my buck-fifty for parking, got in my car and drove away with my $1.79 gasoline quickly burning out of my tank.  Still, every thought in my head drifted back to TWO DOLLARS AND NINE CENTS A GALLON.  Three summers ago it was ONE DOLLAR AND NINE CENTS on the Fourth of July.  I took economics, but the fact that I know the logistics about the prices doesn't make me feel any better.  If anyone wants to visit me, I'll chip in a few cents (or nine...make it an even two dollars) for gas.  I'll give you directions.  I'm not going anywhere for a while, unless I get THE call.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I got to talking to my brother yesterday and we both realized that very few students left in the ASU band program remember the mother of all basketball tournament trips...  Mobile, Alabama!  It started with your typical eight-hour overnight bus trip, leaving Jonesboro at midnight in the freezing cold of early March.  Trying to sleep was a futile effort.  Eight hours later and thirty degrees warmer...we get off the bus at a McDonald's just outside of Mobile, eat breakfast, and head straight to the arena to watch the women's game, which ended their tournament rather quickly.  Now, we FINALLY get to go to the hotel.  My three designated roommates and I take our keys and open up the room...only to find that it is occupied! When they switched our keys, they sent us up to a very nice club floor since they had an empty room.  Then, everyone showered and fell asleep.  Thus begins the adventure.  Dinner...rather routine.  Most people slept until late that night, then EVERYONE woke up, beginning a five-day pattern of nocturnal habits.  It's an easy pattern...wake up for game, go to sleep when sun rises, play music all night.  Or cards.  I played my fair share of spades for a while.  We did a little sightseeing some of those days, visiting the battleship or going out to nicer restaurants.  But nighttime was the high point of the day.  Except for the final night, when we left at 11 p.m...and we thought we'd never see three of our pals again when they made a last-minute taxi run.  I can't possibly go into everything that happened on that trip, but nothing as of yet has surpassed it in terms of fun.  It was my first tournament trip, and I went on two more, but they were nowhere near that one, even though one was in New Orleans! Oh, yeah...the men's team made it to the semifinals somewhere in that chain of events, but lost to the home team in front of their very rowdy crowd.  I hope that someday another generation of...to use a term from someone I know..."cool" folks will evolve and have a trip like that...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      All right...I mentioned the Harry Connick, Jr. concert one time and I get the whole "my, the tickets are expensive" thing.  Yes, they are.  Yes, I'm broke too.  But, I can safely say that the going rate for those tickets is much less than it could be, comparatively speaking.  That's what I've heard on the radio and such.  See, I recently dished out twenty bucks to go see Terence Blanchard.  The sound system was subpar, the driving conditions from the storms were terrible, and I was disappointed overall.  That's the first jazz concert I've been to that disappointed me.  Granted, I heard one tune that I really enjoyed, enough to want to go buy the CD, but I couldn't really hear the soloistic work over the guitar.  Maybe it's because the amp was pointed directly between my eyes.  I am pretty sure the rest of the summer concert series at the garden will not be as expensive.  I haven't checked on prices, but I would put my last few cents down to see every last one of them.  I was truly impressed with the lineup, and I love the atmosphere.  Check out the lineup  urlLink here .  Meanwhile, enjoy the impending summer weather.  It's beautiful today!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay...this entry couldn't wait.  My poor, dear, sweet little kitty cat is sitting in the garage with an ear full of staples.  Why, you ask? Well, he had his corrective surgery for a hematoma and his ear will never look the same again.  Looks like raw hamburger meat.  Now we're supposed to watch him and make sure he doesn't pick at it.  Doesn't pick at it? Are we insane? It's a CAT.  Cats pick at everything.  I'm having flashbacks to our poor little Schnauzer...Scooter.  May he rest in peace.  He had his ears fixed once, and he wound up living the majority of his doomed little life with a funnel on his head.  He looked like a freakin' vacuum cleaner when he ate.  He also stepped on a thorn and had an abscessed foot, hit his head at the vet and had to have stitches, got snake bitten once, and had an inherited epileptic condition that ultimately ended his life.  I thought about making greeting cards with his picture on the front.  The caption..."Think YOU'RE having a bad day?" He was the most expensive doggie we ever had.  Most dogs from Corning met their fate on U.S. Highway 67.  Poor little Scooter didn't quite make it that far.  On a lighter note...I've just read the concert list for the Memphis Botannical Gardens this summer...and it's awesome.  Ya'll let me know if you're interested in, oh, say, Harry Connick, Jr. tickets!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Greetings and salutations! Good day and hello! Hola!  I've been on a major Yoo Hoo kick lately.  It's in the little refrigerator on the back porch, next to the grape juice and Miller Lite.  The beer's not mine.  I really don't know who claims it at this point in time.    Anyway, I'm not crazy about chocolate like I was in high school, but there's something about a nice, cold, refreshing Yoo Hoo that makes me happy.  I've been drinking about two a day for three weeks now.  No, I am not a large couch potato by now, even though I've left a nice dent in my spot on the sofa.  I thought maybe unemployment plus Yoo Hoo would bring about that growth spurt I've been waiting on for the past twenty-three years.    WRONG!  I'm still a walking toothpick.  I turned sideways last week and my mom spent three hours trying to find me!  I stepped on a scale last month and it registered negative numbers!  So, I'm trying to do something about it.  Weight training.  I've got time on my hands, and a brand new set of weights to work with.  Nothing huge, just enough to try to build up, well...something.  I'm really looking forward to the day my dad gets the swimming pool ready.  Believe it or not, I used to go out there every day and swim laps in all the strokes.  Butterfly, breaststroke, freestyle, back...I used to even try to make up new ones!  I never joined the Corning swim team, though, because I wanted to keep enjoying swimming.  I didn't want it to feel like a chore.  I wanted to be able to stop and play "Jump or Dive" on a whim.  I love being on and in the water, and I think my decision to keep it recreational has helped that.  People don't really realize those things about me...that I actually channeled all that energy into athletic stuff.  I can throw a pretty good spiral, ace a pretty good tennis serve, and I once was a pretty good gymnast.  But, I enjoyed playing music too much and had to study hard to keep ahead, so I didn't have time for any of that on school teams.  I had to settle for being a good half-hour pre-marching rehearsal frisbee player in college.    So, if anyone is looking for a good pickup game of frisbee, an afternoon of water sports, baseball, tennis, or even catch, come on over!  I've got Yoo Hoo for when you get thirsty!  I've gotten a request to write some of my infamous old short stories.  As soon as I can get some good ideas, it'll happen.  Okay, Vinessa?!? :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I watched Saturday Night Live last night despite the recent poor quality of the show.  What I saw was a host that couldn't get their act together and laughed through nearly every skit.  One of the sketches was pretty funny because they were cracking up, but it got a wee bit old by the third screwup.    They need some real talent.  I'm starting to doubt real talent exists anymore.  True, there are some members of the current cast being swallowed up and branded with the overall label even though they don't deserve it.  At least two of them have real potential, if the writing was there.  Bad news from the veterinarian...my poor little kitty cat has "pillow ear."  In other words, one of his ears is swollen and lopped over, making him look positively goofy and feel pretty rotten.  He's having surgery tomorrow, but they said his ear will never quite look normal again.  He never has really had a name, but I've been calling him Floppy lately.  I think this name could finally stick...  I don't really feel like digging up a quote today.  I'm too sick of my current situation and I'd like to roll in self-pity for a while.  Just a few minutes.  I know that I was always perky and smiling in college, and now I can understand why some people found it revolting that someone could always be that happy.  I can't wait to move.  I can't wait to make my own money and live in my own apartment.  I can't wait to socialize again without feeling like I'm bugging the snot out of everyone.  And I really can't wait to switch cell phone plans so that I can speak more than two minutes a month!  Right now, I make calls from home and people don't answer because they don't recognize the number (it's what I'm telling myself, anyway). The good job prospects keep me going...  Isn't my site count pathetic? ;)  I wish the ASU folks luck on the rest of their finals! There's something I don't miss...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahh...the Kentucky Derby.  The most thrilling two minutes in sports.  I've promised myself I will go someday, but I'm stuck here in soggy Heber Springs today watching it on television.  Oh, well.  I guess you see more of the action this way.  I'd probably only see the back of somebody's hat at Churchill Downs.  Maybe I should learn how to make a mint julep to enhance the experience.  I'd probably hate it.  I would like to see the Oaklawn horse, Smarty Jones, win this one.  May Day, and I'm STILL living at home.  Maybe I should give up on the job search and begin my work on the great American novel.  And screenplay.  And perfect my interpretive dance skills.    I finally got to see the 2004 yearbook.  I always get really excited to see a new yearbook.  But, I really like old ones...like when they used to put hometowns next to every name, many years ago.  Old high school yearbooks are neat, too...especially with student quotes.  Of course, fewer college students actually get their pictures made anymore.  I'm always about an inch outside of the photos...I see pictures that I can identify exactly where I should be!  I didn't really expect to be in this yearbook since I was only there one semester.  Today's Family Guy words of wisdom...from Peter to Lois... "You're my silver medal."
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I should kick myself.  Sometimes I catch myself watching MTV.  Some of the shows are painfully addictive, but not too great.  However, the MTV I remember (before the cable ban of '90 or '91) of my early youth actually showed...are you ready for this...music videos.  Janet Jackson, Bon Jovi, Paula Abdul...videos.  MUSIC TELEVISION.  Not only are the majority of the new shows  not  even remotely related to music, they are also the most ill-conceived shows in history that have only created a stereotype for the American youth.  I believe that the new trends in programming are degrading to twenty-somethings.  We are not all attracted to the slick-haired drunk guy with six pack abs who will violate any girl in a bathing suit.  We do not all believe that Britney Spears is the most talented "musician" ever to grace the planet.  We do not all think that tuna really is a chicken that lives in the ocean.    But, nooooo.  MTV makes us all look like idiots.    "Eat this pile of rotting, raw cow innards for a chance to win five bucks and get on national television."  No, thanks! I do not need to contract e.coli just to get on television.    In a generation where no one learns how to spell a full word due to the abbreviation of anything and everything, it's no wonder nobody trusts young adults.  Someone please...PLEASE...make it stop!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I can recall one of the major things for my circle of friends to do during college was come up with theories that help explain the little things.  There were rules that were developed as well.  (Chew, swallow, speak.)  I was watching television the other night and flipped channels...Beetlejuice was on one of the networks.  I've loved that movie for years, and when I started watching, it reminded me of one of our little theories.  So, I began to explain this theory to my mom, telling her that we believed that saying someone's name at least three times would make them appear.    Specifically, I told her about a handful of people that, through no fault of their own, simply seem to exemplify this theory constantly.  I laughed the whole time thinking about at least one person that did tend to show up in unexpected places if anyone asked about this person.  Six o'clock...time for me to turn off Beetlejuice and turn on the news.    Lo and behold...  The person I had mentioned was on the news that day.  Now, my brother and I believe we have some kind of family-psychic-telekinetic ability (he thinks it's because he was born at 11:11).  Our gut instincts have been eerily and unfortunately correct on more than one occasion...through dreams, thoughts, intuition.  Needless to say, this freaked me out.   But...I don't think I'll "geaux" into the details.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I feel like all I do these days is wait.  I even had a dream a few days ago that exemplifies my life.  I called someone to come out to my dad's to go swimming with me.  They said they'd be over in a few minutes.  I waited...  ...and waited...  ...and waited...  ...and woke up before they showed.  It was when I woke up that I realized that my whole existence has been a waiting game.  The only thing I did before anyone else I knew was read.  I really cannot remember a time that I couldn't read.    Granted, I have been proactive about many things, but you take action, then you wait.  (Odd..."wait" starts to sound funny after you say it a few times.)  Yep, I've waited my fair share and it's time for something good.  I sincerely believe that things will be awesome for me since I have put in a good long wait on...well...everything.  It should just make the good that much sweeter.  Right now, I have to put up with the jokes and the teasing about my waiting game.  (Like the time someone in high school said I'd be an old maid...forever.  Or the times I visit people and they make cracks about my living off the land, so to speak.  Ugh!)  I take great solace in knowing that Independence Day is coming, and no one will care about that stuff for the time...they'll all be too intoxicated to care.    So...I'll just wait until next Saturday for the big party.  That one's definitely worth it.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Fun, true story for all you fans out there.  A few days ago, after my weekend excursion to Clay County for Father's Day, my mom decides she wants to test her new fishing lure at the lake.  We're just about a block from the water, so we decided to go down there, even though it's not a great fishing spot.  I got to take a few turns casting on her reel, which is different from ones I've used in the past.  I'm really starting to get the hang of it, too...  Then...  I decide to really let it fly.  I mean, I leaned back and put everything I had into this particular cast.  I heave the line out...then I hear something akin to "WOOOOOSH!"  The lure has come loose, sailed a hundred feet out into the water, and landed gracefully.    My mom, who hasn't quite realized that her lure is no longer attached to the line, looks at me with an amazed expression on her face and says, "Wow...good job!"  I look at her, dumbfounded, and look at the fishing line flapping in the breeze on the end of the rod.    Ding Ding Ding!  (That's the sound of putting two and two together.)  Silence.  Hysterical laughter.  There may now be a bass in the middle of Greers Ferry Lake chewing on a plastic fish.  Perhaps a dumb bass...*snicker*...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had a memory the other day about my internship last summer.  Basically, it involves the fact that some jokes don't translate well across cultures...no matter how basic you think it is.  Somehow or another, I (with little working knowledge of the road system in Pulaski County) wound up the designated driver for a group of fellow interns on the day we went on media tours.  This particular morning we went to the Clear Channel studios and then back to KARK near the capitol building.  We were actually on the news that day, and, as usual, I was the only enthusiastic face in the bunch.  Sound familiar?  ANYWAY...  In my car were three other interns, all in the creative department.  However, I was the only American-born person in the car.  The others were originally from Poland, Taiwan, and South Africa.  So, my usual Arkansan wit and banter was met with interesting stares.  Especially when I saw a fairly common road sign.  Dip.  Simple, yes.  So was my joke.    "Hey...they knew you were coming and put up a sign for you!" Snicker, laugh.  I'd heard it before...people used to get me on that one.  Just a little kidding.  Laugh, ha ha, yada yada.  Here's what I hear from the backseat.  "Huh?"  ...chirp chirp...chirp chirp...  "Sara...is that Arkansas humor?"
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's been a few days since my last post.  Turmoil...I just needed a couple of days to collect my thoughts.  No deaths or anything, just personal crisis.  If I ignored you on messenger or something, it's not that I'm mad at anyone...just didn't feel like talking.  E-mail me for more details...if you want the whole nine yards.  I'm heading up to my dad's for Father's Day.  Most of the cards I saw were about fathers who tinkered with tools and repaired stuff.  My dad's more of a yard work guy; not so much the socket wrench stuff.  I can remember being asked to help (a.k.a. "being forced to help") lay sod in the yard at our new house ten years ago.  We figured he'd prefer a card with a little smart-mouth bite to it, so we got him one that looked like it had been scribbled and changed from a different card.  That brings up an interesting story.  When I was in high school, my mom's boyfriend gave me and my brother Christmas cards.  However, they were used Christmas cards...in other words, they had been sent to him from someone else.  He scribbled out all the other names and wrote his name in it instead.  The other surprise? I open my card and two five-dollar bills fall out.  My brother opens his and two twenty-dollar bills fall out! Oops...  I must say it was kind of difficult to get that one straightened out, after my lil' bro thought he'd made out with thirty bucks more than me.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is just one of those days.    Pure boredom, rain and clouds define my little corner of the world this afternoon.  I'm sitting at the computer in an empty house watching the rain slowly drag this day along.  The ceiling fan continues its pointless chore, only to be upstaged every thirty minutes by the air conditioner.    I wonder if the fan ever becomes jealous...I mean, all it does is keep stale, hot air circulating in an endless battle with the vaulted ceiling.  The air conditioner, on the other hand, sends a much-needed blast of cool air up through the vents at ground level.  I am much closer to the ground than the ceiling.  I'd be jealous if I were that ceiling fan.  It's like the pesky little brother of the house, stirring up just enough dust to make me sneeze and keeping just enough heat funneling downward to irritate me.  It has to hold that long chain with a smirking turtle figurine on the end so that short people like me can adjust how quickly or slowly we prefer to swelter.  I only thank that fan when I've been sweating and I don't realize that the air is warmer than it should be...I just notice moving air.    But, no, I don't have many thoughts of admiration towards the ceiling fan.  I'm in love with the air conditioner.    Like I said, today's just another day.  Perhaps tomorrow I'll ponder thoughts in favor of our new electric can opener over the manual one.    Exciting.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Tina was right; it's unbelieveably hot for this time of year.  I would also like to add my two cents and make sure everyone is keeping well-hydrated.  I made my own lovely pitcher of lemonade yesterday and hope to drink that instead of the three million sodas I've been drinking!  I remember a fishing trip I took a few years ago, during the last week of July.  I was on a fishing river, not a swimming river...the water is about 55 degrees.  However, the water was perfect for dipping a shirt or towel into and covering my sunburned shoulders.    Which leads me into my stupidity...I have a lopsided sunburn because the pool chair I sat in yesterday hurt way too much to turn over and get my back.  So, I have a distinct bright red line marking where I neglected two things: sunscreen and the "brown-on-one-side-then-turn- over" edict.    I graduated high school in 1999, which was the year the sunscreen song came out.  It's the truth...wear it! I'm miserably pink...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some people just shouldn't pick their own children's names.  They just don't seem to get it.  I was just watching the news and heard that Courteney Cox-Arquette had a baby girl.  Then, I sat back and awaited the name, praying it was traditional.  Nope.  They named the kid Coco.  These are not poodles or Siamese cats.  These are HUMAN BEINGS whose names not only follow them everywhere, they can indirectly impact the way others perceive them.  As if this kid's not going to have a hard enough time growing up in a two-celebrity household!   Every family has their eccentricities, including mine.  At least, thank goodness, they had the soundness of mind to make sure I didn't wind up with a name like Vanilla Day.  My name was a little bit of a work in progress, as I have been told.  I believe they said I was originally going to be Rachel.  But, this brings up the issue of finding something that fits my last name.  There aren't that many girl's names that fit with it! I think they got it right, though.    The only problem I have is that people try to add the "h" to the end of my name.  People always ask..."How do you spell that?" I finally got so tired of explaining it that I started telling people I spell "Sara" with an "S." 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Having taken many advertising classes in college, I pay more attention to ads than most.  It's just a given fact that those of us who study it closely are very observant when it comes to the time between shows.    I know from my experiences that research is vital in creating a solid advertising campaign.  Slip up, and someone will point out your mistakes...it's better that they do it at the agency than after the spot goes public.  However...somebody made an ironic judgment call that has me scratching my head.    I don't know who the agency of record is for this particular client, but it is an electric company that I will not name.  It's nothing hugely obvious to most, but not only did I study advertising, I studied music as well, and I approach that discipline with a more critical ear.    Basically, it has something to do with the background music.  Someone pointed out the irony in a daily newspaper about a month after I first noticed it and made remarks.  The spot itself is fine...one of those "we're there for you" types of things.  But, the background tune begins to annoy me quickly because I know what it is, and it seems much more fitting for advertising another form of power.  The tune?    "Classical Gas."
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Such a beautiful summer's evening seems befitting of the final ceremony paying respect to President Reagan.  I have been watching all the ceremonies this week, and it occurred to me that I had never seen an American state funeral in my lifetime.  It also seems amazing to me that such an outpouring of honor and dignity has been given to a man the public has not seen in slightly over a decade.    In watching many of the ceremonies, I was especially amazed at parents who took their young children to witness history.  Most of the children were not yet born when Reagan left office.  Granted, I was only in elementary school when he left, but I did get to see some of the results of his wonderful actions.  Of course, I was born thirty-five, so I paid attention to things like that. ;)  I took a little trip to Jonesboro yesterday, and ran into just about everyone.  I wound up going to the library with my brother and Matt to listen to old Tribe concerts.  When we left, Grant's phone rang.  I heard him start a typical conversation, and then he said,  "Ray Charles died?"  Grant was on KAIT last night doing a tribute to the music legend. I don't even think the word "legend" can sum up his particular brand of genius.  Now, as the sun sets tonight, we are reminded of not one, but two legends in American history, both of which left well-earned respect in their paths.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I sincerely hope everyone likes my new setup here.  I'm still learning some of the ins and outs of blogging, so bear with me.    I decided that the lighthouse better suited my interests than the cut and dried basic template I had before.  I think it is more aesthetically pleasing...even if it does slightly resemble a funeral program.  I hope changing just one little thing will help change my fortune.  I'm in a bit of a rut here.    This is my least insightful and expository entry to date, so forgive me...I've been fighting with the computer for over an hour! Hopefully I will be adding photos sometime soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The last time I went to my dad's, we wound up watching "Back to the Future III."  It was on TBS, and my dad had never actually seen the whole thing.  So, I watched it for the millionth time.  I have the trilogy on DVD, and I know practically every line, but it never really gets old.  True new classics.    I love those movies, but the time continuum issues bug me when I have a lot of time to think about them.  For one, the second movie should be obsolete given the central theme and message of the third, which says that the future is not set.  The basis for that second movie involves altering future history.  If the future is not set, why didn't Doc Brown, in his infinite scientific wisdom, decide only to travel to the past? With no set future, what in the world would one expect to see traveling into the future? According to this convention, there are far too many variables for the future to have any concept to it!  Be that as it may, the movie portrays the year 2015, which is now not terribly far away, as a flying-car, post-mega-inflation parallel to the Hill Valleys of 1955 and 1985.  The parallelism among the films is classic; it's very detailed down to the inevitable chases in the town square.  Now, we learn from the first film that knowing too much about your own future could create a major paradox, unraveling the threads of the space-time continuum to ultimately rip apart the universe.  Doc learns a bit about his future, though, by reading the letter that foretells his violent death.    HOWEVER...  Are we left to assume that the shooting would actually take place, given that he and Marty had slightly altered the past? Since it all fits in a loop, and he apparently must "rip off" the plutonium in order to travel in the first place, these events probably would occur.  But, he severely goes against his own doctrine of ignorance about the future by going forward in time, setting the stage for the second movie.    Finally, at the end of the third movie, Doc travels forward from 1885 to 1985 to show off his new time machine.  He explains to Marty and Jennifer about his discovery that the future is not set and that they should make it whatever they want it to be.  Then, he flies...yes, flies...away on his steam-engine locomotive time machine, saying he had already been to the future.  Now, it seems to me that if the future was not set, hover conversion might not actually happen.    This is giving me a headache.  I cannot believe I've stooped to over-analyze one of the most genuinely entertaining movie series of my lifetime.  I just think that if time travel were really possible, we might have seen some folks from the future by now, unless they are being much more careful than Doc and Marty in revealing themselves.  Or, perhaps our era in history is not interesting enough for travelers to visit!  Whew.  I could rack my brain over this all day.    By the way...autochthonous means indigenous or Aboriginal.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, Shane...this blog's for you.  Six summers ago I attended Arkansas Governor's School.  It's a program for rising high school seniors designed to put 400 of the state's "best and brightest" in a totally unique academic and social environment, discussing the best of twentieth century, well, everything.  My "Area I," or major subject for the program, was drama.  I figure very few of my college friends know that I once really enjoyed theater.    So...  We're about two weeks into the six-week program when our drama class does some improv exercises much like the ones on "Whose Line." Now, I was a very self-conscious little girl from Nowhere, Arkansas thrown in a room full of people who had done some real stage acting.  Needless to say, I was a bit nervous when I was paired with a guy from Little Rock Central for the exercise.  We are given our little poses and topics, and just as we step on the stage, I hear one of my classmates whisper, "She reminds me of someone."  After class, this girl walks up to me and says that I am like the lady from the Beverly Hillbillies movie...the one that Lily Tomlin plays.  Miss Hathaway.  I heard that name all summer.  From EVERYONE.  They even called me that when they wrote in my AGS yearbook.  I thought it died with the beginning of my senior year, but I was wrong.  It resurfaced five years later, by two people who knew nothing of my previous experience.    I guess it's the truth.  I guess there are far worse people to be compared with in this world.  I was just watching an old Carol Burnett clip and she does resemble me when she was younger.    And, hey!  At least she's funny. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dreams are strange.  I've written about them before.  There are some mornings that I don't want to wake up because they are so pleasant.  Then again, there are those mornings, like today, that daylight couldn't show its face fast enough.  This one's weird...maybe writing it down will help me sort it out.  Or, it could just be an amusing tale for your pleasure.    My whole family was at my grandmother's house.  She lives a few miles from a large power plant.  You can't see it from her back porch, but in this dream, it looked like it was in the back yard.  (The storyline in this dream was in bits and pieces, so bear with me.)  Suddenly I look at one of the smokestacks, and a huge mushroom cloud bursts from the top.    Now, one of the things I know in waking life is that it is NOT a nuclear plant.  I have a feeling that whole element came from my listening to President Bush mispronounce "nuclear" in a speech.  In this particular dream, it was a nuclear plant, and we knew immediately that we were in trouble.  Everyone, that is, except for my mom.    She got a little ticked at me for panicking.  We knew it was certain disaster, and she kept saying that there was nothing we could do; we just had to live with it.  As long as we could, that is.  It's odd how you can have a physiological response in a dream...my skin was tingling...I seriously doubt this is the actual impact of nuclear fallout to your central nervous system.  I NEVER want to find out what that's like.    I woke up no worse for the wear.  I was a bit scared that I would wake up and not be able to move...ever happen to you? It's creepy.  It usually happens to me when my regular sleep pattern is disrupted for a few days.  I've read a few things about it...I think they call it sleep paralysis.  Apparently, it's harmless, but it is SO scary when it happens.  Part of you is awake, but you can't move a muscle, talk, swallow, blink...anything.  It may only be a few seconds, but it feels like forever.  It's only happened to me about three times, but that is three too many.  The last time was three years ago after the Mobile trip...talk about disrupted sleep patterns...  Well...I think I'm off for a few days to my dad's for a weekend visiting by the pool.  Have a nice one!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Big word, huh.  I thought so, too.  I especially thought it was pretty ruthless to ask a fourteen-year-old to spell it!  But, he got it right, and secured his place as the best speller in America.  I've spent my afternoon watching nervous children spell words.  Reminds me of when I competed, although I didn't make it past the county level.  Basically, I studied too much and wasted my energy on words that never even appeared in competition.  I don't think I would have been too happy to compete at the national level.  Most of these children look terrified, and, while they are light years ahead of most people in their grasp of language, they are bound to have some adjustment issues.  When I look back on it, it's unbelievable how young these kids really are when they are thrown into the proverbial pressure cooker.    However, if any of them are like me, they probably do it all for themselves and the quest for perfection.  It took a long time for me to realize that I didn't have to be great at everything to be satisfied.  I didn't get grades below an A until college, and it was a relief.  Now, I'm not endorsing total slacking, but there comes a point where you have to ask yourself if all the sacrifice is actually worth it.  When I lightened up about all of it, things came much easier...and my grades were no worse for the wear.  Even better at times! And...I had some more fun.  You know what might be a little bit fun right now? Figuring out what that darn word means.  I'll let you know!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Good afternoon, one and all!   I've been digging through my computer files today, just for kicks, and I realized how incredibly sentimental I am!  It's bordering on packrat.  I have a feeling it stems from having lost absolutely all of my possessions in a fire at a young age, and I don't want to take anything for granted...ever. I sometimes still miss some of the photos that we'll never see again.    I save a lot of my favorite e-mails.  I also save letters and cards from Christmas, birthdays, and my times away at things like Governor's School.  (Most of you know that I am a card fanatic...nearly everyone gets a Christmas card.  I fell down on the job this year, though, with graduation and moving...sorry!) Some are silly, but most reveal little things about my friends that their written words capture more eloquently than any photo.  I even have some that I saved from my time at Hendrix.  It's a way to keep those friends around, even though I rarely see them.    I also take lots of pictures.  I'm about to start working again on the scrapbook I started in the fall, and I hope to put lots of pictures on this site in the near future.  Digging those out of the closet will be a monumental task, though! I don't know how many of you really want to see what I looked like at age eight, but I might post one or two to give you an idea.  Let me just say that any photo from 1992 to 1999 inevitably showed off my metal mouth.    My high school classmates swore I was born with braces.  Try playing the trumpet like that.  It hurts like nobody's fool after about three hours.  When I made the All-State bands, a few directors took notice that I was, in fact, the only trumpeter with braces that year, and always had sympathetic words.  I would just reach in my pocket, produce a tube of Anbesol, making them laugh and realize that I knew how to handle it.  Of course, that year was particularly difficult, since I also had the added pain of having the darn things tightened the day before I left for the clinic!   For those of you who never experienced the torture of braces, a tightening, or, in orthodontic circles, an "adjustment," makes eating cereal a daunting task.  AND...when you get them on for the first time, they rub nice raw spots inside your mouth.  I remember taking Twizzlers and jamming them under my lip to stop that.  My trumpet playing left semi-permanent square indentations, too!  Of course, at the orthodontist's office, they try to make things fun for you, like letting you pick the colors of the little rubber bands that go around the brackets.  I chose a light sea green once and never did it again after someone called me "Salad Shooter." School colors were popular, too, but the yellow and black made me look like I had holes in every other tooth.  I began asking for generic gray.    I didn't mind the way braces looked.  Another odd thing...one of the nurses added an interesting twist to my look.  I had requested metal braces instead of clear, and my top ones were metal.  However, when I went back for the bottom teeth, for some odd reason she placed clear brackets.  They felt kind of strange, but I didn't smile much with my bottom teeth anyway, so it was no big deal.  Except for removal.  They remove the clear ones differently than metal, and if you accidentally open your eye, you could be gouged by flying brackets when they pop the suckers off.  I should know.    Ahh...physically painful memories.  I think I'll go outside and add a sunburn to the list.  I look downright ghastly this year, since I don't have Premiere Tans around the corner.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      All righty, faithful readers o'mine! (All five of you...)  This could very well be my last post for a while, as I am moving tomorrow and don't plan on setting up Internet access for a few weeks.   Since I don't have anything monumental to say (save for "ouch, my arms are sore") I think I will just leave it at this and go about the business of cramming personal items into small vehicular spaces.  And watching what's left of my money go away quickly.  Have a good weekend! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I did not realize what a monumental task my move would be this time around.&nbsp; I have found stuff in dresser drawers and closets that I completely forgot I had! Some of this stuff could be valuable in the future...magazines, basketball cards&nbsp;and such.&nbsp; The vast majority of my belongings, though, have that priceless sentimental value.  Dust isn't what I hoped to find.&nbsp; I found plenty of that.&nbsp; Dust is one of those physical oddities.&nbsp; It can find its way into places that nothing else can.&nbsp;   My goodness, I'm tired! My room is upstairs, so I'm dragging everything downstairs to make things easier next week.&nbsp; If any of you have packing tips you would like to send my way, please do so! Better yet, if anyone wants to volunteer...  Speaking of hassles...I am having computer trouble.&nbsp; Nothing&nbsp;gets under my skin&nbsp;more than dealing with computer problems created by&nbsp;someone who is&nbsp;out to do nothing but cause trouble.&nbsp;&nbsp;  On that note, I'm going to take a small nap.&nbsp; Visions of pop-up ads are dancing in my head. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Everybody was right.   As soon as you get a job, the phone starts ringing.&nbsp; The phone has been ringing all morning for me...for the first time in months.&nbsp; However, I am confident that what I will be doing is right for me and that I am getting a great deal.&nbsp; I can't wait to get started.&nbsp;   I suppose I should&nbsp;be sorting through stuff right now.&nbsp; I have a closet that needs to be tackled, several boxes to sift through, and a mini-storage unit half-full of my living possessions.&nbsp; I can't quite make myself do it right this minute, since my right leg still has permanent gas pedal syndrome from all the driving I've done this week.&nbsp; At least the headache's gone.   Speaking of which...you all should see the pathetic job I did of washing my car.&nbsp; I made a few mistakes...   1.&nbsp; Washing while tired.&nbsp; Not good for appearances' sake.&nbsp; I wanted to get the mud off certain&nbsp;spots, and I didn't think too much about the other places.  2.&nbsp; Washing in bad lighting.&nbsp; Also not good for appearances' sake.&nbsp; It was around 8 p.m., and we have lots of trees, so I neglected to see the streaks I left behind.&nbsp; My dad was quick to point them out, though!  3.&nbsp; Washing with small cloth.&nbsp; Doesn't work on big vehicle.&nbsp; I think I just spread the mud around.   I think I'll wash it again tomorrow.&nbsp; Unless, of course, it rains.&nbsp; I guess if I really want it to rain, I should wash my car.&nbsp; Murphy's Law.&nbsp;   Just like the phone.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've never loved a headache more in my life.  It's the one that comes with finding a place to live, trying to get things set up, et cetera...  It's a good one.&nbsp; One that I worried would never happen.&nbsp; I really don't want to post too many details about things, so give me a call or e-mail and you'll get the whole story (that is, unless I have already talked your ear off).  I could write more...but I'm thinking too much right now.&nbsp; I'm not doing my best writing in this particular situation.&nbsp; Maybe I should think of something introspective.&nbsp; Something deeply riveting and thoughtful.&nbsp;   Nah.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Friends...I have landed a job!  &nbsp; I'm not going to make this&nbsp;a long entry because I am officially apartment hunting! &nbsp; I'll be home soon! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Boy, oh boy...having jawbones is nice.&nbsp; They help you chew, they help you speak, and they open and shut on mental command.&nbsp; Mine, particularly my right one, has popped for years.&nbsp; Sometimes it gets caught and makes a really loud click when I try to shut it. &nbsp; But...what does it mean when that popping noise gives way to a crunch? &nbsp; For about two weeks now, my right jaw has made this disturbing crackling, crunching, grating noise when I chew or yawn.&nbsp; It makes me wish that bone wasn't so close to my ear, because I hear EVERYTHING! (Ugh...there it goes again.) &nbsp; Does anyone have any idea what could be causing this horrid sound? It sounds like someone is crumbling pork rinds east of my eardrum.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Oh, well.&nbsp; Another notch in my orthodontic/dental/mandibular belt.&nbsp; I'll bet my dentists start&nbsp; planning their Caribbean vacations when they see me walk in the front door.&nbsp; Maybe I should go to dental school... 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My brother and I met up last week to go get some lunch in Jonesboro.&nbsp; (I was there for personal reasons.&nbsp; Call for details.&nbsp; Void where prohibited.&nbsp; See dealer for details.&nbsp; I've used this disclaimer before.)&nbsp; We've exhausted just about every place in town over the years, but there is one place I could never visit too many times.  &nbsp;  China Garden!  &nbsp;  I had been craving their tomato beef, spicy-tangy chicken, fried rice and eggrolls for about a month and a half...since the last time I met someone for lunch!&nbsp;Many of my friends and I decided...during college, of course...that this place was practically perfect.&nbsp; Close enough to campus never to be late to your one o'clock, regardless of the train schedule...consistently good buffet...good laughs at the fortune cookies by adding phrases to the end of the message...wonderful hot tea on a cold day...an ASU&nbsp;band member's&nbsp;favorite.&nbsp; I've missed it! It was as big a tradition as anything else we did...a staple of the Friday 2:00 lunch.  &nbsp;  I could fill up one of the frequent customer cards in less than a month.&nbsp; They always knew me when I walked in...it was like being in "Cheers" or something!&nbsp;Everyone was always up for going, even if they had already eaten.&nbsp; I think they should do their own version of the ASU Band special, since&nbsp;that organization&nbsp;probably shells out enough to keep their place going through the academic year!  &nbsp;  I distinctly remember being taken to the China Garden after our long Club Swing rehearsal.&nbsp; It was a welcome break and good fill-up after a long morning.&nbsp; That show turned out to be one of those defining life experiences.&nbsp; Along the same lines...you can see a slide show of our experience with Club Swing  urlLink here!   &nbsp;  Anyway...I've gotten a little off-track.&nbsp; I just had to get the word out about the best of Jonesboro's thousand Chinese restaurants.&nbsp;  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'd like to hear that noise.  Don't be surprised if some of you do in the next few days.  I go on this calling spree about every three weeks or so.    Basically, I pick up the phone and talk to everyone's machines.  Sometimes I don't even give the machine the time of day.  Sorry.  I know of one person whose voice mail is like being put on hold for the phone company.  You have to jump through hoops just to hear the little "beep" so you can leave him a message!  I think the real reason I haven't made many calls lately is because there's not much to say.  "I went swimming the other day.  And 'I Love the 90s' was on today...it's much too soon.  How are you?"  Of course, I did find out recently, through a conversation, that I have kept up with people more than I thought.  I guess it's just because I'm not right there that makes it strange.  I guess I could make a list of topics to touch on...in the interest of furthering conversation.  Really important, significant topics that shape our lives.  Okay...here's the short list.  1.  My toenails are pink.  What color are yours? 2.  I ate ham for lunch.  What did you have? 3.  Yellow Post-Its are cooler than orange ones.  Debate? 4.  Which way should toilet paper hang on the roll? 5.  I sunburned my ear.  You ever do that?  I feel this is a good starting point for shaping public policy.  The deep sentiments and thoughtful ideas presented above represent the very fabric that holds our society together in turbulent times.  We're talking genius level here!  Yup.    Why don't I just give you a call and we play Mad Libs or something?  ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You HAVE to check out this link.  After you go to it...it sheds a little light on why I've laughed at it for twenty minutes.    Be sure to turn on your computer speakers.    And...  Click  urlLink HERE! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just another entry this afternoon...  Watch Jeopardy.  If you haven't been watching, you're missing out on Ken.  Ken has been winning on the show equal to the amount of time it takes to complete a leap-year February.  I'd be willing to say that he'll probably break a million dollars in winnings tomorrow.  He's amazing.  Some of you know that I tried out for College Jeopardy a few years ago in St. Louis.  If you've ever sat screaming at the contestants, I can assure you that they go through hoops to get that far in the game.  The audition questions are not easy.  Respect the players...it's rough!  Had it not been for a series of questions about The Simpsons I doubt I would've gotten any of them right.  I left St. Louis with an ink pen.  I still use it to this day.  I looked at it like this--I was lucky to get the chance.    It makes me appreciate King Ken that much more!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have some competition.  And he's supposedly a little old man.  With large glasses.  And a bus.  I wonder what someone has to look up, type in, or ask about to be given the opportunity to do what "Mister Six" does.  To be given the opportunity to dance like crazy on a national commercial spot.    I think we should have a dance-off!  Granted, I'm not bald...I don't have those big ol' glasses...but I did ride the occasional charter bus and I have the agility.  Ever since the Levi's "Crazy Legs" spot aired a few years back I've thought that perhaps the routines I created for drum cadences were not just a need to make games more entertaining.  I mean, while they also kept me physically fit, there appears to be a small niche market for such an ability.  Ellen has also tapped into it on her talk show...she dances a bit before the guest segment.    However...like Pop Rocks, the Twist, and slap bracelets, those fads don't last long.  And the key words are "SMALL niche market."   I think I'd better stand by my DEGREE.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My uncle recently bought a dog.  It's part Lhasa Apso, part Maltese, and cute as a button.  Little dogs have big personalities.  It made me want a puppy of my own really bad!  From prior posts, you can establish that I have a cat.  Allergy testing in 2001 revealed that I had developed an allergy to that cat, which I received as a Christmas gift in 1996.  Basically, my mom had to shampoo the carpets and make the cat a little home in the garage so that I could come home during college breaks.    I like medium to small-sized dogs, partly because I have been a cat person for a long time.  Big dogs are more apt to run me over when I'm not looking.  Granted, I do like some of the bigger dogs...members of the collie family...and German Shepherds.  It would be nice to have a frisbee pal again, and they'd make good ones!  Like I mentioned before, little dogs have big personalities.  Our poor little Schnauzer Scooter was a shining example.  He barked at the ground, spoke on command, and had awfully good agility for a pup with his neurological problems.  My cousin had a Boston Terrier that was of wonderful temperament.  They are easy to share a house with because of their size.  Perfect little companions.  Very little shedding.    Of course, if you want a pet that won't shed, make noise, or cause sneezing or wheezing, a fish tank is the way to go.  You can't really play with them, though...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It really doesn't, but for the time being, it will have to do.  I went out and received a lovely sunburn yesterday.  I seriously thought I was past that point with my previous sun exposures, but I was wrong!  It was the least I could do...fry away all my troubles at the swimming pool.  I love the water.  I have always loved being around the water.  It never mattered how bad I felt or how unhappy I became, the water always made everything better.  Just a quick swim to relax.    When we started taking family vacations to the Gulf, I couldn't get enough of the ocean.  Boogie boarding...body surfing...fresh seafood...collecting shells...sand castles...the only thing that bothered me was washing the sand out of everything.  I probably have sand in my luggage from as far away as Grand Cayman!   Still...I never really burned when I was younger.  I tanned so easily that it usually took about a week in the summer sun to remain dark well into the winter.  Once I became old enough to wear makeup, though, my face never really tanned that well again...it's probably for the best.  Maybe I won't wrinkle too badly in the future!  All right, sports fans! Catch you all later!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Peepers.    I finally figured out what I see in a guy when I first meet them.  Call it "my type" if you will...people are always asking what "my type" is, and I never quite could define it.  Recently, though, I just kind of figured it out.  It's all about the eyes.  I always notice eyes.  They have to be honest, friendly, inviting and welcoming.  Must match the smile.  And they have to smile...none of this "too-macho-to-show-teeth" stuff.  I don't know what author quoted that the eyes are the window to the soul, but he was right.  (If you know, throw me a line on that one.  I like to be accurate.)  Maybe that's why I'm constantly searching for very natural eye makeup and better ways to apply it.  I want my eyes to be a focus of attention.  I only hope other people (NICE other people) have a thing for eyes as well.    I watched "The Truman Show" a few days ago (VHS copy...had it for years) and noticed how Truman was intrigued with Sylvia's eyes (well...whole face) to the point that he tried to recreate them with photos.  (If you haven't seen the movie, watch it, think deeply and let your head spin.  Later I'll tell you about an interesting name in the film, relative to my family.)    Coincidentally...Jim Carrey has nice eyes.  Quirky at times, but nice.  I don't really think eyes make a good conversation piece for a group of guys sitting around talking.  "Oh...yeah...look at the set of pupils on that chick."  Doesn't quite work.  Alas, I yearn for chivalry.  Some modern songwriters sing about eyes, even in the generation of "The Thong Song."  I suppose chivalry's not clinically dead...just needs reviving.    Bottom line...if I can't trust someone's eyes, I can't trust them.  You can learn a lot from someone's eyes.    Wink.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I'll talk now.  If you've been following my boring saga, I left Heber Springs on Thursday afternoon for my weekend of freedom-rific fun.    First stop:  Jonesboro to hear my little bro play at the 501.  I was shamelessly hit on by a freak who claimed he knew how to play over a dozen instruments.  I guess no one explained to him that the washboard doesn't count.  So...Grant gives a friend of ours a call...and I was never more glad to see him in my life!  On my way back to the house my engine decided to play "Let's Screw Up at One in the Morning" with me, leaving me no choice but to have to get up and go straight to the dealership in the morning.  Stupid computer sensors.  Thank goodness for the warranty.  Rainy night number one ensues.  I woke at about three in the morning to lightning.  Woke again at four to mosquito...five to mosquito...six to scratch mosquito bite...seven to alarm.  Friday, July 2.  Second stop: Corning.  Wet yard, dirty swimming pool furniture, food to make.  No time to sit...must go straight to third stop:  Poplar Bluff.  Time to pick up groceries for forthcoming large party, despite rumors of rain.  Fight Supercenter crowd for vegetables and pound cake.  Fourth stop: Corning again.  Unload said groceries and begin cleaning process in and around pool, despite rumors of Biblical flood.  Hours later...break and shower.    Now comes the fun part.  Evening.  My dad's girlfriend and I begin to make the sweet treats for the impending July 3rd large crowd, despite rumors of tsunami.  My dad returns with a jug.  Inside the jug is a very strong homemade blackberry wine.  Gulp.  I begin accurately predicting the weather as a squall moves across northern Arkansas.  Gulp.  I begin telling stories of my meteorological accuracy.  Gulp.  I am a genius.  Gulp.  The most beautiful genius alive...(Friends...this is a rare state for me.  I only tend to have this kind of fun once or twice a year, so don't expect to read about this very often.  Of course, you know this.)  Saturday, July 3rd.  Three in the morning.  Floor and ceiling cease spinning in time for rainy night number two.  7:30...alarm goes off.  Sunshine and birds. Time to get dressed for the big parade, despite rumors of dam burst.  Go to picnic in the park and buy car tickets.  Meet and greet, mingle and mix.    Okay, enough of that.  Out to the house to get in the pool, despite rumors of massive inland hurricane.  Still sunny.  Hmmm...guess it won't rain today.  Swimming and relaxing, visiting and talking.  It was a great day.  Sunday, July 4th.  9:00 a.m. Real Independence Day.  Have already celebrated the big town celebration, but will celebrate with friends again later.  Wake to sunshine and birds.  Hmmm...guess we missed the flood.  WRONG.  My dad's television shows a storm watch.  I take one look and tell him it will be here at noon.  His girlfriend comes over and asks when it's going to rain, since I'm so good at predicting this stuff.  I tell her noon.  11:15.  Still sunny.  11:30.  No worries.  11:45.  Pitch black.  Noon.  Projectile sticks.  Deluge.    Five.  Sunshine and birds.  Over to another house for fun.  Nine.  Amateur fireworks show draws large crowd of spectators on roadside.    Monday, July 5th.  I become part of the storm cleanup crew.  Goggles and a net.  Bottom of pool.    Yep...ya'll missed out this year.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay...this is just a quick update to let you all know that I'm still alive after the fireworks, swimming, and massive land hurricane.  I will give you a better wrap-up of the events when I feel a little more refreshed.  It was a good weekend, no doubt about it! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, sports fans! I'm off for my weekend of revelry! We will have plenty of food if you're interested...just give me a call!  (Maybe the rain will hold off...)  I don't think very many of you know and understand just how monumental the fourth is at home.  (Actually, the third this year...) The whole town shuts down.  I usually spend about an hour or two in the park, then I go to my dad's for the pool party and food.  I used to spend nearly all morning and all evening in the park...back when the rides didn't make me queasy!  Of course, I have to buy tickets for the free car for myself and my family that will not be in attendance.  Three dollars and you could win a Lincoln.  (Void where prohibited.  See dealer for details. Offer expires July 4, 2004 at 12:00 a.m.  Yada yada and I don't think those are the real rules.)    Anyway, enjoy the weekend and shoot lots of fireworks! (I love fireworks.)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi, everyone!  Just a quick update to let you all know that I have moved back to Jonesboro, but I do not have personal Internet access yet.  That may be a month from now, so I'll be in touch with you all shortly! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>