<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      all right. quick little rundown with whats been up with me since I last posted. I've come home from cambridge, mn. mowed the lawn. cleaned my room and watched a lot of t.v. for those of you (haha) that were anxious to know what my school schedule is I've finally taken the time to go to my room before I wrote a blog. so I guess here it is:    Semester 1:   Band - Saiger  Math - Carlson  Team Sports - Calliguri  Wellness for Life - Torgerson  Pre-IB Themes of US History - Laroque (BLOCK)  Jazz Band - Saiger   Semester 2:    Symphony Band  - Saiger  Biology - Ward (BLOCK)  Math - Carlson  English - Leonard (BLOCK)  Jazz Band - Saiger   There you have it folks. I don't know how happy I am having to spend two hours every week day for nine months with saiger but I guess thats just life,huh? (just kidding)  well, yesterday I had gundy/wedding band practice.  tonight we have a performance for the blandin foundation, where they/we will be welcoming mr. jim hoolihan as the new president.  the ceremony starts around 5:00 p.m. at blandin.  and then on friday, we have a pre-wedding rehersal at the gunderson residents.  saturday is the wedding.  that begins at 2:30 p.m.  only 36 days until MB Camp.  i can't wait.  it is going to be so much fun.  and no, I don't really have a count down, I just counted them now.  i do have a little bit of a life.  not much though.  thats really all I have for you now.  not a whole lot going on.  see y'all later.  cory leppanen  RELATED LINKS  urlLink Grand Rapids High School (Minnesota)   urlLink Grand Rapids High School Marching Band (Minnesota)   urlLink Blandin Foundation   urlLink Jim Hoolihan Article (Herald-Review)( Please note:  Article is in PDF format)
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hello. there.  i'm hee at my great grandma's in cambrige, minnesota.  i told you time between posts was going to increase.  i just thaought I should blog because I can.  I'm using WebTV, one of technologies biggest mistake.  but I guess I shouldn't complain.  not a whole lot happening here.  just playing a lot of card games and backgammon, which, i just learned yesterday how to play.  iit's pretty fun, once you get the hang of it.  My g. grandma, grandma, my grandma's sister, and I play cads, while, my little brother cody watched tv.  i feel kind of bad for him, though, I don't think he minds.  as I am sitting here, I can hear my grandmother snoring, and she's downstairs.  the floor is the thickest in the world, but the downstairs room is pretty tall and there is a lot of traffic going by the house.  I don't know for sure, but I know there are probably some spelling mistakes.  sorry for the inconvienience.  um,  I think thats all for now.  cory leppanen
      
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      two posts in a row.  wow.  but as time goes on, you will start to notice that time will seperate in between posts and soon enough, I'll dump this and find somewhere else to go.  As for now, this is my home, and it's going to stay that way for now.  today, I was watching the reruns of "Last Comic Standing" on Comedy Central.  I must say, seeing them for the third time, they are still funny as hell.  Especially Mr. David Mordal.  Some of you may think that I have a bias because he is from Minnesota, but this guy is hilarious.  Especially his pitch for the T.V. show.  The "Wacky Terrorists" show.  The funniest thing ever.  I think I wet myself a little laughing at it.  If you don't know what I'm talking about, you are missing out on a lot.  And I won't try to explain it because it isn't as funny when I try to do so.  So go out and find a copy of it, and I promise you'll piss your pants (sense of humor is required).  i still think he should have won the competition, but what can I do now, right?  today I went to my cousin's Grad. Party. some of you may know him.  his name is Justin.  he's a pretty cool kid.  but the most enjoyable thing about any party is the old people.  you might be going "what the hell is this guy on" but old people are funny.  if you don't think so, then you have no sense of humor.  the way they can rip on each other is marvelous.  and it always seems to end up being a dirty joke too, that none of the "youngsters" can get because of the "slang" that the old people use.  and other things are more obvious.  I think it's extremely cool, but then again, i don't really have a whole lot of people to hang out with, so old people may be my "haven".  and now that we have the fun stuff out of the way, lets talk about what pisses me off.  I don't like people that want you to feel sorry for them.  you know, the one's that expose themselves too much on purpose, looking for sympathy and pity.  I think that is just annoying and not right.  there are limits to where you can go before it goes to far.  i think it's wonderful to talk about things, but when you talk about them all the time and you blame your actions on a horrific event in your life then you have crossed that line.  the line is very thick.  but just because the line is thick, doesn't mean that when you step on it, you aren't out of bounds (like in football, or the baseline in basketball).  All you need is a little too much momentum to cross that line, and once you do, everyone that was on your team is pissed off at you because you screwed up.  here's a note to all that do this:  take life as it come's.  other people's actions that only effect emotions can't ruin it for you.  only your actions will stop you from what you want to accomplish.  my parent's are divorced.  i can talk about how it affected me, but I was too young to know what life was like when they were together.  i don't go and cry to everyone I'm close to about it.  i just let it slip by and FORGET ABOUT IT.  I know i have the ability to go up to someone like billy sackett and just go "oh my god billy.  the seperation of my parent's is ruining my life.  i can't do anything because of it.  they never get along and i can't go anywhere with both of them because they'll just fight."  i know i can do that, but I don't.  Why you ask?  because IT ISN'T NECESSARY!!!  i seriously don't see how pissing and moaning about it is going to help any.  i think that you have to just sit back and enjoy what you do have, because I will guarantee, that somewhere, at any point in time, someone has it way worse and they won't say a thing because they know it won't help how they feel.  well, that's my horrible, un-caring post of the day.  if you'd like to read more posts like this, go ahead and contact our president at The White House c/o George W. Bush 1600 Pennsylvania Ave. Washington, D.C.  thatss all I got for now.  I know I said I'd post my shedule for next year, but that's at my moms.  so, maybe next time.  cory leppanen  RELATED LINKS  urlLink dave mordal   urlLink comedy central 
      
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am going to take it in myself to start over.  Well, I will try to start over.  I cam upon this conclusion on the 28th of May.  I just feel that I've been acting like a shithead and it needs to stop at somepoint and I think that point is here.  And apparently my body has felt that with starting over should come with a cold.  Though, this could be a result to Memorial Day, when I played taps for the American Legion POST 432 of Warba, MN.  I can't be sure.  Speaking of Memorial Day, I'd like to take this time to apologize.  I'd like to apologize to all of whom I have disappointed when I messed all but 3/8 times I performed that day.  I am ashamed that I screwed up so many times on a piece of music that is extremely easy to play physically.  That may seem kind of funny, but it is just like performing great piece of art like a performance of Romeo and Juliet.  It is easy to say the words, but to make the audience feel what Bill S. was trying to say is completely different.  Or, it's easy to say "I love You" to someone you don't really love, but when you meet the one person you truly care about, it's so hard to even say the "I".  Taps, which means so much to so many people is a very emotional piece of music.  It was played to put the men and women of the armed forces to sleep at night.  It's only 24 notes long, but it can really hit people, no matter how it is played.  But when it is played the way it is supposed to, it can hit almost anyone paying attention to tears, and even break people down.  I feel that my performance this past Memorial Day in no way got close to what it should have been and I believe it was a disgrace to the song and I feel ashamed.  I don't think many other people feel the same way about how I did, and it more than likely is just me, but I seriously feel that way.  Anyone, with the amount of skill I have, and I don't have a lot, but even so, should not screw up on it.  And for this I apologize and ask for the apology from all vets.    Well, now that that's over with, I can tell you about the rest of my week.  I've felt like shit with this cold/allergies since Tuesday afternoon.  I've tried different things, but I think it just keeps getting worse.  It blows the big one.  I certainly hope it's not allergies because I have marching band starting at the end of July, and I'm pretty sure allergy season goes much farther than that.  Wednesday was the day that all of my finals were.  I had one in French, Math, and English.  French went real well, and Math and English were ok.  I hope.  Thursday was just like any other day.  I finished up my math final, then that was really it.  There was no goodbye's or anything.  Just a couple "see you in July"'s and that was it.  The least-dramatic last day of school I have ever attended.  A few holes were closed, and some more were opened.  I also discovered that once damage has been done, it can never be repaired.  It can be covered up, but never repaired.  And also that people aren't always what they seem.  One day a person can seem like a pretty cool person, and the next day they can be the biggest dick in the world.  And then you never remember why they were cool, but only why they were a dick.  So you go, "Ok, I'll forgive this person, for whatever he/she has done.  Next year it will be cool."  But I'll bet anyone that the coolness you once saw in a person will VERY rarely return.  (please note that I used the word coolness for lack of a better word.  The word would be the next level above respect.  And some may go, there is nothing above respect, but to me, respect is only the beginning of the scale).  that's enough crap for now, huh?  Maybe next time I'll fill you in on my classes next year and some other cool things.  cory leppanen  RELATED LINKS  urlLink Warba Legion Post 432   urlLink Taps performer Jari Villanueva   urlLink Grand Rapids (MN) High School Band 
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, i'm psychd to see someone is reading my blog, (see comment in below post) but it would be better to know who they are. i'm not quite sure what they ment by their comment, but it's all good. i wouldn't mind reading this "mean" post they wrote about me if they were to give me a link. i'm sure it'd be real interesting.  so now, it's saturday, and the main week of band camp is done. we still have a lot to do. we havn't even started on the closer, and the ballad is pretty messy, too. to opener, from what i've seen is doing nicely, but, from where i march, i don't get to see a whole lot. all in all, it was fun. the first few days were tiresome, with a lot of repatition and what-not, and i wasn't ready for the physical indurance part of it. but as the end of the week came, it got a little easier. next week, it's back to business, noon-6, monday-thursday. on monday, "deen--r" and i were asked to play some first parts in the show. i was pretty hyped up about that, just being in my first year and everything. i also have a "duet" type thing in the closer. "Tree" and Amanda G. have the 1st section duet and deen--r and i have the 2nd. I feel special. If any of you are in the area when we have a competition, you should come check us out. To find out the dates, check out the link below or the one to the right entitled "Grand Rapids High School Marching Band (Minnesota)" or i will post the dates whenever they get close.  so, in conclusion, band camp was awesome, and people are reading my blog. that sounds like a good week to me. goodbye!  cory leppanen  RELATED LINKS  urlLink Grand Rapids High School Marching Band  (Minnesota) 
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      some may think the title refers to my dad, but no.  today, i drove for the first time with my permit.  i didn't do to bad.  need to work on my stopping.  i didn't drive with an instructor, but rather with my dad.  the most cautious guy on the road.  it's kind of sad.  as long as i don't start acting like him, i think i'll be ok.  i don't really see whats so special about driving either.  i'd rather sit on the passengers side of the car, but thats because i like to space out a lot.    speaking of spacing out, band camp starts on monday.  woo hoo.  i'm so excited.  i get to join up with all my friends.  well, maybe not.  one of my parents said they were going to take care of the payment thing, but they've gotten a little lazy.  and so now, i might not be able to participate.  i hope i can, i've already spent a lot of time on the music.  and i cut my hair to about a half inch for it so i wouldn't get to hot.  oh, well.    tomorrow, i'm going to duluth.  i don't really know why.  i suppose we'll go to gander mtn. and best buy.  i hope we go to the mall so i can go to schmidt music.  it's the only good music store in the area, and it's 80 miles away, so, hyea-ya.  i guess i get to drive to floodwood.  that'll be...fun.    today,  my dad got a call from one of his co-worker type people, named Roger Brown.  He's got a daughter, named Rachel.  And it just so happens she's in my class/grade.  We hang out a little in school.  (and for those of you keeping track at home, this is the same family that Aron, mentioned in a previous post, comes from)  And so, he's alway "teasing" me about any girl he knows about, and rachel in particular.  And since he got this phone call this morning, he felt that he had to "tease" me even more today.  Like, when he got off the phone he made some comment like "that was your father-in-law on the phone" and just other comments like that.  or, when we were at wal*mart today, we drove by the Brown residence, and he made a comment along the lines of "oh, geeze.  i suppose you wanted to go see your girlfriend." and it's just stupid stuff like that that annoys me, and it gets old, after about, well even before the first time..    well, i know i broke my altimate rule of whining, but i have done and did something about it, i talked to him, so it's not as crucial, but it still counts.  i'm such a hypcrite.  and bad speller.      that'll be it for now.  i'm out.  see ya!    cory leppanen    RELATED LINKS   urlLink Grand Rapids High School Marching Band (Minnesota)    urlLink Wal*Mart    urlLink Grand Rapids High School (Minnesota)      and just for the record, rachel is a cool kid and if she wanted, i'd be more than happy to ...   
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey.  time for me to play "ketchup".  ha!  get it? i didn't think so.    Well, I have one more day of classroom training in drivers ed.  i can't to get it over with.  to tell you the truth, i havn't really learned that much from the class.  it's all more or less commonsense.  but, it's all mandatory, so i guess i can't get around it.    Thursday was my birthday.  i am now 16 years of age.  isn't that amazing?  i can't believe i have lasted this long.  oh what a joy.  the only thing i don't like is when people ask you "now how does it feel to be 16?"  and to tell you the truth, i can't tell the difference than from yesterday.  i don't really pay attention to how i felt a year ago.  and if i did, i would have forgotten by now anyways, so if you guys/gals ever see me on my birthday, please don't ask me that question.  thank you.  so, if all goes well, i'll be able to drive legally in january.    also on thursday, a strange looking man named aron brown hit me with his car.  just kidding.  but, he stopped me on my way home from drivers training and invited me to his house.  i figured why the hell not, i'm going to have to spend all year in band sitting next to this kid anyways.  so, i went to go hang out at his house.  mike loidolt was there.  we watched the last 15-20 minutes of "underworld".  that movie is [exploit of deleted] hilarious.  especially when the guys head is cut, and he stands there for about a minute, then his head falls off.  thats funny stuff.  the we put the hard top on arons jeep and went online.  we watched some homestar runner and videos on ebaums world.  like the guy who beat super mario bros.  3 in 11 minutes.  you should go check it out.    i'm very unsattisfied with my Hamilton Trumpet Stand that I ordered.  it's a piece of crap.  i highly discourage you all from purchasing it.  the rest of my order is great.  i enjoy it much.    the new supertones cd is kickass.  theres a couple of songs with catchie choruses and trumpet lines.  you should go to your local record store and pick it up if your into anykind of music.    we had a sectional on monday.  it was really fun.  we went up to the high school and practiced for about 45 min. to 1 hr.  it was kind of hot.  i got sunburned.  afterwords, we all went to tioga pit and swam for a little bit.  then we went to the beach and ate.  and after 45 min. we swam some more.  it was refreshing, though, i can't swim.  after that we went to amanda gigliotti's house and played some volleyball.  i was named the "hulk" because of my oh-so-powerful spike.  there were a few close calls where it almost turned into a "meet the parents" moment, but luckily that didn't happen.    thats all I have for you all.  check out the links in the right margin.  more will be added later.  goodnight, and have a pleasent tomorrow.    cory leppanen    RELATED LINKS   urlLink Homestar Runner    urlLink Ebaums World    urlLink Grand Rapids High School Marching Band (Minnesota)    urlLink Orange County Supertones   
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HHHEEEYYY!!! how is it going?  i started drivers edumacation today.  it was kinda boring.  we learned about traffic signs and stuff.  whoopie!!!  during break me and ryan g. went to m&h and got slurpees.  mmmm.  they were good. i also ordered my moutpieces today.  i got some other stuff, too.  if you really wanna know, here's what I got:   1  Hamilton KB500 Trumpet Stand 1  Bob Reeves 42S Trumpet Standard Screw Rim Silverplated Mouthpiece 2  Bach Trumpet 3rd Valve Slide Stop Nut Silver 1  Pro Tec Small Brass Mouthpiece Pouch (holds 3 pieces) and 1  Bach Trumpet Mouthpiece Group I 3C   the total cost after shipping was $158.89 USC.  now i'm broke.  i can't go to m&h tomorrow.  or the nexr nine days.  or probably ever.  oh well.  i hope i can recover from this soon.  my supertones cd came on friday i guess.  i didn't know until about 8:00 pm today.  i had already gone home and gotten my clothes by then.  i'm sad.  11 more days until my birthday.  then i'm going to hunt for jobs like crazy.  won't that be fun.  then band starts.  my goodness, i'm going to be busy.  well, i better get to bed now, so i can walk to drivers ed. tomorrow at 9:00 am. so, good luck with your problems and may your god(s) be with you, or not.  PEACE!!!  cory leppanen
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today is july 04, 2004.  our nations independence day.  and not to mention, a day in july.  one of the hottest months of the year.  today, i don't think it got past 65 degrees farenheit.  it was pretty cold.  we had a family get-together at my...aunt's? house in penguilly.  everybody there was wearing their winter clothing and stuff.  it was kind of funny.  yesterday was mr. dale william gundersons wedding to the lovely angela marie hemphill.  it was held outside at his parents house over by wendigo golf course.  the notorious rex richardson and my brother the infamous chad were there.  it was pretty fun.  i was in the band.  woohoo.  i didn't screw up once.  i was so proud of myself.  it was really warm during the service, but within 5 minutes of when it got over, it started to rain really hard.  i might go sign up for drivers ed. tomorrow.  since my 16th birthday is on the 15th of july, i thaught it was about time i started.  yeah! and my supertones cd should be comming any day now.  and i gots ta order a couple new mouthpieces for myself, too.  that's going to run me around $130 before shipping.  my goodness things are pricy.  i need a job.  thats it for now folks.  don't come back again either.  i'm out.  cory leppanen  RELATED LINKS  urlLink Rythm and Brass   urlLink Rex Richardson   urlLink Gundy Bio (care of the fine people at grband)  urlLink Wendigo Golf Course 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hello all you frank-a-holics.  just thought i would give you all a little update on me.  today, was quite a fun day.  very exciting.  we finished learning our sets in the field show.  woooo!!!! can i get a what-what?  i didn't think so.  i have set a new goal for myself.  i say new, like i have had others.  my goal is to totally disgust mr. dale "gundy" gunderson.  this guy is unbreakable, i tell ya'.  i tried to tickle him, no reaction.  i even started to feel his "man boob", he just kept going on with his routine.  and the sad thing about it is that i was grossed out.  it was all flabby and everything, it didn't belong on a man. ewww.  well, i'm working on some other stuff too.  i will get him to react by the end of the school year.  yesterday was also a fun day.  i gave tree a huge wedgie.  i can't even think about it without laughing.  it was so gross.  i swear he spent like 5 min. trying to pull it out.  and they were all sweaty and everything.  that, too, was gross.  i am never going to do that again.....i don't think.  you had to be there to think it was funny.  his boxers came up so high, it was hilarious.  i left a comment of my own on...ashley's? blog.  i think thats right.  and i made some cookies today.  they're pretty good.  you should try one.  thats all for me tonight.  i'm going to bed.  so, until next time, don't miss me too much.  mwah!!!  cory leppanen          a.k.a. frankenstein 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today, i went to a twins game way down in the cities.  they played the boston red sox.  they won!  i was so happy.  the game ended with a double play in the top of the 9th.  it was glorious.  i went down their with my dad and a big group of other people on a bus.  it was through my dad's work.  the ride was pretty fun.  on the way down there, we watched "Jay and Silent Bob, Strike Back", which, was maybe a little inapropriate, but hey!  and then on the way back we watched "Tommy Boy".  that movie is still awesomely funny.  i still have no reply from "anonymous" from the post "airbag".  i would really like to know what the comment i supposedly wrote said.  it seems like it could be a big deal.  but i would like to clear the air now and say "i have never,  EVER,    commented on any blog, at any time..within the last 5 or so months.  and if this person is still holding a grudge after that long, then you need therapy.  but, as far as i know, i have never posted anything "inapropriate".  at least not to me.  so, if the person is reading this, then please, either comment me and leave the link to your blog, or click on my name on the bottom of the page and e-mail it to me.  if you leave and comment, i will delete the comment as soon as i see it if requested.  i know i last posted on saturday, but i didn't post about the after party on friday.  it was rockin'.  a bunch of people in the band got together at tioga beach and we had a big shin-dig.  jeff, the texan, was doing the grilling.  he kept getting the lighter fluid on the food.  it was kind of funny.  amanda g. brought her foreign student, iam. (unsure of the spelling)  he's from france.  he was a pretty cool kid.  he knew judo and was pretty laid back.  all the girls were huddling around him.  i ran and jumped off the dock in all my clothes, and forgot to take off my glasses.  it was a good thing they didn't come off.  we played frisbee tag, and i am now either known as "hulk" or "frankenstein".  just because i dominate at everything.  just kidding.  i ended up making a few friends.  it was real fun.  and now, i must go get ready for band tomorrow.  WOOOHOOOO!!!  peace, home dawgs.  cory leppanen  RELATED LINKS  urlLink Minnesota Twins   urlLink Boston Red Sox   urlLink Major League Baseball   urlLink Grand Rapids High School Marching Band (Minnesota)    
      
</post>


</Blog>