<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm going to talk about something that most people find incredibly boring - college baseball. Why? Because I love baseball, and love my Yellow Jackets. I used to work in a lab that was mere feet from Russ Chandler Stadium at GT, so I'd frequently head over to the stadium to watch my boys after I finished working on a Friday. It was a nice way to start the weekend - watch some top-ranked Yellow Jacket baseball, game would end around 7p or so, then go out for the night afterwards. Oh, and living next door to four GT baseball players and becoming friends with two of them - Phillies' prospect Victor Menocal and current Rangers' 1B Mark Teixeira. Great guys, and a lot of fun to hang with...but I digress. Today, the NCAA Baseball Tournament's field of 64 was announced, and I'm gonna see how much I do/don't know by predicting the winners. Somebody prepare that crow sandwich, because I'm sure I'll get a couple really big bites of it by the time this thing is over.  [EDIT: Replaced lots of text with jpeg of bracket]  Here's my bracket:   urlLink    [Click to enlarge]&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink      THE COLLEGE WORLD SERIES  Predicted seeding: 1. Texas 2. South Carolina 3. Miami 4. Georgia Tech 5. Stanford 6. Arizona State 7. Louisiana State 8. Wichita State  Predicted final standings: 1. South Carolina 2. Georgia Tech 3. Stanford 4. Texas 5. Arizona State 6. Miami 7. Louisiana State 8. Wichita State  ...we'll know how wrong I was on June 28th. I'll revise after the Regionals are done.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am what people call "a consumer whore". I like stuff. I enjoy having stuff. Though I'll be the first to admit that I've made some  AWFUL  purchases in the past. Examples are not limited to: A pocket PC [ urlLink Compaq Aero 2110  - $450 in 1999], buying 40 Gamecube games in the timespan of February 2003-February 2004, a Sega Saturn over a N64 or PlayStation, and probably some others. But there are some things that I'm prouder than hell for picking up: my  urlLink Creative Nomad Zen Xtra  [40gb of mp3 goodness for $200, not as sexy or good as an iPod, but cheaper and 2x battery life], my  urlLink Aiwa in-dash car MP3 CD player  [hot shit in 2001, but the AM doesn't work anymore], TiVo, and most recently, the  urlLink modded-to-hell Xbox .  So what's the point? I like cool, new shit. And one such thing that tickles both my "consumer whore" and my techno-geek sides is the  urlLink OQO Personal Computer . This thing is hot. A handheld with the power of an actual PC. And it's running XP, not some shitty specialized OS like WindowsCE or PocketOS. You can actually run normal apps on it. Only thing from looking at the  urlLink OQO specs  is the choice to use USB 1.1 over USB 2.0 and 802.11b instead of 802.11g. Oh, and a 1GHz Transmeta? Boo. But why lie, I'd love to have one of these, a 80GB Apple iPod, a Sony PSP, and a Nintendo DS. And a hot cell phone. But damn, throw in car keys and that'd be one crowded set of pockets.  Another hell of a lot more useful new product is the cell phone dock that connects to your wired land-line and allows you to make cell calls on any of your home phones. I plan on getting one of these promptly upon getting a place of my own. Two examples are  urlLink PhoneLabs' Dock-N-Talk  and the  urlLink Motorola CellSocket . Cool stuff, though neither works with my current phone, the  urlLink LG VX2000 . But since my current phone is a piece of shit, giving it up will be no problem. And I'll be damned if I ever sign a 2 year contract again. Fuck that.  Sad realization: the computer I stream my media files off of to play on the Xbox has a slower processor speed than the Xbox [450 vs. 733]. And one cost $2400 in 1999, the other cost $129 in 2004. That makes my wallet cry. So does the goddamned gas pump. Best I saw today was $2.02 - my car is getting used to that orange light that comes on when the gas needle points to "E". Next job interview: Tuesday, June 9th in Albany, GA with  urlLink these guys  for a  urlLink Process Engineering job . Sounds interesting, but I wont know more until I see it.  I was in Wal-Mart today picking up some things when I saw something that broke my heart. While in the electonics section, looking over wireless Xbox controllers [I bought  urlLink this one ], I was standing next to the wall-o-TVs when I heard one of my favorite songs of all time, "Golden Brown" by The Stranglers. I immediately turned to see what it was, only to see something that saddened and horrified me. On the TV screen were two hands, each holding an Ore-Ida french fry. French fries. Possibly my favorite song was defiled by a goddamned fried potato commercial. I'll never buy Ore-Ida again. Melodramatic? Yes. But justified. This is very similar to the case where the late Johnny Cash's family wouldn't let his song "Ring of Fire" be used in a Preparation-H commercial. Kudos to them. Selling out is fine, but leave that to shitty bands like Smashmouth.  Oh, and a quick clarification for non-Tallahasseans. When I use the phrase "I'm sleeping with Mickey" I'm referring to my dog. Here's some pictures of the little guy from last Halloween:   urlLink    Mickey inside the pumpkin I used to Trick-or-Treat with.&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Hey, dogs can look stupid too.&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So last night was fun. Good turnout, and somehow 32 hotdogs and 10 bratwurst got eaten. I'm proud of you guys. Mickey [my dog] escaped from the ordeal only as a tired little dog, but that's fair because he was up way past his normal "bedtime". Drew decided to recreate the awful face-shaking picture bit again, and boy, it was awful. Awfully great. Basically, you let your lips and cheeks go limp, then you shake your head from side to side, allowing air to get in and puff your face up. And you take a picture in mid-shake, and it almost always looks absolutely rediculous. Exhibit A:   urlLink    Hooray for Drew.&nbsp; urlLink     And of course, we decided to "pose" and make the most rediculous picture that we could. The results are Exhibit B:   urlLink    I'd say we did pretty well.&nbsp; urlLink     In other news that only I care about, you might not be able to make fun of  urlLink the University [sic] of Georgia  because those boneheads went and lost the trademark and all naming rights OF THE FREAKING SCHOOL. Pathetic. Can I submit my vote to rename it "Clarke County Community College" yet?  Oh, and the  urlLink rampage   urlLink continues   urlLink on . For those counting at home, that's 20 wins in a row for GT's baseball team, which as of this posting, is sitting in the ACC tournament's championship game, waiting for an opponent who would have to beat GT twice to win it. The Yellow Jackets are in the driver's seat, and I like it.   Speaking of ACC sports, I was in a Borders yesterday with Alexandria, and while we were talking I flipped through The Sporting News' ACC Football preview. As usual, GT was picked to flounder this season. Here's the schedule and TSN's predictions:  09/04/04 Samford (W) 09/11/04 @ Clemson (L) 09/18/04 @ North Carolina (W) 10/02/04 Miami (L) 10/09/04 @ Maryland (L) 10/16/04 Duke (W) 10/28/04 Virginia Tech (W) 11/06/04 @ NC State (W) 11/13/04 Connecticut (W) 11/20/04 Virginia (L) 11/27/04 @ Georgia (L)  6-5, 4th place in our division [behind Miami, UVA, and VT], and 8th overall in the ACC. Tech should definitely win against Samford, UNC, Duke, and UConn, though UNC might be tough. Tech will probably lose to Miami, Clemson, and [ugh] Georgia. The games against VT, UVA, and Maryland are up for grabs though - GT and VT square off on Tech's home-turf - ESPN's Thursday night football from Bobby Dodd Stadium - where GT has played more Thursday night games than I'd bet anybody else in the country. That game will be good.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, here's the deal.  What: Grillin' and Drinkin' at my place this Friday [Edit: Thanks 'Mander] Why: Because. When: Friday evening, cookout starting around 8p [just show up whenever, but I fire up the grill at 8p] What  Not To  Bring: Hotdogs and hotdog buns. I've got those covered. Just let me know if you're coming so I know how many to buy. There will be hunch-punch if you guys have an interest in it. And absolutely no drugs, guys. What  To  Bring: Any other stuff you'd want grilled [veggie burgers, real burgers, brats] and BYOB. Where:   Directions from Capital Circle and Mahan [aka Tennessee Street] Intersection: [If you can't follow my directions, use  urlLink this ]  1. Take Mahan [US-90/Tennessee Street] away from town, towards Capital Circle SE.    2. On Mahan turn right at the 3rd traffic light AFTER Capital Circle onto BUCK LAKE ROAD.     3. Go 2.3 miles on Buck Lake Road. When you get to the traffic signal at Pedrick Road, take the second right onto AVONDALE WAY [into the Avondale subdivision]     4. Take your first right onto BLOCKFORD COURT WEST 5. Go through the first intersection to near the bottom of the hill. 6. The address is 1312 BLOCKFORD CT WEST, a 2-story blue house with some brick. Look for cars, and a light on the front porch.    Only thing I ask is that we keep all of our noise  inside  the house. Shouldn't be a problem as we actually have a functioning AC. Try to park as many cars in the grass in front of the house and in the driveway as you can - and if you can, carpool. Space  is limited . This is a neighborhood with young children in a lot of the neighboring houses, so I'd like to keep the outside-noise low. Inside though, go ape-shit. Just don't break shit. And there's plenty of room for people to pass out here. So bring a pillow and a blanket or something if that's what you're gonna do.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First off, as an Xbox and Gamecube owner, I was thrilled to see  urlLink Xlink  finally put out the final version of their game console tunnelling software. What does this mean? It means you can fool your Xbox/GC/PS2 into thinking that Internet games are LAN games. It means Mario Kart: Double Dash online. It means that I don't need to pay for Xbox Live, because I can play many of the games online FOR FREE. It's hot. Now I just need to get that stinking Gamecube broadband adapter and an internet connection that doesn't suck. DSL blows. Oh, and if you see "pimpbot5k" online, that's me. So add me to your friends list. Or something.  And now, for some quick movie reviews. [Any review I ever put up, be it for games or movies, will be spoiler free - I hate the assholes who ruin movies and games for me]:   urlLink Shrek 2 : Good follow-up to the original, but don't believe the "it's better than the original" hype. Shrek 2 is a great movie, but the original just seemed better. Though I will admit, Shrek 2 has more pop-culture references and puns than any movie I've ever seen in my life. An entertaining flick, so 8/10.   urlLink Envy : Wow, even with a pretty decent cast [Stiller, Black, Weisz, and Poehler] this movie blew ass. Do not watch this movie. Or if you do, do what I did: watch the first 30 minutes, then when it gets excruciatingly painfully predictable, skip to the end to see the resolution. I never thought there could be a script so bad to make Jack Black unfunny. Well, unfunny isn't fair enough - you end up  hating  his damned character. 2/10, because the beginning isn't that bad.   urlLink Hellboy : I like comic book movies, and this one was pretty entertaining. Good action/hero flick, with a decent enough story. Not quite Spider-Man or X2 material, but worth seeing - a solid 8/10.   urlLink Eurotrip : On par with 2000's  urlLink Road Trip , this movie falls into the mindless teen comedy genre. It's good for a laugh, but lacks comedic genius that other movies like  urlLink Super Troopers  or  urlLink How High  had. But worth it if you can get your hands on it, so 6.5/10.   urlLink Mystic River : I heard lots of hype about this movie, and I guess I felt let down, just like I did when I first saw  urlLink A Beautiful Mind  or  urlLink American Beauty . All three are good films, as their multiple Oscar nominations speak for themselves, but I felt that all three weren't the type of movie that I really enjoyed. Like the others,  Mystic River  left me wanting more. I knew that plot twists were coming, but when they came I felt underwhelmed. I don't think the film lived up to the hype, but I did enjoy it to an extent, so I'll slap it with a 7.5/10.   urlLink Dawn of the Dead : Wow. This movie was as my friend Drew put it, is "100 minutes of people getting their shit wrecked." Zombie movies usually blow, but in the last few years both  urlLink Resident Evil  and  urlLink 28 Days Later  have resurrected the genre and given it some credibility again [and shut up about them not being Zombies in 28 Days Later. They're close enough]. But you know what? Dawn is better than both of them.  urlLink Maddox's review  of it is hilarious, and while I didn't like it as much as he did, I have to admit that it was a great movie. Scary, funny, and genuinely worth seeing - it's a solid 8.5/10.   urlLink Spartacus : I TiVo'd this off AMC, and I have to admit that along with  urlLink Ben Hur  and  urlLink The Ten Commandments  this is one of my favorite older movies ever [and in fairness, these three movies would probably be in my top 25 of movies all time - maybe I should do an post on that list sometime]. But clocking in at just short of 3.5 hours, this true  epic  got the horrible taste of  urlLink Troy  out of my mouth. Simply put, Spartacus is genius, and Kubrick's tale is brilliantly told. Being a sucker for Roman history, I have to give this film credit where credit is due, so 9.5/10.   urlLink Platoon : I had never seen this movie, but after watching it, I have to say I'd been cheating myself for not having seen it before. This movie is a great, great flick. The best Vietnam War movie, topping even Kubrick's great  urlLink Full Metal Jacket  and the pseudo-Vietnam basis of  urlLink Apocalypse Now . [And no, Robin Williams'  urlLink Good Morning, Vietnam!  was not in the mix.] Though both Jacket and Apocalypse are better movies, in due fairness, Platoon is purely about the Vietnam War, and gave you more insight as to life of a soldier during that war. Apocalypse Now is a phenomenal movie, but as it's just a brilliant adaptation of a brilliant book to set [at the time] contemporary settings, I rule it out from the "Vietnam War Movie" set. Though it's still the greatest War movie ever made. Right up there with  urlLink Patton . But back to Platoon - brilliant movie, great story, and it's a necessity to see - 9/10.  I'll do another movie round-up after the next 5 or 6 movies I watch. Let me know how worthless my opinions are in the comments, or by IM. [And use the comments people, it's your chance to air out your trash-talking for the world - and it's anonymous].
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Beulah concert last night in Gainesville was great. Though it was hotter than all hell inside the place [a kid in front of me passed out and fell on me], the show was great. The second band, Dios, was pretty good. I shoulda picked up one of their discs, but that's what filesharing is for. And before you bitch, I still buy a lot of CDs. I'll throw up some short reviews later. Much love to Alexandria, Zoe, Nathan, and Zack for showing up last night at the show - it was great. The ride home was good too, even though we got back a lot later than I planned at 4am.  Around the Horn and Pardon The Interruption - the greatest hour in sports television? I think so. Statboy isn't nearly as good as Max Kellerman was, and when Tony and Mike are apart, the show suffers - but they're still great shows. I love the Paige vs. Mariotti bouts, but Kornheiser vs. Wilbon in 'Toss Up' is still the best. I praise ESPN for basically taking the best parts of sports radio, the interesting hosts and hot topics, and cutting out the crap, the stupid callers, and putting these talking heads on TV and squaring them against each other.   urlLink Xbox Media Center  is phenomenal. One of the best purchases I've made in a long time was my Xbox and the modchip so I could use XBMC. Divx, XviD, RM, WMA, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, SVCD...this thing really plays it all. Oh, and it plays games. Hot, hot, hot.  Current Fantasy Baseball Lineup for the week: C: Paul Lo Duca (LA) 1B: Jim Thome (PHI) 2B: Todd Walker (CHC) 3B: Mark Teixeira (TEX) SS: Omar Vizquel (CLE) OF: Steve Finley (ARI), Jose Guillen (ANA), Johnny Damon (BOS) Util: Chone Figgins (ANA) SP: Pedro Martinez (BOS), Matt Clement (CHC), Andy Pettite (HOU) RP: Eric Gagne (LA), Frankie Rodriguez (ANA) P: Rich Harden (OAK)  I'm curious to see how it'll work. I've got Lowe and Wakefield on the bench, and I hope I don't pay for benching my knuckleballer.  Speaking of baseball, big, big ups to my Georgia Tech Yellow Jackets for going on a goddamned rampage,  urlLink winning 17 straight games  and  urlLink snatching the ACC regular season title  from Virginia while they weren't looking. First on the list is either Maryland, a team which GT  destroyed  in a 3 game sweep last weekend [10-2, 15-1, 18-6], or Wake Forest, who admittedly for some reason, Tech struggled with earlier in the season [9-8 (10), 4-8, 9-2]. GT hasn't lost a game since losing a series at home versus Washington on April 18th. So good luck in Salem boys, and go destroy somebody.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My recent  urlLink job interview  in Vegas went well - the other guys I'm going up against seemed like pretty stand-up guys, and I can't really root against fellow GT grads. Okay, that's a goddamned lie, but at least these would be acceptable guys to lose a job to. [Not that I want to lose the job, it sounds sweet as hell.] I played some Blackjack [single-deck!!] and Texas Hold'Em at the  urlLink Stardust , which really had an old swanky feel to it - I was pretty successful, made enough to cover the trip's expenses, and then left while I was still ahead. Whoo for me.  2004 has been a slow year for music so far, but some of the gems have started to poke through. Of note are Air's  Talkie Walkie , Bad Religion's  The Empire Strikes First  [due out June 8th], Twista's  Kamikaze , Modest Mouse's  Good News for People Who Like Bad News , DJ DangerMouse's  The Black Album  [a remix of Jay-Z's  The Black Album  and The Beatles'  The White Album ], Cee-Lo's  Cee-Lo Green is the Soul Machine , The Icarus Line's  Penance Soiree , The Living End's  Modern Artillery , and this year's current cream of the crop, Kanye West's  The College Dropout  which might honestly be the best rap/hip-hop CD I've heard in a really damned long time. West combines the "thinking man's rap" usually attributed to Mos Def, Talib Kweli, and the Roots with pop sensibilities and some of the most phenomenal hooks I've ever heard. The CD is amazing, and you should listen to it.  Dropout ,  Empire ,  Gray , and  Talkie Walkie  are early favorites for my 2004 album of the year, with the edge given to West at the moment.  And congrats to the Bolts for making the Stanley Cup Finals. I really, really want to go catch a game, and just might if it gets to 5 games. Magee and I are already plotting it.   urlLink Beulah  concert in Gainesville tonight, 1030p at Common Grounds. Cover's $8. It'll be hot. Even if everybody's crapping out on going. You know who you are, and you know you suck for it.  And the chase is on, officially. I'll let you know how it all turns out, hopefully for the best. It's been a while, I'm admittedly a bit rusty, but I've got a feeling this could be a good one.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First thing's first, my thoughts on  Troy .  Since I am very familiar with  The Illiad  I think that it's only fair that I look at the movie in two different ways. First, judging it on whether it was an entertaining movie [regardless of storyline] and two, judging it based on that storyline as a ex-Classics nerd.  Was the movie entertaining? For the most part, I'd say yes. Was it a classic? Hell no.  Troy  was an attempt to create an epic that people would love and remember for years, but all it felt like to me was that somebody saw  Lord of the Rings ,  Gladiator , and  Braveheart  and decided "well shit, let's throw them all in a pan, and loosely base the story on the Trojan War."  Pitt was a good Achilles, Bloom a good Paris, and Bana a good Hector, but the entire movie just left me lacking substance. As a ex-classics nerd, this movie gets an "F-".  Whatever schmuck decided to write the screenplay from  The Illiad  left out a lot of important [in my opinion] parts of the story. I was willing to overlook a lot of them coming in to the movie, because I know that's what Hollywood does to these famous stories. I was just hoping that the story would keep its dignity in the way Peter Jackson and company kept Tolkien's books pretty true to form. I hoped it, but I didn't get it. A 10-year war suddenly became at most, 17 days long. 17 days is the goddamned Olympics, not an epic war. And the real kicker for me was Aeneas near the end, but I won't put spoilers in here. I'll just say that I was dissappointed with how his character was involved in the story, and if this same crew decides to make either an  Aeneid  or  Odyssey  movie, they'll suck.  Did anybody else catch the series finale of "Making the Band II"?  I tell you, watching that show, the respect I have for Sean Combs has just grown and grown.  The man's a brilliant businessman, and a funny bastard to boot. I was amazed that he dealt with those six spoiled, whiny little ego-trips of rappers for two years before giving four of them the boot. Funny thing is, the four who got shitcanned didn't seem to realize that by being canned, they were going to lose  MILLIONS OF DOLLARS . Just goes to show how dumb they were afterall.  It's apparent to me that the album  Sing Loud, Sing Proud!  by the Dropkick Murphys is the best drinking music ever. Only, it would be if sang in a big group. But since nobody around here is into them [they all pick shitty emo over punk] it's just gonna have to stay as my favorite alone.  Hey look, it's the  urlLink new Nokia N-Gage QD ! Hey look, it's still a piece of shit! Whoever came up with the vertical screen concept should be shot. Ever tried to play one of these? Lord knows I tried [keyword being "tried"] to at an Electronics Boutique. Shitty interface, shitty games, shitty product. Now if I got one for free or dirt cheap, I'd take it.  And reading about some tools  urlLink stealing the Metal Gear Solid 3 one-level demo  from the E3 floor was sad. Though  urlLink this picture  was great. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As an avid video gamer, this year's E3 meant two things: new handheld systems from Nintendo and Sony.  The  urlLink Nintendo   urlLink DS  looks cool, but you have to admit that  urlLink Sony's   urlLink PlayStation Portable [PSP]  looks quite a bit cooler. I just hope that both systems can live up to the hype because let's face it, I'll more than likely end up owning both.  Though I have to say, the prospect of playing  urlLink multiplayer Mario 64  on a portable with BlueTooth is white hot. Mario 64 was one of the best games ever (best in the Mario franchise, with Super Mario World as a distant 2nd) and an added twist like this could really be fun.  The DS and the 2nd 'touchscreen' could really be cool additions, but that PSP looks damned sexy.  I wonder if it will  actually  be small enough to keep in my pockets though - one of the definite advantages of the geek-chic GBA SP.  Pedro Martinez had a typical performance tonight, shaky first inning then utter dominance. 11 Indians got fanned, and the Sox got back in the win column. Now that's what I like to see.  I often get blasted by some of my friends for being such an avid hockey fan. I don't mind it, they honestly don't understand the game at all or any of the inherent strategy, so it's boring to them. A lot of people nowadays feel the same way about Major League Baseball, but come on. Hockey is the fastest of the four major sports, and if you can't understand what's going on, just say so. Bashing it is your prerogative, but don't expect me to bother listening to your rationale. So go Thrashers.  In case you haven't noticed, I'm what people call an "avid sports fan" - being labelled as fairweather is something I don't tolerate. Changing allegiances of sports teams, to me, is a very difficult thing to do. When the San Jose Sharks were established in the early 90s, I jumped on their bandwagon and was a very avid Sharks fan until early 2002, when I decided to become an Atlanta Thrashers fan. Why? I couldn't identify with the Sharks, the players I grew up liking all got traded or retired, and I was living in Atlanta at the time and after watching Heatley and the boys play on Turner South on a daily basis, I really couldn't help but to root for the youngsters.  The shift from Seminole to Yellow Jacket wasn't as tough as I thought it would be, and it's remarkable now to look back and see that in the past 5 years, I've changed my attitude completely towards FSU. I no longer bleed Garnet and Gold, but White and Gold. I'm a die-hard Yellow Jacket, and I love it. I think the last 5 years as a GT boy have felt better than the previous 18 felt as a Criminole. So go Buccaneers, Yellow Jackets, Red Sox, and Thrashers. I'll root for you in good times and bad, because where's the fun in only rooting for winners all the time? Don't you need to suffer some losses to make those victories even more worthwhile and special?
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm watching my beloved Red Sox on ESPN tonight against the Indians, and frankly, it's hard to watch. It seems like Boston decided to put their second-teamers on the field tonight. Brian Daubach in left? McCarty at first? Kim pitching and giving up hits as if it's nothing? No wonder this game feels dead - all the big offensive threats aren't on the field. Trot and Nomar can't get back soon enough.  In other news, I found it hilarious that the government's  urlLink threat matrix listed a character from a video game  recently.  Here's a tip to the Department of Defense: I hear that somebody named Vercetti has a stranglehold on the Miami vice trade, might want to look into that.  Much love to Bo for pointing out  urlLink Adblock  to me. If you're still using Internet Explorer, stop. Go download  urlLink Mozilla Firefox  - once you get used to tabbed browsing, the complete lack of popups [and banners with AdBlock], and the sheer speed, you'll leave IE6 behind [and if you use Outlook, give  urlLink Mozilla Thunderbird  a shot while you're at it - brilliant junk mail controls]. I was a Netscape fanatic, but after NS4.7, it became a slow piece of shit. If you've ever used Netscape 6 or 7, you know what I mean. It's nice to see an open source project finally surpass Internet Explorer. Now if  urlLink OpenOffice.org  can just improve their damned interface and surpass Office XP, I might be inclined to give the Penguin another shot on my desktop. Maybe I'll give the next  urlLink Knoppix LiveCD  a shot if they can figure out NTFS compatibility.  I love the concept and notion of Free Software [because I'm both a cheap bastard and I think competition is better for all of us], but it's hard for a lot of the OSS apps to match the usability and presentation of Microsoft's software armada.  The best example of open/free software that I can think of is  urlLink Exact Audio Copy . If you're using something other than EAC and  urlLink LAME  to rip your CDs to MP3, you really should give EAC a look. If you wanna know what settings I use, zip me an IM.  I'm gonna re-rank my 2003 and 2002 albums in iTunes in the next couple days, because I think I gave some albums an unfair share [Ozma] and completely forgot some albums [RHCP's   By The Way ].  And apparently Blogger just enabled comments on these things, so feel free to trash talk, offer critisms, or respond to these posts.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's sad to see that the Tech TV staff is getting  urlLink shitcanned by Comcast , but when you get bought out, that stuff happens.  Back at GT, I loved watching TechTV's random filler shows when nothing else was on.  Speaking of filler content, is there anybody better at it than ESPN? They have assembled some of the greatest programming ever to not have a consistent time spot:  1. Street Hoops: The And1 Mixtape Tour 2. World's Strongest Man Competitions 3. Lumberjack Games / Great Outdoor Games  Those three shows are all amazing. Nothing fills the dead sports days like watching those hulking giants tow an airplane or a semi-truck across a field, or seeing Hot Sauce and Tha Professor (a 5'10" white kid) ball it up, or the odd fascination of watching men cut wood as fast as they can.  In other sports news, I applaud MLB for   urlLink not  selling out like little bitches  and letting Spider-Man 2 ads appear on the bases, as originally planned.  Just proves that if enough people bitch about something,  urlLink shit gets done .  Ashley Holland told me to listen to the band HIM, a Finnish goth-rock band. So I download a few tracks, and it's an okay listen, but I honestly got tired of it fairly quickly.  I'm not a big fan of the goth rock, but AFI's last album blew me away so I figured I'd give the genre a second chance.  I think that AFI might just be an anomaly.  I got bored today and rated all my Bad Religion songs in  urlLink iTunes , and here are the results.  Each song was scored from 1 to 5 with 1 being "ass-in-a-bucket" and 5 being "fucking incredible", then the average score was tabulated and scaled. Here they go:  1. No Control	[89.3%],  2. The Process of Belief [86.7%], 3. Stranger Than Fiction [84.7%], 4. The Empire Strikes First [84.3%], 5. Against The Grain [83.5%], 6. No Substance	[82.5%], 7. Generator [81.8%], 8t. The Gray Race [81.3%], 8t. Suffer [81.3%], 10. The New America [80.0%], 11. Recipe For Hate [74.3%], 12. 1980-85 [36.7%]  Pretty much as expected, though STF and Suffer had suprising rankings.  #1 was never really a question though.  Go Pedro, way to dog the Indians, and Boston Rob is a douche for getting rid of Big Tom.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Somebody think of a good title for this thing. Just IM me whatever you come up with, I'll put results here.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Before I ever get started on posting things here, let me just get something out:   Online diaries are fucking stupid.   Why in the name of God would you want to publish all your most personal thoughts online for the world to see? What kind of masochistic exhibitionist would want to do that? I personally love it when somebody actually does post all their super-personal thoughts [along with their shitty Goth poetry] and then, when other people go online to this  PUBLIC  website and actually  READ  those "personal" thoughs, the original poster gets their panties (yes panties, because it's women or effeminate men 99% of the time) in a goddamned bunch.  This blog (I hate the term 'blog, by the way) will have none of that namby-pamby bullshit. You want to know my innermost thoughts? Then you better learn how to read minds, cause I have always been under the impression that private thoughts should stay that way...private.   Other things you can expect not to see here:  - Retarded IM/Chat speak [e.g.  "LOL I wuz tirred so I took a nap! ROFLizzles! How r u ppl 2day?"]   Just for the record, this shit is pathetic. How much less effort is it to type Y-O-U as opposed to U? And people wonder why the rest of the world equates Americans with stupidity and laziness.  Go to a chatroom with 12-year-olds and your faith in the children of tomorrow will take a serious blow. - Online quizzes. I don't care what X-Men character I am, or what kind of liquor I am, or what flavor of non-dairy sorbet I most resemble. You wanna do online quizzes? Fine. Me? No. - Drunken posts. I never understood the popularity of calling people when you're drunk or high. Usually, people do it just to TELL other people they're inebriated. Big. Fucking. Deal. I hate those phone calls, and to me, getting drunken IM's is just a step below that. So naturally, drunken blogging is the lowest form of communication, with the exception of the aforementioned teen chatrooms. - Overused cliches from pop culture. I'm not Rick James, bitch, and neither are you. Leave the funny business to Dave Chappelle. - A daily rundown of what I did every single freaking day. Why do people do this? It's not a goddamned PalmPilot, it's a web log. Maybe people just take that "log" bit too literally. Maybe they're on to something. Maybe I'm the one looking at it wrong...So I take it back, I will inform everybody of every single thing I do, right down to taking a shit. And look forward to some Goth poetry about said shits.  I will, however, post links and things I find interesting. And if I see a good movie or hear a good album, I'll write something about it [and no spoilers for movies, I promise. I'm an asshole, but not a douchebag.] But I'll try to keep things interesting. Because if it's not interesting, why post it?  In fact, why post at all? I guess because it's easier than instant messaging all my friends one after another. That, and you people need something to do at work that doesn't involve productivity. Don't worry, anything not safe for work (NSFW) will be marked as such and linked to. I could be an ass and just randomly put some  porn in the middle of the posts for your bosses, but again, see above re: 'Asshole'.  Speaking of productivity, Zack, get back to FFXI. Go ride a Chocobo or something.  /mj out
     

    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Donec lacinia lorem vitae nulla. Morbi quis sem eu enim volutpat feugiat. Fusce sit amet urna eu mauris interdum sollicitudin. Morbi varius, urna nec volutpat congue, justo mi iaculis nisl, eget vestibulum ante lectus quis orci. Etiam ligula. Etiam faucibus massa a dolor. Etiam ac leo. Nulla et tellus. Phasellus quis mi vehicula nunc faucibus ultricies. Integer vehicula sapien eget dolor. Morbi rutrum lobortis wisi. Integer feugiat tristique quam. Vivamus aliquam tincidunt magna. Fusce id est. Aliquam laoreet purus a lacus.  Etiam elementum. Mauris eleifend erat vel tortor. Nunc lacus nulla, adipiscing in, rutrum sed, dignissim eget, elit. Aenean ut nisl. Morbi non lectus. Quisque ultrices pellentesque neque. Maecenas porttitor erat vitae ipsum. Proin elementum enim. Morbi ut mi vel orci lacinia laoreet. Sed massa lorem, ullamcorper sit amet, blandit fermentum, ultricies in, purus. Maecenas ac urna. Donec fringilla. Proin lobortis. Cras in nulla. Quisque turpis neque, iaculis at, ornare id, cursus et, leo.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First off, for full disclosure's sake, yes - I am a registered Republican. No, I did not vote for George W. Bush in 2000, and no, I don't know who I'm going to vote for in November yet. But I do know one thing: extremist media sucks shit. On the right are party schills  urlLink Fox News  and on the left, the worst of the worst, that hulking fatass Michael Moore. The way he destorts and selectively edits his documentaries and passes them off as the "whole truth" is appalling. The worst part is the number of uneducated people who see his movies and don't bother to research the things Moore shows them for accuracy. Everybody should read the artile  urlLink Bowling For Truth , which exposes some of the bullshit espoused in Moore's film  Bowling For Columbine . If that article interests you at all, there's more likeminded things at  urlLink Moore Exposed . Now he does say some good things, and point out some things that need to be reformed, but every now and then he does and say something utterly ignorant and stupid:     Now, I'll see  Farenheit 9/11  before I judge it, but from what I've seen so far, it looks like Moore has just taken what he did with  Columbine  and gotten even nastier. In all due fairness, I doubt I'll pay to see it. Figure that one out.  In less serious news, I went out and got a copy of  urlLink Mario Golf: Advance Tour  for GameBoy Advance yesterday, and I have to say that it's freaking great. Like the extremely fun  urlLink Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour  for the Gamecube, Nintendo and Camelot have managed to pack the little GBA cart full of fun. Camelot, developers of GBA RPGs Golden Sun and Golden Sun II, created a great single player mode that can only be described as "role-playing golf". As you complete side games, match play, and win tournaments, you get experience points which you can use to level up your statistics [driving distance, shot height, control, etc] and you can collect various club sets [super power, control, etc]. It supports the yet-to-be-released in the US version of the  urlLink GBA Wireless Adapter , which  finally  shows Nintendo's stepping in the right direction and hopefully abolishing the wired-mess that linking 4 GBAs used to be. With the promise of 802.11 wireless in the new Nintendo DS systems, will wireless, internet gameplay finally be available? I can't tell you how much it would kick ass to be able to sit on my couch, fire up my portable system, and play games against one of my friends three states away. I'd be like a free Xbox Live, but with the extremely kickass Gameboy and GBA library.  urlLink Tetris Attack , anyone?  Staying on the GameBoy, I'll give Nintendo some credit for their latest ad campaign for the GBA. With the new SP that looks like an old NES controller, they're getting a lot of early-twentiesomethings to buy GBAs. There was a good article in Denver's Rocky Mountain News about how  urlLink retro gaming is big business , something Nintendo obviously grasps. I love that they're putting out older games, but $19.99 for  ONE  old game? I loved Zelda and SMB1, but $19.99 each? I would've gladly paid $30 or so for 5 or 6 old NES games on one cart [which is more than technically possible], but $20 for one freaking game is highway robbery, no matter how cool they would look on the new NES styled GBA SP:     Of the games released so far in the "Classic NES" series, only Super Mario Brothers and Zelda are remotely close to being worth $19.99. Hopefully, more older NES games will get ported, but at that price point, I doubt I'd really buy any of them.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nathan and I went to a show in Jacksonville on Wednesday night, and I have to say, the lineup was pretty solid from top to bottom. First off was  urlLink That One Guy  from San Francisco. He played a large metal pipe thingy with a lot of crazy synths and pickups. It's impossible to describe, so if you've got a few free minutes, some bandwith, and quicktime, go  urlLink watch a video . Next up was Ontario resident  urlLink Lederhosen Lucil , who was another extremely arty performer. Picture a girl wearing fake blonde braids, lederhose, and playing up a fake German accent in her electro-synthpop music. She was a great act - besides being suprisingly hot, her facial expressions, stage prescence, and funny lyrics made her a very, very good opening act. Next up was another Canadian act [or rather Canadien, as they're Frogs of Montreal], the ska band  urlLink The Planet Smashers . I'd never heard of these guys [or any of the other opening acts] but holy shit, these guys rocked the house. They tried their hardest to steal the show from the 'Bats, but not quite. It was ska music at its finest, like Less Than Jake in their "Losing Streak" or "Hello Rockview" years. I look forward to catching them at the Warped Tour this year. Last up was the headlining act,  urlLink The Aquabats . There's not much more that I can say other than these guys are fucking incredible. Fun music, but the real gem is their live show. The incredible audience participation, the silly outfits...they just have to be seen to be believed. If they come to your town, see them.    Stupidity Tries   is a drinking game I'm working on. Eventually it will be a card game, where as you get a card, you have to do the crazy drinking-related thing on the card. For now, I haven't made my own cards. The first play test of it was last night at TND, and I have to say, for the most part it was a success. People got utterly sloshed, and seemed to have a lot of fun doing it. It was good hearing other peoples' opinions of the game, and important for me to see how it played out. Glenn described it best: "That game just seems like brutal shit happening over and over again. Mean, man." Excellent. When the rules are good and finalized, I'll post them here.  I used to play a lot of tennis, but I rarely ever enjoy watching it. Today I had Wimbledon on and I watched the replay of Andy Roddick's match against some Polish scrub. I have to say, I was fucking impressed to no end with Roddick's serves and mobility on the court. It was actually fun to watch, which was quite a pleasant suprise.  Work? Yeah, work. I'll be starting back up, full time, at  urlLink TMH  starting July 12. 11p-7a - night shift, baby. Being a child of the night [please don't confuse that with "Emo Goth Fucktard"] I prefer working at night. I did it in '99, so it should be fun do get at it again.  My Cell phone is turned off for good [tired of the 407 number and shitty Verizon], so if you need to get ahold of me, use the home phone, IM, or email me. I'll let you folks know when I get a new phone [Alltel].
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since I don't believe that it's fair to put final rankings on these discs till the end of the year [as I'll listen to some more, the ratings would change] I will simply list the top ten discs that I've heard to date, and I'll babble a little about each one. I will however put a preliminary rating for those discs I feel confident in judging. All scores are via my iTunes rankings for each song [album score is (sum of track scores)/(# of tracks)*20 for a 0-100 scale, with 100 being musical perfection]. The small images to save bandwith on your end. [Edit: I forgot two albums. So I tacked them on.]     Kanye West - The College Dropout [Hip-Hop/Rap]  This album is simply one of the best rap albums I've ever heard. Phenomenal hooks, good lyrics, the album artwork is top-notch - overall, it's just an excellent production. The only knock keeping this album from greatness is the number of skits on the disc. I hate rap skits if they serve no purpose, and Kanye breaks a cardinal rule by putting two skits back to back, leaving the listener with the following sequence: skit-worst song on the album-skit-skit. That's awful. Fortunately, the rest of the album is killer, so this one's looking like the best of the year so far. Rating:  88.6      Bad Religion - The Empire Strikes First [Punk]  Bad Religion had faded in quality before putting out 2002's  The Process of Belief , which signalled a return to their punk roots. Following in the footsteps of  Belief , BR has another great punk rock record in  Empire . Solid tracks with few exceptions. Rating:  84.3      Modest Mouse - Good News For People Who Love Bad News [Indie]  I admittedly haven't listen to this album a whole lot, but I have really liked what I've heard. It might be harsh for some, but once you get past the harsh vocals and see the way the music plays out on many sonic levels, you get an appreciation for it. Rating:  pending      Air - Talkie Walkie [Ambient]  This album really is a sonic masterpiece. The only thing keeping it from the top of my lists is that you really have to be in a certain mood to want to hear this music. But when you do, and you slip on a pair of headphones, the music that  Talkie Walkie  puts in your brain is irresistable. Download "Cherry Blossom Girl" if you need proof. Rating:  82.0      Nellie McKay - Get Away From Me [Indie/Vocal]  This album is very, very hard to categorize. Nellie, a 19-year-old New Yorker, tears through styles, ranging from rap to jazz to crooning. While it certainly is a sonic rollercoaster, there are a few absolute gems in her double-cd debut - "Waiter" and "The Dog Song" both come to mind. Not your typical album, but that's a good thing. Rating:  77.8      Ash - Meltdown [Rock]  I'm not as big a fan of Ash as some of my friends, but I have to say that I enjoyed this album for the most part. There are some real diamonds on this disc, "Evil Eye", "Vampire Love", and "Renegade Cavalcade" are all brilliant. But it seems like a lot of the rest of the album is filler-pop. A good album, but too many lowlights. Rating:  76.4      The Icarus Line - Penance Soiree [Indie/Hard Rock]  Another album I need to listen to more,  Penance Soiree  is a dark, heavy rock performance. I wish I could say more here, but I really haven't listened to it enough. But the couple times that I have, I was thoroughly rocked. Rating:  pending      Cee-Lo - Cee-Lo Green Is The Soul Machine [Hip-Hop/Rap]  Better than his first album,  Soul Machine  is a lot kinder to the ears. Great hooks and Cee-Lo's signature harmonies really bring this album to life. Tracks vary from soulful, to club-pounding tracks that make you want to move your ass. But I refrain. After all, fat white kids shaking their asses usually result in someone getting hurt. Rating:  74.4      The Living End - Modern Artillery [Punk]  When I started listening to this disc, I was admittedly floored through the first five tracks. All were punk rock bliss - energetic, harmonic, great lyrics. But sadly, the album took a nose-dive after that, barely surfacing later on in the album to retain the CD's decency. If it were a 5-track EP, it'd be near the top of my all-time lists. But it's not, and I've got to stick it to the album for all the rest of the crap tracks. Rating:  72.9      DJ DangerMouse - The Grey Album [Hip-Hop/Rap]  DJ DM got the really clever idea of taking the a capella version of Jay-Z's  The Black Album  and laying the tracks down over samples from The Beatles'  The White Album . White+Black=Grey. Get it? Okay. This album, as well crafted as it is, falls short in only one way: the source material. I wasn't a big fan of  The Black Album  with the exception of a few tracks. DownhillBattle.org organized a large protest of EMI's cease-and-decist letters to DJDM about using copyrighted works [EMI manages the catalog of the Beatles], so you can find lots of places to download it online. I'd suggest starting over at  urlLink Illegal Art , which also is a good place to kill time. Rating:  68.3      Franz Ferdinand - Franz Ferdinand [Indie/Rock]  No rating on this one yet, as I haven't listened to it enough. But I have to admit it, "Take Me Out" is one hell of a song. It's a little hard to get into, like  most indie rock, but it's good. I look forward to hearing more of this one. Rating:  pending      Dios - Dios [Indie/Rock]  I'd never heard of these SoCal rockers until I saw them open for Beulah. They put on one hell of a show, and the music was great. This album's been growing on me. It's a good listen, very melodic. This one could surge up my rankings. Rating:  pending   And just for comparison's sake, the best album I have rated right now is a 98.3 [Cursive's  The Ugly Organ ] and the lowest is a 36.7 [Bad Religion's  80-85 ]. Though I've really only gone through and ranked 2002-2004, with a few exceptions. I'm sure I can do much, much worse than 36.7 in the ratings. I do own a Deep Blue Something CD...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink RealPlayer  is the worst piece of software ever created. Even in its newest, 'sleekest' version, RealPlayer or RealOnePlayer or whatever the fuck it's called is absolute shit. RealVideo and RealAudio, or .rm and .ra files, are totally worthless. Closed source, extremely lo-fidelity, and not worth your time. I remember back in 1998-1999 downloading South Park and anime episodes in .rm format, and even then, the quality was unbearable. Size was small, which was important in the early days of broadband, but jesus christ, with such horrible quality, why bother? The free version of the software is "hidden" on the damned Real.com website, and then after you do install the goddamned thing, it runs wonderful background processes [check for RealSched.exe] and tries to hijack every single media file's association and force you to use RealPlayer to play all your files. Fuck that. The other horrible thing about RealPlayer is the fucking buffering. Even files locally stored on your computer still feel a need to fucking buffer. Maybe that's why this image makes me so damned happy:     The only thing I like about RealPlayer is uninstalling it. What a piece of shit. It's a sad, sad day when I'd much rather get a .wmv file and deal with shitty Windows Media Player. Thank goodness for the phenomenal [and open-source]  urlLink Media Player Classic , which will play everything without all the damned bloat of players like WMP9 and RealPlayer. It mimics the old WMP 6.4, except streamlined. Free, quick, and lightweight. Gotta love it.  I haven't really talked about video games yet, which is suprising, considering I have a rediculous amount of them. But here are some quick run-downs on what I've been playing.  1.  urlLink Grand Theft Auto 3  [Xbox]: the freedom and scale of the city are great, but admittedly, the gameplay just feels boring. Sure, I can run around and obliterate everything in sight, but it got old quick.  2.  urlLink The Simpsons: Hit and Run  [Xbox]: this game has the same scale and freedom of GTA3, but it's fun. The excellently crafted world of Springfield totally immerses you into the world of The Simpsons. This one's a lot of fun, and even the 'collecting' aspects of the game are fun to do.  3.  urlLink Strike Force Bowling  [Xbox]: an awful game, but yet, Zack and I played this one into the ground. Computerized bowling...does it get any sadder? Once I figured out how to get a strike every time, I put up a 299 and have never played the game since.  4.  urlLink UEFA Euro 2004  [Xbox]: a sweet-ass soccer game, based on the namesake tournament going on in Portugal as I write this. All the national squads that make up UEFA are there, and it's fun and worth playing. Better than FIFA 2004, this is the best soccer game I've played to date.  5.  urlLink ESPN Major League Baseball 2004  [Xbox]: a really fun baseball game, with great ESPN presentation elements, and lots of unlockables. Good game mechanics, and it's truly fun to play.  I'm working on my "Best Albums of the 1st Half of 2004" list, so that should be ready fairly soon. I just need to listen to Modest Mouse and a couple others a little more.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First off, the Mozilla team has just released version  urlLink 0.9 of Mozilla Firefox . Go get it [and go get  urlLink the old 'Qute' theme from here  if you like it better than the new theme, 'Pinstripe' - I think the new theme is hideous.]  After reading a story on Slashdot about  urlLink 3000 Bloggers getting their blogs closed  it seemed pretty obvious what I should do next:   urlLink    WGET springs into action!&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink     Yes, this was just another ploy to have a reason to display another screenshot. And yes, I know one of the cardinal rules of storing your data on someone else's network is to always have backups under your control, and I failed this time. Thank god for those fine people who ported  urlLink WGET to Windows  for those of us not in the *nix world to use. For those of you not familiar with WGET, it's basically an advanced file-retriever. You can quickly and thoroughly download files from HTTP and FTP protocols, and it's very useful for "ripping" a site, or simply mirroring it on your hard drive. But regarding the closing of 3000 blogs, the best quote was from an  urlLink Anonymous Coward on Slashdot :   At least LiveJournal didn't shut down without notice. Otherwise we'd all be up tonight digging mass graves for disfranchised teenagers all over the world.   The sad part about that statement is how true it is. Speaking of sad things, here are some things I am not proud, or am sad about:  1. I somehow got myself put up in the pictures section of my sister's sorority's website. I don't know the link, because I don't want to know the link. 2. My sister has a livejournal. Once again, I don't know the link, because I don't want to know the link. 3. I still can't find Euro 2004 coverage, but as Drew Magee pointed out, I can watch shit-tons of MLS and WNBA. Whoopity shit.  But who the fuck likes being downhearted? So instead of go on about that, I will instead list things online that make me laugh on a consistent basis:  1. SomethingAwful's  urlLink The Weekend Web  feature.  "The Weekend Web" is the project of Zachary "Spokker Jones" Gutierrez and the SA Forum Goons. What it is, simply put, is the worst-of-the-worst of internet message boards. The SA folks dive into these message boards, which are often absofuckinglutely rediculous [and hilarious] and they do what assholes do best - they make fun of people. Always worth a read, just like other SA features:  urlLink the Comedy Goldmine  [where the truly hilarious things are],  urlLink the ROM Pit  [where the worst of old video games are reviewed],  urlLink the Horrors of Porn  [where comically awful smut is criticized], and  urlLink Your Band Sucks  [an asshole's view on shitty music].  2.  urlLink Fark's  Photoshop Contests, and the much-better  urlLink Photoshop Fridays at SomethingAwful   Photoshop contests, simply put, are contests where users are given a stock photo, and are challenged to create funny or technically gifted image modifications using an image editor. Since the most common editor is Adobe Photoshop, these contests are called "Photoshop Contests". Simple enough, eh? Well the folks at SomethingAwful have gotten particularly good at this, and every week you can see just how talented at their craft they've gotten. For example, last Friday's contest was to take the one of the  urlLink old posters of Smokey the Bear  and  urlLink create your own new sign . What does this mean? It means something as innocent as this:    can be morphed into something as wonderful as this:    Another example. Here's the original:    and after the SA goon is done with it, it's much funnier:    3. Webcomics  The ones I frequent are as follows:  urlLink Penny Arcade  [video game humor],  urlLink Diesel Sweeties  [relationship and robot humor],  urlLink Real Life  [more game humor],  urlLink PVP Online  [even more game humor],  urlLink StrongBad's Emails on Homestarrunner  [general humor],  urlLink 8-Bit Theater  [yes, more game humor], and  urlLink Sexy Losers  [relationship/sex humor]. All are updated fairly regularly, and are good ways to pass the time.  4.  urlLink The Onion   The greatest satirical publication of our day [even more so than the recently-faded  urlLink McSweeney's  - though in truth whenever I get money I'll subscribe to both] is online and free to read. Turned on to it by a coworker in my days at Tallahassee Memorial [circa early 1999], I've been reading The Onion for years. The compilation books are something that everybody should own, as they are quite possibly the most perfect bathroom reading material ever. You can read it in short bouts, or you can trudge through and read the whole thing - The Onion's perfect for all that.  5.  urlLink X-Entertainment   X-E is a blast from the past. As a child of the 80s, like the webmaster, I enjoy looking back at the toys, commercials, and other things of my childhood years. X-E is essentially one living shrine of the 1980s, and the features are brilliant. While not everything is 80s-based, it's generally funny and worth the time you'll waste on it.   So there you go, ways to waste time. My primary time waster, nerd news blog  urlLink Slashdot , is always a good place to waste the hours. Cheers for unproductivity. And a big thanks to the aforementioned sites for wasting my time, countless hours of my life I'll never get back. Whoo!  Oh, and here's a quick run-down of countries that have at least one visit to my blog to date:  &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The job hunt has been horrendously slow for me, with a whopping 3 interviews since I left school [yes, I took the first one and worked for 7 months, but that still doesn't excuse my current state]. After hearing that I'm not moving to Vegas, as the company opted for a Doctoral student of Electrical Engineering, things are looking admittedly shitty once again. So the thoughts of going back to school to pick up my masters in either Bioengineering or Mechanical Engineering have recently popped up in my head. While I'm not uber-keen on the idea of more school, since it'll definitely be a state school [probably FSU over UF or UCF], at least it won't break the bank. Only problem is, if I choose to take this route [and in all honesty, I'd rather just have a good job] then I have to move quick - deadlines for admission are July 1st for Fall 2004, but I guess I could always take a menial job and hold out for Spring 2005 admission. My undergrad GPA held me back in a lot of ways, but not as much as it did when coupled with my lack of experience getting out of college. At least a Master's degree would give me another chance to wipe that GPA clean, and to make myself more marketable than I am in my current state. Now all this might dissipate if I get the job in Albany, but who knows?  Congrats to the Detroit Pistons for obliterating the L.A. Lakers. While I'm a big Shaq fan, and admittedly pulled for the Lakers going into the series, I have nothing but respect for the way that Detroit dominated the series. They're a hard working team, and the value they put on solid, defensive play is amazing. After hearing the whining of the Lakers from after game 1 through their crushing defeat in game 5, I've got to say, I'm glad Detroit won. L.A.'s primadonnas, especially Kobe and Gary Payton, deserved to get a boot shoved up their asses. Instead of ever giving the Pistons credit, they just pointed out that their team just "needed to make some adjustments" to win the next game. As Tony Reali said on Around The Horn today, this was the first 5 game sweep in NBA Finals history. Wow, a paragraph about pro basketball, a sport I hate with an intense passion. What the hell is wrong with me?  And what the hell is the point of reversible clothing? My sister and mom, when shopping recently, found some cheap shorts at Aeropostale (a store I don't think I've ever been in, honestly) and decided to pick them up for me for frisbee. They're decent athletic shorts, but they're reversible. Now honestly, what in the hell is the point of reversible clothes? Sure, there's two different styles, but these are athletic shorts - manufactured for purpose, not style. If you get the out-side dirty, it's not like you can flip them over and wear them the other way - the nasty, dirty-ass side would be rubbing on you. I guess you're not supposed to care, but they still just seem stupid to me.  I'm pissed that I can't find anywhere in Tallahassee to watch the UEFA  urlLink Euro 2004  tournament. In Atlanta or Detroit, I'm sure I'd be able to find somewhere to catch a game, like at a sports bar or something - but no such luck in tiny Tallahassee. At GT, I remember the student government ponying up the funds to broadcast the entire last Cricket World Cup, at the request of the Indian and Pakistani student societies [which are a very large group at Tech]. That was in interesting experience, but I can honestly say that cricket is boring as hell, and at least an international soccer tournament like this would be entertaining to watch. Guess I'll just have to deal with the online post-game highlights [shitty RealPlayer format] and read the write-ups. Here's to hoping the Frogs don't win it.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First off, Friday night was one of the best nights I'd had in a really, really long time. The "roving party" made its way to quite a few places, and covered about half of Tallahassee.  Staney's Birthday DrinkFest was great, but admittedly, using that green "menthol" Kool-Aid for the hunch punch was an awful idea - stick to Tropical Punch [or any other "red"] next time. At Staney's party, Fiske got the idea for kickball, so after acquiring a neon-green kickball, it was on. Playing in the dark at Winthrop was fun, even if you couldn't see where the damned ball was half the time. A good time was had by all, until one of Tallahassee's Finest decided to crash the party - being the good Samaritan that I am, I shuttled our minors, Amanda and Charlotte, off to a safe place. [Yes, of course we were drinking our beers in the park playing kickball - booze and kickball go together like boxed wine and oreos.]  Then a decision was made for some swimming action - neither I nor Charlotte had anything to wear for such an activity, so I swang her by her house and dragged her out to mine before we met up with the rest of the crew over at The Exchange where they went swimming - the only problem was, they'd just been busted by the exact same cop as at the park, and asked to leave the place. So we headed over to another apartment complex, Frog Pond, where we played in-pool dodgeball and volleyball for a couple hours before tiring out. Zoe, apparently on her way to Pensacola, stopped in for the night and it was great to see her. After enough swimming to make us hungry, me, Drew, Zoe, and Charlotte left the pool to head to Steak and Shake [about 5am at this point].   After a really good dinner/breakfast/meal at S&S, complete with a drunken Drew who yelled at people unintelligbly, passed out on the table, and oh yeah, was wearing only an undershirt and boxer shorts into the place - I dropped Charlotte off at her car and got home just a shade shy of 7am. So that's a party my friends, from 830pm-7am. Floridians get down, don't we? It was very cool to have Zoe make a cameo on the night, as she's awesome, but it was also extremely cool to meet Charlotte, an amazing girl. She likes AFI's new album too...she even knew all the words! Hah!  So after sleeping a long-ass time, I wake up to find that my Yellow Jackets were eliminated from NCAA Baseball play by the goddamned Georgia Bulldogs. Here's a quick rundown of teams I hate more the the University of Georgia:  1. The New York Yankees [except for football season]  So losing to those sons-of-bitches [pun intended] really burns. U[sic]GA beat GT in all three major sports this year, winning the football game, the basketball game, and winning the series 3-2 over us in baseball this year. In times like these, I remember that timeless chant of GT fans:  What's the good word? TO HELL WITH GEORGIA How bout them Dawgs? PISS ON 'EM  After GT's falling-apart, I watched my Red Sox get dismantled by the LA Dodgers. Complete and utter horseshit that game was - not only did my team get pounded, but my Fantasy Baseball team took a nice hit with Wakefield's 10+ ERA. Thanks, guy.  But it's been a great weekend, even if frisbee got cut short on Sunday due to only 6 people showing up. At least I got to show off my Power Forward skills in some hoops.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Recently, I've noticed something that's a problem with a good deal of the albums I buy - artists aren't making  good  albums. Instead, I seem to get a lot of half-albums. They'll start off strong, but by track 6 or 7, the album's usually taken a huge turn, and just gets boring. Rap albums in particular have been notorious with this. I love rap and hip-hop, but by god, is it that hard to put together 14 or 15 solid tracks? Example: today on my way to Albany I listened to one of the better hip-hop albums of the last year -  Elephunk  by the Black Eyed Peas - the first 7 tracks are great, but after that...it gets boring.  And speaking of the Black Eyed Peas, their record company's gotten odd. I'm sure by now, you've probably seen those "24 Seconds To Live" promos that they did for the NBA Playoffs - they were by far and away the best part of the playoffs early on. The song in those promos, "Let's Get It Started", is just a radio friendly edit of an album song "Let's Get Retarded". Way before those promos, that was probably one of the best songs on the album - great beat, great hook, just a really fun song. Turns out now though, with all the exposure the "Get it Started" version has gotten, the people at their label have now decided to make that version, the radio-friendly version, the version on the album. So all future copies of Elephunk will have the edited version, and not the original, much better version. A damned shame, if you ask me. "Let's Get Retarded" is a great song - go download it.  Oh, and  The Empire Strikes First  is out today. New, good Bad Religion - you should get it.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For posterity's sake, and for your amusement, I'm gonna post my old NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament Brackets for all the world to see. Don't care? See you next post.   urlLink    My 2000 NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament Bracket [click to enlarge] &nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    My 2001 NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament Bracket [click to enlarge] &nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    My 2002 NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament Bracket [click to enlarge]&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink        urlLink    My 2003 NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament Bracket [click to enlarge]&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    My 2004 NCAA Men's Basketball Tournament Bracket [click to enlarge]&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink     [Edit: Added 2000-2002 brackets]
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This serves no purpose other than me wanting to write something about music and technology. Who knows, maybe one of you will like what you see and you'll adopt it - but probably not. If it's long winded, forgive me. Feel free to go browse  urlLink Fark  or  urlLink Slashdot  or something if it gets too boring. [And by the way, those of you who have done the right thing by  urlLink downloading Firefox  and reclaiming your fast and pop-up and ad-free internet, congrats. I can see browser stats via the counter at the bottom. For those of you who haven't, why? Do you love pop-ups? Support open-source software. Support  GOOD  software.]  So how does an mp3 come to be in my digital domain? Well, it's obviously one of two ways, from either a direct rip of one of my CDs or from somewhere on the internet. Let's discuss the former first.  The ripper of choice, for the last couple years, has been  urlLink Exact Audio Copy  [or EAC]. EAC is a ripper designed by and designed for hardcore music enthusiasts. The bit-whores, if you will - they want the absolute best quality rips done as quickly as possible. It's open source, COMPLETELY FREE, and simple to use. My dad freaking uses it. As it's only a ripper, you need an encoder to go with it. Since we're talking mp3 here [as opposed to OGG, APE, WMA, or something else], the encoder you want is  urlLink LAME  [ L ame  A int a  M P3  E ncoder - stupid recursive name, I know]. So I load EAC, pop in the CD of choice, and EAC connects to  urlLink FreeDB , an online [open source, free] database of CD information: Artists, Song Titles, Album Titles, etc. EAC will then automatically name the tracks, supply the year, genre, track number, and artist for each track for the MP3's ID3 tag. What's an ID3 tag? More on that later. So I click 'Rip to MP3' and a few minutes later, steaming hot mp3 goodness is at my fingertips. They then get tagged, renamed, and sorted.  I've been asked where I get my mp3s from, now that services like KaZaA and [in the old days] Napster have gone to shit. The first place I turn to is IRC [Internet Relay Chat], which over the years, has developed into  the place  to get shady stuff. So what does IRC'ing entail? First, you go and download  urlLink mIRC , which is the best IRC client out there. Now that you've got the software, how do you find the files? One of the easiest ways is to use an IRC indexing site like  urlLink IRC Spy . Just type in what you're looking for, like say,  urlLink "Bad Religion"  and IRCSpy will tell you where you need to go to get it. Then you click on the pack numbers, join the servers, and grab your loot.   Another hot place to get files is Usenet, or "the newsgroups". Get a newsreader like  urlLink NewsLeecher  and hit a binary newsgroup search engine, like the one at  urlLink alt.binaries.nl  and search for what you want there. When you find what you want, click on "download NZB" and once you run that NZB file, the object of your downloading desire will get thrown in your download queue. Downside to Usenet? You usually gotta pay for server access. And software too, if you're one of those "honest" people. I don't claim to be one.  Then there's an old standard, P2P [peer-to-peer] filesharing. Since KaZaA has become [and in my opinion, always was] a total piece of spyware-ridden crap and the RIAA is hunting file-sharers on basically it exclusively, you might as well look at alternatives. I don't really use P2Ps all that much, but if you want to use them, I suggest first  urlLink SoulSeek . Cost-free, ad-free, and spy-ware free. You  will  experience some nasty waiting times, but if you've got the patience, you can get just about anything. Other worthy things to use are  urlLink LimeWire  which runs on the Gnutella network, and  urlLink eMule , which runs on the eDonkey network [ed2k links].  And the only other option I'll discuss is  urlLink BitTorrent  [BT]. To use BT, you download a .torrent file, which serves as a "guide" for your downloading. You connect to a tracker, which directs BT as to who has the file shared for download, and what parts of the file everybody has. Then you and the others, as a collective "swarm", connect amongst yourselves [all this is automatic, people] and you download and upload pieces of the file concurrently until you've gotten it all. Where do you find torrents? Well, torrent sites are all over the net now, but I recommend  urlLink SuprNova  as a starting point.  Okay, now we've got the mp3, what happens to it next?  I'm a messy person. My room is always in a state of disarray and chaos, my car is messy - I'm messy with just about everything with one exception...my computer files. I keep my mp3s neat and tidy with a set naming scheme:  \multimedia\mp3\[genre]\[artist]\[album (year)]\##-artist_name-track_title.mp3  Since renaming a lot of files can be a tedious task, I enlist the help of this free  urlLink Batch Renamer  to help me rename files all at once. Lots of good features, and it's a tiny download.  Now that we've got the files, got them properly named, it's time to make sure the ID3 tags have good information. ID3 tags are little text files appended to the ends [or beginnings] of your mp3s that contain information about the track - technical things like bitrate, size of file, name of encoder - but they also have 'metadata', things like the Artist's name, track number, album, genre, year, and any additional comments. Why is it important to keep tidy ID3 tags? Well, it's not important per se, but if you want to use your mp3s in some of the more exciting ways mentioned later, it's nice to have them nice and organized. Besides, you only have to set the ID3 info once, and if used EAC from earlier, it did it for you already. But if everybody had their ID3s right, you wouldn't download a song called "Outkast - Hey Ya!" off KaZaA only to open it up and see that it's a copy of "For Whom The Bell Tolls" by Metallica, and yes, that has happened to me.  Okay MJ, you anal bastard - you've got them sorted, named, and tagged. Are we ever going to play the goddamned mp3s?  When mp3s were in their infancy, the only player you bothered with was  urlLink Winamp . I won't lie, Winamp is still the king - those people at Nullsoft take their product seriously, and by god, it's a solid mp3 player. Everybody who listens to mp3s should have Winamp installed on their computer. End of arguement. And if you use any of the following to play your music, please, please stop and find a better player [Winamp or iTunes]: 1. Windows Media Player 2. MusicMatch JukeBox 3. RealOne Jukebox Those three programs are total, useless shit. If you want a jukebox application, and trust me after trying it you'll love it, you want to mosey over to Apple and pick up their wonderful  urlLink iTunes  program. I'm a PC user [WinXP] and their Windows version works flawlessly. So go get it, it really makes listening to your mp3s a lot of fun. A great interface, no more fumbling through Windows Explorer windows, and it's integrated into the iTunes Music Store, the world's largest online music download store. The smart playlists are incredible. And if you've got an iPod, it's a no-brainer. How pretty can it be?:   urlLink    My iTunes in action [whoo Elephant 6]&nbsp; urlLink     Okay MJ, so you can play mp3s on your computer, BFD. The real fun is when you put them to use in other places.  For Christmas in 2001, I got an  urlLink AIWA CDC-MP3  in-dash mp3-cd player. I can put a CD full of .mp3 files, and my car will play 'em, and show me stuff like Artist Name, Track Name, album, and song length on the player's face. It was super-hot technology at the time, but since has been eclipsed by much better players. It's still reliable, and I still use it on the go. Though admittedly, I mainly use the 'Auxilliary Input' jack on the front nowadays.  In late 2003, I realized it was time to get off my ass and purchase a portable mp3 player. As I had about 90gb of music at the time, I figured nothing less than one of those huge jukebox players would cut it. So I ended up with a  urlLink Creative Nomad Zen Xtra  40gb music player. The choice was simple economics: 40gb Nomad for $200 [after rebates] or a 40gb iPod for $550 [after buying a firewire card]. The iPod is sexy and great, but not 2x the price great. 40gb is nice, but 120gb would be nicer [though I'd settle for 80gb].  So now we've got the car and on-the-go covered, that leaves only one major area left: the rooms of the house away from the computer. Solution?  urlLink Xbox Media Center , an application for modded Microsoft Xboxes that allows you to play video, audio, and picture files. And just about every damned format that you can imagine. So I share my mp3s and movies over the network, and then I can pump the sounds through my Xbox into my good speakers near the TV. Home entertainment bliss.  So as a whole, I'm a big, big fan of the digital music revolution. I still buy CDs, but what's the first thing I do with it? Fire up EAC, rip and encode it, then put the disc in its case and back on the shelf. I buy CDs to support good artists, but also as higher-fidelity sources for my mp3s. That, and most CD players don't have mp3 capability [yet], so taking a CD to a friend's place is just easier.  MP3 might not be the best format out there [Apple AAC, Ogg Vorbis, and a few others are noteably better] but its widespread acceptance and integration makes it the clear winner. So keep the technology alive, use it, fight DRM [Digital Rights Management - which dictates to you, the user, how you're allowed to use YOUR OWN FILES], and don't buy copy-protected CDs.  urlLink Go read Downhill Battle for some more great digital music advocacy info .  Holy shit that was long-winded. If you made it to the end, congrats, and I apologize. Make me buy you a beer sometime or something.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, here's what I think of the latest crop of movies I've seen recently:   urlLink You Got Served : Okay, this movie was rediculous. Rediculously goddamned good. It's a dance-off movie, and by god, it's fun as hell to watch. If you can catch it in second-run theaters, do it. By all means do it. Remember watching the dancing in the old video for Thriller and saying "that is hot shit!" - well this movie is just that feeling, stretched out for an hour and a half. So go see it already. A solid 9/10, for pure enjoyment. [Yes, I know it's #3 on the IMDB bottom 100, but those people must've been expecting something different. IT'S A DANCE-OFF MOVIE. IT'S AN HOUR AND A HALF LONG DANCE-OFF, WITH MINOR PLOT TO MOVE THE STORY. Not a fucking drama people, you should know better. And I stand by my rating.]   urlLink Waiting for Guffman : I'd seen  urlLink Best In Show  a couple years ago, and really liked it, so I borrowed the DVD for this and  urlLink A Mighty Wind  from Will V. to catch Guest's other movies. WFG was a funny movie, but at times it really showed some pure comedic genius. Eugene Levy was great, and the culmination of the movie, the play, was fantastic. A good view, 8/10.   urlLink A Mighty Wind : Along the lines of the aforementioned Guest films, this is another mockumentary, documenting the lives of three folk music groups leading up to one large tribute concert. What really makes this a great film to me, besides from all the brilliant performances (including Harry Shearer) was the incredible music in the movie. The only time I'd felt as much about the soundtrack was in the phenomenal  urlLink O Brother, Where Art Thou?  [which now that I think of it, should watch again. Clooney's great in it]. But this movie is funny, has drama, and great music - yet it still holds that documentary feel. Guest is a master at this artform, and I hope he keeps it up, because he's doing a great job. See it, 9/10.   urlLink Van Helsing : The summer's first true action flick, this movie was entertaining throughout. A decent enough story, lots of action, and great special effects made it a good time-waster. I can't say I'm in a rush to see this one again, but it was worth watching. If it ever pops up and you've got the time to watch it, you might as well. An above average action flick, 6/10.   urlLink Most Wanted : Every once in a while, you do the unthinkable - you watch the late night TNT or TBS movie. After a Lakers game, I kept the TV on and watched this Keenan Ivory Wayans "masterpiece" of a movie. An action flick, a conspiracy flick, and a political thriller - this movie tried it all, and for the most part, failed. I shouldn't have expected much out of a Wayans movie, especially a Wayans movie that was  not  a comedy. Stupid me [for watching it all], 3/10.   urlLink Mean Girls : Okay, this one took me by suprise. I looked over at the tomatometer for this flick at  urlLink Rotten Tomatoes  and the ratings were suprisingly good. Didn't critics hate stupid little teen girly movies? Yes they do, but this one was different. Written by the brilliant SNL writer Tina Fey, this movie did what all other teen-girl movies don't ever bother to do - be witty, tell a good story, and have some decent freaking comedy. Lindsey Lohan is brilliant, and this honestly is the best movie I've seen in a long time in the genre. You should see it, 8.5/10.   urlLink Shaolin Soccer : Comical, but nothing phenomenal. It was worth watching, but not worth watching repeatedly. So a 6/10.   urlLink The Triplets of Belleville : This movie left me sad, because I honestly was expecting a lot more. I do like, however, that I watched an entire movie in French but managed to understand everything that was going on [the flick is real, real short on dialogue]. There were some amusing moments, but I just wasn't that impressed. A just-above-middle-of-the-road 6/10 for this one.  Now this is the part where you IM and comment that I suck. Coming in the near future:  urlLink Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban ,  urlLink The Day After Tomorrow ,  urlLink O Brother, Where Art Thou? ,  urlLink Spartan ,  urlLink Club Dread , and whatever else my bandwith and TiVo scrape up.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's admittedly been a while since my last post, but I've been *gasp* working full time, and just lazy to boot. But some things of note that I should bring up:    Trip to Pensacola was great this past weekend. Went to a concert at some bowling alley, and while most of the bands sucked, the last two,  urlLink Cruiserweight  and  urlLink Second Saturday  were both very good. SS especially - I can't wait to hear more of their stuff. Great harmonies.    After "orienting" on day shift (7a-3p) at  urlLink TMH  for the past week, tonight (Monday) marks my return to the graveshift (11p-7a). I'm a night owl, so the shift better fits me [if you don't believe I'm a night owl, check the timestamps of most of my posts on Blogger] - though the 11p-7a shift does tend to hurt the social life. All that means is that I won't be participating in things like Thursday Night Drinking - which is fine by me, as TND's dead in my mind. I enjoy traditions, and to see TND die the quick and brutal death it's died in the past month is just sad. Nobody cares about it, or wants to have it. Same thing is happening to some extent with the Sunday Frisbee Games. Oh well, if they're not happening, then I sure won't miss a thing being in the ER all night. I've got the one job where I never want to see friends come and visit me.    I need to get a damned cell phone again, not having one is just getting annoying. Coupled with the fact that I can't depend on a good number of my friends lately to keep their word and show up to things, the lack of communication is driving me batty.    NBC Home Video and Lion's Gate recently released 8 or 9 "Best of" sets for different SNL alums - I picked up the Chris Farley and Eddie Murphy ones last night. Murphy's is the best by far, and if you haven't seen it, well - you're doing yourself a disservice.    Speaking of disservice,  Fahrenheit 9/11  was a complete piece of shit. Boring as far as documentaries go, the amount of sheer sensationalism that Moore piled in there was just too much to take at times. I downloaded it (thanks for the permission, Mike) and my family watched it - and not a single one of us (we're a half republican, half democrat family) thought it was worth anything. On the other hand,  50 First Dates  was enjoyable. Adam Sandler 1, Michael Moore 0. It's odd, but I can think of at least 5 Sandler movies that I've really enjoyed:  Happy Gilmore, Billy Madison, 50 First Dates, Punchdrunk Love,  and  Mr. Deeds . Odd, eh? 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One thing that the Tallahassee crowd tends to do is end up swimming during a night of drinking. It's almost like we're magnetically drawn to them. But honestly, is there anything more fun than swimming around with friends, all boozed up? The Pensacola trio consisting of Melissa, Meghan, and Anthony have come to town both last Monday and yesterday for concerts, and both times drinkin' and swimmin' have been part of the night. Good people, and they're a lot of fun to spend time with. Melissa came back from Will's CousinFest with me, and stayed the night over here [along with Will] on my couch. It's been great getting to know her - a real cool girl. There's a standing offer to her to be my roommate if we're both in Tally next year. That could be a blast.  After seeing  High Fidelity  for the umpteenth time, I'm reminded how much I like lists. So here's a quick list of songs that I've come across recently that I enjoy. Some you've heard, some you haven't. Look at the list, fire up  urlLink SoulSeek  and go get some of them:  "C'mon, C'mon" by The Von Bondies "Shanty for the Arethusa" by The Decemberists "The Chimney Sweep" by The Decemberists "The Soldiering Life" by The Decemberists "For the Widows in Paradise, For the Fatherless in Ypsilanti" by Sufjan Stevens "Starting Five" by Dios "Lightness" by Death Cab for Cutie "Title and Registration" by Death Cab for Cutie "Carry Me, Ohio" by Sun Kil Moon "Every Year You Wasted" by The Wrens "Bandages" by Hot Hot Heat "Adapt" by Cursive [There's a bunch I'm forgetting, they'll get posted some other time]  Melissa told me to go test out  urlLink Orkut  which she described as "less gay than Friendster" it's essentially a tool to chart, track, and build relationships online. You basically list your friends and your interests, and through other friends, online communities, and the like you can link up with friends, some long lost, and keep up relationships. I found communities for the High School I went to, my college, my hometown, for my favorite bands, and for people who think the New York Yankees can suck it. Go give it a shot. If you want to add me, send me an email or an IM. [Wow, that description didn't do it much justice, but trust me, it's a cool thing.  urlLink Just go sign-up for it, already .]
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love punk rock - that's been well established. So what kind of music rubs me raw? What kind of music gives me waves of nausea? What kind of music inspires a murderous rage deep within me? Shitty pop-punk. I even feel dirty having to put "punk" on the description of that shitty, shitty music. Who are these musical offenders? A list:  1. New Found Glory [the worst band in the world] 2. Good Charlotte 3. A Simple Plan 4. Bowling For Soup 5. American Hi-Fi 6. Stroke 9 / SR-71 / other pop-punk of 1999 7. Bowling For Soup 8. Yellowcard And countless, other shitty bands who I can't recall the name of other than as "that shitty pop-punk band with that one really fucking annoying song."  But don't get me wrong, pop-punk itself isn't a bad thing. Good, fast punk songs with pop-sensibilities are a great thing, but it's just hard to pull it off without sounding whiny or stupid [see above list - especially NFG, whose lead singer's voice makes me want to murder someone] - but some bands pull it off well. Examples:  1. Green Day 2. Sum 41 3. Rancid 4. Blink 182 [I'm not a fan, but they don't deserve to be in the earlier list] 5. The Offspring 6. The Living End 7. The Yeah Yeah Yeahs And a few others, but those just popped into my head at the moment.  Since looting the Zack/Nathan/Glover/Will compound of their digital cable box, I've been able to get 50 or so more channels on my TVs - including a long-awaited return of MTV2. M2 was part of basic cable in Atlanta, so I watched it and TechTV a shit-ton while at GT. It's good to finally have them back, but with TechTV merged with G4, I doubt I'll watch it much. But in one 15 minute span on M2, I saw the following videos: "Float On" by Modest Mouse, "Take Me Out" by Franz Ferdinand, "All Caps" by Madvillain, "Mass Destruction" by Faithless, and "Jesus Walks" by Kanye West. That's five incredible songs, all in a row. From August 2002 through May 2003, I would go to  urlLink MTV2's online playlist  and download all the tracks, and it was a good source for new music. Sure, they play some shit [the new Ludacris is awful, anything by Juvenile, and a fair share of shitty pop-punk], but there's some gems in there too. Download those five songs and judge the quality yourself. Of course, this amazing streak of 5 videos was ended by the 6th video being a New Found Glory video.  New Found Glory...what an awful fucking band. The fact that they're going to share the same stage as Pennywise, NOFX, and Bad Religion on this year's Warped Tour is fucking bullshit. Can you possibly listen to one of their songs without wanting to obliterate their lead singer? How fucking whiny can you get? That guy's voice is fucking atrocious, and their lyrics are fucking cotton candy - no substance. As somebody who's listened to (some) Bright Eyes, I can honestly say that I would rather hear Conner Oberst cry into a microphone for an hour than listen to one minute of a NFG song. [And yes, Conner crying into a microphone is a good way to describe any Bright Eyes album ever released. Fucking emo.]  Recently downloaded albums [within the past week, a fucking long list of stuff to catch up on]:  Beastie Boys - To The 5 Boroughs (2004) Dead Prez - Let's Get Free (2000) The Von Bondies - Pawn Shoppe Heart (2004) Desaparecidos - Read Music/Speak Spanish (2002) The Elected - Me First (2004) Rilo Kiley - The Initial Friend EP (2001) Rilo Kiley - Take-Offs & Landings (2001) Rilo Kiley - The Execution of All Things (2002) Broken Social Scene - You Forgot It In People (2003) The Decemberists - Her Majesty The Decemberists (2003) Iron and Wine - Our Endless Numbered Days (2004) Sufjan Stevens - Greetings from Michigan: The Great Lakes State (2003) [what an album...] Sun Kil Moon - Ghosts of the Great Highway (2003) Wilco - Yankee Hotel Foxtrot (2002) The Wrens - Meadowlands (2003) Madvillain - Madvillainy (2004)  So as far as new music goes, I think I've got a backlog. And jeez, Jenny from Rilo Kiley is freaking hot. Go watch the video for  urlLink "The Frug"  and you'll agree with me. God I love redheads.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>