<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello?  Are we thru buying this house yet?!?!  I spent all day on the phone moving utilities - disconnecting them and reconnecting them.  UGH!  I still haven't finalized out homeowner's insurance because I can't get the needed information from my loan officer.  I am so stressed about this.  I want it to be over and done with!  We are moving next Friday, the movers are scheduled, the utilities are scheduled.  Can we make this happen now so I don't have to go and undo everything?  Our move came to a screeching halt for two weeks because of our appraisal.  The first appraisal didn't come back high enough for the asking price of the house, so no loan for us unless we came to an agreement.  There was another appraisal done and we agreed at a lower price, but have to pay some of the closing cost - which raises what we need to have to bring to the closing table.  We have it, but it's been stressful.  We seriously thought we would be unpacking and staying put by now.  Now, this weekend, I need to make up for the week and a half that I haven't packed.  YUCK!  I really need some freaking help around here.  I need a packing party.  I'll provide pizza and drinks if you'll come help me pack!  I am about ready to change my name and run away.  Sorry, just venting! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       People are stupid.  I'm selling some things on eBay and I get this frantic email from this person saying that they entered the wrong bid.  The grammar of this email was horrible.  I felt like suggesting that she use the 1.25 she bid on my item towards an English for Dummies book.  I can't help but post the email...see below...  ---  Dear kpfeiffer79,  Hi there i'm sory i bidd wrong. my children was annoying me.. how ignore this?? can I pay for just $10.00 include S&H asap??  To view the item, go to: http://cgi.ebay.com/ws/ebayISAPI.dll?ViewItem&item=3480948623    Thank you, l*****e     From me to her: Right now it is at 1.25.  You can go in and retract your bid and then re-enter your bid right after that and enter the correct amount.    I'm sory I dont know how to do that. I'm so stupid!!   can you please let me knw how?? or just dellete my bid. please..please..my husband will beat me if i spend that much money. Help...   lynn    From me to her again: I cancelled your bid.  If you want to reenter a bid, please feel free to do so, but please make sure that you enter the bid correctly this time.  Thanks  ---  I probably was too nice.  This just goes along with all of the other stupid people I encounter on a day to day basis at work.  I manage some opt out email lists and the unsubscribe requests are priceless!  Sometimes it's hard to not email this people and correct their grammatical errors.  Some variations on the spelling of 'unsubscribe' have been: unscripe, unscribe, unscrible, un scribe, un subscribe, etc.  I could go on forever.  And let's not forget the people who type English like they are from a foreign land or a relay user.  I fully expect one of these days to get an email that says "PLS TO STOP SENDING THE EMAILS GA" 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1)  Talk about weird...we've had this woodpecker for a few months flying around the neighborhood (I'm sure there's more than one, but still).  Well, he had started pecking on one of our trees, but really hadn't gotten that far.  When I came home from work yesterday, it looked like someone had dumped a bunch of wood chips all over our yard in front of our tree.  (It looked like a hamster cage.)  Anyway, there were like 5 holes all over the branch and some of them we all the way thru the tree.  That woodpecked must have had his woodpecker friends over for a pecking party, because the tree WAS NOT like that when I left for work yesterday.  There's no way he could have done all that damage by himself.  Especially when there was only one hole about one inch into the tree and it had been that way since February.  I took pictures with my digital camera, but haven't uploaded them yet.  I just thought it was weird after the tree dream I had...especially since it was the same tree that was in the dream.  The only difference inthe dream was that it was larger and it was swapped with where the other tree is in our yard.  2)  We didn't really get any thunderstorms like I thought we were.  It really sucked.  I was really wanting a big storm - what with all that's going on around here.  We got some rain, a little bit of thunder and lightning and some wind.  Where are the Lubbock storms when you need them?  3)  I woke up this morning at 3:20 and couldn't fall back asleep.  The last time I look at the clock before the alarm went off at 6:40, it was 5:30.  4)  You know, for Dallas to be a major market for Radio and for us to be market number 5 in the nation, radio sure does blow goats around here.  Seriously.  I'm so tired of the 10 same songs that all Clear Channel stations play every hour.  I even listened to NPR this morning.  There's no formats here that appeal to me - they're all really screwed up.  I usually listen to this one AM news station in the evenings on my way home because they have 'traffic and weather together on the 8s' and it's better to listen to than all of the afternoon drives here pot together.  So, I'm trying to find that station on my radio here at work, but I can't.  All I seem to get is sports radio, some weird ass alien noises, some fundies (same on the FM side, too) and the SAME Spanish station OVER AND OVER no matter which direction I scan in (no, I'm not circling the stations that quick).  I am about to throw this POS radio out of the window into the atrium.  POS RCA - all RCA radioes I've ever had with a digital display have been defective.  They all quit working after 2 or 3 months.  BOYCOTT RCA!  (There is one cool thing about AM radio - if it's really late at night and you're bored, you can always channel surf and hear stations from all over the country.  Which is weird since it seems like AM radio is so poor quality all the rest of the time.)  5)  I'm so swollen and puffed up.  I'm ready for this baby to be born.  Everyday, I'm a little bit bigger and a little more uncomfortable.  The good thing is that his feet aren't in my ribs today like they have been for the last two weeks.  I don't mean to bitch about being pregnant, I am really enjoying it.  But, man, I am getting really ready to meet this little man.  We still don't have names and for some reason, I don't feel really compelled to hurry and pick one.  Picking a name is eally stressful - more than you would think.  I mean this is how he will be judged all of his life.  When running thru lists of names, you find yourself trying to put yourself in the mind of a mean school aged child.  (i.e. Gabriel's a nice name, but what if kids start calling him 'gay'?  And then you think, what if he is gay, you don't want him exposed to that any sooner than he has to be - you're a parent and you're trying to protect him with everything you have.)  6)  I'm tired of hearing about all of this corrupt shit going on within our military in Iraq, etc.  I don't know what more to say about it, especially without offending some people.   7)  I'm tired of all of these damn conservatives blowing their hot air all over the place.  I'm about ready to throw my hands up and move to Canada.  When my grandmother was really sick the time we ended up putting her in the nursing home, the paramedic asked her who the president was.  She replied with, "I don't know, but I think John Kerry will be come November."  God Bless Her, I hope she's right.  I realize at this point it's the lesser of two evils, but it was that way when Bush/Gore ran.  I don't think our country can take another 4 years of Bush.  I wonder which state he'll have 'recount' their votes this time.  Surely, he won't be able to pull off Florida again, but who know's since Jebby's in office there still.  8)  What is with everyone anyway?  In the last two weeks it seems like everyone has been driving like crazy - really extreme - either fast or slow.  No one can seem to stop their car before they get in the middle of the intersection and no one will back up when they are sticking out.  Everyone in the stores are crazy.  Everyone and everything is just crazy.  I think I'm thru ranting...for now... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I woke up late this morning.  Not too late, but still.  I had to stop and buy gas so that took some extra time this morning that I didn't have.  Oh well.  When I left my house this morning, it felt like something was weird outside or in the world.  Maybe it was the weather.  It was so soupy and steamy this morning.  You could feel the storms brewing in deep in your soul.  It's been rainy/stormy all around us and I am hoping that we get some of those storms.  I could really use a very loud, crashing thunderstorm right now.  There's something about spring storms that make me feel alive...maybe growing up in West Texas that did it to me.  ---  Maybe I had a weird feeling because I had a really strange dream this morning.  I fell back asleep after I got everyone up and out and this is when I had the weirdest dream I've had in a while.  I dreamed that it was very dark out, not because it was night, but because there was a very large dark cloud in the sky - it looked stormy, but it was a weird gray/purple color.  Part of one of the trees in my yard had broken and was stuck on the bottom half of the tree.  What was remarkably weird was that the tree had just broken in the middle of the night and it was springtime and it appeared that it was about to rain and there were all of these brown, dried, dead leaves ALL over the place.  WAY more than my broken tree would have produced.  Kids and parents were outside walking across the street to the school and I thought it was morning – maybe around 7:15 or 7:20, but something about the air made it seem more like an evening in the summer.  I called Scot at work to ask him about what was going on.  I knew we were having a conversation in the dream, but I couldn’t hear his end of the conversation even though we were communicating.  Maybe I heard it, but I can’t remember it.  The last thing I remember about the dream was that I told him that I would try to move the broken tree on my way out to go to work.  For some reason, he didn’t seem to think it would be strange that a woman who was 7 months pregnant was moving a tree alone.  I really expected him to tell me not to mess with it, that I didn’t need to be.  But he didn’t.  And I woke up, so I don’t know if I ever moved that tree or not.  The dream was so realistic in a way that I’ve never had a dream feel realistic.  Yet, I can’t describe the realism of the dream – there are no words.  I looked out my window twice to make sure that my tree wasn’t broken when I finally got out of bed this morning.  ---  Dreams kind of freak me out.  I usually don’t dream a whole lot, but when I do, they usually make up for all the times I haven’t dreamed.  I’m sure that I must dream something while I am asleep and that it’s just that I rarely remember them.  Most of the time in my dreams I believe that I am seeing colors but I always remember everything as though they were black and white.  That’s how that dream was this morning – everything was black and white, but I knew the leaves were brown and they sky was gray/purple.  The tree was also much larger than in real life.  My dreams almost always foreshadow something about to happen.  Which is really scary based on how the last few days have been for me.  For example, one time, I dreamed that an older lady close to my family had passed away.  Later that day, my ex-boyfriend’s mom called to tell him that his great-grandmother died.  The lady was vaguely familiar in the dream (I had never met her in person) but I knew she was related to me in some way.  I told him when the phone rang what was about to happen.  That’s the only time that’s ever happened and it was so weird that I don’t know if I ever want it to happen again or if I want to keep that power.  I assumed when I woke up (and at the time of the dream) that it was my grandmother that I was seeing in the dream since she wasn’t very clear in the dream.  There are a lot of things that have happened just in the last few days.  I can’t talk about all of it now, which is hard.  I’d like to get some of this out of me and into the open.    Stay Tuned…  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I've played around with Blogger's new features for a couple of days now and decided to make the big switch back to Blogger.  We'll see how this progresses.  It seems that I've blogged pretty steadily for about 2 years now, but I can never stay satisified with something long enough to keep it around for any length of time. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>