<Blog>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      testing the first blog?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      PHP blog package http://s9y.org/  urlLink  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today we want to Toronto African lion Safari, the admission cost for our family of 3 can cost around C70$, not including tax. then we found out there were online coupons available, so we print a coupon and safe 20%, actually, if we have time, we can go to eBay and people there are selling family pass for around C30$, it seems there are always ways to reduce cost if you spend time. Weather was perfect, and this is the second time we go to the safari, we planed the schedule very well and make the full day exactly finish all of the attractions in the park(Drive Through Game Reserve, Jungle Playground, Parrot Paradise show,Elephant Roundup demonstration, A scenic railway tour, Pets' Corner, Birds of Prey flying demonstration, take a cruise aboard the "African Queen"), only thing left out is the water play which Burwin dose not like. Even the food in the Mombasa market restaurant we enjoy it and not too expensive.  After the whole day tour, we are exhausted and I am afraid we would be too tire to play like this every day.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One big truck overturned to the sidewalk just before the windows of my office, shaking the floor just like an earchquake, lucky the driver was safe and can walk away by himself and nobody else got hurt. People were standing by and talking for whole afternoon, making lots of fun of the poor guy. and following will be our company meeting for status update, is this a bad sign for our company's future?  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Trying to get some up to date information on VoIP and Internet telephony, seems SIP is the hottest topic in this area, H.323 seems to be out of date based on some articles such as this one,  urlLink http://www.cs.columbia.edu/~hgs/papers/Schu9807_Comparison.pdf  , the conclusion is like that SIP provides a similar set of services to H.323, but provides far lower complexity, rich extensibility and better scalability. Since I prefer the open source stuff,  urlLink http://www.vovida.org  is the resource for different VoIP protocol resource, and the RTP information in  urlLink http://www.cs.columbia.edu/~hgs/rtp/  more internet voice/video resource in  urlLink http://www.topology.org/soft/avnet.html      
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Burwin and Tommy&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The application for Delin aunt's visitor visa was rejected by Canada Beijing Visa office, we complained to our local MP office two weeks ago, today I got a phone call from the MP office, with the negative result that Beijing Visa office insists the application be rejected, the reasons listed as:   Young age(before 50)  Financial status not good(don't know who's financial status it means)  The area of Shantou China has many people applied for refugee status (bad credit)  No direct relationship with sponsor   overall, all the reasons are pretty much objective, even ridiculous, we as sponsors have very good credit(financially and historically), why our aunt be rejected only because she is living in Shantou area? we as good citizens should have the basic right for our relatives to visit us, actually there is no human right in this country, what can you do when your basic right is taken away from you by the government, while you are doing everything legally?  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The picture for my profile 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My son and me&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Burwin&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The company(VanguardMS) is getting clear to shuting down itself, while the effort of pursuing a buyer is going dim, it has no other choice. Having been working on the same company for 5 years, it is not a short time for me, it is almost half of my career so far, and I love the work I was doing, ie. the network protocol development is kind of fun as well as challenge for me. Looking to the future, I don't know if I can get the same fun out of the job, anyway, the money to support the life is more important. During the 5 years, even it maybe only a short time from some points of view, the company has been changed a lot, from Motorola to VanguardMS, with different style of company cultures, you can feel the different bettween working for a big company and a middle(or small) size company, during these years, you can also feel the big changes in the IT field, and the global econocial changes, people are talking about IT jobs outsourcing, the outlook is pretty dim for IT worker in America like us. Anyway, this is a change in my life, maybe it is even a chance for me, or maybe I am just too much optimistic and should keep in mind the tough life waiting for me?
     
    
</post>


</Blog>