<Blog>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      16 Springbourne Road St. Michaels-in-the-Hamlet Aigburth Liverpool L17 7BJ  Thursday 13th May 2004  Dear Miss Howard and Mr Christian,  Taking three A2s next year, I also intend to begin an AS in Critical Thinking; furthermore, I would like to continue taking Japanese lessons with Myazaki-sensei and my individual music lessons. Additionally, I hope to continue with my role as a Senior NCO in the RAF section of the Combined Cadet Force. I am also interested in carrying on debating with my team-mate and opponent Nicola Cross, we have both learnt a lot over this past year and thanks are due to Mr Halton and Mrs Reid. We both feel that we can now take a step back when considering an argument and keep, we hope, a degree of impartiality when it is required. My studies coupled with my other responsibilities may pad out my timetable considerably but I feel that I have still more to offer to the school community.  I have been asked by Mrs Reid to be a senior librarian in advance of other library positions being filled so that I can learn the ins and outs of the library system before the current librarians leave to bigger and better things. I look forward to helping out in the library and fulfilling my responsibilities. Being an avid reader myself, I feel this job is ideal for me and it also provides excellent opportunities to form links with all parts of the student body.  I would like to build upon the responsibilities I will have and hope that I would be an acceptable candidate for the position of prefect. I imagine that the links I will have from being involved with other areas of the school will help me to communicate to other pupils. In addition, I hope that the leadership skills I feel I have learnt from being a part of the CCF will be useful when judging how to handle situations that may arise. I enjoy helping people and hope that I would be able to put what I consider to be my personal strengths to good use.  I hope I have been able to put across in this short letter my true intentions and have given you some idea as to why I think that I could successfully fulfil the role of prefect within our culturally and socially diverse, ever-changing school community. I would like to thank you both for taking the time to read this letter and eagerly await, with my fellow classmates, your decisions.  Yours sincerely,     Oscar Marcus L6A (A. C&ecirc;line) 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am on temporary hosting while my new hosts sort out a server problem. Aplogies for my absence but I'm back now! I promise I'll never leave you again, wihtout wanting to anyway.  So this week in school everyone has to write a letter applying for what they want to do in senior year next year. I'm not sure what to apply for and so far I'm really annoyed at the pncy pretencious tone that I've been writing in. It's much harder than I thought actually.  I have so many essays to do and my first exam is a fortnight today so I'll bullet point:   -  Summer is officially here as today I wore some 3/4 length troosers when I got home from school.  -   urlLink Keane  album out, go buy it!  -  I need glasses, it's official. I have to go pick some frames tomorrow.  -  I need a haircut... urgently.  -  Physics is hard.  -  I'm suffering from a sleep deficiency.  -  I lost my cashcard... again.  -  I need a job.  -  I have a headache.  -  People who earnestly tell other people what they should and shouldn't do kinda creep me out. I refer to the guy who was emphatically telling a cyclist that he shouldn't cycle on pavements.  -  School is broing me to death and I need to get out and do something, any ideas/offers welcome.  Work, sleep and food (i.e. the daily routine)  beckon.  Toodle-pip my much missed munchkins.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Coming back soon
     
    
</post>


</Blog>