<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We went to his keynote this morning. Interesting guy, definitely not what I expected, but not by any means in a bad way. Of interesting note is the temptation inherent with Apple's Rendezvous technology. Berners-Lee was on the same wireless hotspot I was on and using his laptop during his speech. If you have, or ever have had, an Apple anything, you know this could be very bad.... If I was just a hair more malicious. His name popped up on my Rendezvous buddy list and I so wanted to IM him, but held back that urge. Would that not have been in the middle of his keynote.... muhahha. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So we rolled into New York, New York last night around 12:00am. Long journey, but nonetheless very fun. We entered into the city through the Lincoln tunnel, which was amazing to see and to go through. We, Naren, Michael, Sammy, and myself, are staying at the Sheraton New York and wow. It was amazing walking through the doors. This morning we got to walk the streets for a bit and so far, I have to say... not incredibly impressed. I mean yes the buildings are huge, the city is vibrant, but something in me (maybe the 5 years of college) still thirsts for the smaller town scene. Either way, this week will be an incredible time. I am sure of it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever reached a point where you have worked for so very hard for so very long and one day it just stops? It is a very strange feeling, because every part of you wants to fail due to the stress you have put on it, while your mind still convinces you that you have work to do.   I am at that point.  Too many long nights balancing school. research, and work. Too many caffeine inductions to even concieve of taking a nap or getting sleep before 3 AM. And the worst part, everyone I know keeps telling me to relax. I guess I am attempting to figure out what I will do from here on out now that my over filled life have just been reduced by two-thirds. Guess I should try for some rest, maybe Hawaii will bring respite and re-focus.   I intend to begin posting more web philosophy here some day. Just don't know when that day will be, but keep checking. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I am going to try to actually consistently use this blog. I hope that I can stick with it.   Today kinda sucked. Between my Virtual Environment demo sucking a big one and the trouble with my thesis, I can honestly say that today sucked. Alas, I am almost done with my Masters thesis stuff, just need one more signature. I am completely done with the academic world once I get just one, little, tiny signature on my ETD form..... Cannot come soon enough.  I need more sleep. I need more fun. I need a life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I just got back in town from Hawaii. It was a lot of fun, though I had little time to actually enjoy Hawaii, due to work, the reason, and funding, I was even able to go there. On the trip I got to visit the Polynesian Culture Center, great place, but it sucks that they force the Mormon lifestyle, read in no caffeine and no alcohol, on their visitors. They could make a killing if either of those were made available. Ah well such is life though. Just in case you were wondering about the night life in Oahu, lets just say there is not a bar in Hawaii without a Karaoke machine somewhere in it, I tried to avoid the horrible singing Asian "Want to be American Idol" thing, but no matter where I went, always karaoke was there before me.   Oh and the title, the great burn, well during the trip I did not have much time to enjoy the (perfect) Hawaiian weather since I spent most days inside. On Sunday, our last day there, my girlfriend decided we should go snorkeling. NEVER GO SNORKELING WITHOUT SPF 400 ON. Trust me, my back is now lit up like a stop sign and at night it fuses to the bed... very not sexy.   All in all though, I enjoyed every last bit of Hawaii from eating Octopus and Eel at Sushi King (name harkens bad sushi, but was very good, Mike swears) to burning at Haunama Bay (which is the number 1 beach in the US by the way). I would do it all over if just for the extra time there.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>