<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys - great idea!  Can't wait to finally meet her in person.   Love, Jeanette & Darrin
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Gina and Dale,   Maya keeps getting cuter and cuter! (I love the double chin) She loves to get her scalp massaged?- she's a little diva already. (When does she get her first manicure, Gina?)    I can't believe how much she has grown and filled out. She's a sweetie! I can't wait till she's home where she belongs. Kadry, Sarah, Noelle, and Zach say hello.                                                 Love,                                                 Debbie
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Dale and Gina:  The new pictures are absolutely adorable.  I can't believe how Miss Maya has changed in just one week.  She is so beautiful with her round little cheeks.  I am so proud of both of you for having presented me with a grandchild like Maya.   This is really fun.   Love you all Mom
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maya had quite a weekend.    On Saturday she had an eye exam.  She doesn't like these much.  They wipe the poor thing out.  She was pretty sleepy the entire day and continued to be so for part of the day Sunday.    She was back to herself on Sunday night though.  We gave her a bath which she thouroughly enjoyed.  She likes to have her scalp massaged.  After her bath she ate her entire bottle for her daddy.  She is just over 6 pounds.  To see the latest pictures of Miss Maya click here:   urlLink Maya Pictures   Love, Gina
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Maya Pictures 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there - We are always happy to hear updates of Miss Mayas development.  It sounds like she is doing great, especially, since she is smiling and rolling over.  If her development is to be judged by her due date and not by her birth date, then she is way ahead.  Never heard of a baby smiling and rolling over at birth.  Let's face it, she is  absolutely incredible, wonderful, strong, cute and great.  Is she still a night owl?  The other day, when I was talking to Dale on the phone, I could hear her cute sounds in the back ground and it made my heart jump.  We are so excited that we get to meet her soon.  Hope there won't be a delay because of Luke's surgery.  He was supposed to sit in a chair today for 10 minutes, but could handle only two minutes.  We'll see how it goes. I am looking forward to the pictures.  Give Maya a kiss from me.  Love CO Mom
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there-  Sorry for the lag in posting....we've had our hands full literally...    Maya had her first pediatrician appt on Monday.  I really liked the doctor.  He seems to be very experienced with Preemies.  She was weighed and measured...7lbs 8oz and 20".  He said that she appeared very healthy.  The poor little thing had to get three shots.  Not even one week in her life without some poking and proding.  This coming week we have another doctor's appt on Wednesday and hopefully her final optometry appt on Thursday.  We're hanging in there, figuring things out as we go along.  Still struggling to get her to allow us to put her down to sleep.  It is getting a little better though.  Dale gave me the night off on Friday so that I could get an entire nights sleep.  I felt like a new woman on Saturday....        Today she is 3-months old.  This Tuesday was her due date.  They call this her "adjusted age."  When assessing her developmental milestones we are told to do them from her due date not her actual birthday.  I think that she will be ahead of her adjusted age developmentally though as she is already smiling, focusing on faces and this morning she rolled from her tummy to her back.  I had to put her on her tummy again to see if I was imagining it.  :-)  New pictures to be posted shortly.  We'll send out a notice and post the link here.  Love you all,  Gina.     
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Gina,Dale& Maya Well I hope by now that Maya is over her tummy pains.We are busy working in the yard.  Seems like that is all we do. We have been having cool weather here.  The wheat harvest is in full swing.  A special hello to Debbie, Kadry, Sara,Noelle,& Zach.  We miss you.  Hello to the rest of the family.  Will be going to the Lake for the 4th weekend.   Love, Dad & Evelyn
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dad- This seems to be the best deal right now.  Please let me know if you want me to book.  Cheers,  Gina.   $229 	 	   Leave:  Tuesday, Aug 24	 Frontier Airlines 433	 Depart: 7:10am	 - Omaha, NE (OMA)	 Arrive: 7:40am - Denver, CO (DEN) Change planes. Time between flights: 0hr 55min Frontier Airlines 169 Depart: 8:35am - Denver, CO(DEN) Arrive: 10:05am - San Jose, CA (SJC)  Return: Sunday, Aug 29	 Frontier Airlines 326	 Depart: 10:50am - San Jose, CA (SJC)	 Arrive: 2:15pm	- Denver, CO (DEN) Change planes. Time between flights: 0hr 55min Frontier Airlines 434 Depart: 3:10pm - Denver, CO(DEN)	 Arrive: 5:30pm - Omaha, NE (OMA) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning everybody, I just wanted to thank you for the coming home pictures and for sharing your life with us.  It has been a rough road, but it sure is turning out smooth.  The nursery can only be described as beautiful and unique and I am thankful that Debbie was able to play such an important part in that. I just love hearing her mews and grunts and I'm sure she makes cute faces along with that.  What a wonderful Father's Day gift!!    Love, Ct. Mom
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As all of you know...Miss Maya finally came home yesterday.  It almost felt like a dream.  What a treat to have here here with us.  Right now she is snugged out in a little baby sling across my lap...making her little grunts and sheep noises.  Everything checked out fine with her MRI.  So far...so good as far as her health is concerned.  She's having some tummy problems so our first night was a bit restless and sleepless.  I'm happy to give up sleep....if it means that I can have her here with me.  Gotta go....she's awake and demanding some attention.  :-)  Love,  Gina.    Dad- Go here for the pictures:  http://homepage.mac.com/dlbender/PhotoAlbum43.html                   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Gina, Dale, and extended family!   We are so happy to hear Maya is home. Thanks for the pictures. She's really growing and the room looks great. I love the hanging chime thing- Sarah thought it was part of the painting.      Thank you Jeanette for your sweet compliment. It really made my day! Hopefully next time I come to CA I will be able to meet you and the rest of the family.     Enjoy Maya. She will grow up so fast you won't believe it!  Our hearts to yours,   Debbie, Kadry, Sarah, Noelle, & Zach
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there - I can't believe how much our Miss Maya is growing.  And with every once she gains, she gets an ounce cuter, if that is possible.  She is absolutely adorable.  She looks like she is getting really long.  Love those legs!     Sometimes I am still awed that she is our grand daughter.  Take care, give her a kiss from us and tell her to drink up her bottle every time so she can come home to her pretty room and be with Mommy and Daddy all the time.  Love you all CO Mom and Luke
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Indeed it was great that we got to see Maya last weekend.  G&D snuck as in, myself pretending to be another sister of Ginas :-)  as only immediate family is allowed in the unit.  Maya was just adorable.  The pictures are great, but seeing her move around and making all these cutesy sounds, especially while sucking down her bottle top it all.  She is just the cutest thing and you know, Darrin and I couldn't decide who she looked like most at this point...  Debbie: I couldn’t stop looking at your "production" in Maya's room. UNBELIEVABLY BEAUTIFUL artwork!  I know Gina and Dale are working their butts of getting the house just perfect, doing a lot of painting themselves, but that room of hers is a true showpiece.    We had such a great time visiting.  I am still reminiscing a week later.  Wish we were closer :-(  Love ya - Jeanette 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it was a bit of a rollercoaster week.  Monday Maya was completely wiped out.  I could barely wake her up for her feedings.  Tuesday and Wednesday she was more alert, but she was only finishing about half of her bottles.  She would start out strong and then fall asleep half way through.  Thursday and Friday she did great.  Last night the doctor told us that they are working on her discharge paperwork.  I think that means that the plan is for her to go home next week.  It all, of course, is contingent upon her eating consistently well.    On Thursday she had another eye exam.  Very stressful procedure.  I was so glad that I was there to comfort her and hold her afterwards.  The  good news is that the doctor said she has turned the corner and that her eyes look great.  Just one more eye exam in three weeks and we should be able to put that behind us.  Maya has an MRI of her brain scheduled for Monday.  We will let you know the results.  The doctor said that there is no reason to think that anything is amiss.  Well...we will be going to see her in about two hours.  It is bath day.  Promise to get some pix and post them later today or tomorrow.  Yesterday she weighed in at 6lbs 14oz.  Perhaps she will hit the 7lb mark today??    Cheers,  Gina.          
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Gina,Dale,&Maya,    Received your message.  But have not been able to send. Maya is so cute.  Hope she will be coming home soon.  Had good luck fishing.  Caught a 5 l/2 lb. pike.  Will write more later.   Love, Dad &  Evelyn
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there - I sent, what I thought was a really nice message, yesterday.  And today I did not see it.  So I'll write it again.  I noticed that Maureen signs her messages Ct Mom, so I decided to sign mine CO Mom.  (Just so you can tell the difference).  I think you can tell the difference anyway.  I spoke to Jeanette on Sunday and she told me about visiting Maya and that her pictures don't do her justice, that she is so much cuter in person.  How that can be I don't know.  She is already the cutest baby I have ever seen.  Gina, I love your postings to keep us up-to-date in Maya's progress.  Hope she continues to eat well and has no further set-backs in her eating habits.  I know you can't wait to have her home.   Love you, all three of you, CO Mom
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning everybody.  It was a beautiful cool week with temps in the low 60's & 70's so we planned a first time condo tag sale and, of course, it rained.  By Wed. it is supposed to be 90'. Sorry to hear that Maya took a back burner for awhile with her feedings and know that you are a little disappointed.  But one must remember that she would still be incubating and you wouldn't have had all this time with her.  Babies have a tendency to do things their way and in their time frame. Isn't it amazing how quickly one can come to love someone?  Glad you had a nice weekend.  Love, Ct Mom
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Toward the end of last week the Neonatalogist decreased the number of bottle feedings because Maya was getting really tired and not finishing many of her bottles.  We were pretty bummed as we know that she has to be eating like a champ in order to come home.  Today they increased her again as she has been doing pretty well.  If all goes smoothly, she'll be home later this week.  It really all depends on the eating at this point.  Today she weighs 6 pounds 10 ounces.  Maya briefly met Darrin and Jeanette this weekend.  We were able to sneak them each in for a few minutes.  We'll try to take some new pictures tonight.  Love to you all,  Gina.   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had our "transition" meeting with the Neonatologist and social worker.    Maya was moved out of the incubator to an open crib this morning.  They said that she will likely be home in about a week.    They will keep bottle-feeding her two out of three feedings until she consistently finishes them all.  Next they will increase her to all bottle feedings using the feeding tube only when she isn't able to finish the bottle.  Then they will move her to "ad lib" feedings where they don't automatically feed her every three hours, but instead wait until she "demands" a feeding.  If she doesn't do so in four hours then she will be fed.  With these feedings, they feed her until she is full.  Once she is doing the ad lib feedings she will be about two days from coming home.      Dale and I had a great visit with her tonight.  Dad fed her.  She ate the whole bottle in about five minutes.  She was definitely wanting more.  She kept sticking her tongue out.  She was very playful.  Love,  Gina.    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from visiting Maya.  I think that it was my best visit yet.  She was wide awake and alert the entire time.  She ate her whole bottle in about 5 minutes then she sucked on her pacifier for about 30 minutes.  I wish that I could have captured it with a picture.  She crossed her little arms and held her pacifier in her mouth herself.  The physical therapist stopped by to see her.  Maya was smiling and making sheep noises (these are the coos of premies) the whole time that her arms and legs were being moved around.  I hated to put her back in the isolette as she was still wide awake when I left.  They have increased her bottle feedings to every two out of three.  It had been every other feeding previously.  Getting closer to her homecoming every day.  Love,  Gina.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When Dale was trying to explain this to me while in Cal. it sounded pretty "far out", but now seeing it in person I feel differently.  I hadn't seen the newest pictures where Maya has filled out more and it brought tears to my eyes of happiness for all that Maya, Mom, and Dad Bender have gone through and OH what an ending!!  This experience has shown us the love of family, friends, and strangers and  most of all- the love of God.      Love, your Ct Mom
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there-  Not sure what happened to my last post.  I wrote a whole update, but only the title seems to appear.  All is going well with us.  Maya has cracked the 10lb mark...as you can probably tell from the most recent set of pictures.  She is also now 21.5"...she has grown 3.5" inches since birth.  We recently changed her formula to one that is made for babies with tummy issues.  It has made a world of difference.  She is crying less often and seems to be more comfortable after feedings.  We're still struggling through the sleeping thing a bit.  Hoping that she will soon start sleeping for more than three hours...and that she will sleep longer in her own bed.  It is hard for us to sleep when she is in bed with us as she makes a lot of noises and really likes to snug.  With the recent heat wave, it gets rather warm :-)  My mom just left this morning.  It was wonderful to have her here....an extra pair of hands made things much easier.  Maya seemed to recognize her voice as when mom got here and said her name, she gave a huge grin.  We're looking foward to Luke and Irene's visit next week and my dad's at the end of August.    Love to you all,  Gina.  Dad- In case you didn't get the email about the pictures... go to  http://homepage.mac.com/dlbender/  Look at the album dated July 25th.      
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      8 pounds 2 ounes is a lot for a little girl that started out at 2.5 pounds.  I am just awed every time I see new pictures of Maya.  She shows lots of personality and you can really tell what mood she is in, compared to earlier pictures.  She is adorable.  So glad that she won't have to have those nasty eye exams anymore.  I had several retina exams and know how miserable and painful they are.  Must be even worse for a little baby.  The good thing is, her eyes are O.K.    Can't wait to get more pictures and soon I don't have to look for pictures, just take look in person.  Gina, give our love to your Mom.  I know she will enjoy being with all of you.  Love CO Mom and Luke
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maya had her second pediatricans appt yesterday.  She weighed in at 8lbs 2oz.  She's doing great.  Still having some reflux issues but the Zantac seems to be helping.  Today we visited the mean opthomologist...she's not really mean, it is just what she has to do to the poor baby.  Anyhow, the good news is that her eyes are fine.  No retinal issues at all.  Our next visit is in six months.  At that point they will check to make sure that her eyes are focusing right, no lazy eye, etc.  For that appt. they just play with the baby.  No eye drops or painful procedures.  I hear the beginnings of a cry so I'm going to cut this short today.  Cheers,  Gina.      
     

    
</post>


</Blog>