<Blog>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's here. Finally, the wonderful end of the week. I can almost garuntee that there will be no new posts over the weekend. I'm rather disapointed at the response of reviews for H:TNG, so that isn't going to be updated until my other stories have, probably Tuesday or Wednesday. It's going to have to take a back-seat, though the two reviewers for chapter 16, still have my whole-hearted 'Thanx'. The response i got for  17Whatever  was incredable. That will definately get an update on Monday, but right now Sebastian is out-of-town and therefor we cannot update. My newest story, Hiding In Plain Sight will also be updated either Monday or Tuesday, so have no fear about that! I got three positive reviews for it and that made me extactic!  Now for the reviews,  Hiding In Plain Sight, Prologue   biblios  - Thanks for the review, Mcgonagol in Oven-mitts, that image is enough to make ME shiver. Hehe. Who says Snape even has feelings for Harry **whistles inocently**. Hope you keep reading, i enjoy reading funny reviews!  Miki23  - I completely understand. I love seeing that to. The best part of any Sev/Har is the part where Harry is trying to convince Snape. It's my first time in this pairing, so i'm going to try and make it completely original, but since there is only so much i can do, i'm not promising!  Crys Skywalker  - I'm glad you like it. Don't you just heart mean Snape? I know i do. Therefor he's going to be typically Snape in the fic. I can garuntee minimal fluffiness!!   17Whatever, Chapter 5   The Shadower  - as always, i'm thrilled about your response. You're possibly one of the best reviewers a writter could have. I like the fact that you tell me what you like and voice your ideas. I'd tell you if you were right.....but that would be far to easy **evil grin*  amy  - don't worry. You won't have to wait long.   H:TNG, Chapter 15    Yaoi-is-gay-13  - Thanks a lot. I still adore 'spiffiness' mind if Skyler uses it? I know about the whole Harry/Ron/Mione thing, it's really hard to write, i keep wanting to make Harry go running to Hermione every five minutes!!! Don't worry though, who knows, maybe it'll take a turn for the better....then again....maybe not ;-)  Sowen  - I'm glad i'm writing it too. Glad you're getting back into the story also!Updated Wednesday at the very latest. Thanks for the review.  And that as they say is that. Chances are i won't post again until the weekend's over, i have much to do!  Enjoy your weekend people. Akasha xxx   PS  if your bored this weekend check out  Walking The Plank , it's an amazing Snape/Harry archive.   I heart it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone. I’m so completely relieved that my stories are still being well received despite my insane lack of attention. I updated 17Whatever last night and I intend to update H:TNG tonight. I also plan to update  Circumstances , my original slash story. If you read and like my other stuff, you should check it out on www.fictionpress.com I promise I’m going to update that if not this week then next week for sure. This week I’m just settling back into the other two. Also in the midst of all that, I need to get my own website back online. I have a busy few weeks ahead of me! Hehe. By the way, I boarded a new Harry Potter ship a few months back and plan on writing a story in said ship, so if anyone else likes  Harry/Snape  then please comment, encouragement is well appreciated. Watch this spot.   Reviews 17Whatever   Blackie   -  we’ll try to get it up as soon as possible. I’ll try to encourage Angel to write some tonight. It’ll probably up by the weekend at the latest.  artwork  – glad you liked it, we aim to please. We’ll try not to make you wait to long.  The Shadower  – again I owe you a lot. Without you the story would have probably been forgotten since I had no motivation to write. You provided that, if you would like, I’ll dedicate the next chapter to you.  That’s all for the reviews today, again, the reason I choose to answer them here is it doesn’t clog up the chapters – but I do like to show appreciation to the reviewers. For  17Whatever  though I must point out that Angel doesn’t really read the reviews, so if you would like to hound him for chapters too (which I think is only fair) you can at his hotmail adress - (just mention it's about the story) --  angel_investigations_box@hotmail.com . Thanks again, Akasha xxxxxxx 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, Thanks for the reviews. I'm really glad you actually still read H:TNG. It makes me feel all tingly inside to know that you'd keep checking for so long. I don't deserve such ego boosts. Since i don't want to clog up my storys with authors notes, i've decided to do the proper ones here, to thank reveiwers. So here goes,  H:TNG, Chapter 14  -  Elebereth  - thanks a lot. i promise i will try to update much more often. I'm sorry it took so long the first time.  yaoi-is-gay-13  - i love that word, 'spiffiness'. i may have to start using that! i'm glad you like it.  Sowen  - i'm glad you managed to catch up, i had a feeling that would happen so i tried to keep that particular chapter within a very short time-space. i promise to try and not keep you waiting so long.  Stardust  - it's to your review the others owe their thanks. if i hadn't have got that i may never have revived the story in the first place.  Thanks, thats all the updated stories i have for today. I will try to get a new H:TNG chapter up ASAP, maybe tonight. Also, 17Whatever will be updated soon. Angel and i are already working on the latest chapter, but seeing as it is in fact co-written, it will take longer than one of my own.  Also in the planning stages is a sort of buffy/harry potter crossover. If people are interested in that, please comment and let me know.  Akasha xxx
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s bad when you check you old fanfictions and realise you havn’t updated in over a year. That happened to me yesterday. I was searching happily through ff.net and found my old stories. I realised I hadn’t even thought about any of them in a long while.  However, I updated H:TNG yesterday. I have no reviews yet, although I know I don’t deserve them. I’ve given up hope anybody even reads it anymore. I plan to update regularly, which hopefully will bring my fanbase back. I just started this blog for everybody who reads my fanfictions.  Please feel free to comment about which stories you’d like updated. Or comment on idea’s for stories. I made this so that I can answer more personally to reviews than I can on ff.net. Help me make this great. Akasha xxxx 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>