<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had a great time on our trip! :)  We had to get up at 04.00 .. :/ And then we caught the train at 05.11 and got into Central Station at 06.10, and then we took the subway to where we needed to be.. which was about a 10 minute walk then from the boat. :)  We were there around 06.50, and we had to be there no later than 07.30.. :D So, we were there a little early. :/ :)  Finally, some older people showed up with a banner for the Club. And we went over and introduced ourselves, and more people showed up eventually. There were about 25 of us totally.. and we were the youngest. :) The most common ages were btwn 70-50 years. :) There was one woman who was almost 40, and another man who was close to her age, but other than that, Fredrik and I were by far the youngest. :)  But everyone was very happy to have us though, a comment made that they needed younger people in the group, and we were (are) now it. :)  But we had a lot of fun. :) The people were great. :) Very nice and polite. :) Most everyone was American, and a couple of Brits, and a couple of Swedes, and then one Finnish woman. :) But I think we made some new friends, hopefully, and that is really nice. :)  We got on the boat around 08.00 and then went straight to breakfast. Which was delicious. :) We had one of the "elegant" breakfasts, with a piano player, and champaign (for those who wanted to drink at 8 in the morning).  And then we went and looked around the ship. The first boat we were on, held about 2100 people. We stood outside for awhile and looked at the beautiful Swedish cottages and houses on the islands out in the Baltic Sea.  There was about 1½ hours of time that there was no land, out in the sea, until we could see some land of the Finnish island, Åland.  We did some shopping at the Duty-Free (Tax-Free) stores, candy mostly. And we sat by some windows and chit-chatted while we watched the ocean. It was very nice. :) And a bit of chit-chatting here and there with the other people from the club. Everyone just ran around everywhere.  And then around 13.30 those who were returning to Stockholm, got off the ship, and just walked right onto the other (smaller) ship. And then the rest of the people travelled onto Finland.  And then when we got on the other ship, we went and had dinner. Salmon, Finnish meatballs and some boiled potatoes for Fredrik and I. They had lots of different fish and kaviar, and meats and chicken, etc..  After that, Fredrik and I just sort, became very, very tired. :/ Since we had woken up so early, we became very tired. :/ So, we tried to go outside a little to get some fresh air, but there was no where to sit down. :( The 2nd boat was not nearly as nice as the 1st one. It was much smaller, only holding about 1500 people or so.  We chit-chatted a little more with some of the club people, and we went through that boat's duty-free shop and we sat and rested a little.. and began anxiously awaiting our return to Stockholm. :/ :) But that is where we probably had our most fun. :D We sat infront of some elevators, in the main lobby, and watched people go back and forth, etc.  Cause see, on these boat trips, people go on them to buy booze and drink beer, because it is much cheaper, it is tax-free. So, we sat and watched people walking (tripping over their feet) around everywhere, we watched lots of couples fight, and we watched a little boy (maybe 10 years old) playing with the elevators. It was very entertaining. :)  And then the ship finally docked in Stockholm, around 19.15, and we let all the drunk people get off the boat, so we wouldn't have to deal with them, and we got off the boat around 19.20-30 or so.. And then we met up with the other people in the club (mostly the older people), and told them all goodbye and such. And then we walked to the subway, watching more drunk people, and more couples fighting and yelling at each other. :D  And we realized that we were going to miss the train back to Nynäshamn. :(( The train leaves T-Centralen at 52 after the hour, and it was already 20.00.. :( before we even made it to T-Centralen, because all of the subway-trains were behind schedule (big surprise).......  So, we made it to Centralen, and then we were very hungry, and had an hour to wait for the next train, so we went to the Burger King in the station. And while in line, I recognized one of the people from the Swedish Big Brother show from last season. (She is very annoying and very unliked.) But it was sorta neat to see someone that was on tv, etc...  So, we ate and then we went to the train platform, and caught the 20.52 train. And it was raining lots, but there were beautiful rainbows everywhere. :) And where we were sitting on the train, there were 3 people with puppy-dogs.. :D So, I was in heaven. :))  We made it home by 22.00 (10pm). And we got in the door, and sat on the couch for a couple of minutes, and then we went to bed. :/ :) We were so tired. :)  It was a VERY long day, but we had a very nice time. It was very worth going on the trip, and it has made me very excited  for our trip to Estonia in July. :) But the boat will be even bigger than the bigger one that we were on Saturday. And it should have lots more to do on it.  Sunday we just slept all day, and were very lazy. :/ :) That was a recovery day. :))  And today is a "Red Day," a holiday day in Sweden, it has something to do with religious stuff (which is so funny because no one here is religious). :P So, Fredrik didn't have school today, so another day to just sleep and be lazy, and recover from the night of no sleep and getting up early. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love thunderstorms. :)  It is thundering lots and a little bit of lightning and some rain, too. Caesar is a little confused, but he is sitting out on the balcony watching everything. :)  And Fredrik should be home soon! :D He called around 15.30 and said that he was about an hour from home. :) He had left early, but was stuck in traffic in Stockholm. :( I called him back at 16.00 and he only went about 2 km farther than when we talked before. :/ (2km = 1.24miles) But at least he will be home a little earlier. :) And that will be nice. :) So anxious to see him. :)  I need to repot some plants. :/ They are just growing so fast. :/ Maybe I can take some pictures of our apartment since it is much cleaner now. :) Everything except the bedroom of course. :/ I put some boxes infront of the closet, so that the cat can't get to the wall and scratch. :// But I'll see what I can do. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up around 4am and let him back inside. Luckily, he didn't bother me anymore last night.  He has been avoiding me this morning, though. He knows that I am unhappy with him. :/ It is just so annoying, cause when he is calm, he is very sweet and cuddly, but, otherwise, he is the devil. >:-|  But Fredrik will be home today. :) Yay. :) Happy about that. :) He should be home hopefully btwn 18.30 and 19.00. :) He will stop and get some pizza on his way home.  And then Saturday morning we leave for our trip. We will take the train into Stockholm. We'll have to catch the 06.11 train.. :/ Hopefully, we can catch that one and get there on time, cause I don't want to take the 05.11 train. :(((
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to bed at 11pm because I had a really bad headache.  And then the cat wakes me up at 2am....... He was, like normally, scratching on the bedroom (built-in) closets, trying to tear the wallpaper off the wall- for his enjoyment. I get him, throw him in the bathroom. I usually set my alarm, so that I can let him out in an hour.  But, after last time, being up every hour on the hour from 4am until 8am ... I decided to make him suffer, and I was going to make him stay in there until I woke up again..... because I really need my sleep. I should not have to deal with this from a cat.  Well, I could hear him digging at the wooden door, and I didn't want him to ruin anything else in the apartment, so I took him and threw him outside. And now he is stuck on the balcony, and I plan on leaving him there until I wake up in the morning. I think that I am secretly wishing that he will jump...........  I just don't understand why he does the scratching at the wall, he only does it at night while we are sleeping. During the day, he doesn't pay any attention to it. I am REALLY, REALLY thinking about getting rid of him. I can't take this anymore. This is NOT normal behavior, or acceptable behavior.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink US Wedding Pictures 02 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink US Wedding Pictures 01 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wednesday, 2004-05-26    Lengthy waiting lists for operations have long been a source of complaint about the Swedish state healthcare system.   Now the head of government is experiencing the problem first hand.   Prime Minster Göran Persson needs a hip replacement operation, but he’s decided to share the lot of ordinary taxpayers and wait.   Speaking to reporters Tuesday, Persson admitted he was in a lot of pain.   The prime minister says he’s been taking painkilling drugs for two years, but expects the operation to be carried out before Christmas.    Radio Sweden News -- May 26, 2004  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wednesday, 2004-05-26    Another Swedish retail monopoly may be ending soon.   Philippe Léger, Advocate General at the European Court of Justice, has ruled that the state pharmacy monopoly is in violation of EU law.   His statement will guide the court in its formal decision, which is expected later this year.   Under the Swedish system, all medicines, even over-the-counter drugs like aspirin, can only be sold in the 900 state stores around the country. With only one store for every 10,000 Swedes, many have complained about the long lines and restricted opening hours.   The issue has gone to the European court after a health food store in Stockholm started selling prescription-free nicotine gum and patches to help people quit smoking.   However, Prime Minister Göran Persson points out that the EU court over-ruled the Advocate-General’s determination that Sweden’s state liquor monopoly was illegal.    Radio Sweden News -- May 26, 2004  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wednesday, 2004-05-26    Two more Stockholm policemen have been implicated in Tuesday’s child pornography raids.   The two, along with a third Stockholm officer, were allegedly among those who used their credit cards to buy child pornography over the Internet.   One hundred eighteen Swedish men were taken into custody in Tuesday’s raids. Altogether as many as 350 people were arrested in what has been described as the largest pedophile raid ever in the Nordic region.   The police officers under suspicion were reportedly questioned last week to insure that there was nothing to interfere with Tuesday’s raids.    Radio Sweden News -- May 26, 2004 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week just won't end. :( Missing Fredde lots still.. :/ He calls twice a day, we prolly talk a total of a couple of hours a day, and then SMS-messages and e-mails are sent everynow and then during the day as well. So, I think he misses me, too. :) And that is a nice feeling. :)  I had a dream last night in Swedish. :/ Everyone spoke in Swedish, even I, and it was very strange. :/ Hate it when that happens. :/  I have been spending the week cleaning, that has helped to make time pass by, along with tons of horror movies.. :P I've already gone through all of the Friday the 13th, and most of the Nightmare on Elm Street, and random old movies like The Fog, etc.. :/ :)  And I have our passports on the desk ready to go on our trip Saturday. :) Hopefully, I'll get some kind of an immigration stamp. :D One with a boat on it instead of an airplane. :/ :)) (Leave me alone - I'm tired.) Would be fun, but they don't stamp that much anymore. :( Not with the new scanning of passports. :(  Blah blah blah...
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I only took 2 antibiotic pills, but now everything feels back to normal.. :/  Jag mår jätte bättre. Kanske jag skulle prova lite svenska.. :/ ehh.. not in the mood for that..  But I will take some more antibiotics tomorrow, just to make sure it stays away. :)  Miss Fredde still.. :( Only Tuesday night now. :(  Caesar has been driving me nuts today.. :/ Won't stop running around in circles in the apartment. :/  And I think that Fredrik is very bored at his parents house.. :/ Even though they have a lot more channels than we have.. :D I think he misses home though.. :( And we miss him, also. :/ The week has gone by soooo slow.. :/   But Saturday, we shall go on a cruise-boat trip to Åland. It is a Finnish island btwn Sweden and Finland. We have to be at the port in Stockholm no later than 07.30 and then we will leave for a slow trip to the island, and we will get there sometime after noon, and then switch boats and then come home (on a different ship). The city we will stop at is called Mariehamn. It should be lots of fun. :) We should arrive back in Stockholm around 18.00. I got a great deal for the trip because I belong to the English Speaking Club in Stockholm, and they were able to get a good group price.  There are lots of different kinds of trips to the island. Some faster boats, etc, and trips where you can spend the day on the island and come back later in the day, or weekend trips, etc.. Like how we are going to Estonia in July.  So my parents will be here in almost 4 weeks.. doesn't seem like it! :/ Time has flown since we were in the States in January. Hopefully, Fredrik and I will be able to go back to the States next summer.   Not that much else going on here.. :/ The weather has been awful.. :/ Just lots of rain and dark clouds (normal Swedish weather).  I am approaching my 2 year anniversary here in Sweden. :) Sept 13 is the day.. but my VISA expires in the beginning of July.. :/ :) I'm still awaiting my paper in the mail telling us when we have to go for my renewal interview.. I just have to hope that they give me the Permanent Permit, instead of the Temporary one again.  It is normal to get the Permanent permit after you've lived here for 2 years, it is possible to not get it, but of course, with my luck, I won't get it... *rolling eyes* (With the temporary permit, you have to renew it every year ... the permanent one just means that you don't have to renew it unless you have to renew your passport).  Exciting huh? :P
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think my illness is coming back. :/ It is very uncomfy and sore. And starting to feel a little poofy. :/  So, I started back on my antibiotics. Luckily, the surgeon gave me an extra prescription, to get a refill when I finished my dose, so, that I could keep some pills on hand if it came back. He said that it was definate that it would come back everynow and then.. but I didn't think it would be so soon....... :/  So I will take my pills and hopefully it will go away without troubles (and pain), and Fredrik and I can still go on our boat trip on Saturday. :((
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink First apartment pictures 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Swedish Wedding Pictures 02 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Really miss him. :( This evening has been much more difficult than last night.. but maybe that is cause I saw him yesterday. :P  Ugh.. :( 4 more days until I get to see him again. :(  Hopefully, he will never have to travel much with work, cause I could never deal with this. :(  He called twice though, today, and it was very nice to talk with him.  But I have been trying to keep busy. :) Plenty of clothes to wash since I was sick, and always fun to play with the cat. And I have an endless supply of horror movies. But none of it replaces Fredrik.  I like my new journal. I have a feeling I will write plenty while Fredde is away. I have already added a link of pictures. It will just be a link in a journal entry. Easiest way to do it I think. And it is possible to leave comments under each or any journal entry, which takes away the need of having a guestbook, I think.  But now, to add more pictures..
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Swedish Wedding Pictures 01 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I received an e-mail from my mom last night, upset that she couldn't get onto my old website.. thinking that I was personally banning her from the site.. *rolling eyes* So, I had to explain that I removed the website, and that  no one  can look at it anymore.  So yes, I got rid of my old site, and decided to just keep a journal. I thought it would be a little easier for me, and easier for me to keep updated. I can still (and will still) put up pictures, so no worries about that!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My first time alone in Sweden. :/ A very strange feeling.  Fredrik left for Vallentuna today, for his last week (2nd week) of work in Norrtälje. He will be there until Friday afternoon. His first week, I went with him because of me being sick. But now, Caesar and I are staying here in Nynäshamn.  I miss him lots. :( He called in the evening and we talked on the phone for an hour. :D I was very surprised that we would talk for so long, but it was very nice.    Jag saknar dig jättemycket, älskling! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We shall be going, soon! Just waiting for Fredrik to get home from school. :) Could be here any time now. Then we will pack up the car and get goin'. :)  Remember, I can't receive e-mails while I am away. If you want to reach me, you have to call ..  011 46 730 91 41 23  Or, if you want to send an SMS (for free), go to:   urlLink Click Here   And send to phone number:  46730914123  We will be gone until July 1st. :) We'll get home that afternoon/evening sometime. Depending on when we leave of course. :)  I hope the weather will be nice there. :/ :)  Vi ses snart!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fredrik went to the "interview," which was very promising. He wouldn't start but for a couple weeks yet, so. And in the Fall, it would only be like everyother weekend or such.  They were looking for 3 people and have picked one so far, and Fredrik got a hint that he was another very probable candidate. So, that is something. :)  But, we can go to the summerhouse tomorrow. :) I couldn't decide if I did or didn't want to go. I want to go and relax and such. Nice to get away from the computer for a little bit. :/ :) But I also wanted to be here and get things done. But things will get done anyway. :)  So, I am glad we are going.  We shall stop and see mormor (grandma - Kerstin's mom) at her apartment tomorrow. Today was her and her husband's 60th wedding anniversary. :) Unfortunately we won't be able to stop at morfar's (grandpa - Kerstin's dad) place, but we will try our best on our way back. For those of you who don't know, Fredrik's grandma has the beginnings of Alzheimers and she lives in a seperate housing apartment than her husband. He couldn't take care of her any longer, so, she went into an assisted living apartment a little while back. And she is pretty much blind, so, things were difficult for her living on her own. It is very sad, because he can't visit her very often. But she is getting good care, so, that is good.  Getting everything packed for the trip. Fredrik will drive to school tomorrow, so he won't have to wait for an hour for the train to show up if he gets done early. :/ :) Not sure when we will get gone. The trip takes a little longer because of having the cat with us, and it will be interesting to take him out in the street and apartment where mormor is, but.. :/ :) he'll have to live with it. :/ :) But I have a feeling that she will like to see the cat. :) She's heard enough about him and she and I always talked about him (in Swedish) when she would call last year all the time. (That was before she got worse.)  Going to take my camera and try to take lots of pictures. :)  Friday is a Red Day, a holiday day, so people have a day off before Saturday, "Midsommar" (Midsummer) ... and all the parties on Saturday. Which is one reason why we are going to the summerhouse, to get out of the city and be in the middle of nowhere. :P  But.. I should go charge the battery for the digital camera and my cell phone.  Sov gott!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I received a call today from the Shell station here in Nynäshamn. A couple of weeks ago, I made Fredrik send an application to a job placement at the gas station. It was just for parttime - a fill in if others couldn't make it, etc...  And she called and I told her he was at school, and told her to call his cell phone, that he should be at lunch and should be able to talk.  Fredrik then called me after he talked with her, and he is going to go in today for a short interview, right after school.  So! If he gets the job, then we might not be going to the yellowhouse.. :/ :) Depends on when they want to do some training and such.. or when they will need him.  They are pretty desperate. All of their old parttime workers have now become fulltime, regular workers, so, now they really need new parttime workers.  Would be nice if he could get it.. esp if it isn't just a couple of times a month that he would work.. :/ :)  So, we'll see what happens with the interview/meeting thing and I'll let you know if we're going or not!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        SWEDEN SCORED!!!!!!!!!    HEJA SVERIGE! :)       Woohoooooooo!!!! :D  Sweden tied Denmark 2-2 at 89.18 :) .. (out of 90 minutes) and then there were 2 added extra minutes, and then Sweden just passed the ball around until time ran out. :D I bet Italy LOVED that. :D  And Italy ended up scoring in the 94th minute against Bulgaria.. but it doesn't matter. :D Because Sweden and Denmark go through!!!!!!!! YAY!! :D  After the game the Swedes and Danes swapped jersey tops and then the Danes cheered infront of the Swedes and the Swedes infront of the Danish fans. :/ :D And all the fans had signs that said "2-2" written on them.  It was a great game!! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.. :( Denmark scored again. :( So, it is 2-1. We have little hope now for Sweden to score again. :/  Ugh.. will give the end result soon. 15 minutes left of the game now.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY!! :))  HEJA SVERIGE!!   Sweden just scored on a penalty shot to tie 1-1! :)  But Italy has scored, too, now. And it is also 1-1 for them.  More to come!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it is halftime and the score is 1-0 for Denmark. :( Ugh.. :/ Not good. BUT! Bulgaria scored against Italy. :D So, if Sweden loses, but Italy loses as well, then Sweden can still go through with the group.  If Sweden loses to Denmark and Italy beats Bulgaria, then Italy and Denmark will go through. If Sweden ties to Denmark and it is 2-2 or greater and Italy beats or ties Bulgaria, then Sweden and Denmark will go through. If Sweden ties to Denmark and it is 1-1 and Italy beats or ties Bulgaria, then Sweden and Italy will go through.  Did you get all that? :)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.. I am SO tired. :( Been cleaning all day. :(  Right now I am going through ALL the cabinets in the kitchen and taking everything out, scrubbing down the inside and outside and putting everything back in. Of course doing this for when my parents come. :) But also a good 1 year cleaning from since we moved in. (Can't believe we've been here almost one year. :/ One year the beginning of September.)  Just need to go through the cabinets and get rid of stuff we never use and organize stuff better and give tupperware back to his mom and stuff like that.  But Fredrik and I are doing well! He passed his last test with flying colors. :) Very proud of him. :)  He missed school on Friday, accidently slept in, which is really no big deal. He will learn the stuff tomorrow instead. Swedish schools aren't very picky with attendance, unless you are receiving CSN money -and CSN REALLY cares if you go to class or not.  So, my week has been all messed up because of his extra day off.. :/ Yesterday felt like Sunday and today feels like Monday.. :/ And I keep thinking that I have an extra day before we leave for the summerhouse.  But tonight, Sweden plays Denmark. :) Should be a VERY good game!!  Been washing some clothes, always Fredrik's socks.. not sure how he goes through so many socks.. :/ Instead of eating them, I think our washer multiplies them. :/  I'm still undecided on if I want to take a Swedish language class again in the Fall. :/ Don't really want to. :// If I do, I am also thinking about taking a Web design class for fun. It is based on the same programs that I have used to make websites myself, so, it shouldn't be too difficult. :) And Komvux classes never really are that difficult.. so.. :/ :)  But I will be *hopefully* taking a Teaching English as a Foreign Language correspondence class in the Fall as well. (From the US.) And that will hopefully help me get a job. Unless unemployment here gets worse... but not sure how it could get any worse than it is now.....  Very anxious for our trip to the summerhouse. We will have to paint some barns. Which shouldn't take but a couple of days with both of us working. But after that, plenty of fishing and swimming in the lake. :) I know that Caesar will be very happy to go back. :)  But now, back to cleaning. :( My break is over.  Jag ska skriva igen, snart! Kanske.. :/ :)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever think your English was bad? Don't worry, it can't be as bad as this. :/ :)      
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       01. What time is it?  17.38  02. Name a it appears on your Birth Certificate?  Hillary Georgette Bates  03. Any nicknames?  Hurly, Sötnos, Hill/Hil  04. Parent's names?   Hillard & Carma  05. Number of candles on your LAST birthday cake?  24  06. Pets?  Yes, cat, Caesar  07. Favorite indian power animal?  Eagle  08. Tattoo?  Hopefully someday  09. How much do you love your job?  Don't have one! Studying at the time.  10. Birth place?  Lorain, Ohio, USA  11. Favorite vacation spot?  Prague, Czech Republic  12. Ever been to Africa?  Not yet!  13. Stolen any traffic signs?  No.  14. Ever been in a car accident?  No.  15. Croutons or Bacon Bits?  Croutons.  16. 2 door or 4 door vehicle?  4 door.  17. Salad Dressing?  Ranch.  18. Favorite Pie?  Peanut Butter Pie.  19. Favorite Number?  13.  20. Favorite Movie?  Too many to name.. but a few are: Cinderella, Lord of the Rings, any horror movie, Rocky Horror Picture Show.  21. Favorite Color?  Anything besides purple.  22. Favorite Holiday?  Halloween.  23. Favorite Food?  Salsa & chips, dressing (or stuffing), anything spicy.  24. Favorite day of the week?  Friday.  25. Favorite brand of soap?  Softsoap wash (melon smell), Palmolive- Aroma Therapy.  26. Favorite TV shows?  Six Feet Under, SouthPark, Simpsons, Scrubs, (I see a repetition here somewhere....), Everybody Loves Raymond, Grounded for Life, CP Magasinet (Swedish), High Chaparall (Swedish), Room Service (Swedish)   27. Toothpaste?  Most anything.  28. Most recently read book?  Thinner -Stephen King  29. Perfume/Cologne?  Deep Red -Hugo Boss, Creamy Coconut -Purely Silk Body Splash from Bath & Body Works, Light Blue -Dolce & Gabbana  30. Favorite Smell?   vanilla  31. What do you do to relax?  Read, sit on the balcony, stretch out on the couch.  32. Favorite Fast Food?  Pizza Hut  33. When was your last hospital stay?  July 2002  34. How many times did you fail your drivers license test?  0  35. Where do you see yourself in 10 years?  Still learning Swedish?! :P Just kidding! Living in Sweden (hopefully up north), in a nice big house, a couple of children, working, and travelling all over the world.  36. What do you do when you are bored?  Read, watch a movie, play with the cat, sew, see how all the plants are doing, write an e-mail/letter, write in my journal, read some Swedish.  37. Furthermost place you sent this message?   -  38. Who will respond the fastest?    -  39. Least likely to respond?  -  40. What time is it now?  17.51 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sweden tied Italy tonight in soccer (European Championships), 1-1! It was a great game. :) Since Sweden beat Bulgaria 5-0, now Sweden only needs to tie with Denmark on Tuesday to go through with the next group. Jätte bra! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.. rain, rain, rain. :( Only rained for a little while, but still dark clouds everywhere. :/ Although, I think Caesar is happy the sun isn't shining anymore, so that he can get some sleep.  Been busy. :/ Getting everything ready for all our trips. Have to pay bills, and get Fredrik's signed CSN papers out in the mail. And defer my student loan and send in my request for an absentee ballot for the General Election. The deadline is July 31st, but I want to send it in so I don't have to worry about it later. And it takes so long for the snail mail and such.. so.. :/  Washing lots of clothes and dishes.  I have a 3 page long *To Do* list. :/
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry I didn't write back again last night.. just didn't get around to it.  Sweden played Bulgaria in soccer last night and won 5-0. :) So, Fredrik was in a good mood last night. :) The games go all the way until July 4th, which is the Final. I have 3 out of 5 right on the betting so far, so we'll see how that goes. :/ :) 13 games total on the betting. Getting 13 right usually means you win a good amount of money. And it is possible to win for 12 or 11 correct also, and even 10 if it is really messed up results. It is always fun to do. :) A little bit of entertainment. :)  The weather has been nasty.. :/ Rainy and cold and dark. :/ And cloudy. Normal Swedish weather. :P  Fredrik has the day off, he always has the day off before a test. They give it to them so they can study. It shouldn't be too difficult. It is the stuff he has been doing intensively for the last 4 weeks. What he did when he went away with school and what he has been doing around town near his school (Haninge).  It is a test with the big instruments they use to measure land. And he has plenty of practise. :/ :) So, I think it should go well. And then the rest of his schooling (a week left after the test).. is just measuring more stuff and learning some new techniques and programs.  And then he is done June 24th.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It ended up being 33ºC/91ºF yesterday! It was so nice outside. :)  Fredrik just got home. :) He doesn't have school tomorrow. He has a day off to study for his last test that is on Wednesday. And then Thursday next week is his last day. :) And I think that that evening we are going to go to the summerhouse. And we will stay there until the following Thursday, and go home, and on Friday evening go to his parents house and then pick my parents up from the airport on Saturday. :)  Will write more later!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       1) Grab the book nearest to you, turn to page 18, find line 4. Write down what it says:  "Lillebror, var inte dum nu, sa mamma. Du har..."  Lillebror och Karlsson på Taket -Astrid Lindgren   2) Stretch your left arm out as far as you can. What do you touch first?  Swedish-English dictionary, telephone,  CSN papers, date book.   3) What is the last thing you watched on TV?  There is soccer on tv now.   4) WITHOUT LOOKING, guess what the time is.  20.00   5) Now look at the clock, what is the actual time?  20.08   6) With the exception of the computer, what can you hear?  Swedish soccer commentator.   7) When did you last step outside? what were you doing?  Today, sitting on the balcony, sewing.   8) Before you came to this website, what did you look at?  Itenerary for my parents visit in July.   9) What are you wearing?  Sweatpants and shirt.   10) Did you dream last night?  Yes, a very strange dream about Fredrik and I getting married, and something with me stealing money from Sandra Bullock. :/ (It was about 1.5 million dollars.) :/ :)   11) When did you last laugh?  A little while ago.   12) What is on the walls of the room you are in?  Paintings, beautiful picture of Prague, and my university diploma.   13) Seen anything weird lately?  Today, outside the apartment, a naked child. (She was changing out of her clothes and putting on her bathingsuit to lay out in the sun with her little friend.. but it was a double take.)   14) Last movie you saw?  Funhouse.   15) If you became a multi-millionaire overnight, what would you buy first?  A very nice, new Saab and my own private jet so I could travel where I wanted when I wanted.   16) Tell me something about you that I don't know  My lifelong goal is to teach myself how to play the violen.   17) If you could change one thing about the world, regardless of guilt or politics, what would you do?  Make a woman president of the United States.   18) Do you like to dance?  Depends on the song.   19) George Bush: is he a power-crazy nutcase or some one who is finally doing something that has needed to be done for years?  He did something that needed to be done, but it should have been done by someone else, and he has definately stayed past his welcome.   20) Imagine your first child is a girl, what do you call her?  Kajsa (not sure on middle name - although I am leaning toward Astrid or Lillian) and Magdalena, but not sure if I want that as a first name or middle name. Kajsa Astrid Molin (kie-sa ast-reed mo-lean) Kajsa Lillian Molin (KLM - HA!) (kie-sa lillian mo-lean) Magdalena - we could call her 'Lena' (lean-a) for short. (mahg-dah-lean-a)   21) [Same question for a boy]  Sebastian Fredrik (not sure on middle name - although Vladimir is still an option) Other options: Henrik (hen-rick), Gustav (gus-taav)(although Fredrik doesn't like this one), Mattias (mah-tee-us), Jonas (yown-us), Björn (very difficult - b-yern)   22) Would you ever consider living abroad?  Hmm... :D 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We went uptown this morning, looking for some shoes for me. Found a decent pair, but I just.. I dunno.. :/ I am really picky with my shoes. And they were nice and all.. Ecco shoes. But I just .. there was just a little bit of a doubt in my mind so I didn't get them.. :/ :)  And then we went looking in some "cute" stores uptown, with fun stuff. Glass and kitchen stuff, etc.. :) And I bought some plant holders. Some nice pots.  And then we went and did a little grocery shopping (milk, eggs, and some coke).  Lots of people uptown, for the EU voting that is coming up. Everyone wanting to hand you papers and such.. And they never try to hand them to Fredrik, they always want to talk to me about the stuff, and that is.. rather annoying to say the least. :/ :) But stuff like that always happens and I just say "nej, tack" no matter what they are after.. :/ :)  And around 4pm yesterday it started getting dark and cloudy and cold.. and then it started raining.. :/ And rained the rest of the day. But it has been nice today, but supposed to rain this evening, too. :/  The cat is having trouble with his pooping again. :/ Hopefully, we won't have to take him to the vet again and have them sedate him and shave all the hair off of his behind. :/ We tried cutting off some of the hair yesterday ourselves, and Caesar cried. :/ He was not happy. :/ But hopefully it is a little better. It just sucks because he smells like  POOP  all the time. :/
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An absolutely beautiful day outside today. :) It rained ALL day yesterday.. :/ But today the sun is out and there are no clouds and a nice light breeze. :) 18ºC/65ºF :) And it should warm a little more before the day hits its warm peak. :)  The cat ... grr.. everytime I clean up his toys and put them in his box.. he takes them back out again .. :/  But Fredrik's "interview" went really well on Tuesday. He will start "working" for Nynäshamn's kommun on August 16th. :) He asked about doing a summer job there but there was nothing, they said that the work during the summer was non-existent.. But when they come back in August, they have plenty to do. :)  Sorry I haven't written in a while, though. :/ I have been busy playing my Zoo Tycoon game. :D It is lots of fun! Trust me ... and very addictive.  But we have been looking for houses in the North of Sweden, at about 20 hours North of where we are. :)) (Above the Arctic Circle.) 6 months of light - 6 months of darkness .. and snow almost all year round.. :/ :) I don't mind the snow and darkness, but Fredde HATES snow.. :/ :) But.. I always remind him that he can go fishing during the summer, and then he doesn't mind so much. :)  But the houses there are SO much cheaper than here in Stockholm. A newly built house in Nynäshamn, with 2-3 bedrooms, living room, kitchen, and 2 bathrooms, goes for 250,000$ .. :/ Up north, we can get a 5-6 bedroom house, kitchen, dining room, huge library, sitting room, laundry room, sauna with a shower, 2 full bathrooms, a guest house on the property with 2 bedrooms, bathroom, a living room, a laundry room, sauna and kitchen, a barn that is a car garage,..... for 180,000$ .. :/ You are getting about 3 houses for less then the price of 1 here in Nynäshamn. :/ And we are a 40 minute drive from Stockholm City. :/ Crazy.. :/ So, I definately don't want to live in Stockholm anymore.. :/ You can find houses like this all over Sweden.. An 8 room house in Nynäshamn was going for ohh.. about 800,000$ .. :/ :)  Oh well.. :/ :) Just depends on where Fredrik can get a job, but we are going to try to look up North and in Falun. Which is where I have been wanting to go to school for the last 3 years. :/ :) There, they have a University that has a program where I can get my Masters in English Lit in 1 year. :) So, that would be really nice. :) Even if we just move there for a couple of years and he work, and I go to school, and then move wherever after that (not somewhere I would want to stay all the time) ... don't want to live in a "university town" .. :/  So, our prospective cities will be (with my horrible attempt at trying to show you how to say them) and links to where they are located in Sweden: Kiruna (Keer-u-na) -  urlLink MAP   Boden (Bo-den) -  urlLink MAP   Luleå (Lue-lee-oo) -  urlLink MAP   Falun (Fa-luun) -  urlLink MAP   Härnösand (Hair-new-saand) -  urlLink MAP   (In the Map - you see the map of Sweden to the Left - and that shows where the city is located in Sweden, and then the picture on the right shows the town a bit closer up.) (Luleå and Boden are very close to each other.)  And don't mind me ... I am bored.. :/ :)) Who knows where we will end up by the time he is done with school next year.. :/ :)  But things are going well here. Nothing too exciting or interesting I don't think. :) We'll be heading off to Strand (the summerhouse), soon, and then my parents are leaving 3 weeks from today! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not sure about other parts of the world, but here in Sweden yesterday, Venus passed infront of the sun. Here is a really cool picture of it:     
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Lord,   I pray for   Wisdom to understand my man;   Love to forgive him;   And Patience for his moods.   Because Lord, if I pray for Strength,   I'll beat him to death.   AMEN
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Today is Sweden's National Day. No one celebrates it. :/ :) It is a very boring, typical day, just like all the others. The only difference is that everyone makes sure that they fly their Swedish flags.. which most people do all the time anyways.. Everyone here has high flagpoles, and Swedes are proud of them, too.  Not that much going on really. :/ I've read a little about Estonia, from a book that my Austrailian friend in Nynäshamn has let me borrow for the summer. Trying to figure out where we should eat while we are there.  And I have spent some time writing my Aunt and Uncle in Kentucky a letter. I haven't seen them in a few years, and my husband has never met them (along with all my relatives there), so we are going to try to make a trip to the US next summer, and make a trip to Kentucky and see everyone.  I repotted my mini-rose plant today. It really needed it and I think it is happier. :) (At least I tell myself that.) :)  Caesar has been good, he is playing on the balcony with a straw.. presently his toy of preference the past week.  And my orchid is growing a new flower, so I am happy about that. :) And some other plants are starting to bloom, so that makes it purdier around here... not just GREEN everywhere. :/ :)  There are so many job openings for preschool teachers/caretakers, and I really want to apply for them, but I am too nervous to do so. :(( I'm always too afraid that my Swedish isn't good enough. :( The age group for the children is 1-5 years, so I probably know more Swedish than the children do anyways. *rolling eyes* But I am just a scaredy-cat. :( Since the job market here is the worst, everyone is unemployed, and there is always someone who is more qualified anyways.. Ehh...........  Hmm... Not that much else going on though.. :/ I washed a whole load of laundry today that was ONLY Fredrik's socks... :/  I have been playing my Zoo Tycoon game today ... I have 3 more senarios to go until I have finished everything, and I REALLY want to finish them.. :/ :) Sorta a petpeeve of mine. And Fredrik has been playing his Nintendo a little, and a little on an icehockey demo game (that is like his soccer game).  The weather has been a little unfun today. :/ Cloudy and a cold wind. But when the sun shines, it is really nice out.  It starts getting dark around 11.30pm now.. :/ And it is daylight at around 2am.. :/ :) Midsummer will be the longest 24 hours of light.. hopefully I can grab some pictures. And after that, the days will get shorter again, until winter, when it gets dark at 3pm. Ahh.. Sweden......
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fredrik and I ran (not literally) to the Pharmacy today. I made him buy some suntan lotion, and sun-block. To help since he is out in the sun all day long.  And the cat has been lazy all day. :) Just sleeping and being cute. :)  Total Recall is on soon! :) Yay! :) Last night Terminator was on, but they always show the good movies so late at night. :( Unfair. Cause then I get sooooo tired.. :/ Jag är redan trött.. :(  But my mom and dad are the best, yay! :) They bought me a present.. or.. well.. they bought our future child a present. :) Here it is:       It is really neat. :) I'm very anxious to use it. :/ :) But not for awhile! It is like a playpen, or a "play-yard" is what they are calling it nowadays. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fredrik just saw on the news that Ronald Reagan has died at the age of 93. Ehh.. :/ Very sad news. Never fun when a President dies, whether you like them or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Honeymoon to Prague 03 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm baking some Sockerkaka. :) (Sugarcake for those of you who are Swedish-challanged.) :))  I still can't get it as good as Fredrik's dads.. :( But mine is a little special now. :) I don't bake one big cake, I make muffins, and I add a little vanilla sugar.. :) And it gives it a really nice taste and Fredrik loves it, so.. :) Thought I would make some for him. :)  And washing clothes now, too.. :/ :) My most favorite thing in the world!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  :/ :)  Might make some chocolate chip cookies, too.. :/ :) We'll see. :)   Right now I am adding the rest of the Prague pictures to the bunch. :) It just takes forever! Cause the pictures are so big and such nice quality. (Put on from the CD I got when developed.)  And I am also working on something else, too. I am putting together a collection of my best photography and I'm sending it to a publishing company. :) See if they like my work or not. :) Who knows. :)  Men vi har skitbra nyheter, oxå! But we have some great news, too! :)  Fredrik has an internship interview appointment next Tuesday. :)) The 8th of June. :) To work here in Nynäshamn. :) With the kommun.. or our local area. :) He would just do a bunch of different stuff, which would be a great assortment of different things to work with, which would be great practise. :) He would, measure land if they want to build a new house somewhere, things like that. :) So, we are hoping for that, esp since it is right here at home. :) His schooling isn't THAT far away, but it is a good 30 minute train ride in each direction, which can get a little tiresome. :) And now he can come home for lunch, or we can meet somewhere in town, and that would be lots of fun. :)   Fredde bought me the Mangler yesterday. :)) A very silly, scary movie with Robert Englund (Freddy Krugger from Nightmare on Elm Street). I've been wanting it for awhile, and he found it in a store yesterday at lunch. And I let him get a game for his Nintendo. :) He doesn't play it (the Nintendo) that often.. :) Just everynow and then when he gets tired of his soccer game on the laptop. :)  Our evenings consist of having dinner, and then both of us plopping down on the couch for some tv or usually a movie or two, and he sits and messes with his soccer game a little and I sew. :) Usually always a nice, quiet evening. :) Until the cat starts running around. :/ :))
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Beautiful outside today. :) Perfect weather. About 22ºC/72ºF. :) Nice warm sun and a cool breeze. :)  Good Swedish summer weather. :)  Fredrik is getting a bit of a tan, though. :) Since he is doing so much stuff outside all day for school, he is all red. :D His arms and face. :) But it is turning brown. :)  I need to get a squirt-gun, though. :/ For the cat. He keeps walking in my flowers on the balcony. *rolling eyes* He's trying to catch the bugs that land on the flowers....... So he crawls through them (I'm surprised the holder can hold up his weight).. but then he squishes the flowers and now they don't look so good as they did..... So that annoys me. So I want a little squirt gun to shoot at him when he is up in there, and it should deter him to keep away. Might work, too, for him scratching at the wall when we sleep? But that has been a little better. Because we got a lot of boxes and suitcases to put infront of the wall.. so there is no empty space where he can get to the wall to scratch. :/ The room is cluttered because of it.. but at least we can sleep the whole night through. :/  Och jag behöver prata mera svenska med Fredrik. :/ Jag vet inte varför vi inte kan göra det.. kanske för att engelska är lättare.. :/ För att han kan samma som jag. :/ Men jag har inga problem att skriva och läsa (tror jag).. och jag kan prata när jag måste, vilket inte är så ofta.. :/  Kanske skulle jag ta SAS igen.. men jag vill inte. :/ Men pengarna.. :/ Det skulle vara värt besväret.. :/ Men bostadsbidraget...... :/
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is a nice June day today. :) Time is going by so quickly, though. :/ The weather is pretty nice though. :) 20ºC/~70ºF. The weather is slowly getting better. :/ It rained for about 3 weeks straight. :/  And I am feeling much better. :) My boo-boo is almost all gone I think. :) Should probably make a trip to the husläkare.. :/ but I don't wanna. :((  Fredrik got a call last night from a telemarketing place (sorta), and asked if he wouldn't mind working this summer. (YAY!) We sent out plenty of applications a long time ago, and finally someone responds! But they demand that you work 3 weeks straight. And he only has 4 weeks free during the summer, so, he will try to work those 4 weeks. Would be something at least. :) And better than just sitting around here all day. :/ :) So, hopefully, that will work out. :) And it is better than just "telemarketing," that is the name we are giving it. It is to help sell products for cancer research or something like that.  I am almost finished putting up the pictures of our trip to Prague. :) One more set of photos left to do. :)  I did take pictures on our boat trip, but I still have to get them developed. Along with a lot of other rolls of film. :/ :)  But we bought tickets for a soccer game for when my parents are here. :)) Should be fun! We are in the 3rd row from the bottom. :) The tickets were 220sek a ticket, which really isn't that bad. :) I have an itenerary of things to do while my parents are here. :/ :) So, that we can try to do as much as possible. :) 3 days gone with the trip to Estonia, 6 days hopefully spent in Stockholm, a couple of days here in Nynäshamn and shopping round in Haninge, etc.. and a boat trip with his parents from Stockholm to Vaxholm. So, I think we should have a very nice time. :))  And my parents are also planning on coming for Christmas. :) Which I am almost even more anxious for. :) I really want them to experience a Swedish Christmas. :) A bit different than in the US, lots of fun traditional stuff I would love to share with them. :) And, hopefully, my nephew, Craig, will be able to come with them. He is 18, and I think it would be lots of fun for him. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Honeymoon to Prague 02 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Honeymoon to Prague 01 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fredrik and I just watched    Fahrenheit 9/11   , and I must say that it was an incredible movie. Everyone must see this. I don't care if you  hate  Michael Moore, or if you  love  him. You  need  to see this movie. It has absolutely nothing to do with Moore, it only shows a different view of Iraq. It shows military men, actual fighting, it shows Iraqians, it shows Americans who have lost their children in Iraq, etc... etc...      It just shows something a little different than the normal, American, biased news reporting.  This might upset some of you, but as I decided long ago, I am voting for  anyone  else besides Bush Jr. come November.. (or October for me, my absentee ballot has to be in by the end of October). I hate War. And it is wrong, always wrong. And I will not vote for someone who takes my country to War and doesn't give me a good reason to do so.  I guess I could go into a big tangent on what I think about War, but I won't do that. :/ :) Not the time nor the place, maybe. And I don't want to upset any of my readers.   On a happier note, Fredrik and I shall go to the movies tomorrow. :) We shall see  Spiderman 2 , hopefully, it will be good. :/ :) Considering we paid SEK 185 (25 USD) for 2 tickets for a showing at 2p.m.. :/ :) And we have to drive a good 45 minutes to get to the movie theatre. :/ :))  And we are planning something for our Anniversary. :) Trying to at least. :/ :) Fredrik is only scheduled to work the weekends now. So, we are going to see if we can take a week (try to get a full 7 days - if he can get off work) and rent a cabin up North somewhere! We can get a 6 person cabin for ourselves for about 530$ for 7 days. Might seem like a lot. But it is like a house pretty much. :) Kitchen, bathroom, 2-3 bedrooms, and an awesome view. :) We might be going to where we went about 3-4 years ago or so. Probably end up in the same cabin, even. :/ :) Which I wouldn't mind. :) Some beautiful streams and rivers there, and some absolutely beautiful mountains. :) Or we might go to some other place, we're not sure yet. :) Just waiting to see if he can easily take the 2 days off without anyone getting upset or not.  This idea (Fredrik's) has cheered me up a bit, from my depressed state about the job. My mom suggested we go and spend a night in Gamla Stan (Old Town), and the quotes are around 80 USD, but that is  per person . Rooms in Sweden are usually paid for by person.. :/ And that gets expensive. :/ :) So, the cabin for a week for that money, really isn't that bad. The neighbor can come and feed Caesar and water the plants (if they are home), so that wouldn't be a problem. Or the older woman that lives below us..  Now I'm rambling. :/ :) More later! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Still no news today. So, I have accepted that I didn't get any work with the school. Ehhh.. a bit depressed, yes. But I'm living with it. I know I'm not the only one who didn't get the job, so, that helps just a little. Not like it was between me and one other person or something.  Fredrik is working now. He was supposed to work from 12.00-16.00, but they asked him to work 08.00-14.00 instead. Two more hours of work. But I think he prefered this, because he would be home a little earlier.  Caesar is doing well, he's just been sleeping the entire day so far.  Not sure the rest of Fredrik's working days for next week, I think that he has the entire week, and then he works the weekend. He might be working on Monday, though, I don't remember. :/  Downloading lots of movies and burning them.  The weather is very warm, hot even. I'm anxious for Halloween.  Men, nu ska jag gå.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No word yet on the job. :( She said that she would call or e-mail me on Friday, of course if she had everything figured out. But I knew it would be later in the day when she would get ahold of me, she seems to like doing things later in the afternoon.. after 5pm and such. So, If I don't hear from her by today, then I will just figure that nothing worked out, and just go on from there. :P  But, they found the 4th prisoner this morning, around the same area as the others, but around here.  The orchid has bloomed! :) I will put a picture on. :)       I'm still trying to get together pictures of the apartment.. :/ Promise. :/ 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who don't know, 4 Swedish convicts escaped prison the other day. :/ :)) The prison is about 40 minutes north-west of here. :) They drove, guess where?? Yupp.. South-east towards this area, and were actually found in Sorunda, which is about.. oooh.. 10 minutes from here by car. :D If even that. :/ :) It is a little village that is in our "Nynäshamn" town. :/ :)) But they have caught 3 of the 4, but the 4th one is still missing, he is a "cop killer."  So yeah! An escape convict is running around our town!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The interview went pretty well I think. :) The woman was really nice, the principal of the school. She is Swedish. And there are 65 students in the Pre-school. My job would be in the Nursery (1.5 year olds - 3 year olds).   I am still hopeful for the job ... esp since things went so well. But I have learned that that doesn't mean anything. :/ :) So, but I am hoping, and we'll see. Her last interview is on Thursday, and she said she will let me know on Friday.   So.. we'll see. :/   :)   I stayed up until Fredrik got home last night. :/ :) He got home around 00.20.. :) I was pretty tired, and so was he, but we stayed up a little bit.. so we could see each other (nasty long shifts). :/&nbsp;And then we ended up sleeping all day. :/ :) Which is okay I guess. :) And he left for work around 14.55 ...   So a long day by myself. :( *pout*   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wish me luck! *gulp* :(( 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. It's acceptable to eat lunch at 11.00.   2. You think Leif "Loket" Olsson is entertaining.   3. You rummage through your plastic bag collection to see which ones you should keep to take to the store and which ones can be sacrificed to garbage.   4. You associate peasoup with Thursday.   5. The first thing you do on entering a bank/postoffice/pharmacy etc. is to look for the queue number machine.   6. You accept that you will have to queue to take a queue number.   7. A sharp intake of breath has become a part of your vocabulary, as the sound of ahh'.   8. You associate Friday afternoon with a trip to 'Systembolaget'.   9. You think nothing of paying $50 for a bottle of "cheap" spirits at 'Systembolaget'.   10. Silence is fun.   11. Your native language has seriously deteriorated; you begin to "eat medicine" and "hire videos".   12. Your front door step is beginning to resemble a shoe shop.   13. When a stranger on the street smiles at you, you assume that: a. he is drunk, b. he is insane, c. he is American, d. he is all of the above   14. You stay home on Saturday night to watch 'Bingolotto'.   15. It seems sensible that the age limit at Stockholm nightclubs is 23 or 25.   16. The reason you take the ferry to Finland: a. Duty free vodka b. Duty free beer c. To party   17. The only reason for getting off the boat in Helsinki is to eat pizza.   18. It no longer seems excessive to spend $200 on alcohol in a single night.   19. The fact that all of the "V's" and the "W's" are together in the phone directory seems right.   20. You care who wins "Expedition Robinson".   21. Your old habit of being "fashionably late" is no longer acceptable. You are ALWAYS on time.   22. You no longer see any problem wearing white socks with loafers.   23. You know that "religious holiday" means "let's get pissed!"   24. You are no longer scared of Volvos and Volvo drivers.   25. You have your own innebandy club.   26. You enjoy the taste of 'Surstromming'.   27. You find yourself debating the politics of Carl Bildt.   28. You see 'mmm' as conversation filler.   29. An outside temperature of 9 degrees Celsius is warm.   30. When someone asks for "three cheers", you say: "hoorah, hoorah, hoorah, hoorah".   31. You wear sandals with socks.   32. You eat jam with savoury dishes.   33. You have only two facial expressions, smiling or blank.   34. You think riding a racing bike in the snow is a perfectly sensible thing to do.   35. You think it's more fun to stay at home and drink than to go out.   36. You wear warm clothing when it's 25 degrees plus in April - because it's April.   37. You wear shorts and T-shirt when it's barely 10 degrees in July- Because it's July.   38. You get extremely annoyed when the bus is two minutes late.   39. You think women are more equal than men are and deserve to have better positions in the work place.   40. Your wife watches TV while you look after the kids.   41. You become a punctuality freak and dump your friends for being late more than once.   42. You spend week's entertainment budget on a pack of cigarettes and a drink in 'Gamla Stan'.   43. When a stranger asks you a question in the street, you think it's normal to just keep on walking, saying nothing.   44. You've been engaged for four years and don't have any plans to get married.   45. Americans start to look entertaining, witty and fun, and you just want to go to the USA travelling "across the country on a Greyhound, because it's romantic..."   46 .You and your friends know exactly the same information, and have the same attitudes and beliefs in the value of Social Democracy.   47. You lose any artistic talent whatsoever.   48. You think that if you smoke a joint you will wind up in an insane asylum (or become habitual criminal).   49. You seriously contemplate getting S&M. You wear a dress or skirt over your trousers and combine them with training shoes (it's especially problematic if you're male)   50. You jot down "fisk fingrar" on your shopping list.   51. You no longer look for Vegemite on supermarket shelves, even if it's your first time in that particular store.   52. You think black rimmed glasses are cool. Your wardrobe now consists of 20 different shades of black and grey.   53. You get excited watching a bunch of lame 'celebrities' on a fortress island playing games that are about as intelligent as mud-wrestling.   54. You look forward to the next program about practical jokes done on lame celebrities/ has-beens by other lame celebrities who don't really deserve air time.   55. It doesn't feel like lunch unless it's hot, full course meal drenched in gravy.   56. You eat unlimited amounts of sausage products without worrying about your nitrate intake.   57. You think that an unripe wedge of tomato on a limp leaf of iceberg lettuce can be called a salad.   58. You don't question the concept of 'telephone time'. It seems reasonable that no business can be conducted on Friday afternoons (or the entire month of July).   59. You assume that anyone who apologizes after bumping into you is a tourist.   60. You think that it's normal that a huge restaurant has a smoking section, which consists of three tables near the door.   61. You reach for your pocket 20 times a day as mobile phones ring all around you.   62. You actually care if your mobile phone meets the fashion standard and so do your new Swedish friends!   63. It seems reasonable that even those asking you for money at 'T-Centralen' reach for their pocket as the melodic music of the Swedish mobile phone resounds.   64. You get into a Mercedes taxicab and think nothing of it.   65. Paying $5 for a cup of coffee seems reasonable.   66. You understand that when a colleague asks you out for 'a drink', it will probably be a long night with a severe hangover the next day.   67. You start to think that having a sauna in the nude with a bunch of strangers is a necessary part of daily life... and a necessary part of business.   68. You believe that when you finally win your Nobel Prize, it is best to be modest and say; "Oh really, it was nothing..."   69. You get offended if, at a dinner party, someone fails to look you in the eyes after raising their glass for a toast.   70. Seeing a young woman with candles stuck to her head no longer disturbs you.   71. You become extremely skilled at assembling pre-packaged furniture kits.   72. "Candles" are a PERMANENT fixture on your weekly shopping list.   73. You get to the movies early so that you can watch the commercials.   74. Most of your friends have the same names and you must use both names to distinguish between them.   75. You can calmly accept 52% tax without trying to incite a revolution.   76. A "wild party" is defined as 23 people all crammed into someone's one bedroom apartment drinking 2.8% lager.   77. Your Swedish friends convince you that Finnish people are all uncultured barbarians because they do not stop drinking after the pubs are closed.   78. The only words in your quick memory is "Hey" and "Hey Hey."   79. You find yourself debating the politics of G. Persson and the EU membership.   80. You think is perfectly normal that nobody talks in the bus or in the subway.   81. You think that if your colleagues don't say hello to you is a sign of respect.   82. You are sure that Swedish people are very well educated.   83. You accept the fact that to rent an apartment you have to stay in line for 5 years.  84. It's tolerable to see young girls spit on the street and burp on the subway.   85. You are not offended when a man offers you a suck on his sorbits.   86. When you accept you must walk 2 kilometers to collect your book/tape from the postoffice because they don't deliver small packages (or large ones...).   87. When you no longer try to just present your VISA card on its own but in tandem with your obligatory ID card.   88. You take every opportunity to raise an enormous flag in your garden.   89. It feels natural to have every floor in the apartment consist of wood and no carpet.   90. It feels right to call Coke, Cola.   91. You like having rice with breakfast, lunch and dinner.   92. You mutter "oy,oy,oy" continually to yourself even though you are the only one in the room.   93. You understand why there is a Green, Red and Blue underground.   94. You understand why the underground does not only operate underground.   95. Even you can hear your own accent.   96. When someone asks you for "sex" you assume they mean half-a-dozen.   And my own personal one:  97. You stop converting Swedish crowns into your native currency.    
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.. :/ Still nervous but I am doing better I think (better than yesterday). But we'll see how I'm doing tomorrow. :/ :))   We're watching  The Lord of the Rings - The Two Towers.   Very good movie of course. :) But we just ate dinner, paused the movie to eat, and now we're finishing it. :)   I will probably leave on the 15.11 train tomorrow. And I'll get into Central Station around 16.08, and then the next train that I have to get onto leaves at 16.20 ... so, I'll have 10 minutes to get to the platform next to mine. :)) I think I can deal with that. :)  And then it will be a 10 minute ride on that train and I'll get off at the 2nd stop. And then the school is right near the train stop. :)  The interview is at 17.00 ... So, I will be there a little early, but that is okay ... can take my time walking and try to get rid of any butterflies in my tummy. :)   I want my orchid to bloom!! :((  It grew new .. umm.. what is it called..? Pods..?!! :/ It is ready to bloom ... but it just won't .. grr...!  I am just impressed that it grew a stem for flowers. :D :/  Kerstin bought it for us last September as a "moving in" present. And it of course had flowers then, but they eventually died, and we kept the plant, never thinking that it would actually grow something new. :/ :)) But it did. :) And now I want flowers!!!! :D   Ugh.. :/ :) Don't mind me. :/ :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I won't write again today in Swedish. :) Jag lovar.   Right now we are watching  Children of the Corn 2 . A GREAT movie!! :D But we are taking a lazy day. I will prepare myself for my interview as best as possible. I've already read and learned everything about the school that I can (I think). And I want to try to prepare myself with good answers for interview questions and stuff like that. Is it silly to do that?! I want to try to be prepared as possible, to try to help me be not so nervous. :/ Because I get really nervous with things like this. :/ Because I know how important it is.  I am also getting ready to send in some pictures to a publisher, and see if they would like to buy some of my photos. I want to try to start doing some freelance photography. I really enjoy taking pictures and I'm pretty good at it, so, might as well try to make some money. :P :)  And Fredrik only works 3 days next week! Tuesday, Wednesday, and Thursday. But he works from 3p.m. to midnight on Tuesday and Wednesday, and on Thursday he works from 8p.m. to midnight. :/ Maybe not so much fun. But he gets good&nbsp;extra pay after 6pm.  What do I wear to my interview?! I want to wear something comfortable, esp since I have to walk from the trainstation to the school. And then home again after I get back to Nynäs. But I also want to look nice. So.. ugh... what do I wear?!  We'll see.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Allt e jävligt skitbra idag här i Nynäshamn. :) Vädret är jätte fint och idag har Fredde och jag städat lägenheten (inte så kul men det är bättre nu).  Jag har fått ett jätte "snällt" kort från Kerstin och Lars (och Simson) för att önska lycka till med intervjun på tisdag.  Jag e jävligt nervös.. :/ Men hoppas att allting går bra.  Kanske ingen mera svenska just nu?  Mera sen..  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.   Today, I walked uptown, took a whole 8 minutes, but anyways, I had to go to the Police Station to get my criminal record print-out, my background check, for my interview next Tuesday.   I go in and there is this REALLY old woman behind the desk.  And I told myself earlier, this is a police station, they have to know English, I am speaking English. :P  I walk in, and she knows NO English.. grr... and at this point, I didn't even think about switching to Swedish.. :/  And another woman came in, middle aged, and her English was so-so..  But they finally figured out what I wanted .. att jag ska jobba med barn...  And.. they give me a form to fill out... :-| ... to send to KIRUNA........  Which is.. as far north in Sweden as you can go, about 20+ hours north of here..  I don't see why I couldn't get a print out from Nynäshamn's police station, since uhmm.. that is where I live.....   But, I always forget that we are in Sweden.. *rolling eyes* ...and nothing is ever done simply here.. :/  I know that that is the way it is done, fill out the form, send it in, and then they get back to you, but I just don't like it. :P :)  So, the paper says that it will take  TWO WEEKS  for them to process everything. And, since it is summer now, and no one works in Sweden during the summer (June-August), it will probably take 2 months to get everything done. Grr...   Ugh.. sorry.. :/ I guess this is my anti-Swedish ranting for the day.   But, on the other hand, I had to go uptown, so I stopped in the betting store (yes, the betting store - not the post office) to pick up my package! I ordered a really, really nice scarf and hat from my "favorite" soccer/icehockey team in Sweden. They were on sale on the team's online store, so, I ordered them. :P They are really, really nice. :) Very thick and such, perfect for a Swedish winter.   I will put pictures on!        &nbsp;  &nbsp;    They aren't black, they are a dark blue. And each have the team logo on it. They look nice, and aren't very flashy. So, that makes them perfect. :P   Fredrik worked again today from 10.00 - 20.00.. :/  Probably be home for lunch again at the same time, at 17.00 or so ... And then he'll be home sometime after 20.00. But he has the weekend off .. so, I know he will sleep a lot. :))   Caesar is sleeping curled up on the couch now. :) Cute as a button. :))   And the weather ... cloudy, windy, cold. :/ :)   Fredrik and I watched  The Hidden  last night. :) Great movie. :)   But I think that that is all for now. :)  I am already getting anxious about my parents visit for Christmas and New Years. :)) And, hopefully, my nephew, Craig, will be able to come with them! A great experience for him&nbsp;I think. :) We won't be able to see much of the city, because of the weather. But at least he'll get to experience Christmas (eller Jul) in another country. :) Food, traditions, etc.. :) Always fun. :)   &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been trying to think of things that Fredrik and I could do&nbsp; to celebrate our First Year Anniversary.  It is on a Monday.. blah.. so.. it will have to be the weekend before. Which he might have to be working on, but hopefully not. And Monday, he would probably definately be working, and *hopefully* I will be, too.   It is August the 9th. But the weekend before would be best.  (The weather today is INCREDIBLE, btw! 23ºC/73ºF .. warm and a nice light breeze - a beautiful day!)   But I can't think of a thing we can do. Going away probably isn't possible.  A quiet weekend at home?! Grr.. that is what we always have.. :/   Ugh. Help!   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tjena!  Things are actually going okay for once. :/ :) Or maybe I am speaking too soon?!  But I sent out my application yesterday remember? On Tuesday, and today is Wednesday, and since Swedish mail is so efficent, I knew that the Pre-school would receive my application today. Well ... they did, and I received an e-mail from them at 5pm, asking me if I would like to come for an interview next Tuesday. :D Sweet! :) I think that that is good news. :)  I am just so excited that I  might  have the opportunity to get a job.. :/ That is sad, huh? :/  But they were looking for either:    &nbsp;A teacher's helper, for either 4 or 6 hours a day.
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fredrik is sleeping now. He went to bed awhile ago. Ugh.. :/ Feel sorry for him, he was up around 4 this morning, just cause of having to get up so early (that was a little earlier than he wanted).  But the job is going okay. The other people working there are nice. I think that he thinks there should be more working, that they need the personel, but we are in Sweden :P and companies/businesses hire as little people as possible.  But lots of people just left from working there - or some will be leaving. 2 became pregnant and are going on maternity leave, and one guy was sent to prison.. :/ :) So Fredrik was one of the three that were hired new.  But things are going well here I suppose. :) We watched  Slaughterhouse  this evening.. :/ :) Fredrik was  highly  impressed! :/ :)  Oh my.. it is starting to get dark.. winter is coming.. :/ :) It is 10.40PM and it is dusk outside.. :/  Today was actually a very nice day. :) Very, very warm. :) When we went uptown, Fredrik and I could tell that we were still sick.. :/ Any type of movement made us have that annoying I-have-a-cold sweat.  But! I sent out my application for a job at the Pre-school. Although, I doubt anything will happen. The ad was out only a week ago, but they wanted someone to start August 2nd or something like that.. :/ So,.. it wouldn't surprise me if it was filled already.  And Fredrik and I's (does that work?) .. Fredrik and my.. ? Well, our 1 year anniversary is coming up soon. :/ :) Doesn't seem like we've been married for 1 year - feels more like 20.. :/ :D  Nah.. it has been a great year. :) But it does feel like we've been together a lot longer than our 6 years. 6 years in December, the 15th to be exact. :/ :)   Ooh.. and I've decided to pick a NameDay for myself. :/ :)  Swedes have a thing with names ... every day on the calendar has 1-2 names on it, usually one male and one female, and that is that person(s) "NameDay." Fredrik's is on July 18th. I always remember and say "Happy Name Day" ... :/ :) But his mom always sends some silly scratch lotto tickets or some money or something.  And Hillary (obviously) isn't on the calendar. :( But! Hillevi is! :D (Pronounced as: Hill-uh-vee.) It is the Danish form of the old German  Heilwig , meaning a combination of heil (luck) and wig (battle). Which.. Hillary means cheerful I think.. not sure if the names are the same variation, but it has to be close, yes??  BUT.. the name day is October 15th, which is 2 days before my birthday.. :P So, that is no fun.. :/ To have my Name Day right before my birthday.. :/ Ugh..  Oh well.. :/ :)) Can't have everything, right?? :)  Ugh.. but it is getting a little late I suppose.. :/ And I finally got out some of the wedding photos for family and friends in Sweden. Got some sent out to Fredrik's aunt and uncle, and some friends near the Summerhouse. And some to some friends of the family. But still have to send to the grandparents and Johan and such.  But, maybe it is close to bedtime now for me, too. :/ Or at least plop down on the couch.. :))  Hej så länge .. jag ska skriva igen snart! Kanske imorgon.. :))
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A cardiologist died and was given an elaborate funeral. A huge heart  covered in flowers stood behind the casket during the service.   Following the eulogy, the heart opened, and the casket rolled inside.  The heart then closed, sealing the doctor in the beautiful heart  forever.   At that point, one of the mourners burst into laughter. When all eyes  stared at him, he said, "I'm sorry, I was just thinking of my own  funeral...I'm a gynecologist."   And at that point, the proctologist fainted. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cold just won't leave.. :/ Going on its 8th day now I believe. I feel MUCH better, it is just all the mucus and such.. :/  Fredrik got home 2 hours early last night, :) So that was nice. He was home at 6 instead of 8. They realized that he looked pretty dead, with being sick and all, and let him go home a little early. But today he had to be there at 05.15 .. :/ But he will be home by 14.30. And he works the same tomorrow, and then on Thursday and Friday he works 10.00 - 20.00, These are long 10 hour shifts, I know.. :/ But, before like 8am, he makes extra pay, and after 6pm, he makes extra pay, too. Because it is not regular working hours, so he makes more money to work those hours, the same with the weekend.  Working normal hours during the day, he makes 87sek/hour (~$11.60/hour), and on the weekend, if he works, he gets 120sek an hour (~$16/hour), so not too bad. :) Esp for a gasstation. :/ :) (But you have to remember the cost of living in Sweden is much higher than in the USA, so, the fact that he is making 16$/hour at a gasstation means - absolutely nothing.) :/ :) :/ :(  Today, we hope to go uptown when he gets home, and I need to get some copies of my passport and VISA/work permit, so I can send it in for a job application - at the Pre-school. I have to send in my permit, so they know that I am here legally. :) And we need stamps (always need stamps), and milk of course.. *rolling eyes* .. I hate buying milk in 1 liter containers.. :( Or, that that is the only way it is sold, nothing larger. :( 3.8 liters = 1 gallon :( So, we normally try to buy about 3-4 liters of milk everytime we go to the store, which is 3-4 containers of milk,  and that lasts us like ... 2-3 days. :( So, we, like all the other people in Sweden, have to run to the store everyotherday for milk. :/ And it gets a little annoying after awhile. But, then again, you just get used to it and realize that that is the way it is. And milk here, only last for about 4 days in the fridge anyways, it isn't as pasturized (?spelling) as American milk, so, you can't stock up on it and leave it in the fridge for a week or something.  And gasoline here is also in liters..  Right now, about 10sek for 1 liter of gas ... Which doesn't seem so bad ... but..  10 sek = ~7.5 usd 10 sek x 3.8 = 38 sek /gallon 38 sek / 7.5 = ~$5.10 /gallon  So, all of you Americans who complain about gasoline prices, just think that gasoline in Sweden is around 5$ a gallon!!!!!!! And Sweden doesn't even have the worst prices in Europe. One of the worst, but not the worst.  Ugh.. don't ask me why I'm doing this.. :/ :))  Fredrik and I are still planning on going on another cruise. :) Sometime soon we hope. :/ :) Back to Estonia I think. :) We want to take a trip to St. Petersburg.. but.. ugh.. they just do not exist. :( We can take a trip to Estonia, and then take a bus into Russia (only take a couple of hours), but ugh.. that doesn't sound like fun. :/ And anyways, if we go into Russia, we have to apply for Tourist VISAs, and that takes awhile, and it is expensive.. so.. we'll stick to Estonia for now. :)  The new TV looks great, btw. :) I still have to take pictures. :/ :) I think I was waiting until the place is cleaned up a little better. Only a little bit of clothes and sheets to do now. :) But now we have to put the other TV somewhere, probably in the bedroom (Since it is the only other room we have besides the kitchen and bathroom...) :/ :)  But, now I shall go clean, or something.. :/ :)
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.. :( Miss him lots. :(  He worked today at 10.00 ... And he came home at 14.30, and I was VERY happy :)) but he was only home for lunch. :( He has to work until 20.00. :(((  And then tomorrow, he has to start at 05.30 :/ but he will be home then at 14.30, so that will be nice at least.   But I miss him lots. :( We've spent so much time together the past 3 weeks that I was so used to having him around, and now he is gone all day long. *pout* :(  We did receive our new TV today, though! :) And it is purdy. :)) 28" widescreen - Panasonic :) It came in a huge box, and Caesar has found a new favorite toy. :/ :)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Corner shelf/cabinet thing ...    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my.. :/ :) The blog options have become much more special.. :/ :)  &nbsp;   Lots more options and    stuff to play with.. :/ :)        &nbsp;   Very special.. :/ :))    But Fun.. :/ :)     &nbsp;    &nbsp;  But Fredrik and I are still sick.. :/ :(( Slowly getting better every day, but VERY annoying.. :/ I hate having a cold. :(  &nbsp;  But Fredrik's dad got here a little after 11am, and he brought us our new ... corner piece for our hallway.. not sure what to call it in English.. :/ Caesar likes it lots though.. :/ :) I'll have pictures to add of that. :/ :)  &nbsp;  And he also brought Fredrik's bike, so, that he can use that, and that will be nice for him I think. :)  And we sent back with him a coffee table that we didn't need/want any longer.  &nbsp;  My parents made it home safe and sound. :) Even though I know they aren't happy to be away, they at least made it home safely.  &nbsp;  Fredrik and I have plenty of cleaning up to do on the apartment.. :/ We let it go since we've been sick.. and there are plenty of clothes to wash, and the towels and sheets that my parents used, etc.. :) So, that will keep me busy for awhile. :/ :)   Fredrik starts working tomorrow.. :/ :) He has 5 days of "training" ... and he is working at SHELL btw, for those of you who don't know ... he'll work parttime ... like.. everyother weekend or when people&nbsp;are sick, stuff like that.. to fill in. Which will be good.. The gas station is only right down the street. And since his internship is also right down the street, everything should work out well I think.  &nbsp;  But now, I need to go fold clothes..!   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is already Thursday evening, and time for my parents to go home. :/  I know that it will be difficult for them. We've had such a great time these 2 weeks. :)  Last night we went to the soccer game (DIF - Malmö) in Solna and that was loads of fun. :) We were in the 3rd row, so, hopefully, I took plenty of good pictures. :)  So, my parents will leave tomorrow morning, we are leaving at 6am for Arlanda. And their flight leaves at 10, we should get there around 8. Then they fly back to Chicago and then to Cleveland.  Monday we had the boat trip with Fredrik's parents. :) That was fun. :) Only my 2nd visit to Vaxholm. :) And we spent the day with them and ate there before we took the boat back to Stockholm. And Tuesday we went to Skansen. It rained a little both days. :) But both were enjoyable. :)  Wednesday we had the fotboll match and we went around in the mall across the street, and had dinner at a kebab place there. And today we took it easy and went grocery shopping and had lunch, and then we let mom and dad do some packing and then we walked to a pub/restaurant behind our apartment, and that has been about it.  I have been sick since Tuesday. :( (But I had a very, very sore throat on Monday.) Jätte sjuk. :(( A bad cold and upset stomach. :( And I'm still sick. :/  But Fredrik and I will come home after we say goodbye at the airport, and then Saturday I'm sure we will spend sleeping, because I've gotten Fredrik just a little sick, so hopefully, he won't get as bad as me. :/ And then on Sunday, Fredrik's dad will drive down with a piece of furniture that is going in our hallway, a cabinet, it is really nice. :) And also bringing Fredrik's bike, so he can cycle to his internship location and to work on the weekends. :)  I am planning on applying to a job, but it is far away from here. :( On the other side of Stockholm. I applied to work there once, but then Fredrik and I ended up living in Nössemark, 6 hours from Stockholm.. :/ :) So, I had to turn down the position. :( But, now they are hiring again... it is a very private International Pre-school, for English speaking children. (Diplomat's children, etc..) It would take me 1½ hour to get there by train and subway every morning, and the same to get home in the evening, but it would be worth it to get a job. :/ Which are getting even harder to come by. :/  So, wish me luck! And pray for a safe flight home for mom and dad!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tja!!  Sorry I haven't written in a while. :/ :) We've been busy and tired. :) Running around Stockholm for the last 3 days or so. :)  The trip to Estonia was great. :) Lots of fun. :) Fredrik and I are already planning another trip, hopefully soon. :)  We came back on Wednesday and did some big grocery shopping for the next 2 weeks. And then on Thursday we went into Stockholm - into Gamla Stan, and went to the Castle (Kungliga Slottet) and we were there at noon, so we were able to see the changing of the guards and the military band. That was fun. :)  And then we walked around OldTown (Gamla Stan) and did some "touristy" shopping. :)  On Friday we went to Fjärderholmarna. :) We took a boat to the beautiful Baltic island. :) Walked around there and looked in the cute shops.  On Saturday (yesterday) we went to the Vasa Museum. :) And then walked around Drottninggatan. And did some shopping. It really wasn't that crowded for a Saturday. Not as bad as I was expecting. But we had 3 day SL cards, so.. We sorta had to go into town on Saturday. :/ :) The Vasa was VERY crowded. LOADS of Americans everywhere. :/ :) Even on the train from Nynäshamn into T-Centralen.  But today is my dad's 60th birthday! :) Today we are going to IKEA, the biggest one in Sweden. :) It is like 6 stories high or something like that. :) And it is loads of fun to go around in. :)  And then we shall buy a new TV, hopefully. And get a new black cartridge for the printer. And then we shall go to the mall there and look around, and go to the arcade place, and go bowling and shoot some pool. :)  And then dinner at the Pizza Hut there. :) Should be a good day. :)  And then on Monday, we shall go on a boat trip with Fredrik's parents. We'll all meet up in Stockholm and then leave from a boat terminal there and go to Vaxholm. Spend the day there and then ride back. Have dinner either in Vaxholm or Stockholm. (Vaxholm is a cute little tourist town on the Baltic that is a little North of Stockholm. It will take the boat about 2 hours to get there, but it will be going pretty sloooow. :) I've been there once, and it is a very nice place. But usually lots of tourists, though.) :P
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are off to Estonia soon! :)  Should be great. :) The weather is nice here in Stockholm, and hopefully it will be nice the whole cruise. :)  We are leaving at 2 to get to the port at around 3pm, and then we can check-in and wait a little and then get on the ship and it leaves at 5pm. :) We arrive in Estonia at 10am Tuesday morning, and we leave Estonia at 5pm Tuesday and arrive in Stockholm at 10am Wednesday. :)  This morning we went around in Nynäshamn, in the stores, and did some shopping. :) Then we grabbed some food from the grocery store and went and had a small picnic on the Baltic Sea. And we sat there awhile and picked flowers and took pictures. :)  Everyone is having a great time. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mom and dad are here. :) We stopped at Kerstin and Lars after we picked mom and dad up from the airport and had some scones and tea. :) Was very nice. :) And then we drove to Nynäshamn, rested a little and went uptown. It was 3pm - and all the stores were closed..... So, we will try back again tomorrow, and hopefully catch everything earlier, so we can look around. :)  And we hope to get a hotdog for lunch right on the ocean, at the touristy-antique shops.. (Ugh.. I almost wrote "antik" -- Swedish for antique.. and then I couldn't think of the English word.. :/).  And then we will go to the Ösmo (little group of houses near where we live) Plantshop and see if we can buy some pretty flowers or such. It is a fun place to look around.  And since it is 4th of July, going to grill some hamburgers and hotdogs, have some potato salad and chips, and deviled eggs, watermelon and peanut butter pie. Lemonade and ice tea. :) Should be nice! :)  And we'll see whatever else we can do tomorrow. :)  And then on Monday we go to Estonia. :) Going to drive into the city and leave the car at the fenced parking lot for the cruise line. Better (cheaper) than taking the train and subway into the city, and a little nicer for when we come home and will probably be tired, and can just drive home. :)  And then next Monday, we will go on a small boat trip with Kersin and Lars. We'll all meet in Stockholm, and take a couple hour boat trip to Vaxholm, a very, VERY beautiful Swedish city on the Baltic Sea. I've been there once, and it will be nice to go again. :)  But we have plenty planned for our 2 weeks. :) Should be lots of fun!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           I shaved Fredrik's hair this morning. :)) We waited as long as possible. It should be nice for summer. :)  We got home yesterday at 4pm (Swedish time) and unpacked all our stuff. Caesar was happy to be home. :)  And then we walked to get food at a Pub/Restaurant down the hill. And then we went to the grocery store and grabbed some milk, etc.  Mom and dad will be here tomorrow. :)) Very excited. :) Soon, Fredrik and I will go to his parents house, North of Stockholm. Should take about 1½ hours to get there. Unless we hit traffic and then it could take like 5 hours.. :/ So, that is why we are leaving earlier than we planned, so we won't get stuck in traffic. And we will have dinner with his parents.. and then pick my parents up from the airport tomorrow morning. :) They leave Cleveland today, and then fly to Chicago, and from there they go to Stockholm. Depending on how many layovers people have, the flight can take anywhere from 8-15 hours. :/ Straight from NewYork or Washington to Stockholm can take about 8-9 hours. But with my flights.. I go from Cleveland to Cincinnati (2 hours) and then Cincinnati to Paris (9-10 hours) and then Paris to Stockholm (2-3 hours). So.. that is a looooong day. :/ :)  But, hopefully, my parents will have a safe, nice trip. And we will see them soon! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Trip to the Summerhouse - June 2004 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Friday, June 25th, 2004  - 17.37   Hi! :) I thought that I would steal Fredrik's laptop and write a little. :) I'm making him put in a movie now for us to watch.  The trip on Friday was an okay one. :) Caesar did very well. He either slept on the floor in the backseat, or he mostly slept on my chest, resting his head on my shoulder. He was a good kitty. The best that he has ever behaved in the car. He never cried once.  We didn't get to stop and say hi to Fredrik's grandmother, we missed the exit on the highway, and Swedish roads are horrible (no signs and no good places to turn around), so we couldn't get there. And the traffic was horrible and it was raining LOTS and LOTS. So, we will stop there on the way home.  We stopped and ate at mAx, a Swedish hamburger chain. Fredrik ran in and got the food and we had to eat in the car because of the cat. He would have died if we left him in there alone. :/ He would have been too confused.  We ended up getting here at 10.15pm or so. But it was still light outside, so no troubles. :) Now is the lightest time of the year in Sweden. Around the Summer Solstice or Midsummer.  Caesar has been running around outside a lot. :) He is happy to be here.  We stayed up awhile last night, went to bed after 1am and let Caesar inside, locked the door and we went to bed.  I woke up during the middle of the night, and Caesar was laying in the bed between Fredrik and I. :) It was very cute. Petted him lots and he just layed there and purred. :)  We are watching High Anxiety now. :) We found lots of old VHS tapes here at the house, and just put it in to watch. :)  We woke up this morning and realized that we didn't turn on the hot water last night. :((( So, Fredde turned it on and we had to wait until the water heater filled up, and then we took fast showers and went into town.  Almost all the stores were closed for Midsummer, but I was able to get some postcards! So, that was nice. :) We were in the store and Fredrik and I were talking in English, and then I walk up to the register to pay, and she said "hej" and I said "hej" and then she rang everything up, and then she said in English "Do you need stamps?"  I HATE THAT!!!! How am I ever supposed to feel comfortable speaking Swedish, if everyone always speaks English?!  Fredrik says I should just respond as if I don't speak or know English ... I said I could just say something like: "Va?! Jag kan inte förstå vad du säger!" (What?! I can't understand what you are saying!) "Jag förstår inte engelska!!" (I don't understand English!)  It is so annoying. :( I mean.. it is nice, I know that they are trying to help and they think they are making things easier and such. And I know they can't know that I speak Swedish if Fredrik and I are speaking in English, but maybe I think they should wait if I speak in Swedish or English.. ugh..  But she handed my money and said "thank you," and I replied with "tack" in Swedish (thank you). :P Ugh!!!  But I thought I would write a little while I was away, that way it would be easier for me than just writing about our trip when we get home to Nynäshamn.  I've taken lots of pictures! Lots of Fredrik. :/ :)) But he's so cute, so how can I not want to? :))  And I've taken some pictures of the house and the barns and yard.  It rained almost all morning and midday ... so there was no painting today.  But after I got some postcards, we went and ate some pizza and then we did some grocery shopping. Just getting a little, because we plan to go back into Ed on Monday.  It has been pretty quiet here in Nössemark, though. I think it is supposed to be better next week, the weather I mean.  Fredrik's fishing lures (fishing box) is at his parents house. :/ It got messed up with all the moving stuff. So, we also have to go shopping for that stuff on Monday, so that we can do some fishing! Hopefully, we'll get to go swimming, too! Just have to hope that not too many people are visiting their summer houses up here and there won't be other people wanting to swim, too.  The Norwegian neighbor that lives next door to us was out walking his dog, and Fredrik and I went to say hi, and so did Caesar. :/ :)) Caesar kept walking up to the dog and wanting to sniff it and the dog kept wanting to sniff Caesar. And they did sniff each other, but the dog wanted more and Caesar got a little cautious and hissed at him. I have a couple of pictures and it is really cute. :)  But now I think that it is time to do something else. :) I brought my sewing stuff, and plan on doing lots of that.  Tomorrow, fixing salmon and potatoes for dinner. With a spread to put on toast that has shrimp and crab meat in it for appetizers. :)) Yummy!  I'll write more soon!    Saturday, June 26th, 2004 - 10.18   Grr..! Stupid flies are making me mad. :/ Only 2 of them in the house, and they keep landing on my arms.. very annoying. There were 3, but the cat caught and ate one yesterday. :))  Caesar is out now. He slept with us most of the night and then Fredrik let him out sometime this morning.  Fredrik just woke up. :/ :) I've been waiting for him to get up and shower so that we can eat breakfast.  The weather is a little better today. It rained sometime during the night or early morning, but it is dry now (except for some spots on the road.) ... and the clouds are moving lots, and there is pretty, blue sky behind them, so, I think that we might have a nice Midsommar day. :)  Will try to pick some rhubarb so I can make a fresh rhubarb pie. There is some that grows down by the pond.  I'm watching Norwegian TV ... :/ Very scary.. :/ We have all of 5 channels here. :/ :) SVT 1 SVT 2 TV4 Which are all Swedish national channels that you get no matter what (otherwise you have to have a satellite or go digital). And we have 2 Norwegian national channels because we are so close to Norway. (At home we have the Finnish channel instead.) And when we went on a vacation about 3-4 years ago up north, when we stayed in the cabin and such, we had German TV then ... which was scary, too. :/ It is because so many Germans go there .. so .. And lots of Norwegians live where we live ... being right on the boarder and such.  Not sure what we will do today. Hope that the weather will clear up nice after breakfast.  I need to get some more postcards on Monday. :/ I bought 10.. but I need more. :/ :))  Fredrik is almost done showering. So, I'm gonna go. :)  It's been a little cold here in the evenings ... not bad outside.. very nice outside actually, but cold in the house. :/ Have had to build fires every evening so far.  His parents are fixing up the guestroom now, so there is nothing in there. No beds.. so I think that that is why the cat is sleeping with us. And that he is so tired from getting to run around outside.  But I should get goin'!  Hejhej!    Sunday, June 27th, 2004 - 17.40   Baking the rhubarb pie now. :) Didn't get to it yesterday. (The cat just flopped down on the couch. :) A bit tired.) With fixing our big meal yesterday, too full to fix it right after dinner and by the time we wanted it, it was almost 9pm.. so.. thought I'd just wait until today. :)  But on Saturday, after breakfast, we painted plenty. :) All of the front of the big barn. Except up at the top, where we would need a ladder.  Then we had our nice big dinner. Had: fried salmon (would prefer to grill it but didn't want to deal with that - was raining by that time anyways), boiled potatoes, corn on the cob, and the spread we put on toast with shrimp and crab meat.  Right now Caesar is licking a bowl clean. :) Fredrik was wisping some vanilla cream, to put on top of the rhubarb pie, and the cat is getting to lick the bowl clean, and he is pretty happy. :))  But Sweden lost last night in the quarter final. :( To Holland (The Netherlands.) It was 0-0, and since now there can be no ties, it went into two 15 minute overtimes, and then it was still 0-0, so they had to go to penalty shots. (The best out of 5.) And it ended up being 4-4, so then they keep doing shots until one team ones. And then Sweden missed and Holland made it, so we lost. :( *pout* Ohh well.. :/  Then we got up this morning and had breakfast, and we started painting again. It rains a bit during the night, and then the morning - noon time is okay, and then in the afternoon it starts raining again.  So, we painted some more - I did the side of the barn, while Fredrik got up on the ladder and painted the top part. But that was really difficult; difficult to reach. So, he did a little and then helped me to finish it.  But the paint is running out, so tomorrow Fredrik will get the ladder and paint the top part of the side, and hopefully we have enought paint to finish that. And then we will leave the rest for his parents. :)))  It is the "Swedish" red paint ... that Sweden is famous for. :) But it looks really great, with the painted parts, it is very easy to tell that the barn needed painting. :/  But we definately don't have enought paint for the smaller barn. But that is his parents problem. :/ :)  Then after we painted today, we made a trip into Ed. We needed some Coke (I swear we are addicted to the stuff - it is worse than drugs). And we bought some milk and some breakfast items, etc..  But now the pie is done! Will have to get a piece. :) And then fix dinner in a little bit. Having tacos. :)  More later!    Monday, June 28th, 2004 - 22.47   I just took some pictures outside. :) It is still light outside and I thought it would be fun to share. :) It won't start getting dark for awhile yet. :)  Fredrik made dinner today. :) Some chicken with spices, fried in the frying pan and then some lime sauce and some "potato balls." They are like french fries sorta, but balls. And they are super yummy. :)  We didn't paint any today, the weather was a little questionable until later in the day. :/ And after breakfast, we went to Ed. Went to the Pharmacy to get Fredrik some mosquito lotion to stop the itching. And 5 more postcards from the "bookstore/betting store" and then to the grocery store (both of them) to pick up some items. And the fishing store was on lunch break until 2pm. :( And we were there at 1pm and had nothing to do until 2 .. so we had to go home. :/ But Fredrik found some stuff here in the house that we can use as lures, that will do this trip. :)  So, today when we got home, we fished in the pond, watched Boston Public (the new season has started here). And we just watched some British show/movie about a detective. It was pretty good. :)  And washed some clothes and sheets and towels that his parents left here dirty.. and hung them outside.  And Caesar climbed the big tree infront of the house, and I got some cute pictures of that. :) I caught a small fish in the pond, and Caesar jumped up and took a big bite of him. :(((( He killed my fish!!! :((  Tomorrow we plan to finish painting, until the paint runs out, and then go fishing out on the boat. :)    Tuesday, June 29th, 2004 - 13.53   Ugh..! The stupid weather. :(  Woke up this morning and the sun was shining and the sky was very blue. And we had breakfast and I went outside to sit in the sun and sew and Fredrik got up on the ladder and was painting. Very nice and warm out.  And right infront of me was a mass of daisies, so I decided to make a Midsummer flower headpiece. So, I sat in the flowers and was almost done when it started to rain. Grr.. But I sat there in the rain and finished it. It rained very little.. just a little sprinkle and then it stopped. Now Fredrik is out painting again, he is almost finished. And I decided to sit inside and finish sewing. Unless the sun is shining, no use to be outside right now - too many mosquitos. :/  And don't even think there is anything on TV. :/ :) This morning I woke up to find a black and white Swedish movie - and they were speaking in Swedish but with a German accent. :/ Was very strange.  Men, nu ska jag gå o brodera ...    Wednesday, June 30th, 2004 - 10.12   Fredrik is still sleeping. :) We end up going to bed very late, so that it is easier to fall asleep. It was dark around 11pm, and pitch black probably around 11.30pm - and then when we went to bed - around 2.30am - it was already getting light outside. :/ And by 3am it is daylight outside. And then we always wake up during the night anyways, so if we stay up as late as we can - then we just sleep.  So, we went to bed at 2.30am and I just got up at 10am - so..   And the sun is shining! Always shines in the morning, even in Nynäshamn, and then by the time noon rolls around, it gets super cloudy and rains. It never stopped raining yesterday. It even thundered, the rain got worse and the electricity kept flickering.  But now, like yesterday morning, it it a clear blue sky, sun shining, warm, very nice outside. Just don't trust it. :/  Not really any plans today.  Yesterday, we just sat inside and I sewed A LOT. Which was good - needed to get it done. And we watched lots of movies. :) And the cat came in last night around midnight - soaked to the bone. :)  Today, Fredrik will try to finish that stupid end of the barn. :/ :) And I will try to get the 3 areas of the house vacuumed that we spend all our time in. The living room, kitchen, and hallway (track lots of stuff in from outside). And the bedroom isn't bad at all. And wash the rest of the dishes, and clean up here and there and pack and wash any clothes.  Going to try to get gone around 08.50 - that way we are insured to catch the ferry down the road at 09.00 - it runs at the top and bottom of the hour on our side of the lake. It takes about 10-15 minutes to get across. It is Stora Le, one of the deepest and biggest lakes in Sweden.  Definately the biggest lake around here.  We can either take the ferry across the lake and continue to Bengtsfors and then on to Åmål, or go around the lake and go to Ed and then Åmål ... If you take the ferry - it cuts about ½ an hour off the trip at least.  But in the evening and at night, they only run the ferry once every hour ONLY if you call ahead. That is when you know you are in Sweden. :/  And then we will stop and Fredrik's grandma's apartment (mom's mom) and say hi to her. And we should still get home at at a decent hour.  But now ... going to go shower and sit outside in the nice sun and hopefully start a nice tan. ;)  Vi hörs!    Wednesday, June 30th, 2004 - 20.50   Watching the game now btwn Portugal and Holland. We are cheering for Portugal. :) Don't think that Holland deserves to be there, and all the games are in Portugal, so sorta fun if they get to get to the final. This is the Semi-Final now, and the next game will be tomorrow btwn the Czech Republic and Greece. Greece doesn't deserve to be there either, so we will cheer for the Czechs.  The weather has been absolutely wonderful today. :) Sunny and warm the whole day. So warm that we had to come inside cause the sun was too hot. :) Fredrik finished painting and I sewed some outside. :) And we cleaned the house up and I washed more clothes and they hung outside to dry. And I vacuumed out Fredrik's car and cleaned the windows. Would have washed it, but with the trip tomorrow, it will just get dirty again.. :/  Probably my last time writing until we get home, so.. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Almost time to leave. :) Very excited. :) Should be a fun trip. :) We've spent the last two days cleaning like mad. I vacuumed the couch today, ick!! Nasty.. :/ All the cat hairs. The couch was a different shade of blue.      And Fredrik just took my apartment key and gave it to the neighbors. The guy answered the door and he just looked at the key and looked at Fredrik and pointed at his girlfriend.   That sounds SO much like Fredrik and I. :/ :) But they will take care of Caesar this week and water the plants and "collect" the mail, etc. :) And we offered them 2 liters of milk that we had that we couldn't possibly drink before 4am tomorrow morning. :/ :)  So, yes. :/ We'll get up around 4a.m. in the morning I suppose. :/ Try to leave around 5a.m. or so.. because we want to get through Stockholm before rushhour.. :/ Monday morning rushhour. :/  We'll be close to Norway, but not sure if we are planning a trip there or not. Already have a few outings planned around in the nearby areas. Hopefully, the weather will be very nice. :)    And if any of you are bored, I suggest watching  Evil Dead . :/ :)  But we won't be able to check e-mail, or anything like that. If you need to get ahold of us, you have to call cellphones!  Hillary: 011 46 730 91 41 23 Fredrik: 011 46 708 92 26 71  And if that doesn't work (considering we'll be in the mountains), you can call the place we will be staying, that number is:  011 48 643 200 00  And just ask for "Fredrik Molin." (And it isn't "Mole-in," it is "Moh-lean." :P :)  That isn't our house we are renting, but it is the head renting office. It might be busy or no one answering, but just keep trying, because there isn't much business this time of year (it is a winter place), so, just keep trying!   I guess that is all for now! I will write again when we get back, and hopefully have lots of pictures to share! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      STOCKHOLM, Sweden (AP) _ Three inmates broke out of a prison in Sweden on Wednesday, assisted by masked men with automatic weapons, police said. It was the second high-profile prison break in the country in a week.  Police spokeswoman Susanne Abrahamsson told The Associated Press that the gunmen crashed a van through the gates of Norrtaelje prison, about 75 kilometers (47 miles) northeast of the capital, Stockholm.  The inmates, along with their accomplices, then fled through the gates and jumped into another car, which sped off.  She said police were searching the area around the prison with helicopters, motorcycles, cars, dogs and boats on the lakes surrounding the area.  No shots were fired by the masked men and no prison guards were injured, police said. Guards are not armed at Swedish prisons.  The escape came a week after four other inmates, including a man convicted of killing two policemen in 1999, escaped from a maximum security prison near Stockholm, embarrassing the country's prison system and resulting in calls for the justice minister's resignation. All four were captured by police.  The convicts who escaped Wednesday were not immediately identified.  It was the second breakout attempt at Norrtaelje this year.  In March, two armed men were arrested after trying to scale the prison walls in an apparent attempt to help inmates break out.  Earlier this week, the state Prison Board proposed installing metal detectors at some prisons and pledged to beef up security at the facilities.  The proposed changes came in response to last week's breakout from Hall prison, where one of the inmates used a pistol smuggled into the prison to threaten guards.  Police suspect one or more prison workers smuggled the gun inside and then let ringleader Tony Olsson out of his cell. Olsson then used the gun to force guards, all of whom were unarmed, to unlock the cells of the three other inmates. The four men took off in a red Saab that was waiting outside the prison. All four men were captured with 48 hours without incident.  The daring escape generated a public outcry about security in the Scandinavian country's prisons, and right-wing opposition leaders called for Justice Minister Thomas Bodstroem to resign. The calls were rejected by the Social Democratic government.  Sweden's penal system has long focused on rehabilitation instead of punishment. Swedish prison inmates are offered psychological counseling, anti-aggression workshops and drug rehabilitation along with high school and college courses and factory work.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Mom and Dad's Trip to Sweden - July 2004 -- 02 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Mom and Dad's Trip to Sweden - July 2004 -- 01 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Fredrik and Margareta. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fredrik and I will be going away. :) We called and made our reservations today.  We are staying at a place called Höglekardalen. The closest town to it is probably Hallen, and it is probably around a 20 minute drive. The place is in the mountains on the West side of Sweden. Not that far from the Norwegian boarder. It will be an 8-10 hour drive for us from Nynäshamn. :/ :)  Here is the website of the place we are staying:  urlLink Höglekardalen.   Hopefully, the link will work, and it is all in Swedish btw, so.. :/ :) You'll just have to look at the purdy pictures. :) We were going to stay in one of the cabins, which would have been SEK 2895 for a week (USD 390), which isn't that bad I suppose. But, when we called, the type of cabin that we wanted - they were all booked. :( So, they offered us a house instead. :) They now have (didn't have this when we were there before) entire houses that you can rent. This also holds 6 people, and has everything that the cabin has (bathroom with shower, satellite TV, kitchen, dining table, and fireplace), but the house also has dishwasher and a sauna. :) Well equipped with everything a Swedish house has. :) It was a little more expensive, SEK 3500 (USD 470), but well worth it I think for a week.  We thought about taking another cruise to Estonia, but the price wouldn't be that much different for getting a nice room on the boat for 2 nights.  So, we will leave on Monday morning, early. :) Not taking the cat with us, not allowed to have it in the house. So, today we will try to find a neighbor to come and feed him and water the plants while we are away. :)  We are very excited and anxious for the trip. :) I'll make sure to take plenty of pictures. :)  Fredrik and I even talked about bringing my family up here, too. My mom and Melissa (my sister), have talked a little about the 4 of them coming to visit Fredrik and I in the next couple of years. :) (My mom and dad, and Melissa and her boyfriend [hennes Sambo], Dustin). And if they come and vist for a couple of weeks in the Fall or something, we could go up there for a week or something and stay there. :) Cause the price would be the same for all 6 of us. :) Still only 470$, so that wouldn't be bad at all. :) It is the same price whether it is 6 people in the house (or in the cabins even) or if it is only 2 people. And it is beautiuful there! Right in the valley of the mountains, next to a river, etc, etc.. :)  And lots of cute little towns to go to. :) Fredrik and I wouldn't mind moving up there actually. Here is where we would like to live:  urlLink Östersund.   And here is a map:  urlLink Map of Östersund in Sweden.   Just click on the red dot to zoom in, etc... This is probably the biggest town near to where we will be staying. I've been there only once, Fredrik has been there plenty. :) Very cute place.  But now, I shall go. :/ :)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Spiderman 2  was great! We left around noon and got there almost at 1p.m. and then the previews started at around 1.15p.m. or something, so it was perfect timing. And then the movie was 2 hours long and then afterwards we went to the Pizza Hut there. And then we came home and drove around some different ways around Nynäshamn and found some absolutely beautiful estates! Very old, huge houses with houses on the property that could probably house 4 different families.. :/ :)  Fredrik works 15.30 to 00.15 tomorrow. :/ Not fun hours, but he only has to work on Monday, and then the weekend. And then we would probably leave next Monday (our Anniversary day) for a trip, if we go.  Not that much else going on around here. :/ Hopefully, soon, I'll have lots of pictures to share! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>