<Blog>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I LOVE female singers to death. Everyone from Etta to Janis to Tori to...Amy Lee? That's right, I said it. Say what you will about the "popness" or the "christianity(sp?) of their music, but goddamn has she got a voice. Nothing turns me on more than a moving female voice. It started, for me, with Janis. To this day you can't compare the emmotion she projected. Over the years, there have been many equals (within different genres), and silent supporters who carry on the torch of what she stood for and represented through that era of emerging blues/rock. I commend them completely. Even Pink, who soon will be playing and singing the role of the immortal legend that is Janis.  I'm veering away from my point as usual. Jains was the shit, same with Etta James, Nina Simone, Diana Ross & Gladys Knight. Myself, I'm a product of the 80's and Stevie Nicks was my beloved songbird (no pun intended).Right now, Amy Lee...fuck. Operatic with an attitude. You cant ask for more at all. I really hope she goes further than just the pop/rock scene because she honestly has the talent. Obviously, we'll see. But this is what I hope.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Didn't do shit Friday because Thursday night my friend and I simply destoyed ourselves like the obedient alcoholics we are (I don't think I've consumed that much liquer in a a REALLY long time). Bike rode most of Saturday, ran around doig errands, paying bills and what not. Caught Greyboy at the H.O.B. (see previous post). Today, biked around a little bit, went into work for a few hours. Only to find out that my new office, which was being built this weekend, is literally HALF the size of my current one. This is NOT going to work...ugh!! Now I'm chilling out, listeing to Ryan Adams "Demolition", and trying to finish up my Coachella review (yes Claire, it's coming). Tonight is the second to last episode of the Sopranos...so sad, yet so thrilling. Couple drinks at the bar after that to cap off the weekend, then back to hell tomorrow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw these trmendous musicians last night at the House of Blues L.A. They played a searing 3 hours of non stop jazz/funk/soul/R&B fusion. Talent ooozes out of each the band members pores.  Learn all about Greyboy Allstars    I first got into this band seeing Karl Denson's Tiny Universe open up for the Dave Matthews Band a few years back. If either Greyboy, KDTU, or Robert Walter's 20th Congress ever come around, I highly suggest checking them out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll start off with a quote:   I dig music -Russell Hammond, Almost Famous  That pretty much sums up how I feel about it. With a lack of a better quote off the top of my head. There is nothing I dislike about it, and with the passionate love that I have for it, I feel like I have every right to critique it with total emmotion. My main love is Rock and Roll. So if I ever knock any rap, country, pop/mainstream...it's just me either a. not knowing too much about the certain artist or b. me being an idiot. I do like certain forms of rap, country, and pop, but I just don't have the same passion for it as most.   Example: Rap. Love N.W.A., Public Enemy, Beastie Boys, Dizzee Rascal, Emienem, Biggie, Tupac. Hate DMX, Ja-Rule, etc.  Example: Country. Love Johnny Cash & Wille Nelson. Hate Garth Brooks & Travis Tritt.  So, with certain future concert reviews of mine, please bear all this in mind. Granted, I usually only go to rock, funk, pop, bluegrass, and folk type shows, I feel like somewhat of a disclaimer was in order, so please, bear this in mind.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It actually worked. Back to work on figuring this thing out a little bit more. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...popped a few pills to boot. Lately, I'mve been doing that a lot. Why? Because I've been just so...so...all over the map. SOmedays it seems my head is just going to explode from all the thoughts that swirl in my head. They not neccesarily bad thoughts...there's just too many of them. Anything I start, and seem to have some promise at...promise meaning fruitio...it just either goes away, or prompts to think of something better...or different.   This is definately drabble.  This happens with a frequency...but in my head. I don'r really, or wouldn't, do this normally. But the internet is a supr-highway. One which allows us to do exactly this. Fall into one thing, after another, after another...There should be a twelve step for the WWW. Actually, I bet there is....I should search google for it...haha...see?  What I should be doing right now, that is if I had a decent somputer and scanner, is doing a fat ass shot list and treatment for my short. I was just thinking about it actually. Reading it, coming up with ideas....but of course, I can't really do anything about it because of my "grandureness"...it needs to be perfect, flawless, and BIG. Come to think about it...that statment...it's kind of what I wish I was. Maybe that's why I want it to be like that. Shit...that's pretty fucked up, huh? Trying to mirror what I want through my work.   Am I as fucked in the head as I think. or am I normal?   It's too tough to tell these days.  I should just watch Conan.   Till next time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I moved into my new, yet smaller office today. It sucks. I'm losing so much room for equipment and what not. Thankfully, people realize that it's not working out too well, so I think we're gonna customize it with shelves and a built in desk.   People are annoyinh to me today for some reason...come to think of it, it's happening more frequently these past few weeks. Maybe it's just me, but I don't know. I think I need to start looking for different work. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel that I'm totally unstable...wanna know why?  My grandmother, who raised me, is slowly dying. We don't know how long it'll be, but she's for sure on her way out. I don't pray, but I really hoped she wouldn't survive the operation two months ago, because I KNEW this would happen. She's just sitting in her hospital bed getting infection after infection. She hardly recognizes us, and nor do we her. It's killing my mother, and just making me angry that she's a fighter. All I wanted was for her to go peacefully. That just isn't the case now, though. Man, how I wish they didn't outlaw assisted death. It seems the only thing I can think of right now that will make things not only better for her, but for the sanctity of my small family. Who knows what'll happen, but it kills me to see her suffer like this.  Life is rough. Living from check to check is by no means fun. Neither is being totally scared shitless of doing what you want to do. I seriously think I'm fucked in the head or something. I have so much support and access through work to start Directing stuff, but I simply cannot do it. After a talk I had with my friend today, I felt a little better vecause he told me what I already knew...we all go through it. But even knowing it just doesn't make it better. There are so many things I want to do with my life and my time, but sometimes all I can do is just sit here and wallow about it instead of trying to take steps toward my goals. It's what I need to do, but it seems to me that after the aforementioned conversation, I figured out what I need. It's one of two things: A partner or a woman.   If I had, let's say an up and coming producer or a D.P., on my side, ready to go and change the world with our combined brilliance, things would be different for me. I think this choice is the best. Now if I had a girlfriend (which I really am LONGING for these days), I would have a little more confidence in myself. Which in turn wouold lead to more hard descisions being executed and acomplished. Everytime I've had one in my life, it seems that things have been set in motion. I've either gotten great jobs or had really good luck with life. I don't know...I mean...you should be able to only rely on yourself in this world, hell, this town alone, but I don't think you can. I think everyone needs somebody in order to become who they are. Sort of like evolution. Every action has a reaction...etc.   Either way, things are far from good. I'm hoping getting all this out helps me out in some way, but I dont think it will. These days I think the only thing that can help me is a miracle...well...one in regards to my wants and desires. I think I deserve it. I've had a really rough life, and even though I'm doing "decent" right now, I can't help but feel that I need/want/deserve more.   Oh well...enough ranting. Time for a drink and...and...well...something else. :-)  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, these past couple of weeks I've seen some decent shows. Last weekend I hit up the Doheny Heritage festival in Dana Point. Saturday was James Brown & Etta James (among others), we heard them from the beach. It was kind of a bummer to not SEE James Brown, but hearing him and his band was enough. Very fucking talented musicians.   Sunday we actually went into the show, toasty and un-sober. Saw the Dirty Dozen Brass Band which is always a pleasure. The real treat was of course the one and only, Robert Randolph. I will travel far and wide to see him and the Family Band. We were right up front against the stage, and there we stood for his hour long, explosive set. DDBB came onto guest and they covered Papa was a Rolling Stone. HOLY SHIT!! WOW!! To top it all off, I caught his thumb-pick. The rest of the day was spent seeing various other bands that weren't that great (Lucinda Williams....SCREEEEEEEECH). Except for the closers, Los Lobos. They were really good, but just not my style. I really tried getting into them, but they were definately lacking something. DDDB guested with them as well. It was a great weekend by the beach with good music. I couldn't ask for more.   As for this past Memorial Day weekend, a friend of mine came into town and we got tore up on Friday night till 6am. The proceeding Saturday hurt bad, but I managed to make it to my friends graduation party. Good food, good laughs, good people. Good times? Yes. Hot? Yes. Hungover? YES!!!!! Thankfully, over time, I recouped nicely and got to getting over to Irvine to see...PRIMUS!!!  Such a good show. The performed the entire Frizzle Fry album after a full one hour set of brain crushing rhythms. Mud, Jerry, Puppies, & Rush's yyz in it's entirety were just a few of the memorable moments. During the intermission between sets they had these hilarious drug related propaganda videos from the 60's & 70's on the screens. The entire place was not only filled with smoke, but bellowing with laughter at these things. Such a good time.   Sunday was a relaxing day at Topanga Days, a music and arts festival in the hills. Very family orientated. Kids, Food, Beer. Saw some old faces and met some new. Heard a really good reggae band called Resonation. They were down from SLO. Ran into an ex and went back to her and her man's house for drinks. It was chill yet a bit awkward for obvious reasons. On the way out there I ran into a girl I have a crush on, and of course, didn't act on it as usually...but that's a whole nuther story that involves certain inept brain funtions. I'll touxhon those next I think.   Til the next shows. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>