<Blog>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is an experiment for a rainy day.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wrote some entries for this blog a couple of weeks ago but deleted them. I don't want fame ! But I do enjoy reading blogs and now that I've mysteriously acquired a comment, I feel it's only right to give something back.    So about this lack of desire for fame. I bought Playstation SingStar for my nieces and they came round last night for a karaoke session in our lounge.  It was so funny, especially my sister having a battle for singing supremacy with mr C ("Suspicious Minds").  He won, v funny.  Then she beat me singing "I Believe in a Thing Called Love" by The Darkness.  (Impossible to sing!)  And The Darkness are so ridiculous, just the sight of them makes me laugh. Which is the intention, I'm sure.  Anything for a laugh. On that note, a couple of nights ago we listened to a radio interview with David Sedaris, including a reading from his latest book ("Dress Your Family in Corduroy and Denim"). He is hilarious, I must buy the book. "Naked" was extremely funny. In the interview, he talked about his current obsession for catching flies to feed the spiders resident in his house. Very very funny.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK we're done with the film festival now.  Did we really need to go to 8?  They were all excellent, so I guess so.  Hearing the excited reaction to the shooting star in the Civic started to wear thin though ...   On Friday, we saw "Before Sunset," which was lovely, and set in Paris (so I'd watch it for that alone). Julie Delpy was especially good.   On Saturday, we saw "End of the Century" (not sure if that is the title), a documentary about the Ramones. My favourite interviewee was Johnny - such a hardarse.  Had an exam on Saturday, slacked around a lot on Sunday and now Monday has dawned to ... I don't know what!  I'm not sure what to do next.  Find something remunerative to do, I suppose.  Tonight we're going to see Franz Ferdinand.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We saw "Fahrenheit 9/11" last night and it was pretty much what I had expected. While worth seeing, it is hardly ground-breaking stuff.   Christopher Hitchens makes some valid points in this  urlLink scathing review  of the film.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night we saw "In My Father's Den."  After a slow start, the plot picked up in pace about half-way through and by the end I was almost in tears. (I'm not one to cry at movies.) Fantastic performances - go and see it ...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night we saw "Touching the Void."  As expected, it was a fascinating film.   Apart from anything else, I love seeing the mountains and vivid colours of the scenery.  Clear blue, white and black.  (It has been clear blue skies here in Auckland for the past few days - beautiful.)   I love to read and hear about mountaineering and exploring, and especially stories of adversity.  As in "Touching the Void," the storytellers are nearly always articulate, philosophical and flawed characters.  Forced to face their mortality, their insights and the way they express them are so interesting.    Joe Simpson seems like a classic example.  His experience was so horrific and yet there is no way it can be portrayed as heroic or, according to him, as the central event in his life.   What's really amazing for me is the incredible resilience of the human body, and how the body and mind work together to force survival.  Trying to relate this to events in my own life in the past few days, there isn't much comparison. Of course it is good to see yet more confirmation that there is so much more to life than working in dreary offices.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      100% success rate with the film festival so far.  "Super Size Me" and "The Yes Men" are excellent. Informative and interesting but above all entertaining.  Both films had me falling about laughing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We're going to see 8 films at the festival, including 6 documentaries, 4 with an anti-corporate theme:  "Fahrenheit 9/11," "The Corporation," "Super Size Me" and "The Yes Men."  I'm looking forward to it. In my current mood I'm very receptive to anti-corporate views because I have just been done over by one particularly vindictive individual from my previous employer. I'm powerless to do anything about it, and stunned into a state of submission and defeat.    So for all his faults, I am full of admiration for Michael Moore, and others like him. Anyone who can take on the powerful has courage. It wouldn't be easy. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>