<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so i was sifting through some old files of mine -- dream journals actually, and it turns out that they are pretty wierd....i'm going to post this one because it's totally non-sensical, and if my computer ever dies i want to have this one saved somewhere...  Morning of December 16th/99  The first thing I can remember is being in the top room of a old house or apartment building and having Captain Kirk and Spock explaining something to me very important about not leaving a trail or something like that.  They tell me to come with them, but I go back in the room for my watch and other little things.  I go out into the hallway and I pass a group of black guys and I see an elevator, but I pass it and proceed down the stairs following shortly behind two figures, which are now my father and his friend.  I run after them down the stairs and the stairs turn into a long wooden catwalk.  Then I’m in a room again, and it seems to be something out of a dream I’ve had before.  I suddenly imagine a story about a man who had a car drive into his house and destroy part of it, but luckily he had a model of it built so he could show others exactly what the car did to it.  So I walk around the living room and kitchen of this “house” and realize that I’m in the model.  I look in the closet and there are strange paper cutouts of a vacuum and regular closet stuff.  Then I close the closet door and go into the kitchen and notice a broken, clear yellow plastic glass on the floor and wonder why it’s broken.  Then I remember breaking it.  I’m then walking down the hallway towards, I guess, the bathroom and I’m thinking about committing suicide and whether or not anyone would miss me and I thought of how horrible it would be for them to find me hung in the bathroom-because I recall how horrible the face of a person who’s hung themselves looks.  The eyes bulge out and the body bloated and purple because the blood has no place to go.  I decide not to because I would upset those who care about me.  Then it cuts to me out near a wide street that curves, sort of like Finch Ave. Near where I live.  I am a young Chinese boy and I seem to be an important heir or something like that because I know I am important and rich and I have an older Chinese man that seems to be keeping an eye on me.  I see to my right an odd pathway leading down an alternate route that some people have chosen, but I decide not to go there.  I notice a bus coming down the road and I run to catch it thinking, I’m rich, I can catch it.  So the bus stops and I get in and I ask the driver where it’s going and he says Edmonton, but I think for a second that maybe that’s not a good idea.  Then I get on anyway, and the man that’s supposed to be looking after me just smiles, so I get on.  There seems to be no room on the bus because people are being greedy with the seats, or so it seems.  But I soon realize that there are some weird blankets hanging from the ceiling and there is an old lady knitting onto one.  I still think for some reason that these are seats and she is being greedy.  I tell he to let me use and she eventually accepts, wrapping me up in the blanket.  Then suddenly I’m in the back of the bus on a bed that’s secluded from the rest of the passengers.  I notice a girl to my right and I’m talking to her.  It’s Faruza Balk and she’s my girlfriend and I give her a plastic bag full of gold dimes and various other coins and she’s happy and we talk about something. I start telling her about plans I have that will allow us to rob Fort Knox and she gets really excited and then she tells me about her brother I think, who would love this plan if he weren’t being hung that day.  Cut to many people lining a path and walking down the middle is Ed Norton on a crucifix strapped to his back and he’s carrying it.  I tell him how odd it is that he’s there and ask him what he did.  He disappears.  Then cut to me getting in a police car with some sugar cookies in my hand.  I start to eat them and drive the police car away, but realize the siren is on and I can’t turn it off.  I go to turn the corner and I see another police car that turns on it’s siren and I’m scared that its going to come after me, but it doesn’t.  It just passes by and I turn the corner and I wake up to what I think is my alarm clock, but it’s actually the fire department testing the alarms in my building! Stupid....fire people.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      http://www.kamelot.com/  BEHOLD!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      doo doo -- flim --- doo doo dah.  eeeeoooooohhh.  skittle nipple turkey baster, in the backseat of my car.  aaahhhhhhhh, ooooohhhhh, bing bang, goin' down to the ol' lemon tree.    whoops.  no, not right.  that was a song i made up this morning.  okay, fuh real now:  ________   ________  (2 words, 3 syllables total)   LYRICS A-LA  HUH? -----------------  Blind date with the chancer we had oysters and dry lancers and the check when it arrived we went dutch, dutch, dutch, dutch a redder shade of neck on a whiter shade of trash And this emory board is giving me a rash I'm flat out You're so beautiful to look at when you cry Freeze, don't move You've been chosen as an extra in the movie adaptation of the sequel to your life.  A ______ ____ -- everybody wants one A ______ ____ -- everybody needs one Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god Oh my god, oh your god, oh his god, oh her god It's everybody's god, it's everybody's god, it's everybody's god, it's everybody's god The worlds collide, but all that we want is a _____ ____  Glance, don't stare Soon you're being told to recognize your heirs No, not me -- I'm an island of such great complexity Stress surrounds in the muddy peaceful center of this town Tell me off in the hotel lobby right in front of all the bellboys and the over-friendly concierge  A _____ ____ -- everybody wants one A _____ ____ -- everybody needs one Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god Oh my god, oh your god, oh his god, oh her god It's everybody's god, it's everybody's god, it's everybody's god, it's everybody's god The worlds collide, but all that I want is a _____ ____   **Whoooo....this one's a toughy**  -- again, whoever wins gets some respect, or gold stars, or a funny hat...whichever is cheaper to send in the mail.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      man, every single person in my neighbourhood has a dog.    i think there must be an exclusive club.  i'll bet that they have, you know, little get-togethers and talk about their dogs, much like those who "individualize" their $250 Honda Civics after having taken a walk down THAT aisle in their local Canadian Tire.  You know the aisle I'm describing.  The one with the matching Yosemite Sam floormat and mudflap sets and the dark headlight covers that decrease the visibility of your headlights to a level on par with two bic lighters.  Ok, so not a fantastic analogy, but back to the real topic: those people with the damn dogs.  Did I mention I think they have a leader?  Just one guy with 5 dogs.  Not a royal sort of ruling...no king, no queen, just an affluent member of the community.  Kinda like a biker gang really, except without the bikes...and tattoos, and violent knife-fights.  Well, I bet they have cool embroidered jackets that they wear to their secret hideout.  They must have walkie-talkies too.  I can just imagine a whole wall of televisions sunk into the wall of their subterranean sanctuary being monitored by a dedicated staff of volunteers, all entranced by the unblinking eye of their powerful leader encased, like a demi-god, in a gigantic glass throne room under the watchful eyes of twenty more volunteers, all armed with magical dog whistles. These whistles would control their army of extremely ill-tempered and recently underfed Rottweilers, German Shepherds and Schnauzers.    Ok, perhaps that's being a touch dramatic, but damnit, they parade around out front of my house and pause, almost as if they know they're being envied from afar, and wait while their beloved donates some butt-mud to my tiny patch of municipally-owned lawn.  They nod to each other, as if it was just natural for everyone to nod to everyone else because they're both being pulled along by a demanding, crotch sniffing, barking, ball-fetching, ass-licking, baby-talk inducing store-bought mammals who's primary functions are to crap and eat.  They compare trophies.  "Hey Phil, my wittle Muffin here has take first in the state competition 3 years in a row now -- where's your Precious??  At the groomer's again?"    I ought to get one of those shotgun mikes and record some of their conversations.  I'd then hide in the bushes outside and wait for them to walk by and play clips.  "Hey Doug, you know, you could keep Ranger's coat shinier with simple egg whites and the blood of the rare Alaskan ice-floe sloth" the bush would quip.  A confused Doug's head would then explode, a result of his world just being turned upside down by a talking bush.  Die Dog Owners Die!   Let me into your club!   Sigh.  I want to get a puppy.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow...just noticed it's been awhile since i logged on here.  what makes this sad is that i'm only going to say this:  i just made chicken for dinner.  it had better be good or i'm going to jump out the window.  actually, i'll probably just cry and order a pizza.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the group stepped forward in the shadows, their arms at their sides and hands clenched tightly into fists.  their faces hidden by the darkness, the four moved slowly, closer and closer to the light thrown by the flickering, humming streetlamp.  from the left to right emerged first V, his head down and hand gripping the imaginary tool of the trade; his left hand gripping the neck, his right hand the pick, both held so convincingly that someone with poor vision might mistake it for the real thing.  Next emerged Drum.  He did not walk into the light, but rather rolled in in a sitting position.  His head was also down, his hands holding sticks high above, his right foot aimed at the pedal.  Low-end came in next, the only one not poised to rock -- he didn't have to though, all those who knew him knew he rocked with stealth.  Lastly, Scream emerged, the only one whose face was visible.  His eye sockets were darkened, but you could see the snarl at the corner of his mouth.  Both hands outstretched towards a mic and they were ready to go.    they all stood still for nearly five minutes before a deep smoke rolled across the ground from the darkness and obscured the collective.  The smoke then retreated and left behind instruments belonging to each of their masters.  The gentle hum of a stack.  The whole place was suddenly bathed in a light so bright it was blinding, and I stumbled backwards, arms flailing, hoping to find something to brace myself, only to find that I was inches from the edge of a dark, seemingly bottomless pit, rimmed by rows of glistening teeth.  The light kept getting brighter and I began to feel rather than hear a rumbling...And then a single thunderous chord rang out casting me backwards into the hole and all went dark.    i woke up in my living room next to a massive puddle of vomit, presumably my own.  I came to a conclusion after that experience: never, under any circumstances, drink something on a dare after being forcibly bindfolded and goaded on by a roomful of strangers at a frat party.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i realize of course, that there is little to be done about the homogenization of radio.  Like the mighty rock pushed off the crest of a mountain, it will roll roll roll, and roll some more until it crushes at least 3 or 4 villagers.  There are 2 or 3 main players that own everything, and the direct result is a consistent sound, regardless of geography.  And the newish trend of assigning stations human names is a deplorable one, an opinion formed quickly after being assaulted by endless tv commercials featuring an array of catchy, VERY brief call letters, stupid animated gnomes and some guy with no head who has thrown down his submarine sandwich so many times it makes me want to break into tears; first for the images being recklessly burnt into my grey matter, and second for the poor sandwich that is torn asunder by Bob's carelessness, a result no doubt of misdirected rage towards his parents who named him Bob.  When will the major players realize that there is a market for other music?  It wouldn't matter of they were to pepper a playlist composed of Modest Mouse, Interpol, Stephen Malkmus, white stripes, pinback etc...with commercials, I'd still listen--I'm not so ignorant as to think that they'd willingly wave away their main source of income.  And while it's well known that their repetitive playlists are the result of mutual hand-jobs with the record labels that produce such poo-poo as Nickelback and Theory of a Deadman (and all the other marginally talented artists that are, at best, indistinguishable from their peers regardless of how many singles they release per album) there is also a rising demand for good music.  Although they wouldn't instinctively know what that would sound like, they could tune into just about any university/college station to get a vague idea of what people are requesting.    There is small part of me that wishes all commercial radio stations would burn to the ground, but a larger part of me realizes that they have the potential to eventually make the collective, one by one, sigh in disgust, get out their vertical horizon cd's and help them fulfill their destiny by turning them into coasters, much like everyone has done in the past with those mountains of awful AOL cd's.  But hey, free coasters, who can bitch about that?  Anyway, for those about to rock, I salute you.  Also, if you're going to rock hard, which you most certainly should, remember to share with others.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just kidding.  I hate octagonal things though.  8 sides?  What the hell is with that?  " Oooh...I let people know when to stop"  Why, I remember when I was a kid, things only had 2 sides.  Even squares.  Don't ask me how or when things changed, but they did.  I hope that somewhere, the guy who invented numerous sides to things is feeling his shame; like a warm, shameful stream of urine leaking down his leg that one time when I almost got beat up by that mean bastard kid down the street.  I hated that guy. I loved those pants...and my pride, and both were taken away, in one thoughtless act of mild annoyance.  I'll find you, wherever you are.  Next up, I'm going to talk about how my apartment is too warm.  I place the blame squarely on the sun.  I realize the planet and all life on it relies on it for warmth, and brightness and all that crap, but seriously, I wouldn't be sitting here sweating madly like I just consumed 67 packets of Taco Bell sauce on a dare if that hot bastard in the sky would just fuck off already.    Hmm...  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey simcoe, i have a blog now.  millions of people will be able to read my worthless crap.  probably not though, cause i'll likely forget about this tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      jason.greatestcanadian.com  riding the coattails of a buddy's site....whoa! don't all rush there at once!
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>