<Blog>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well here we go!  I've started my journal about 100 times, but have never contented it.  I think this will work just dandy...I just hope I use it. Please feel free to comment...IF YOU DARE! (Just kidding)   Anywho I'm just enjoying a nice triple hamburger from Wendy's after I committed my self to start eating healthily.  After seeing my cholesterol at 222 I felt I should lower it...So I went to get a burger.  Mmmmm...Triple cheese burger.  I know that's gross, but it's so good.  So after this nice burger I'm going eat better...Maybe.     My wife (Jessica) is pregnat, and very cute.  I love her so much, and everyday I wonder...Why did she marry me?  I know if you asked her that question she would just laugh, and say "I don't know either."  No..I know she would say "because he's HOT!!! Rarrr!"  ok...Maybe not, but it's a thought.  I hope it's a boy, but I wont die if it's a girl...But I hope it's a boy.  Brett Isaac!! I think that is the coolest name ever.  If we have a girl I'm changing my name to Brett Isaac.  I really couldn't because my name is so important to me, and has lot's of meaning.       One thing I hate when you start in a new place, or new class, or new group most of the time they as "Ok...Say your name, and the most embarrassing moment in your life."  MOST EMBARRASSING MOMENT!?!?!?  Would you be embarrassed to share your most embarrassing moment?  I've really never had an embarrassing moment, and whenever I say that people say "Well that's impossible, everyone has an embarrassing moment"  I just don't.  When I was born I realized that I was clumsy, goofy, stupid, and I would allways walk in at the wrong moments.  So when things happen I just shrug my shoulders, and start laughing.  Oh well...  Speaking of new place this is my office...it's nice!  I work behind a bookcase in the very corner, so people are always surprised to see that thier is a person working back thier. I just started here, and I hope someday to move to the backroom as my new worksation.  (Don't you love the Chair)      I've better get back to work.  Will see you tomorrow!  John  * You'll notice that my spelling is horrible    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was taught throughout my life to always apply scriptures in my life.  I was introduced to  urlLink Zechariah 5:1  which reads: THEN I turned, and lifted up mine eyes, and looked, and behold a flying roll.  This clearly reminds me of the way Jessica's Mom passes rolls during dinner.      With most of us receiving, or wishing we were receiving our Tax Return I've added a little humor that you can do for next year for the lovely IRS!          To Annoy The IRS     1. Always put extra paper clips on your forms. Any foreign fasteners or the like have to be removed and put away.   2. Always put staples in the right hand corner. Go ahead and put them down the whole right side. The extractors who remove the mail from the envelopes have to take out any staples on the right side.   3. If you send two checks, they'll have to staple your unsightly envelope to your half destroyed form.   4. If you're very unfortunate and have to pay taxes, send two or three party check. On top of paying with a third party check, pay one of the dollars you owe in cash. When an extractor receives cash, no matter how small an amount, he has to take it to a special desk and fill out of few nasty forms.   5. Line the bottom of your envelope with Elmer's glue and let it dry before you put in you forms, so that the automated opener doesn't open it and the extractor has to open it by hand.   6. Never arrange paperwork in the right order, or even facing the right way. Put a few upside down and backwards. That way they have to remove all your staples, rearrange your paperwork and re-staple it (on the left side).   7. Sign your name in ink on every page. Any signature has to be verified and then date stamped. These are just a few of the fun and exciting things you can do with the IRS. These methods are ONLY recommended when you OWE money.   8. When you mail it, mail it in a big envelope (even if its just a single EZ form). Big envelopes have to be torn and sorted differently than regular business size ones. An added bonus to the big envelope is that they take priority over other mail, so the workers can hurry up and deal with your mess.   9. Write a little letter of appreciation. Any letter received has to be read and stamped regardless of what it is or what it's on.   10. Write your letter on something misshapen and unconventional. Like on the back of a supermarket sack.   11. If they owe you money, being nice helps.  From:  urlLink Jokefinder.com        Life behind the bookcase     So I though about changing my my title from "A day in the life of john" to "The man behind the bookcase."  Although I don't live behind the bookcase, so it really wouldn't work; however I want to create section that has news, and updates about my postion.  Wether I'm going to move, were I could move, and if I'm getting a better chair.  (For those who havn't seen the chair look back on day one)  The porblem is I don't know what to call it, and I'm not all the grand at making names, so your input will help.  Maybe "Where in the office is john now", or "Office updates."  I don't know.  Just let me know, so for right now I'm just going to call it "news"    NEWS!    Sorces tell us that new furniture is on the way, but added with that is this comment "you might get one."  "Whooo hoo" was the comment receved from John, "Might is better than nothing."  More news on the way.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      With the comming of our new baby I've been really nervice about finding out about finding out what the sex is.  I really want a boy, but I wouldn't mind a boy, but I thought that all of you would like to have a part in this great event.  First of all here are some crazy sites were you could find all the information you need to figure out your babies sex.  (Jen you could check to see if it's true)    urlLink  38 fun ways to guess your baby's sex    urlLink  Will it be a boy or girl?    urlLink  Boy or Girl?    urlLink  Who chooses the sex of the baby?          Poll     Ok here is the poll, and to reply please write your first name, and your answer by pressing the comment link at the bottom of this post, or E-Mail me at john@vanhorns.net.  The question is fairly easy, but it's going to be fun.  What do you think the sex of the baby is going to be?  See it's simple, and not that hard.  Next month we are finally going to have our ultra-sound to find out!  The Polls will be open for a week, and please let people know to send in thier votes.  The winners will get a prize!  Noo...it's not a pat on the back, but you'll get something.  For those who board at work here is a site that you can go to that has some fun games.     urlLink  tekzoned  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I've combined Saturday, and Sunday due to the lack of time I had.  Anywhoo....Saturday we morn for the removing of Dad's beloved fathers day tree.  The tree was knocked down during a windy night, and was finally removed (Not very easily that Mark can atest to) and chopped up into a million pieces, and grounded, and smashed till gone.           Ok so the last part was fake, but it sounded good.  Their is going to be a new tree placed when next fathers day comes around.  Further note, Mom's tree is still standing!  GO MOM!  In celebration of this great moment...We tore down the fence.  The fence wasn't all that bad when we looked at it.  All we needed to fix a couple of posts, and call it a day, but when we started we noticed that it needed more than that, it needed an over haul!  So we tore the most of the back fence out, and the left gate.  All you had to do to really remove things was to just lean on it, and it just came apart.  We took the old slats, and added new braces to them, and instead of having a gate on the back fence we are just going have slats.  This will be the 150th repair on the rickety old fence.       We had everything all over the yard, and everything torn apart.  It gave some opportunity to relief some stress off because of school.      This little number about just killed me.  When I was digging I never really new if I was hitting a pipe or a root!  It felt like I was digging around for fossils.  So we got the cement in, and then will work on putting it all back together.  Mark was the project manager for this project (After doing work on his fence, he's an expert at doing all of this.)        Poll Update!!      ok...Their is no one that has entered, and it's my fault I really never published it yet, so everyone is going to get an e-mail, and please refer to the 3rd day, because that's were all the information is to send in your vote.  Please, Please send in your votes.        E-mail Me!      I have a new system up were I'm able to e-mail you the summary of today's entry, and the link to the site.  If this is something that you want please e-mail me at john@vanhorns.net, or post a comment.   In conclusion we heard a great joke in Regional conference today, so here it is:   A man, and his wife wanted to take a vacation to Florida.   Coming from Alaska during the early spring it would be a nice, warm, and relaxing vacation.  Due to other arrangement his wife was going come a day after the man arrived.  After reaching his destination the man checked in their hotel they were staying at, and thought that it would be nice to send his wife an e-mail.  He searched all over his luggage for his wife's e-mail address, but couldn't find it.  He felt he had a pretty good idea of what it was, but unfortunately it was sent to an old preachers wife, who's husband just recently passed away.  She looked at the e-mail, screamed and passed out.  Her family came in to see what was the matter, and they looked at the screen and read the e-mail.     Dear Wife,   Just checked in, and getting things ready for you tomorrow.   P.S. Man it's sure Hot down here   yours Truly   Have a good weekend!   John 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I Take too many Pills!!!  I had to have an artery ultra sound to check to see if I have any plaque, or build up.  Well no plaque, but their was some build up, and according to their records I have artery's of a 36 year old!!!  That just killed me to hear that.  So I'm taking a million pills, and to keep them all in order I have a sheet that tells me when I should take them, and how much.  I feel so old.  I thought I would never have to take a million pills in my life, or I thought it would be later in my life...well that came too soon.  I think I take more pills than everyone in my office combined.  I know it's good for me, it's just a killer to hear that I'm like a 36 year old...Before I know it I'll be having my midlife crisis when I'm 30!    Oh man... So this is how I feel...old...decrepid ...Dennis...actually this picture doesn't show it real well, but I'm having a reaction to my niacin (Spelling?)   My face is all red, and it's puffy.  I think I'm having hot flashes, or something...but Jessica says that I'm going through menopause.  It took me about an hour to take all my pills, and two glasses of orange juice to make taking them worth while.  Another comment that killed me from my doctor is that I need to do more exercise.  I feel I do enough, but more?  So I started working out bright and early in the morning, and I feel good afterward, but this waking up early is making me feel like I'm 36.    Ok I know I'm complaining, and it's boring you...Oh well this is my web page!! HHAHAHA!!!  If you disagree I've got fluffy here to take care of you.      Were in the office is John?      According to a recent discovery John hasn't moved "yet" he replied earlier this morning.  "They've brought in the table pieces for the back area, and all the parts to put it together...now I just wait till I get the green light to help assemble it."  As for right now he will be at the same small desk behind that lonely bookcase.      Poll       Nothing...Please place your votes in.  Read day 3 for details.       Site of the day      This site will make your smarter than you are now...Actually it does the opposite.  Enjoy!   urlLink Poke the Bunny     Have A Great Monday!!!   John
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ok that's an interesting heading.  Well again I combined the days due to me being really tired last night.  I've been going to the gym to get my 36 year old body in shape, and I had my rear kicked in Karate last night, so when I was going to write my blog I turn the other direction to my bed, and woke up a little late today. I felt that I needed the day of from exercising...and then I remembers to help Mom, and Dad with their yard, Oh Pain!  So instead of acting my age its exercise to your age.  If I don't exercise I will look like this cat!  First of all thank you for those who've visited.  I would like to take this time to comment at:    John's Comment Corner     This is what mom wrote:    "This is the mother-I don't want to join blog at the moment, sorry. So since I want you to come back & work here, guess I'd better answer with a reaction to your site. I am impressed you can spell Niacin. You look horrible in the picture, by the way. Well, with your middle name of Derald, you should remember that your grandfather took a pile-o-pills. Sorry. Gladly, you get your artery in line with your age & you'll be able to back off the stuff. But breaded chicken ain't a way to go. you'll remember that your parents were eating breasted chicken sandwiches with TOMATOES & LETTUCE; with canalope & milk for dinner. HMMMMM. Hey; sweetheart; father in the next winter to come-spell WHERE not WERE; Or I will put Suzie Allred on to you as a personal teacher...... Love You Both: (that's Jessica and the baby)-MOM HA HA"   First I would like say Hmmm...and that's all.   Alright that was exciting!!  Scott gave a comment also, and I would like to tahnk him ofr sih comemnt.      Poll      Ok I've received 2 votes, and I need some more.  Right now we have BOY: 2, and GIRL: 0.  Keep the votes coming.  Thanks for those who have voted.      Where in the office is john?        I have some great news!!! I have a new chair!!! Isn't it pretty!!! I love to use explanation marks!!!!  The table tops are still in the back, so I'm still in my new place.  So in celebration I'm burning my nasty chair...oh I can't...oh well!  I'VE GOT A NEW CHAIR!!!   Have a good Tuesday, and Wednesday -    John  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Again may I suggest my title is kinda interesting.  Well as we all know gas prices are just about, or even above the $2.00 mark.  It's incredible!  I can believe its that expensive, but It's more expensive in other places.  LA is just about $2.50, and New York is $2.40.  That's just a killer to your bank account.  So to make things just a little sweeter their is a site that you can go to that will tell you were the cheapest gas can be found in your area.  I find it great, because I'm always around downtown, so I just plan on finding what the closest gas, and the cheapest, and it's saved me so much money!  It's found at  urlLink Gas Buddy.   I hope this helps us all in this crazy increase in gas prices.  Here's an article more about this:  urlLink MSN      Well school just started up again for the summer.  I've decided to get some more of my school done, and I don't know if I can take 2 hours of math in one sitting.  I have it 1 a week, but for 2 hours...ouch.  Oh well, and I'm also taking a architecture class were we design things in a world without gravity.   It sound interesting.  So I hope to get this done, and finally get started in the program.  I don't know if I can take anymore general classes.  Sometimes it feels like I'm going no were in my carrier, but I know sooner, or later is going to be done. I thought I had a chance to beat mark in getting my schooling finished, but then I realized to go anywhere with architecture you need to at least do 5 years of school to have good schooling...AHHHHHHH I'll be 29 with 80 year-old artery's!       John's Comment Corner      Thank you for those who've added their comments.  It's been great.  Scott you I'm sure you have artery's your age, but mark you're more of a 3 year old; However for being a 3 year old you can but up a good fence.  See I have 36 year old artery's because I'm wiser.  That's what happens when you become a sensei...you become wiser!  "John says...Never swat fly from friends head with an ax."  See that's wise advice, but mark I would like to congratulate you for loosing that much weight, I think your beating dad.  So don't you win, or is the bet over?...I don't remember.        Poll Update!!!      We have had some votes submitted.  We are now standing at BOYS: 2, and girls: 1, and 1 I don't know.  I asked mom what she wanted to vote, and she wanted me to tell her the babies heart rate...That's cheating MOM!!!!!!  We've also have about 4 weeks till the untrasound. So will see who the true winners are.     I hope you all have a good Thursday!  Take care   John
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know I havn't updated it, but I've been very busy, but I promise that I'll have something for you tomorrow!  Thanks!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Man my Architecture teacher is so mean!!!!  She seems like a nice lady, but then she turns on you.  So I was working on the "characteristics of a line" and first of all she didn't even explain the problem all that well.  So I slaved on my project, and even did more than what was required.  Now I tried to streach the rules, but it was to explain my view on the project.  Well that wasn't what she liked.  We put our drawings up on a cork board wall, and went over all of them, and she made comments and she always tells us "No drawing is wrong we are all explorers trying to figure out the problems."  When she looked at mine she asked me what I was trying to do, and I felt that I explained things very well to her, and then she said that I needed less exploration, and more application.  I felt that was contradicting to her previous comment, but I took it, and made note for my revision.  She went to the project that was above me, and raved, which I was fine with, but then she wanted him to take all his drafts and put them up also.  So she takes ALL of mine down, and puts this other guys drafts up!!!  Then she just handed them to me like they were trash!!! OHHHHH I was so mad....  It's like she doesn't think that I'm capable of doing what she wanted, and the worst was their was no positive feed back, but disgust!!  Ohhh she's not on my good list.  I feel a ninja run coming on....hehehe...ok I wouldn't do that.      Poll!      Yes we have received to more votes.  We are now BOYS: 3 GIRLS: 2.  We will know the sex on June 16th.  So stay tuned.      Web Page      I think that this is great, and I've enjoyed the pictures.  Scott, and Ryan have put up their own web page that has pictures of them in Texas.  You might have gotten the e-mail, but if not here it is. Check it out!   urlLink Scott and Ryan's Web Page  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ok, so it's been a while, but with mean teachers, and sugary things are very chaotic!  Well the moment you've all been waiting for is here, but before I tell you I would like to say that after 5 million trillion cabajillion attempts to please my teacher I finally got a good response!  It's a miracle I have a chance in passing this class.  I tell you I've just had about enough of doing the something over, and over, and over again!  I know that I've made great progress, but I'm just about beat!  Oh well that's school, and it only gets better...NOT!  Ok now it's time...to tell you that...we are....having...a...chicken dinner tonight that I know will be quite lovely, with reduction veggies, and Jello...green...with soda...and applesauce...just how mom makes them...mmmmmm that sounds good right now.       Poll!      To help recap the totals for the sex of the baby we currently stand at BOY!!!!!: 6 girl: 4, and the answer is...Coming soon, so hang on tight!      Where in the office is John?      "In the same place" replied John when asked the question where he is currently located, "I helped put tables in the backroom, but I didn't go with them."  This strange phenomenon could be due to the strange loss of remembering that he's there "Working behind the bookcase is like I'm not even their.  They don't even ask me any questions until I come out, then they have this big surprise that I just came out of no where."  The empty desks collect dust minute, by minute until hopefully, one day he will be able to call it home.        Comment Corner      ----Ryan and I just went and worked out -- it was pretty fun...and we watched the end of the Bachelor. If you have the body of a 36 year old I don't want to know what mine is! And you're a sensah! (er...did I speel that wrong??)  Scott - Mark replied - Ya, yur retahrded Scot! Ets Sensai!.......  -------  Thank you mark for your great comment..  __________________________________________________________________________-   I work out every day. I have a set of 35 lb. weights and a set of 24 lb. weights. They both get lifted a lot. Though I am proud to announce that i'm down to 165 lbs. as of this morning. My high was 195 lbs. in 2002. Amy is losing some weight to. She is at XXX which is down from XXX.  (the above post has been edited by the supreme council of wives :))  -Mark   Mark -- what type of weight program are you on or what weight exercises do you do? Ryan and I are interested since we're both ballooning like...well I can't think of a good metaphor but it's not good.  -Scott    From mother: If you are all working on the weights & are getting so buff; why can't any of you get my couch/bed from my office down to the downstairs bedroom? Huh?  ----------   Well that's a typical comment from Mom...Scott thier are many programs that you could do, but it just depends what you want.  That's the main key in working out is decideing what you want to do.  Create that goal, work with it, when your finnished pick another goal and work with it.  You can find this concept in a program that's called a "Body for life" Program.  It's great, and if you click on this  urlLink LINK  it will give you all the information you need.  It's focuses on your workout, and your eat habbits.  Let me know if you have further questions, but it has to be the best well rounded program out thier, and the most sucsessful!  Well thank you for your comments, and for coming to listen to be blab...I hope everyone has a good weekend, and will see you soon...  John  P.S. We    P.S.S. Are     P.S.S.S. Having     P.S.S.S. A     P.S.S.S.S. B     P.S.S.S.S.S. A     P.S.S.S.S.S.S. B     P.S.S.S.S.S.S.S. Y     P.S.S.S.S.S.S.S.S. GRIL!!! yes another one...oh the poor boys are going to be hating life... 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well it's been a month since I've updated my Blog...but that's ok because it's kept you on your feet.&nbsp; Infact in commemoration of this moment I'm going to be breaf in my log today.&nbsp; Well I've moved to my new desk..Pictures will come soon.&nbsp; I've started on the company web site  urlLink GA Architects , and I've gotten on the good side of my teacher, so I see an "A" Coming at the end of the semmester.&nbsp; Thats about it so far, so until then....aaaaaaaaaaa keep waiting......    &nbsp;  John  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>