<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the last Monday of the school year in the Clay Co. school system.  I’m sure that all of you who read this who are in school will be rejoicing.  I, for one, am torn.  I’m torn between rejoicing with you, because I always enjoyed being out of school and I like it when everyone’s schedules are opened up (a little bit), and lamenting because I’ll miss the regular visits to lunch at the high school.  Yeah, the food’s not all that great, but the company is why I’m there.  Sure, I’ll see everybody at least once a week on Sundays and whenever we get together for other activities, but there’s just something about that setting.  I like hanging out with  your  friends, sitting at  your  tables, eating  your  food.  So just so I don’t miss you all this summer, make sure you a) come see me in my little office from time to time and b) come to our fellowship events and bring a friend so I don’t miss them either.  Hope your Monday goes well.  Proverbs 24:1-2 says “Do not envy wicked men, do not desire their company; for their hearts plot violence, and their lips talk about making trouble”.  It’s easy to look at a rich man and say “Man, wouldn’t it be nice…”.  We can think of all the ways to spend that money and what we would do with our time because we wouldn’t have to work any more.  Think about all the new friends you’d meet and the places you could go.  What if that rich man asked you to come and hang out, to be able to enjoy his wealth for a while?  It would be nice to have friends in high places!  But what if that man, who has all the money and the cars and the mansions and the other rich friends, were a drug dealer or murderer?  Would that change your view of him and your desire to associate with him?  In our lives, we’ll probably never have to face that scenario but there will be times when we’re tempted to be like someone else or to have something someone else has, even when that person is of low morals or just an outright bad person!  It says here in Proverbs that we’re not to envy these folks because to be like them, to have what they have, would cause us to fall into their lifestyle of evil and violence.  Their fate is sealed.  I, for one, don’t want their end.  Yeah, it might be nice to have a little extra padding in my wallet by not at the expense of losing everything…forever.  I hope that we can learn to be content with what we have, in little or in much, and keep our lives focused on peace and godliness.  Wednesday: BIG Big Deal 7-9pm!!!! Saturday: People of Prayer Sunday: Youth Sunday  Later 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning was our 5:30 (am!) leadership breakfast meeting.  Last night, I set my alarm for 5:00 am and went to bed.  Recently, I’ve had a fan going to keep air moving through my house so I can sleep without perspiring so much that I stick to my sheets.  Last night, I moved the fan into my room and went to bed.  I woke up at 5:14 am, really for no reason at all, because I still couldn’t hear the radio over the sound of the fan.  By the grace of God I made it to the meeting on time.  After the meeting, I went home to get some things ready for the rest of the day and made up for the time in bed I lost by getting up soooooo early.  I was in the office a little before 9:30 (see, it evens out) and am just now (this afternoon) getting to my writing for the day.  I’m looking forward to going to Bogey’s tonight ( and any NHS student reading this is invited ) to help with the Campus Life end of the year party thing at 6:30.  It’ll be good fun.  Proverbs 21:1 says “The king’s heart is in the hand of the LORD; he directs it like a watercourse wherever he pleases”.  Definition time.  “LORD” is capitalized here because in the Hebrew (woo!) language, one of the titles for God was spelled יהוה (read backwards: YHWH, or Yahweh) and this is the English translation.  A watercourse is any kind of flowing body of water.  In this context, it refers more to a canal.  Why a canal?  The one who builds a canal directs it where it wants it to go.  It’s the same way with man’s heart.  It is the Lord who directs our paths.  It is true that many, in fact all of us, resist.  There are many examples of kings in ancient Israel who resisted God’s leading and the nation suffered.  Many times, the nation suffered at the hand of another nation.  However, there are some good examples of godly kings who followed the Lord’s lead and the nation prospered.  In Proverbs 3:5-6, it tells us to rely on the Lord and to acknowledge him in everything we do.  This takes humility.  These kings who obeyed God knew that they didn’t have all the answers and allowed God to do  his  thing  his  way.  If we allow God to mold us and shape us and don’t give him a lot of flack when he tries to steer us in a way that  we  aren’t too sure about, we’ll be in for some pretty neat scenery along the flowing path of our lives.  For those of you who missed it:  Campus Life party at Bogie’s in TH starts at 6:30.  $15 covers everything. Youth Sunday is next week!  Fill a slot, get involved. Saturday 29th, People of Prayer, 6-7 pm.  Later 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, for the first time, I watched Finding Nemo with a group of my Senior Highers.  It was a fun little get together.  I enjoyed the movie immensely.  Yeah, I know, some of you are thinking, “What was this guy thinking not seeing this movie until now?”  Well, it’s not the first movie I’ve planned on seeing and didn’t until much later and it sure won’t be the last.  I’m not so sure that I have a favorite part yet, seeing as how I’ve only seen the movie once.  I really enjoyed the shark support group and seeing how Dori’s short-term memory loss played out in several scenes.  The fish-tank/dentist’s office/Darla (I think that’s her name…the girl who looks like Chucky) scenes were a riot as well as the sea gulls (Mine!)!  Anyways, I’ll see it again someday and be able to pick my favorites.  I thought that including a main character with a disability was a nice touch.  Nemo, and his dad, were quintessential underdogs.  I like a movie with an underdog (even when he’s a fish).  Proverbs 20:1 says “Wine is a mocker and beer a brawler; whoever is led astray by them is not wise”.  If you know anyone who consumes a lot of alcohol, you already know that this verse has a lot of truth in it.  It is described as a mocker and a brawler.  You’ve got to know that drunk people will eventually get themselves in trouble with their mouths (mocking) or with their fists (brawling).  That looseness of mind that comes with alcohol consumption makes it difficult, if not impossible, to control one’s tongue or to shrug off some other’s misguided drunk statement without throwing down.  I know a lot of people who will say that “Well, the Bible doesn’t say that it’s wrong to drink!”  Yes, I’m aware of that.  Some very good friends of mine drink and, for all that I can tell, they do it responsibly.  However, the trouble comes up when we allow alcohol to deceive us.  The second part of the verse talks about the fool who is lead astray by the drink.  It is too easy to get so far into this that you can’t get out.  Sin will do that to a person if he/she is not firm in what they believe.  The deception that says, “You can handle this.  Go ahead, have another drink” will lead you into sin unless you have already made a firm decision about what you will not do.  There is much freedom in Christ, but we must exercise that freedom responsibly (I Cor. 10:23-24).  Many people reading this don’t have a choice whether this is right or wrong because the law of the land says you are underage.  I would encourage those who are of age to really consider your motivations in doing the things you do, whatever they might be, and do those things for the good of others and the glory of God.  Wednesday 26: Last day of School, last Big Deal Saturday 29: People of Prayer Sunday 30: Youth Sunday 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yowza!  We got a lot of rain yesterday!  And in not a lot of time.  I was in Terre Haute yesterday when it cut loose at about 2-ish.  It did it's thing for about an hour then moved on, only to usher in another wave that evidently pounded Brazil a little before 6.  I was standing in a parking lot with a couple other biking buddies looking at the sky all looking pretty silly, saying things like "Well, are we gonna ride?" and "It'll be a little risky."  Unfortunately, it never really let loose in Terre Haute then.  The girls sectional track meet got delayed a bit but got back on pace amidst intermitent rain showers.  Nothing too bad.  I want to congradulate Nikki Royer and Natasha Barnett who both ran well last night.  Proverbs 19:1 says "Better a poor man whose walk is blameless than a fool whose lips are perverse".  One may ask after reading this, "What do these two guys have in common?" or more pointedly "On what grounds can you compare these two folks?"  Both good questions.  For the most part, po' fokes are humble.  Yes, there are they few who act like they have it all when they don't and think that you ought to treat them as such.  However, I think that most people who have less realize that and can deal with their situation accordingly.  So why compare him to a fool?  Throughout Proverbs and the rest of the Bible, "fools" are described as a number of things, and greedy is one of them.  Greedy people are motivated by one main thing...themselves.  So they will grab, get, cannive, to no end to get what they want.  And in many cases, at least for a while, the fool will have a bunch of money.  Good for him (  written with much sarcasm  ).  In this we find the reason for comparison.  So why is the former better than the latter?  With this now in mind, the contrast is a lot easier to see.  The poor man is in fact rich in the Lord's eyes where as the fool is destitute, even though he has everything.  Elsewhere in Proverbs, the Lord guarantees his protection and provision for the blameless (Prov. 2:7).  An old adage goes "A fool and his money are easily parted".  Duh!  Even though that's not in the Bible it speaks volumes here.  Our focus ought to be on spiritual riches, the kind that won't waste away, trusting that the Lord will come through and make life rich and worth living.  I think that sounds Biblical, too (Matthew 6:19-21.  See, I told you!)  Next week:  May 26-The BIG Big Deal.  This will be our last BD of the school year.  We'll tie up with one final lesson and do our best to finish up year with a bang! Remember: sign up for slots on the Youth Sunday list and don't forget People of Prayer.  Later
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I awoke this morning to the sound of a static-marred radio station at 5:45.  Amazingly, I hit the snooze.  Sunday, I had big dreams of going to bed early and getting up early to "get into my groove" for the summer after a busy spring that yielded little time to ride.  Those dreams were not realized in their fullest form, however.  I did get up and get moving at about 6:05 and rode at a moderate, I've-been-off-the-bike-for-two-weeks pace.  I felt sluggish at the beginning but settled in and felt good pulling into the driveway an hour later.  It was warmer this morning than it has been in a couple days. (It was like early March all weekend!)  That in itself helped the fact that I still really wanted to be in bed.  Good start to a (hopefully) good week.  Proverbs 17:1 says "Better a dry crust with peace and quiet than a house full of feasting, with strife".  For most of my life, my family has sat down to eat dinner together at the same time in the same room.  There was a time when we didn't, however.  For most of the time while my sisters and I were in jr high and high school, we were usually on our own to find whatever we could to fill our tummies with until the next morning.  Our schedules were so different in that time that we rarely had time to sit down with each other.  Now that we're out of that stage, any time we're together, we sit down together for a meal and enjoy each other's company.  We've never had a whole lot, but we had (and still do) just what we needed.  If you watch TV much, you can see all the decadence and the "bling bling" that attracts people to a lifestyle resembling a rock star or movie star.  They eat  very  well, drive  very  nice cars, and dress in  very  nice clothes.  It's really sad, though, as you watch the news or strole through the checkout lane at your grocery store of choice and see stories of these people who have it all and read or hear stories of divorce, drug problems, papparazzi, and bankruptcies.  I can't imagine that dinner time in those big houses is nearly as enjoyable as dinner around my family's meager little table in rural Illinois.  We're far from the perfect family but we're certainly not the Osborne's.  I hope you can enjoy your dinner this evening with people you love with happiness and the joy God provides.  We have almost filled our list for Youth Sunday (May 30)!  Keep your eye on the mail box because our summer schedule will be out soon.  People of Prayer will meet at 6 pm Saturday May 29 for youth and young adults.  Enjoy your Monday!  Later
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Grief! Summer is almost here and I'm once again in that state of flux between being totally ready and totally freaked out.  Ahh well, the summer is a time of relaxation but also a time for some good building time both personally and as a group.  I'm really looking forward to this summer's youth group activities, with the fellowship activities throughout the week and Sunday night continuing to show good turn outs.  I hope everything keeps up as much as it can.  If you want anything to pray about, pray for the Young Adults/College Age class that I teach on Sunday mornings.  It's a new group and I'm hoping that some of the planned activities for that group will help in getting it up and running more smoothly.  And speaking of matters of prayer, my little sister Buffy is doing well after a week in the hospital.  She's getting her associates degree tonight, and feeling pretty good about it.  Thanks to you who have prayed for her already.  Proverbs 14:1 "A wise woman builds her house, but with her own hands the foolish one tears hers down."  This one is mostly for the ladies this morning.  I think, however, that the gents can learn from this also.  Once again, we're looking at the wise vs. the unwise.  Shelter is one of our basic needs (thanks, Mr Maslow).  It's a wise venture because it is something that each of us need.  Building a house is no easy task, but it's something that, if done well, will bring us pleasure and functionality for years to come.  Now, I'm no genious, but tearing one's house down doesn't seem very worthwhile to me.  It's just not sane!  Most grandmothers I know are super hard workers.  I know mine is!  It's all a part of the age in which they grew up.  I think that ladies of all ages can look at this verse and look at their grandmother (or any respectable woman of "experience") and see the connection.  I hope that you can learn from these things to be a blessing to your families now and the ones that you will one day raise.  I think we can all learn from this in that each of us are responsible for becoming mature, responsible people.  None of us can blame our surroundings for how we turn out.  We make our own choices, good and bad, about what we say, do & act, think, and so on.  If we are doing things that don't build us up into godly people, then it's like shooting ourselves in the foot, or tearing down our own house.  Keep up reading these Proverbs, ya'll.  It's good stuff.  Remember: Youth Sunday: May 30 People of Prayer: May 29  Later 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mornin', Rain has a certain effects on certain people.  I for one am a fair-weather (ironic, I know) fan of rain.  I know that we need it to have a nice looking lawn and garden, for farmers to have a good crop, and for lazy people to get a free car wash from time to time.  On mornings that I'm really wanting an excuse to roll over in bed for another half hour instead of getting out on my bike, it makes for an understandible excuse.  Then there are those times when splashing in puddles and swimming in ditches (it's a Lincoln thing) just makes life more fun.  Rain saves the day!  However, there are thoses times when I'm really motivated to mow the lawn, ride a hundred miles, weed the garden, wash my car, and do something fun outside with everyone I know (individually!) and it opens up and pours, depressingly, for hours on end, dashing any thought of doing anything constructive outside.  Currently, it's between spurts of rain.  I think that today my attitude toward rain is one of indifference or at least hoping it will cooperate with my plans (of course!).  "Water my lawn but let me get to the track meet tonight."  Seems simple enough to me.  Proverbs 13:1 (NIV) says "A wise son heeds his father's instruction, but a mocker does not listen to rebuke."  Since Proverbs is a book of instruction and bits of wisdom to live by, it only seems right that it would compare the actions of the wise to those of the unwise.  Several times in the book, it speaks of children in relation to their parents.  Since everyone is a child, it's good for us to heed these warnings and take to heart these instructions.  Speaking of that, parents have a tough role of raising and training kids.  Whether or not we (kids) agree with their methods, assuming they are trying to do the right thing (and at this point, those of you reading this have parents who are) it is  wise  for us to do what they say.  They (parents, who used to be kids, but still are kids in their parents' eyes) have been in your shoes, they have done the school thing and have had the pressure put on them from society that you feel is unique only to you (kids, umm, all of us).  The mocker this verse, and several others, refers to is not a person to try and emulate!  Ladies, you don't want to bring one of these guys home to meet ma & pa!  A mocker is rebelious, lazy, apathetic, and usually (somehow) thinks he/she is right! Let me encourage you (along with God's word) to listen to our parents.  Remember, there's a good chance that you'll be parents someday!  (How do you like that for scare tactics!)  Youth Sunday is coming up and Brailyn is the only one signed up (you go, girl!).  Fill the list and take part!  Also, People of Prayer is on the 29th of May.  Plan to be there.  Enjoy your day.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, This just goes to show that I'm hip, cool, and not completely tech illiterate.  So far I've not screwed anything up, so I think that deserves a round of applause ( applaud now ).  Ok, enough of that.  I suppose I ought to describe for you what I intend to accomplish in this little venture, an e-venture, if you will (I made a tech joke!).  On my blog, I'll post morning devotions and commentary on Proverbs, give updates and info on events (esp. of a youth group nature), and really just write my way through life as I see it.  Especially for you Berea folks, I'll be able to keep you up to date on youth events and you won't have to wait for me to forget to tell you something that I think is really important on Sunday or Wednesday nights.  For those of you viewing this that aren't in my youth group, enjoy it for what it's worth.  I hope that this will be enriching for you as I'm sure it will be for me.  Well, if you live in the Brazil, IN area, are in Jr. High or High School, and have nothing to do on Wednesday or Sunday evenings, let me take this opportunity (since it's my blog) to invite you to our Youth Group.  The Big Deal meets tonight and every Wednesday though the school year at 7 pm.  It's at the corner of Billville and Waterworks roads (200W and 800N), south west of town.  Berea folk, I'm done with school for another semester.  I'll be able to spend a little more QT with you all now and you won't have to put up with me saying "Sorry, I can't, I have to do homework."  Youth Sunday is May 30 and there is a sign up sheet on the board in the Fellowship hall.  We need to make sure that all our bases are covered  BEFORE  Sunday morning this time!  Remember to sign up for camp. I'll be at Jr. High I and Sr. High.  Get ready for summer!  I think you'll like what we do.  Oh, and remember to tell your friends.  Ok, that's it for the first one.  Plenty more to come. Later...  Joe
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had a fun time on Wednesday evening as 14 of us went to TH Skate World.  We played tag, ate bad concession-stand food, and had an all-out good time.  Tag was fun, however, we were kindly informed that some of us (myself included) were skating too fast.  Well, being that it was kids night and there were quite a few little ones, we obliged the staff and called off the game.  Matt did notice that one of the rules were "Skate at your own risk" which, technically, we were.  We were also looking out for the folks who, technically, were skating at  their  own risk just by being there.  So this was just an exercise in taking the high road.  Don't worry Matt, we had a good time there so we'll try and rent the place out some time in the future, when there's no one there but us speed junkies, and skate as fast and as wrecklessly as we want.  We'll play tag all night!!!  Ha ha!!!  We'll show them!!...um...eh hem...It was good to take the high road, guys, yeah.  Good show.  I'm going to forego a Proverbs devo for today (I know, you're all broken up) in light of getting my camp lesson finished up.  And so you know, I won't be posting for all of next week, not because I'm lazy, but because I  really  have a good excuse this time.  I'll be back at the beginning of the following week with new excuses...um, I mean posts.  Yeah.  Get your release forms for the canoe trip on the  12th of July  this Sunday.  July 4  is the parking lot party.  We'll be hanging out and serving lemonade to the folks who come the see the fireworks from our lot.   Invite your friends!     Later... (See you after camp)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I slept in this morning.  Not like Michael who will waste away 70% of the day's daylight hours sleeping until, like, 2 pm.  But I slept until about 7:25, which was enough time to shower and eat b-fast and get to work on time.  I sacrificed the morning bike ride because, well, just because the body was telling me I needed the rest after a long and busy weekend.  It wouldn't have been very eventful anyways because I'm still not able to actually ride on the road yet.  No doctor has said "Yes you can" or "No you can't ride" but it just doesn't seem like it's been long enough to be "safe".  Not that staying off the bike will heal me any faster than getting on the bike will kill me any faster.  Anyways, it's the trainer for now.  I spent a nice weekend visiting my girlfriend and her family this past weekend.  If you didn't get to meet her the last time she was here, she's coming the weekend of the 4th, so stay tuned.  After that, I preached on Sunday a.m. and all that contributed to my peaceful, longer than normal sleep last evening.  I'm going to see Buffy at after her surgery later this week.  She'll be in consultations all day tomorrow and then have the operation on Wednesday.  Proverbs 21:2 says, "All a man's ways seem right to him, but the LORD weighs the heart".  This is much like the verse from the other day so I won't belabor this point.  We as people have a way of thinking that we're right all the time and we'll act on those "right" feelings without much concern as to whether or not they actually are right or not.  All things considered (motives, biases, grudges, likes/dislikes, etc.), man is pretty self centered.  The Lord determines, and already has determined, what is right and what is not.  Our thoughts ought to center around God's plan for our lives and not our own.  We have no  real  control over what life dishes out.  Life, death, health, bike wrecks.  All these things will come and go.  God knows the right way, and wishes for us to pursue it.  But he also knows the heart of man is centered away from that way.  Let God direct your ways for he knows us and knows what is best.  This week: Wednesday @ 6:00 pm we're leaving for TH Skate World. $1 for reg. skates, $2 for speed, & $3 for blades. July 4 Independence Day Parking Lot Party, invite all your friends and bring some snacks.  We'll start at 8. July 12 canoe trip at Turkey Run.  Ken Arini and I will be floating along with you.  There will be release forms at church on Sunday.  YOU NEED THEM TO GO!!!  Later...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning was the trip into town to the Brazil Emergency Food Pantry.  We had 6 come in to help do odd jobs around the place while the ladies who normally work there delegated out our jobs.  We finally got into a groove and got some pretty good work done in the time we were there.  I want to thank those who came and remind them that the work done there was appreciated and will not go completely unnoticed.  Good work, everyone!  I had lunch at Eddie's today with Nick.  It's always an experience going in there.  Today was the first day that I'd ever eaten inside.  It's always a treat.  Proverbs 16:2 says, "All a man's ways see innocent to him, but motives are weighed by the LORD".  Isn't that true?!?  As much as we try and fool ourselves sometimes and justify the things we do, no matter how trivial they might seem to us, it is God who knows the real reason and is not fooled.  I'm sometimes embarrassed when I think about some of the activities I've done in the name of "doing a good deed (where I get most of the benefit)" or "no one will get hurt (or ever know)".  We only fool ourselves when we choose to live life in this way.  God, who created us, is not going to be faked out by our little games.  He knows us inside and out, up and down.  This ought to be motivation for us to fill our lives with good things and seek the best for others besides our selves.  When we get in selfish or prideful modes, we lose sight of God's way and his plan for us.  The very next verse (16:3) gives great application to this thought (but you've got to find it yourself!).  Next Wednesday evening is Skate Night.  We're going to Skate World in TH at 6:00.  Bring $$$ for skate rental and snacks (if you want).  Bring a buddy!!!  That's what this is for. Pete's Cookout for Highschool is Friday at 5 pm.  Be there!  Later...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow evening is the first fellowship event for my Sunday school class.  I'm hoping that we'll have a good turn out for it because it would be a real shot in the arm for the class.  Right now, it consists of 3 (+/-) and myself.  True the class has only been around for a school year, and we'll hopefully retain some of our highschool grads, but it's growing rather slowly.  It's a whole different ball game trying to teach peers than it is teaching people who are 5 to 10 years younger.  Plus, not everyone is like me, so I don't really know what will appeal to folks on a mass level when I'm planning things.  Like I said, hopefully we'll have a good turn out and this will be the beginning of some good things for a group who need some good things.  Proverbs 15:2 says, "The tongue of the wise commends knowledge, but the mouth of the fool gushes folly".  I'll come back to the wise in a few, but I want to talk about this other guy first.  Don't we all know someone like this?  You know, the guy/gal who you just pray doesn't say something because you know it going to be colossally stupid/redundant/meaningless/etc?  Sometimes, I just don't know what will help these people more: a swift kick or a helpful word.  But in light of any attempt to help that one might conjure up, the Bible tells us that these will pretty much all be in vain.  The fool doesn't listen to wisdom, whether it's voiced by a caring, empathetic individual or by my size 9 on his back side!  These folks will continue to shoot their mouths off and "gush folly" (great mental images here!) and prove the saying "Better to have someone think you're a fool and keep quiet than to open you're mouth and remove all doubt (or something like that).  No, the person that will gain from correction is the wise!  The person who seems like they need it the least will benefit the most form it, because it will actually do good!  To commend wisdom is to acknowledge that it is good and right, even if that means swallowing one's pride and facing the fact that you might be in the wrong.  The wise man will accept this fact and be better for it.  We have to face the facts, folks.  There are too many foolish people in the world...let's not add to the number.  Seek to live and be wise.  Tomorrow morning (Wednesday)-Food pantry (9:45 @ church.  We're done at 12) Saturday-Highschool Sunday School cookout (5:00 pm)  Later...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, if you haven't heard yet, I had a bike wreck on Friday morning.  If your first inclination is to worry, assuming that this is your first time reading about it, please don't.  For the rest of you who have heard the story and seen the show, ignore the next couple sentences.  *I was just starting my ride and proceeded around a corner that was wet and oily and the bike simply went out from under me.  Because of the angle of the turn, and the relative lack of speed (so, no, I wasn't going too fast!) I went straight down...on my face!  I have several minor scratches on my face and chest, but have a nice black eye and a cheeckbone with 3 fractures.  I spent the morning in the Clay Co. hospital, got x-rays, CT scan, blah blah blah...I'm doing much better now, thanks.  So anyways, I have a little bit of a headache this morning because I'm not going to take my pain medicine anymore.  Why, do you ask?  Well, it's not a matter of being a tough guy, health reasons, or saving the rest to sell on the black market...I just don't think I need it (and my Jiminy-Cricket-esque conscience told me not to!).  I rode on the trainer a bit this morning and got the heart rate up, so I was pleased.  I'm interested in how the rest of the week will shape up.  I've got a busy rest of the month.  This week, I'm preparing a sermon and my sunday pm lesson as well as getting ready for a week of camp and a cookout on Wednesday evening as well as helping with the Food Pantry that morning.  Oh, and I should mention that I'm heading to Springfield to see my Laura this weekend (Three more days!).  Proverbs 14:2 says "He whose walk is upright fears the LORD, but he whose ways are devious despises him".  The person who has respect and reverence for God will live a life that is evident of his commitment to God.  The Bible says his "walk is upright", which means he's living a righteous and good life.  He's not just a "good" guy, but he's doing the right thing.  This person doesn't cut corners or tell "white lies", he's a straight shooter...all the time.  On the other hand, the person who is cutting corners in life, making sneaky little deals, and consoles him/herself by saying "It's alright, I'm a good person" is the one who (as the Bible says) despises the LORD.  It's amazing to me how many people go around claiming to be Christians and to love God and yet see in so many of their lives where they are deficient in morals, ethics, and character.  Doesn't the Savior of our souls deserve a little better than our second best?  We need to straighten up and walk upright!  If you're going to the Food Pantry on Wednesday, be at church at 9:45 to load up. High School, remember Pete's Sunday School Cookout is Saturday at 5 pm.  Come hungry!  Later...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I got up at 5:30 to ride and it was a little wet out.  It wasn't raining all that hard, if at all, at the time, but I didn't ride anyways.  The plan was (and still is) to go to the highschool parking lot and do some laps and accelerate on the straights like I will be on Saturday.  But, those plans will have to wait.  I have a meeting with some camp folk in Wachington today.  I'm looking forward to it.  Camp has always been one of the highlights of my summers and something that I always get excited about.  I hope that we have a good turn out from Berea for the weeks of camp that I'm going to be a part of because they have always had a good rep for being top notch.  Both weeks have new teams leading them but we've worked with some of the best so the weeks will still be great, with a few new flavors.  Proverbs 10:1 says "A wise son brings joy to his father, but a foolish son grief to his mother".  Sounds pretty obvious, eh?  As the whole book up till now has been talking to kids about getting wisdom, and much of that from their parents, it would seem to go with the flow into this section of little nuggets of wisdom.  These sections of Proverbs are great.  If you get in the habit of reading one chapter a day (which I highly recommend), even if you don't retain EVERYTHING, you'll hang on to one or two of these nuggets to work on during the day.  Anyways, we honor our parents by listening to their wisdom and teaching.  They've been where we are.  Although it may seem like they're out of touch and can't relate, I think they deserve to be heard.  They have made (and hopefully learned from) their own mistakes inthe past, so they aren't perfect.  But neither are you!  Ha!  Try seeking out their counsel and doing the things that will bring them joy and a feeling of "Hey, my boy/girl is going to turn out alright", instead of "Why, Lord, why?!?"  Remember: fo the right thing.  We're swimming on Friday (6-8 @ Forest Park) I'm racing on Saturday (1:30 & 3:20 @ 6th and Cherry in TH) We're cleaning & stocking Wednesday (Food Pantry on Pinkley 10am-12)  Later
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I have a confession to make.  I've not entered a new post since some time last week.  I've been on here so little lately that I had to think about my password before entering it!  I'll try to be better.  This morning, I rode a little more than 25 miles on my bike.  It was a good ride that I made difficult.  I'm trying to keep fresh for a race in Terre Haute on Saturday that you should all come to.  I'm not able to go to any group rides, including the all important Thursday night Ventures ride, because of VBS, so I have to ride fast and hard on my own.  It's difficult but it will pay off.  And you should come watch on Saturday at 1:30 and 3:20 at 6th and Cherry.  Find a Bible and read Proverbs 9:1-6.  These pictures of Wisdom crying out desperately for those who need it to come to her are neat to me.  She's done everything, she's prepared and ready, and she's inviting all to come to her for what they so dearly need.  The food and drink that she has is good and life-giving and it's waiting on those who will come and take (as much as they want, mind you).  I feel for the girl, though.  As well as she's prepared, as good as the food, and as eternal the nourishment, the people that need it don't come!  I can't sound more-holy-than-thou and say that I know exactly what she means, because I have kids that just don't seem to listen to me, but many times I'm one of the fools who just walks on by, turning a deaf ear to the truth that's being said.  When will we stop?  When will we stop throwing life away and grasp the good thing that's been there from the beginning?  The Lord is calling to us by his "Wisdom" and offers us understanding and spiritual food that fills and quenches beyond what anyone or anything else can offer.  But it falls back to us to choose.  Do we go to the house that's strong and established with food that is good and eternal or branch out on our own and let whatever happens happen?  Let's do the right thing, eh'?  Updates and other stuff... Friday is the pool party at Forest Park from 6-8. Saturday I'm racing in TH at 1:30 and 3:20 (come and yell) Next Wednesday we're going to the Brazil Emergency Food Pantry to help clean and stock shelves.  This service project will benefit them as well as give us an opportunity to learn to serve others.  Later...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow!  Sorry it's been so long since I've posted something (for all three of you out there who read my blog!).  A lot has gone on in the last week and a half since my last post.  Let me catch you up:  -Wednesday (5/26) was Lizzie's last Big Deal with us until next school year.  We'll miss you Derek!  Also that evening was the revelation of my "special someone".  Yes, the cat's out of the bag.  I'm dating and have been for a little over 2 months.  She's a great girl and hopefully will be around some for those of you interested in meeting her.  Laura, if you're reading this, no pressure!  -Thursday (5/27) was a blur.  I had one of those days where I did a lot but felt like I got nothing (next to nothing) done.  I know I went to my guitar lesson and did the Almost 12 thing and it rained a lot, but that's about it.  -Friday was a pretty good day.  I got most of my lessons done and a good start on my sermon.  That evening, Laura and I went to my cousin's graduation in Oblong, IL.  -Saturday, after staying the night at mom and dad's, I came home, sent Laura off, got dinner and worked out the rest of my sermon.  -Sunday was the long-awaited Youth Sunday.  It went (almost) without a hitch.  Sunday pm was pretty informal.  There were 7 for our yg meeting.  Then the weather moved in.  Warnings and red stuff all over the radar kept us in the church basement for a little while.  Then after a short break in the mess, we all scurried out to our respective homes/vehicles and enjoyed then evening indoors.    -Monday and Tuesday were great!  I've not had two days off like that in forever.  I got to read a book!  I  chose  to read a book for my own enjoyment for the first time in at least 9 months!  Tuesday, although it was my day off, I kicked some tail and got some stuff done.  I got some needed rest, did my devos, mowed the lawn, went to the bike shop, rode 58 miles and went to bed (after calling Laura).  -Today, I'm finishing the Summer Schedule for Youth and Young Adults and starting on VBS lessons for next week.  I'm busy but happy.  Proverbs 2:1-11 "My son, if you accept my words and store up my commands with in you, turning your ear to wisdom and applying your heart to understanding, and if you call ou for insight and cry aloud for understanding, and if you look for is as for silver and search for it as for hidden treasure then you will understand the fear of the LORD and find the knowledge of God.  For the LORD gives wisdom, and from his mouth come knowledge and understanding.  He holds victory in store for the upright, he is a shield to those whose walk is blameless, for he guards the course of the just and protects the way of his faithful ones.  Then you will understand what is right and just and fair-every good path.  For wisdom will enter your heart, and knowledge will be pleasant to your soul.  Discretion will protect you, and understanding will guard you."  I think this one's pretty self-explanatory.  One event to be putting on your calendars is Bowling Night at Brazilian Lanes on June 11 @ 7 pm.  We'll go till 9.  HEY, BRING A FRIEND!!!  Later
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I’m back from another week of camp and so will now give you the old speech, “I fully intend to writing on the blog everyday from here on out”.&nbsp; We’ll see.&nbsp; Actually, I only write on days that I’m in the office, but we’ll see about how I can work in the half hour it usually takes to write, edit, study for the commentary part, then publish the blog on the weekdays I’m not in.&nbsp; Like I said, we’ll see.  Camp was a doozy of a week this year.&nbsp; We had a new set of deans who had worked with the fellows who lead it for the last few years and worked well together, so that helped keep a few of the traditions of Sr. High week intact.&nbsp; However, it was definitely a new flavor of camp.&nbsp; One obvious difference in the week was that we had close to 190 campers!&nbsp; 190 is a good Jr. High week.&nbsp; And for those of you who are a little fuzzy on comparing Jr. to Sr. highers, Jr. High kids have very few inhibitions about anything, where as highschoolers are a little more concerned with looking cool and not making waves and usually that leads to smaller numbers at camp.&nbsp; That wasn’t the case this year.&nbsp; And it was good!&nbsp; Our speaker for the week was intense and really in-your-face as well as biblically solid.&nbsp; The worship leader lead only with a guitar and no other accompaniment, which was a different take from the full, electrified ensembles of the past.&nbsp; All in all, it was a good week and I’m really looking forward to starting on next year’s camp with this group.&nbsp; I just hope we (BCC) can bring more kids next year.&nbsp; I really think they missed something by not being there.  Proverbs 28:1 says “ The wicked man flees though no one pursues, but the righteous are as bold as a lion ”.&nbsp; Have you ever known someone who is completely paranoid or always looking over their shoulder, or ducking authorities?&nbsp; Could it possibly be because they are always doing something wrong and their conscience is, thus, always on the defensive?&nbsp; It’s somewhat amusing to see the lengths to which people will go in order to keep themselves from getting caught. &nbsp;After a while though, it’s just sad.&nbsp; The LORD told the people of Israel in Leviticus that he would punish the wicked with various diseases and invading nations to the point that, even when they weren’t being pursued, they were running.&nbsp; As an alternative to this cowardice, righteousness seems pretty enticing.&nbsp; If being as bold as a lion, like David standing in the face of the giant Goliath (I Samuel 17), is what the righteous are, I want to be righteous.&nbsp; The LORD provides richly for his people even in areas of character, like boldness, if we adhere to his ways.&nbsp; “ Meow ” or “ Roar ”.&nbsp; The choice is ours to make.  We’re serving at the Light House Mission in TH tonight.&nbsp; Leaving from the church at 3:30. Get prepared for a great opportunity to help a young church.&nbsp; On the 21st & 22nd of August, we’ll be heading to Bradley, IL to help serve at Adventure Christian Church.&nbsp; It will be a good thing to get involved with.  Later 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, at long last, I’m back in the office after a week at camp and a couple days with my girlfriend.  It was time well spent (both things included).  I think that the weather that we experienced last week while I was at Illiana was the best that I’ve ever seen at a week of camp!  5 straight days of low humidity, sunny skies, and warm weather is about the best anyone can ask for.  Now watch, the weather for my next week, Sr. High in July, will be an absolute scorcher.  But no sense getting pessimistic, now is there?  Camp was went well but was trying in ways that it hadn’t been before.  Just like growing up, with the added title of being a dean (even on a team), comes more responsibilities and the need to have all our ducks in a row.  This was the first time in years we’ve been without John at the helm and it was our turn (Tim, Brian, Steve, Jennifer, Brenda, and myself) to spread our own wings.  We, or at least I, saw some places where we need to work on for next year.  And that’s ok.  Now I’m back in the office and getting ready for the rest of the summer.  On tap is the canoe trip on Monday the 12th.  I’ve only got 2 signed up right now, so get on the list!  Friday the 16th is a Young Adults (not Youth Group, to be sure) fellowship night at Pizza Inn and Putt-Putt in TH.  Come on out.  Well, now it’s off to the races…or into the sunset…whatever.  Proverbs 7:4-5 says, “Say to wisdom, ‘You are my sister’, and call understanding your kinsman; they will keep you from the adulteress, from the wayward wife with her seductive words.”  Wisdom is to be as close to you as a family member.  Sure, some folks don’t get along or even like their siblings from time to time, but we know them inside and out.  Many times, wisdom is like that, too.  We know what we ought to do but the wisdom of doing the right thing often seems like a killjoy to the fun we might otherwise have.  But in the end, wisdom pays off.  It keeps us safe.  It keeps us heading straight on the safe path.  It keeps us away from the harm that is personified in the wayward wife and the adulteress.  Bad company corrupts good character, and spending time with these chicks will put you in the grave.  Let’s try and spend some more quality time at home with the fam: brothers, sisters, and Father. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the day!  Praise the Lord, it’s finally here.  All the planning and calling and rearranging and more calling comes down to today.  Our Cedar Point trip leaves this afternoon!  I’m excited about it for a couple different reasons.  First off, because Cedar Point is probably the best ride park in the world.  16 coasters, folks!  That’s a lot of stomach-swallowing action!  Secondly, I’m excited, in a nervous sort of way, because all the work is done.  As I write this, 99% of everything that needs to get done before we leave is completed.  It’s a little scary for me.  I’m usually running around minutes before we leave looking for van keys, a screw driver, Kleenex, or extra storage space.  This time, it’s all done before hand.  I’m growing up and learning about planning ahead.  I vaguely remember my mom saying something about that concept as I was growing up, but I was too concerned about learning the finer points of  procrastination .  As lovely of a thing as that is, it’s scientifically proven to take years off your life.  (Well, I really can’t prove that, but it sure feels like it.)  We load up and head out on our little excursion at 1:00 this afternoon.  Pray for us as we go.  We'll gloat…er…tell you all how it went when we get home.  Proverbs 4:4-6 says, “he [my father] taught me and said, ‘Lay hold of my words with all your heart; keep my commands and you will live.  Get wisdom, get understanding; do not forget my words or swerve from them.  Do not forsake wisdom, and she will protect you; love her and she will watch over you’”.  A father’s job is to teach his children in the way they should go.  Again, the book of Proverbs is written from the perspective of a father teaching his son how to live a good life.  We ought to heed these wise words as if they were being spoken directly to us.  The good words spoken to us by our Father in heaven are meant to bring us life.  He encourages us to pursue wisdom in a serious way.  It’s interesting to me to see how many people get into car accidents because they were swerving to miss some small woodland creature.  Squirrel, rabbit, dog (not exactly woodland, but I digress) whatever, it’s a better alternative than Mack, Freightliner, Kenworth…you get the idea.  We aren’t to swerve from the good teaching we receive, no matter how much better we think we understand.  But as youth, we tend to do just that.  As mom was teaching me to plan ahead and get stuff done while I had the time, I thought there were better alternatives.  To this day, I can’t tell you a tenth of what I did fooling around while I should have been doing homework.  But I can tell you what I got on my report cards and homework grades (thanks to mom!).  Learn to be wise now and save yourselves the trouble of having to do it later.  That’s the stuff that matters.  We’re leaving at 1 for CP. I’ll have the sign up sheet for the Adventure Trip posted on Sunday.  Later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember an old Golden Girls episode where Blanche was trying to be a romance novelist.  (Just for the record, just because I used to watch Golden Girls doesn’t make me old.  Good grief, it was a show in the 80’s, so I would have been like 8 when it first aired!)  At one point in the show, she complained to the other girls that she had writer’s block.  This condition is the bane of all writers.  It’s characterized by the inability of the writer to come up with anything beyond what they’ve already got.  The ideas just stop flowing.  Well, all that to say that I have writer’s block.  Well, I did until I remembered that old TV show.  Thanks Blanche!  I rode with the Fast Group to Nevins, IL last night.  This route is the hilly version of the Thursday ride.  A fellow named Bill showed up for the first time (at least as far as I had seen of him) in a while and rode with us.  This man is an absolute beast on a bicycle!  He rode so hard in the first half of the trip out, he dropped me and another girl who are both usually able to keep up at fast paces.  Poor Peanut had two flats and a dropped water bottle that held him up.  I had a day like that last week.  Anyways, on the way back, I felt good on the hills and rode off the front on my own for a bit, but got reeled back in 2 hills from the finish.  The cool thing about the whole ride was that a friend of mine asked me about coming to church!  It was great!  I just pray that we’ll have more opportunities to talk and keep that line of communication open.  Proverbs 3:3-5 says, “Let love and faithfulness never leave you; bind them around your neck, write them on the tablet of your heart.  Then you will win favor and a good name in the sight of God and man”.  Love and faithfulness are key components in the Christian life.  If you’ve been to Youth Group at all this year, you know that our theme teaching has been Love God, Love People, as Jesus said these two are the greatest commandments.  Faithfulness moves in two ways.  First is our faithfulness to God and his word.  Secondly, out of the first comes people knowledge of our faithfulness and their perception of us will be one of a person who can be trusted.  I think that’s what this verse is getting at.  If these two things are with us all the time, like a necklace or garment ( bind them around your neck ) and the written law of conduct for our lives (… the tablet of your heart …) we’ll be seen for what we truly are by God and by the people around us.  Try and guard against writer’s block when you do this, though.  Writing God’s word on ours hearts is not as difficult as it might seem.  *Pray for those of us who will be driving to Cedar Point tomorrow.  We leave at 1pm. *Clear your calendars for the Adventure Trip to Adventure Christian Church on Aug. 21-22.  There will be a sign up sheet on the Youth Board on Sunday. *Big Deal starts up again on Aug. 18!  Get ready for a brand new year!  Later.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>