<Blog>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mmmmmkay, this is pathetic, I'm sitting here thinking of all the stuff I have to do, while I listen to rap, and writing about how I should get offa the computer. I gotta go. Now. Out of the house or something. ::Gets up::
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This after noon, I was feeling pretty good about myself, but now, I'm crying. I feel so depressed, and not only that, but I don't like to talk to my friends about it. I know its not unusaul, or even embarrassing, but I just can't talk to anyone about my problems, it would be too hard for me. Thruth be told, this is really how this blog was born. I didn't really intend for this to be a diary. I fooled myself into thinking that I could make one of those trivial little blogs with funny links. The thing is, I'm just not that type of person. I wish I was, their lives are so simple and happy. They are the type of interesting people that make friends easily, and speak their mind. I don't know why I'm writing my thoughts here where they will fester and die from not being read by anyone. Writing should be read, or else it is still nothing more than a thought. Anyway, I have a lot work to do, though it probably not get done. Depression never helps get work done. I know I'll end up lying on the couch staring at the tele. Oh well, such is my life. Bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One thing I neglected to mention, last Saturday was my 15 1/2th birthday, meaning I should have gotten my temps then. I forgot to mention, but that was another reason why I didn't really like the trip to (sweet, sweet) Canada- it kept me (basically) from getting my driver's license on the day of my 16th birthday. It may not sound like a big deal, but for me it means a lot. Driving is freedom. I can go wherever I want, and it means privacy for me too. I don't HAVE to be in the house all the time cause I'll be able to go places. You know what, I'm fooling myself. Getting my license won't make me any happier, or more free. I just wrote that first part about being free without really thinking about how it really will be. I can tend to be an idealist sometimes, and I hate it. Being an idealist only leads to disappointments. Like just now. Funny how my mind works, I was gonna write about driving, and I ended up having a small revelation. Well, I went to get my temps today, and long story short, we saw a bunch of messed up people at the BMV, and I had to wait forever, but the test was easy and I got my temps. I promised myself I wouldn't get excited, after all, I can only drive with my mom, who is a complete nutcase who screams all the time, and it only means I'll have to go through drivers ed, and all that shit, and later pay for auto insurance. But, I'm embarrassed to say, I did get pretty hyped after I got my temps. Come to think of it, the biggest reason I didn't want to be too excited is because the single person I hate most: Kevin Frick, was childishly flaunting his temps like he was better that everybody else. I really didn't like that, cause temps are like no big deal (ok, I was jealous too). Anyway, this entry is far too long, and I really should refine these entries to what really matters: my deep thoughts and observations on life, and my feelings that matter, not petty goings on in my life. I'ma cut this one off right about no-
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent my weekend in Canada (cool) with my family (not cool). We went to Point Pelee, Ontario to look at the migrant birds there. Uh, not much to say, we saw a few good birds, I had to put up with my family, I made fun of a lot of goofy birders, etc. Anyway, the trip was mediocre at best, and I didn't like that it took up my entire weekend. Make matters worse, noone missed me, or even knew I was gone. One thing to clear up: in my last entry, I said I'd rather distance myself from everybody. The thing is, I still need to know I'm appreciated and liked. Anyway, sometimes I can't decide whether I want to be around people, but am just antisocial, or if its just that I would rather be alone. One thing that I have experienced earlier in my life, is being shy, and I still am today. A thing that a lot of people didn't understand, is that just because a person is shy doesn't mean they want to be left alone and 'let to do their own thing'. Its strange, I have a bit of a love hate relationship with company. I geuss I just don't know what I want, and I don't think I'll be happy anyway that it turns out.  Looks like I have more to learn about myself than I previously thought.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was a bad day, I might say, but it wasn't quite that. I feel like time just seeped past me and I couldn't do anything about it. I didn't do any homework (like I ever do anyway), I didn't talk to anybody that much this whole week, and, basically, its like if I wasn't here, it would have made any difference to anyone. That kinda got me down. This week has made me despondent, and angry, and I don't know why. This week, I just wanted to withdraw myself from any human interaction whatsoever, I guess I more than half succeeded. If that can't make my life better, I can at least it makes it easier. Another thing: I have this feeling that I'm running out of time, but I don't know why, or for what time is running out for. One final thought, if I had wings, I'd fly off into the ocean until I could fly no more, and plunge into the cold ocean to die. My life is a meaningless sequence of trivia, and sometimes I just want it to end.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Based on the life span of my other computer projects (Bloop Diary, my other blog -currently MIA, etc.), I'll guess this blog has about two days to live. In any case live long and prosper, my aspiring creation -if you dare . . .
     
    
</post>


</Blog>