<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why are we so amused by ignorance? Why do we constantly tune in to laugh at ComicView and the myriad of other stupid ass shows that come on TV? To make matters worse, instead of being able to acknowledge this lack of intelligence, we defend it and simply brush the issue off by saying, "It's just entertainment!". Havven't we gotten fed up with simply being entertainers? Why don't we start to function in other facets of society? I guess that all of this is starting to come to mind afetr experiencing the aimless bickering of some black students today. They were arguing over "gear" and who had the most! The conversation was stupid, so instead of butting in and correcting the idiots, i decided to stay on the outside and adopt a new sense of simply observing life. the conversation translates as follows:  PERSON A: I have a lot more cheaply made cotton than you because my parent (note the absence of the plural form of parent and the absense of Person A's job being mentioned)has more money than you parent!  PERSON B: What do you mean? My mother has lot's of money that she gives to me to buy clothes with. i never elect to spen the money on more valuable purposes liek college application fees or books taht have intellectual value. Instead, I enjoy pouring my money out of the community into the hands of the same group of people that my ancestors picked these fabrics for!  PERSON A: Be quiet, your arguement is starting to sound almost as good as mine so now I feel the need to call you a name in a latent act of psychological projection. I feel depressed and sad with my inner self as well as my surroundings (family, neighborhood, etc), so I am going to lash out on you by calling you a homosexual!     im bored now, sleep awaits me, sorry!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whenever I'm not working or doing something else that truly bores me, I'm thinking about something. A problem, a solution, an event, an idea; something to add to the existing pool of knowledge or to at least understand something already in the pool. Today, I found my self thinking about the ghetto and it lead me to wonder why people label themselves as "ghetto" and "easty". I figure that since I am a product of the ghetto and have spent my entire life growing up in the ghetto, I should have some type of say-so in the formulation of the reasoning behind this type of labeling. So let's see:  >> Ghetto is different from easty. Ghetto is a much more universal term, I believe that even a white person can be ghetto!   GHETTO (geh'-to)  adj  a term applicable to any individual that lives a life characterized by: (1)improvisationalism, (2)seemingly free but actually contained thought, (3)ghetto mannerisms and (4)the adaption of ghetto vernacular.   (1) Improvisationalism is the ability to mimic higher things using objects of lesser value or using things not manufactured for such a use. It also signifies one's tendency to try and "put up a front" in order to be mistaken for soemone that they are not.  (2)This would explain people that hold a ghetto mentality about politics and other large scale issues. They believe that they are "beating" the system by not participating in it or that politics is something for white people and was invented simply to hold minorites back. They love their indifference and hold on to the notion that they are excersising free thought when in actuality they are simply playing out the best role they can play in order for the current system to remain unchanged. The system's controllers feel no need to truly convince ghetto people why they should vote or go to college becasue if the "ghettoites" were roused too much they would possibly set out and become too progressive and demand or even force a change in the system.  (3)The cockiness of their gestures, the uniqueness of their walk, their animated facial expressions, etc.  (4)The latent psychological response to being forced to learn standard English. The simple rebellious attiude found in any human being that wishes to debunk the sytem that has tried to put so many stresses on him or her to speak English correctly. Ghetto vernacular is witty and spontaneous, and suffices the need for shorter sentences and a more personal and colorful expression of thought.   As for easty, this word stands for a person that WAS  ghetto but moved too far to the Eastside and was corrupted by everything in the hood. They are the Swapmeet Hoes, the Bustop Bench Weed Smokers, the Every-Color-in-the-Rainbow Weave Heads, and a host of other epitomizing ghetto staples.  Inner City Thought Control is Evil!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tonite, i wasnt moved to type!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw "the video" this morning thanks to Kazaa. Forgive me if I'm out of line, but I don't see the cause for censorship here! The video is piss-poor in quality and I couldnt see anything clearly! Maybe it was just the video that I saw, but the entire thing looked blurred to me! I did catch the audio very clearly and it was sad to hear the poor guy screaming his lungs out but then, in all my skepticism, I asked myself, "The News did say he was there basically for business, why the hell would anyone go to Iraq for business after the 1980s?" I hate to sound callous, but he really should have been a little more critical before going!   War sucks and so does neo-conservatism!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fast food is addictive! It can take over your senses and corrupt your thinking just long enough for you to make the stupid decision to ingest the crap. I had been successfully eating “right” (if such a thing exists in a society that genetically alters basically all of our food) for about three months. However, at my lowest hour, fast food offered guidance and protection, and exploited my stomach; fast food used me like a five dollar hoe! I was at school, and after a long and grueling day an event took place that put the cherry on top of everything. I was frantic; I felt abandoned, ashamed, and psychotic. My mind was in a blur and my heart was telling me that I needed the dirty stuff (you know it’s bad when your heart is giving you bad advice). I literally jogged to the local fast food joint and ordered a Sourdough Jack with bacon, fries, and Coke ®. Of course, the food tastes like metal and wood, but I was appeased. I had broken my 3-month long boycott. I fell asleep as a result of the ensuing “food coma”. When I woke, I had a splitting headache and my stomach was doing back flips all the way to bathroom! The corporate machine that is the fast food industry is very strong and has the ability to stupefy you with great tasting fries. My addiction has started again; I eat fast food about three times a week. I try to stay away from it, but it always seems to make its way into my range! (The shuttle driver in DC dropped me off at McDonald’s instead of Howard!).  God bless the Big Mac (pray for me!). Another example of corporate control! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So next Thursday, I'll be in DC at Howard for pre-Orienation. I have to come in at Dulles unfortunately, but I'm optimistic about everything. I've talked to some fellow students about the trip, and they were all full of jubilance when they were reporting back to me. Hopefully I'll feel the same when I return. I'll be sure to give all the details upon my return. I've been so busy lately with school work and my own personal endeavors...I hope to have more time to blog soon! LOL
     
    
</post>


</Blog>