<Blog>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       >>  *looks around innocently*  *tries to type softly*   >>  Yes... I'm 25 and still live with my parents....(that will change in about 19 days though)...it's 5:11am and they're sleeping.....they will wake up in about 45 minutes and here I am...on my compy...still awake.  It's odd...to feel so guilty just for not going to sleep.  Hee hee.  I guess it's because my parents (mom mostly) care about me so much that causes them (her) to be angry upon discovering that I stayed up all night.  meh.  I'll keep adding more as I delve deeper into this blog world......
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ooooh I've entered the realm of the BLOGS!  hehehe, lets see what mischief I can create....   >>  ]:)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So....I'm married and have moved from Toronto, Canada down to Las Vegas, NV in the United States.  Life has definitely done a 180 on me in a matter of one really interesting year!  But I digress.... so how is here different than there??  I found myself really contemplating on the differences yesterday at a park here in Vegas while watching the 4th of July fireworks.  As several hundred people passed me by (I was confortably laying on the grass waiting for the firework display to start) wearing their red, white and blue outfits or US-Flag T-shirts/dresses or crazy hats 'n stuff...it hit me how patriotic Americans (I dislike using this term as it actually refers to everyone on the North and South parts of the continent called America...but I find I sometimes succumb to pop-culture *sigh*) are.  Seeing the children walk by with their faces painted with little USA Flags and their parents getting them all excited about celebrating the birthday of their country really made me reflect on how un-patriotic Canadians seem in comparison.  Why is that? I don't really understand it.    I'm a Canadian born citizen with Ecuadorian born parents. Growing up, it was never really "cool" to say 'I'm Canadian'... most people that I'd meet would ask, "so what are you?" (yes it's odd but happens more often than you'd think) and when I was younger I'd reply "Ecuadorian" without a second thought, then I'd ask them and they'd reply "Portuguese" or whatever....both of us knowing full well that we were BOTH Canadian-born just that our parents were immigrants.   As I grew older I started answering "Canadian" and most people either laughed and said, "I know THAT! But where are you REALLY from" or some would look at me in frustration and would think that I was hiding my ethnicity from them.  The older I got the more important it was to identify myself as Canadian instead of anything else.  I have a fierce loyalty to my country -- however....it still does not compare to the patriotism of those born in the US.  (I'll continue my musings in a little bit...I must leave to go run an errand)
     

    
</post>


</Blog>