<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's Friday, and I've been more active this week than I have in a long time. Those crazy doctors who concoct their stories of  urlLink exercise being healthy  may be right. I've woken up refreshed this week, ready to take on the day (ok, not really), and had more energy.  Surprising, considering my usual drill of wishing I were more fit. And doing nothing about it.  Ups and downs permeated the past few days, with my stupidity sprinkled throughout. Searching for lost equipment, only to find it sitting out in the open one room over. Not following through and causing a crucial error that took days to solve. Whittling away at projects while they grow even more immense.  I've begun reading  urlLink Timothy Zahn's Conquerors  series. Quite enjoyable thus far. Even though I know my emotions are being manipulated, still the characters are compelling. Simple plot, nothing fancy, twists visible from a distance. Yet enjoyable. As close to Star Wars as you can get without being Star Wars.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My eyes were recently opened to the reality of political maneuvering. Growing up as a teenager during the nineties in a politically conservative home, I was raised listening to  urlLink Rush Limbaugh  on the radio. His ability to create the story behind the story piqued my interest and molded my understanding of politics. During the  urlLink Clinton  administration I deftly followed each scandal, becoming apporopriately appalled with every new revelation. Politics became for me a battle of good versus evil.  After eight years of Clinton, and fewer listening to Rush, I became disenchanted with politics. Voting for  urlLink Bush in 2000  did nothing for my political drive, even after staying up all night waiting for final results.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As the title suggests, the issue of  urlLink violence on television  and movies seems to have two distinct sides. On the one, our culture's violent tendencies are created by a small group of individuals who control the content of most television and movies produced today. Their dismal outlook on humanity finds it's way onto the screen and into the minds of helpless children and young adults, nearly forcing them into similar behavior.   The other side would be that current visual media does nothing more than reflect the common and sometimes gruesome reality. If the violence weren't so pervasive, there would be no need to  urlLink depict  it.  Which argument holds more credence will shape both how you view your culture and your reaction to that culture. Your reaction will form into either action or inaction.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       By far the funniest thing I have run across in my web ramblings this week is the rumor that   John-John are gay  .         After the initial chuckle, reason steps in and assures me that can't be the case. It must be some sort of joke. Only problem is   once you see the pictures   you can't stop laughing.         Certainly this is a low-level assault on two high profile men and totally inappropriate. We must automatically discard any sort of smearing of character not based on hard fact. That's how we should approach both presidential candidates. Simply put, the golden rule applies; I don't want someone slandering me that way, so I won't do it to them.         Except there's those pictures.         Not even Bill Clinton, noted sex addict, was quite so...friendly. Don't recall ever seeing Bill grab Al's microphone during a rally (thank God).         Listen guys, I know you will be reading the article (or at least have a summary given by a staff member), so here's a little advice. Maybe you should, you know, take a break. Give it some time. There's no hurry. Four years is a long time if you win, so don't rush things.         Remember, winning the vote will happen after you   invoke the mystic "values"  , causing independent-thinking Americans to swoon for you. I know how it makes me feel inside.    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Self-awareness is one of the traits that makes us human. Without it, we would simply forage for food in a worthless existence. Part of the wonder of being human is understanding the frailty of our lives. Most of us live without second thought to the cliche of "You could die at any moment," though it's truth may have impacted us in the past. We tend to blaze ahead on life's trail, believing that we can will the obstacles out of our way. Often the small obstacles in life have a tendency to knock us off the path.  During a time of national crisis, people responded individually and collectively with strength and determination. From cities to farms the resolve did not waver. That obstacle, though great, proved manageable for many people. Their focus was melded together in a way unknown before that day.  Now the obstacle that is small, yet peels back a layer of the shroud surrounding your self-awareness is more devastating in certain aspects. The pain that accompanies revalations that deal with personal failure cannot be borne by a nation, but must be shouldered by an individual. The trauma is localized and goes unnoticed, and the victim tries to heal the wound himself amidst those who neither will nor want to help. This tragedy multiplied by millions is the current state of America, the very individualistic tendencies that provide strength when summed spell disaster when ignored and left to fester.  Reach out today, place your bandage on the bleeding wound.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>