<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the man that defines cool for me is a man by the name of dan bern.  a true modern day renaissance man, dan bern is by trade a singer/songwriter, though he is also by nature a skilled painter, writer, and poet.  having written well over 2000 songs, his topics run the gamete from social and political commentary and religion to absurd hypotheticals (i.e. charles manson's real name is charles krautmeyer, and if people would have known that, they wouldn't have followed him).  Every song is beautifully constructed and delivered.  During my tuesday night radio show on wfhb, we have a requisite dan bern song, usually one per hour.  whenever given the opportunity, i play dan for virgin ears.  since learning of him in 1998, i've taken around 25 to 30 new fans to shows, which is not hard to do once they hear him, and since he tours all the time.  i've been to numerous shows here in bloomington, indianapolis, louisville, dayton, chicago, and pittsburgh.  but maybe what makes him the coolest is his down to earth personality.  While he's not a huge rockstar on radio or mtv, he does have a rather large and loyal following, and he is equally loyal in return.  the first show i saw in 1998, at second story, he performed a song called "poor darva conger", a fun little song mocking the travesty of television that was "who wants to mary a millionaire?", which had aired on fox only a few days before the show.  In this song, he jokingly said that he would take care of darva when her sham marriage falls apart, as long as she can handle a few things, because dan's dream girl must be able to: "drive five hundred miles a day, sing harmony, and average 185 in bowling".  I remember my ears perking up after that line.  it just so happened that this particular show was on a thursday, which, at the time, was the one night a week where my friends and i would all go bowling.  it had been a ritual for over a year, and people knew, if you were looking for me, and it was thursday night, look no further than the bowling alley.  anyways, after the show, i went up to talk to this guy who had just blown me away with nothing more than an acoustic guitar and the tapping of his foot to compliment him on his performance.  he said "thank you" with the most genuine smile, looking right at me, not through me or around me as so many people do.  then i asked him to go bowling with my friends and i.  he paused for a second, flashed a bigger smile, and accepted the invitation.  That night he mopped the lanes with me.  but, ever since that night, no matter the months between our meetings, he always finds me before the show, gives me a big hug, and asks me how i've been.  he's just a special guy. i strongly encourage all who read this to go buy a dan bern album and give it a listen.  you won't be disappointed.  or, check out danbern.com.  now, on to "cool" itself.  what defines cool to me is anything that i touch, see, hear, taste, or experience that affects me in a positive manner.  the degree of that affect translates into exactly how cool something is.  On the other hand, those experiences that affect me in a negative manner are decidedly not cool.  and as far as the word goes, cool is as cool gets.  it's been around for so long, the word and what it stands for deserve a little respect.  "groovy" and "rad" and such terms are merely flashes in the pan, a generational adaptation.  say "groovy" today, and people kind of look at you.  groovy is a 60's and 70's term.  that is where it belongs.  cool has stood the test of time.  i understand that all language fades away eventually.  we certainly don't speak the same language as our forefathers.   so, eventually, cool will become, ironically, not cool.  but, for the twenty seven years i've been around, cool is the grandaddy, and i don't see it going anywhere real soon.  the other day i heard an eight year old kid describe a cicada on the ground as cool.  preach on, cool little guy.  as for cool hunters, the strike me as decidedly not cool.  cool hunters are nothing more than hipster p.r. people.  these people take a paper bag full of garbage, wave their wand and dress it up, pronounce it cool, then sell it off.  and people eat it up.  what they fail to realize when they have the cash in their hand is, when they get it home, cool or not, it's still a bag of garbage.  to think that a large learning institution such as indiana university would consider using such practices in order to "compete"  with other schools is deplorable.  what it all comes down to is this:  cool cannot be manufactured.  cool just is.  that is intrinsic to cool's nature.  to tamper with something in order to heighten it's coolness is, you guessed it, uncool. this is all getting a little too eastern philosophy for me right now, so i'll move on.  i have found, in my experience, that you can't look for cool.  cool finds you, it affects you.  that's when it becomes cool to you.  maybe this is why the idea of a cool hunter offends me so.  as far as what's next in the cool department, i again point you to dan bern.  he's been around for a while, but if he's new to you, that's new... and cool.  he appeals to every demographic.  my 56 year old dad likes him.  my southern belle christian mother likes him.  my 22 year old teacher girlfriend likes him.  and i can't imagine you, whoever you are, not appreciating him as well     
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      VALS is a survey used in consumer market research.  Rather than basing the survey research on the product, VALS focuses on the type of person the consumer is, then groups them into different purchasing categories.  After answering questions, the VALS survey breaks your answers down into three separate categories of purchasing motivations, first a primary, and then a secondary.  My VALS survey placed me into striver/experiencer.  At first I was flattered, thinking to myself that one who strives to experience things can't be a bad thing at all.  In fact, I still don't think it is.  Yet, when I read further on the purchasing habits of a striver/experiencer, the flattery sort of dropped off.  Sadly, I still mostly agreed with the analysis.  Though I don't think that my purchasing habits necessarily conform with the model, the VALS assessment of my views was pretty solid.  I am fun loving.  I do wish I had more money.  And I always thought I like going grocery shopping because it made me feel like a responsible adult, cooking for myself and deciding exactly what I consume rather than eating out every night, but I can agree with the statement that it is a social action and it displays my ability to buy, and more importantly, to save.  After all, when I go to Kroger, I go all out, and the Kroger Plus card gets a work out, usually saving me 30 to 50 dollars per 100 spent.  I do look at the newest, "hottest" items on the market, but my impulses have been under control for many years, due to maturation, and more importantly, budget.  Basically, I'd have the ways if I had the means.  This actually tells me quite a lot about myself that I either hadn't realized or hadn't examined.  Mostly the latter.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are some definitions for you...    Browser-    These are what presents Web pages to us on the computer. They often guide us through the internet. In the simpest terms it is the icon on one's computer that brings up the internet connection and lets one go form there.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    URL  - Once in an internet browser you need this address to get where you want to go. The different parts of the URL give the computer different instructions. It literally stands for Uniform Resource Locator.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)      Domain Name  - The domain name is one specific part of the URL that sends the computer to specific web pages. There are two parts to a domain name the IP address and the top level domain. The top level domain is the part after the second dot that tells the computer if the page is a commercial business (com), and educational institution (edu), and so on.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)     IP Address  - The IP address is what most computer users do not see it is the number version of the URL. This is the address where the computer takes you- like the URL it consists of a few different parts seperated by periods. Like phone numbers everyone (or every computer) must have a seperate IP address.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    HTML  - HTML is one of the languages of computers, when this language is used someone can create pages on the internet. HTML dictates what each page or document of the web looks like using this language. HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    Snail Mail  - What the world used prior to e-mail! Snail mail is when a letter is actually sent through the US postal service rather than over the web. Since the use of e-mail has become so prevalent in society some people found a reason to distinguish between the two.  I still have faith, and use snail mail often. www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    Emotion  - Emoticons are the grouping of characters of the keyboard designed to be able to show what the author of an e-mail means by certain sentences. It takes the guesswork out of what someone means by a phrase that might otherwise be construed in many ways. Emotions have become seemingly more and more prevelent with the use of instant messaging.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    Newbie  - A newbie is someone who has little knowledge of the computer or internet. People who are just learning are often referred to as this. www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    TCP/IP  - Literlly TCP stands for Transmission Control Protocol. TCP goes a little further than IP becuase it connects two different computers and passes information back and forth between the two. TCPs keep all the information in the order that it was meant to be sent in.  www.pcwebopedia.com (18.May.04)    wireless  - When there is a computer network that is set up and communicates to one another without the use of wires or other means that we can see the network is set up as a wireless one. Instead of using what we are used to seeing these networks communicate through radio waves.  www.comp.std.wirelss (18.May.04)    Peer to Peer Networking  - With this sort of network set up all of the computers involved have equal power. Each computer can give and receive the same information.  www.freedictionary.org (18.May.04)    IPO  - IPO stands for Initial Public Offering which means that this is when a company first goes public in trying to sell it's own stock.  www.freedictionary.org (18.May.04) 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Speaking of movies, i'm already bracing myself for the hubabaloo already starting to take off for this summer's big disaster epic, Day After Tomorrow.  You can't be around a TV without a commercial of one of the (I can only imagine) numerous large scale disaster scenes.  But the true fun will be watching the message boards and chat rooms insisting this film is more accurate than fiction.  I actually saw a report on the ten o'clock news stating that NASA officials had ordered it's scientists not to comment on the film's plausibility.  This is gonna be ridiculous.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was  extremelty  skeptical when typing in the title of my favorite movie on Google.  I just imagined it couldn't be too easy to do an internet search on a film called "Beautiful Girls".  With those two words, together, no less, i figured i'd acctually find a site concerning the 1996 Miramax film somewhere in the 40's or 50's.  Boy, was i pleasantly surprised.  The movie came in sixth.  Sixth, I tell you!  Sure, i had to pass up an "adult friend finder", a couple sites on Russian and Asian mail order brides and dating services, and something to do with Sports Illustrated models in 2000, but then, there it was.  Thank goodness for www.imdb.com (internet movie data base, THE place to get movie information).  I looked through the first few pages, and the ratio of movie related sites to adult sites seemed to be about one to one, with some random health and beauty sites mixed in.  That's as far as i went, though.  after all, there are roughly 8,770,000 sites on Google containing those words.  Interactivity is just now being realized by the mass media.  Shows like American Idol and ESPN's Dream Job are scoring great ratings by offering viewer voting via computer or cell phone to determine who is eliminated and who will win.  There are even interactive films in which audience polls determine what the characters will do next, in the tradition of a choose you're own adventure book.  All of this is creating a conectedness to the television and silver screen.  More and more we are becoming a part of our own entertainment.  It used to be that the only time you saw information on an upcoming film was right before another film.  Not anymore.  Hollywood is  all over  the internet .  One can not only find out when a particular film is going to be released.  They can view stills and behind-the-scenes footage and check out set designs.  And they surely shell out more than the 15 bucks by hitting the online store for merchandise. Two months ago it was Christ, and now it's Troy.  In another week or two it will be Day After Tomorrow.  My grandmother can't check her email without a pop-up of a luscious Brad Pitt staring at her.  OK, my grandma doesn't use email, it's me.  Stop staring, Brad.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Upon considering the concept of analog and digital, my mind goes two very different directions.  When I think of digital, I automatically think CD's, DVD's, and computers.  When I think of analog, I think of vinyl records and video game joysticks. But, if I learned anything in A110 last semester (other than html is way easier than I expected and word is way more complicated than I ever imagined),  it is that analog is represented in waves and digital is represented in binary form, that, of course, being 0's and 1's.  one can't see it with a naked eye, but all that shiny stuff on the bottom of a CD is really just a bunch of ones and zeros.  Digital signals are running analog signals out of town, simply because they are more precise.  As far as the ability to hear digital, I believe the quality ensures that you don't hear digital.  Analog sounds, and especially recordings, don't capture the essence and vitality of the subject being recorded.  Now, that you can hear.  Digital recordings, I've found, are a much closer, if not sometimes, a perfect replication. The one thing I'm not quite sure of is why, in the world of high tech video games, that the instruction manual for all units refer to the controller having an analog joystick.  All I can guess is that the movement of the joystick is transmitted to the CPU in wave format, and is not the most precise representation of the actual movement.  If that is the case, it makes me wonder, is it out of the realm of possibilities to create a digital joystick?  Are there some aspects of our life that we cannot digitize?  I think that is probably a good thing.  Don't get me wrong, I'm no Luddite, though I used to call myself one in jest.  I appreciate the advances and contributions the digital age has made to our lives.  But, I gotta tell you, there's nothing quite as alive and real as the crackle, pop, and hiss of a needle going over a record.  kinda brings a tear...   Interesting factoid of the day:  the word "blog" pops up as wrong on this spellcheck.  How silly is that?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not of the emergency broadcast system.  rather, this is a test of my blogging skills.  why do i feel like i need to be wearing wooden shoes right now?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, a long day of crying people and not a whole lot of time to think about video games.  i just got home from indy, i have a test early in the morning, and all i really want to do is go online and play some poker.  but, i'm not going to.  with the way this day has gone, i'd get sucked out on a great hand and drop fifty bucks i don't have to lose.  but, while i'm typing with the tv on, i have to wonder: what is it about needing video game units in cars and suv's.  now, i understand a gamers mentality, but i don't understand pulling the car over during a road trip to shoot some aliens or make a winning put.  and i'm not talking about a gameboy.  i'm talking home unit, under the drivers seat, controllers and wires everywhere, flip down monitors.  it's just silly.   by the way, i'm stuck in aniac mansion.  it makes me wonder, when you're all three in the dungeon, the game would appear to be over.  but it doesn't end.  am i to believe there is a way out.  because i've tried.  and i'll keep trying.  i hate that about myself. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, today i was sitting in class, when my phone vibrated.  i took it out of my pocket, and there was a text message.  i was informed that my girlfriend's great uncle had died after suffering a major stroke caused by complications from open heart surgery earlier in the week.  I was not shocked, as my girlfriend had been up in indy with her family since right after the complications had arisen.  the outlook had not been good.  and while the technology at the hospital could not elongate ted's life, it was able to let me console my girlfriend and help her with the least amount of possible harm to my studies.  i guess this matters to me because this kind of technology had never had such serious or helpful implications in my life.  every text message i've received before today i could have done without.  stupid "hellos" and unnecessary "what are you doings?".  but, today, it mattered, and it actually touched my life in a way.  going back to a previous blog and my definition, i think that is pretty cool.  time to put a cap on this day.  to those who read this, kiss the ones you love.  goodnight.  cd
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm absolutely horrible with protecting myself and my digital data.  And I mean HORRIBLE.  A year ago I lost my cell phone, and cursed myself for not writing out or saving to my computer all of the important phone numbers and contact information.  After tracking everyone down and buying a new phone, I swore to myself "never again".  Flash forward to two weeks ago when the display in my phone was cracked and unreadable.  I couldn't access any information.  And could I then go to my trusty hard copy?  Of couse not. For two weeks i was pretty much stranded on a communication island, and that was a hassle.  As far as the computer goes.  I'm even worse.  I have one password that I use for everything, and I've been using it since 1995.  I have actually improved in some aspects.  I do keep a closer eye on my bank account now that I've made on line purchases.  And I save much more of my work to disk since my computer last crashed and wiped out everything. But, there's much more room for improvement.  Identity theft is something that scares me to death, and not just because of the creepy commercials with the people talking with the wrong voices.  It's a growing phenomenon, and it seems to get increasingly easier to become a victim.  While technology is working hard to make it more difficult, criminals will always find ways around the protections. I would never consider comparing identity theft with a physical crime such as rape, but I think it is an invasion of similar stature.  It is simply an assault, and it is damaging.  Therefore, I think the criminals that perpetrate these acts should be penalized as though they have committed a violent crime.  It makes no difference to me if you pull a trigger or press a button, if someone attacks me, I want them to be punished severely.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that most every form of media promotes some sort of stereotype.  Positive or negative, ours is a society steeped in judgment.  So, for the general purpose of this one way discussion, I'll say that games like DOA Beach volleyball do tend to objectify women as sexual objects and impossibly proportioned playthings.  Though the notion that someone would buy into such objectification amazes me, I don't discount it totally.  So, yes, video games do have the power to effect our perception.  Now what I have a problem accepting is the idea that these games hold power over us.  I personally don't buy into it.  Games featuring shooting and carnage "incite" violence as much as watching my grandmother clip coupons gets me in the mode to do some extreme grocery shopping.  While I will admit that children are much more susceptible to images and possible lessons from these games, I still don't believe the games are the sole, or even the major reason children take part in violent acts.  Just once I would like to get a group of kids together for an experiment. Have half spend all morning playing a first person shooter, and the other half play with something non-violent, like WordPerfect or Paintbrush.  After a few hours, I'd let them outside.  Would I see the video game kids running around like crazy while the other kids spell in the sandbox.  I doubt it.  They'd most likely all be running around.  I know this is extreme simplification, but I just can't understand how these games, and not the parenting skills, are being vilified.  I grew up playing games like frogger, and even if it had inspired me, my parents were there to tell me not to play in traffic.  Or jump on logs floating down a river.  Thank you Mom and Dad.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am, one of the only people of my generation to have NEVER downloaded a song due to my strong opposition, and now I have to deffend Napster and the likes.  While some of the points I will list and discuss tomorrow are valid points, when it comes right down to it, free file sharing is wrong.  Record companies ask for it by producing CDs for pennies, then selling them at an average price of $17.98.    Napster and it's clones offer a public forum for underexposed and unknown bands to distribute their material and begin building a fan base.  Napster is an online music library.  You can check out books in the library for free.  Free file sharing will not impact record sales as dramatically as projected.  The recording industry managed to survive the big cassette tape dubbing rush of the eighties, and cd burners on the market before Napster.  Speaking of which, if Napster is to be prosecuted, then why not prosecute the companies (PC and other hardware makers) that allow this piracy to continue?  I've got a couple more so called arguments, but I have to save some ammo for class.  viva la group 1! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Earlier this afternoon, I sat down and had an interesting conversation with Monroe County Library Interim Director Cass Owens.  She was kind enough to take some time out of her day and enlighten me on the library's stance on CIPA and the filters they use.  As it turns out, the Child Internet Protection Act has been voted down and appealed in every court level until it was upheld in the supreme court in 2003.  This being the case with Monroe County Library, libraries that do not comply with CIPA standards and use CIPA internet filters are not given federal funding.  According to Owens, the MCL board voted against the filters for several reasons, and they were surprising to me.  "The library's position on the current CIPA filters is that they aren't good enough, not because they block too little, but, because they block too much," Owens said.  Also, the amount of funding offered by government agencies offered to Monroe County Library to comply with CIPA standards wouldn't cover even half of the cost to install and maintain the filters themselves.  Essentially, it would cost the library money to get government assistance.  Opposition is so divided that last year, Monroe County Library employees filed a class action harassment suit against the library, claiming that their work forced them to view materials offensive to them.  The employees lost, but I think it illustrates concerns of parents of children and freedom of speech advocates alike. I think Monroe County Library is doing the right thing.  According to Owens, one would have to ask for assistance in disabling a filter if doing research on breast cancer, because CIPA filters would flag the word "breast" as  pornographic.  American Library Association attorney Paul Smith claims that such an action would stigmatize internet users.  "You've got to go up and say 'Please turn off the porn filter.'"(http://www.wired.com/news/politics/0,1283,57938,00.html). But, the library doesn't just stop there.  Instead, they offer programs to teach internet safety and promote, such as T101 does, finding truthful and accurate information online.  All in all, it's not the Library's job to keep children or anyone else off pornographic sites.  Parents share that task.  I, for one, can't imagine children with enough gall to look at adult sites in public, but then again, kids have surprised me before, including when I look back on my own adolescent actions.  This is a classic modern information age struggle.  Each side has good points, and each points not so strong.  Until the technology can catch up with the industry it so desperately wants to keep from it's country's children, and while the country itself supports the billion dollar porn industry, I think MCL is on the right side of a shaky fence.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>