<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went in today, after rushing back from my college reunion, to find that nobody was there. The other med student wasn't there. The attendings weren't there. There was about a half-staff of nurses. The only people there in full force were the patients. I was going to just go home, but I figured that, since I was there, I should see my patients and check how they're doing.       They were fine. Still crazy.  My first patient still thinks that she's Jesus, that Mick Jagger is the devil and has been following her to her apartment for thirty years, "circling like a snake," buying and selling heroin. A holy light emanates from her. Her neighbors and friends commit horrible and exotic acts of depravity outside her apartment to taunt her. These beliefs are ingrained into her being. Whereas she may be rational in other spheres (she is articulate and graceful in both speech and movement, and when she told me that she had been a dancer and had "danced up and down the coast," I believed her. It took a few moments before she elaborated that she had danced along a thousand beaches, giving shows of her holy light to millions of fans).  My second patient hears the voices of several supposed childhood friends who scream obscenities at her, tell her to kill herself, offer running commentary, and demonstrate acts of petty theft and promiscuity that the patient must copycat. She is alternately giggly ("they told me to laugh") and tearful. The fragmentation of her existence is such that, every few days, there are a couple of moments when she is in touch with reality, when her disease remits enough for her to be briefly aware of where she is, what she has done, that she is committed to a psychiatric hospital, that she has a child who she cannot see, that she has left multiple relationships in shambles, that she has slept with more men than she'd care to remember. At those moments, she is angry and overwhelmed by a pervasive sadness and self-loathing that is slowly effaced by the return of her hallucinations.  What they look like is not so important, nor are their names and the details of their stories. And, if they were important, I still couldn't write them here. The cases above are typical of psychotic illness, the former of delusions - fixed ideas based on impaired perceptions that do not stem from a "shared system of cultural beliefs" (this is textbook, meant to lend creedence to the cultural relativistic argument that religious fundamentalism is not, despite appearances, delusional and psychotic in nature).   In any case, I'm always shocked at how delusions are so consistent in nature, meaning that , despite the differences in details (you're followed by Elton John wearing a hockey mask and howling "Crocodile Rock" in polyphonic harmony and I'm followed by three men in trenchcoats and my roommate is followed by multidimensional space elves who periodically take the corporeal form of garbagemen to send messages encoded by clanging trash cans telling the subway rats to rally and invade), the delusions are still persecutory and grandiose and referential, or else they're somatic. They range in bizarreness, but they're still strikingly similar.  It makes me wonder at the nature of our rational powers and how our machinery acts in stereotypical ways when derailed. I keep thinking that the goal of consciousness is to predict the future. That is, our sense of self is derived from our rational faculty which is an understandable evolutionary movement from the simplest sensory systems.  An early amoeba-like thing undulates around until it runs into some dangerous chemical, which penetrates its cell wall and causes it to shrivel and die. Amoeba-like things that have some receptor on their surfaces that recognize that chemical as noxious and cause the creature to change directions will survive longer and propagate. Eventually, these amoeba-like things evolve loads of receptors that recognize various environmental stimuli and allow them to stay out of trouble. Then they also develop receptors that recognize nutrients and cause them to be engulfed and used to power the cell. This is the mechanism of basic stimulus-response.   The machinery gets a little more complicated, as stimuli cause more complicated reactions. What evolves next (by "next" I mean in intellectual terms, not necessarily temporal) are systems that allow perception of things at a distance. The reception of photons, of sound waves, of other complex stimuli, these allow reaction to aspects of the environment that aren't necessarily touching our little creature, now a bit more complex than a sac of protoplasm.  What is more complex than even this, is the ability to take these stimuli and not only react to them immediately, but to react to them predictively. Even sea slugs can do this, as the Nobel Prize-winning neurophysiologist Eric Kandel elegantly showed in his work on the underpinnings of memory. If you shock the slugs once, they will withdraw. If you shock the slugs repeatedly, they learn to withdraw even further to avoid the noxious stimulus. This is fundamental. Once you're there, it's not too far from classic, Pavlovian conditioning, then operant conditioning, and eventually what we have developed in our nervous systems - anticipation and prediction.  My understanding of the evolutionary goal of the nervous system (and this is a terrible teleological argument I'm presenting, I know) is to move from stimulus-response to prediction, which allows us to find food, avoid danger, fulfill all of those "id" needs. And the evolutionary apotheosis of prediction is to create an internal representation of the outside world equipped with a modeling function that somewhat accurately guesses "what if?" (We might call this "physics," which derives from the greek word for nature). Consequences of actions can be played out and the best action chosen from a set of possible actions. The "self concept" comes in as an avatar of the thinking creature in their own internal representation, alternately stable and changing. Our whole network of complex social interactions is informed by this self-concept, and it is that self-concept that we protect assiduously, employing various defense mechanisms to maintain a stable self in the presence of constantly changing external stimuli. We slowly learn new predictive "rules" and develop belief systems based on successful or unsuccessful natural and social experimentation.  And when we, through a short-circuit not yet elucidated (though PET scanning should do the trick in the next few years), misinterpret reality in an internally coherent way, that becomes delusion or hallucination. That's psychosis: when we lose the ability to continually test reality against our own internal perceptual world. Interestingly, it is very much possible to be psychotic and correct about the world (thanks to Dr. Eric Marcus for elegantly pointing this out) and, conversely, to have normal cognitive machinery and reality testing and be completely wrong. Hence politics.  N.  P.S. - Tonight I am making maraschino cherries from scratch, candying them with spices then soaking them with their syrup in brandy. Ready in two weeks. For those of you not into preserved foods (cured, smoked, pickled, candied, etc.), I pity you immensely and offer you recipes.  P.P.S. - For dinner tonight: Halibut sashimi, Nobu-style, and miso-glazed cod.  P.P.P.S. - Happy Memorial Day. You may now safely and dogmatically wear linen.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quote of the Day:  Attending Psychiatrist, straight-faced, driving up the FDR en route to crazy court:      "That's it, that's the Manhattan Psychiatric Institute. And right next to it, to the left, that's the circus."  Went to court today, where psychiatric inpatients who want to be set free from involuntary confinement get their chance in front of the judge. What a racket. If the psychiatrist wants them to stay, the court is going to take the word of the shrink over pretty much any patient. One patient today was particularly well spoken, and the judge commented on how well she had presented herself and what good progress she must be making, then denied the petition. The next case was a patient who sat there, seemingly dumbfounded, barely answering questions, the only thing going for him the fact that he had not yet hurt anyone while he had been an inpatient. The next patient didn't bother showing up. Enlightening, the experience was, to be sure.  A patient today with some sort of manic psychosis was feeling hypersexual and giddy. She couldn't keep a straight face, was flirting, asking me about my clothes, asking to see my ID, telling me how big my eyes were. I realized after a few minutes that I was uncomfortable and should leave. It's nice being flirted with, though, even if it's by psychiatric inpatients. Just a reminded of how important positive feedback is.  Ah, and my note to the wise: if you are ever made a psychiatric inpatient, tell every doctor, nurse, and aide that you have a mental disorder and want treatment, even if it's a total lie. Swallow your pills or spit them out, just make sure they think you think you're sick and want the medicine. It's one of the best Catch-22's out there - as long as you don't think you're sick, they'll say you have "poor insight" and keep you locked up, and if you say you're sick, then they'll lock you up and treat you. At least in the latter case you'll get better sooner.   N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, A Clockwork Orange are just two of countless examples in modern literature of the "radical" idea that treatment of mental illness is the ultimate deprivation of freedom, that what is left after the treatment (electroconvulsive therapy in the former case and Alex's aversive conditioning in the latter) is a hollow shell of the individual, lacking the humor, the rage, the human beauty that was described in such wonderful detail, despite the inherent flaws of the characters, pre-treatment.  The other common idea, possibly closer to the truth and certainly more popular in a society when postmodern cultural relativism has become the equivalent of what Freud was to the third quarter of last century - robbed of nuance and pared down to an easily digestible pop psychotheory - is that madness is a social construction more than a set of organic diseases with consistent pathophysiological features. There are many reasonably intelligent people who seem to believe this, among them the philosopher and patient advocate Thomas Szasz.   They argue bitterly with psychiatrists about depression, anxiety, and schizophrenia. Their prime example, though, is Attention Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD), which is a recently discovered/invented clinical entity, refined through the last few editions of the DSM - The Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Psychiatric Illness. One could point that, as recently as the DSM-III (we're on DSM-IV-R, the revised 4th edition, which is like DSM 4.5), homosexuality was considered a diagnosable psychiatric illness.   That ADHD didn't exist twenty years ago makes one wonder if it's just an invention of our society reflecting a change in behavioral norms over time. The discovery that ADHD kids had decreased activity in their brains and responded to stimulants by calming down and focusing and doing better in school lent some intellectual force to the argument for its existence. Unfortunately, as a recent, well-designed study showed, if you give normal kids speed, they study better, too. The fifty and sixty year olds, the ones who've just escaped raising kids with the ADHD label, will remember the kids in their classes who were a little out of control, the ones who got their knuckles rapped repeatedly with rulers, and they'll tell you that those kids just needed discipline and a society that didn't put up with that behavior. The argument continues that having a diagnosis for poorly behaved, spazzed out bratlings merely justifies and validates their behavior. If we look at behavior as a normative function, we must set arbitrary and arguable cutoffs for what constitutes disease and what constitutes normal, and the more we lend validity to ADHD, the more parents clamber to have their children labeled and medicated, and the more basically normal kids get a load of bennies in their lunchboxes next to the soggy tuna fish and Capri Sun. Numerous popular and academic theorists blame contemporary American culture’s frantic pace and tendency towards sensory hyperstimulation for the dwindling attention span of American youth. Psychiatrists would say that the environment is a trigger for the underlying pathology.  There are strong arguments to be made on both sides with ADHD; with schizophrenia, there are not. People with schizophrenia have a disease, a terrible disease, one that runs in families, one whose features are shockingly consistent between patients, and one whose treatment options are a thousand times better than they were in the time of Ken Kesey and Anthony Burgess. Schizophrenia is neither a social construction nor is its treatment an abrogation of freedom or form of thought control. This is not to say that the DSM is the bible, nor is it to say that depictions of modern psychiatry as more pharmacy than therapy are false, at least in the inpatient setting. And stories about schizophrenia are entertaining, seeming to represent the limits of human thought and experience, the way people might be if uninhibited and left to operate without the constraints of formal, logical thought. Madness is a beautiful and seductive thing for those whose lives haven't been personally ripped apart by it.   Having spent time with schizophrenics, I am impressed with how limited their world becomes within the confines of their disease. My psychotic patients lose the ability to express their emotions, miss out on the subtleties of expression and communication, wallow in a void of confusion and involution. Their impulsive actions are not those of an enlightened Nietszchean superman freed from the confines of morality (as one might read Alex’s antisocial indulgences) – they are the unfiltered directives of a will subjugated by animal fears. Though looking at psychiatric illness metaphorically can illuminate the often repressive confinements of social behavior, the sadness of the illness itself is often left in shadow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AARP is supposedly the largest circulation magazine in the country. I learned this last week from a copy floating around the pre-op area.   Just as a literary aside, when you say someone's "pre-op" in the hospital it means just that, while in my neighborhood (Chelsea), if someone's "pre-op" it's assumed they're a pre-op transsexual. I always found this funny, but haven't found any good way to take advantage of it in casual conversation. Hence mentioning it in the blog.  Anyway, the copy of AARP magazine had this great little bit in their health section on how to get the best service from your local emergency room, and it had such wonderful tidbits as telling the triage nurse that you know somebody on the hospital's board, describing your chronic diseases before telling them your new symptoms, and bringing reinforcements into the room with the triage nurse to add useful information to the process. How scary! At least the article did say to keep a list of your medications and dosages, copies of important medical documents, etc. on hand, to wait patiently and be friendly, and other helpful things to mitigate against their more obnoxious suggestions. One thing they said was that you'll get quicker service if you come in an ambulance as opposed to on foot, which is absolutely true, and you'll also get whatever stabilizing treatment you need at the outset instead of waiting to go through triage in the ER.  The truth is, if you want to get fast service in the ER, be really, genuinely, deathly ill. That's why it's an emergency room. AARP forgot to mention that.   The real way to
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paging through my journal, I found the following note from my medicine rotation, where I first got to practice doing blood draws and arterial sticks, starting IV's, etc., which is daunting at first (and remains so for some).  Names have been changed to protect the innocent. "Shirley" is the pseudonym of my medicine resident.  "9/18/04 Again I get the blood, start the IV. 4/4! I am da shit. Shirley called me a stud. If only I could find a date to these f***ing poetry readings." 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Overheard in OB/GYN grand rounds this morning, as part of a heated discussion of liability in a delivery where a "failed forceps application" was noted in the chart:   Senior attending: "Remember that every obstetrical adventure involves risk to three people: the mother, the fetus, and the doctor."  It was funny, and the discussions in grand rounds, which were a bit  acromonious and defensive, one might go as far as to say _litigious_, were very instructive. I've never been in a culture as fearful of litigation before, and it casts a pall over the whole field of OB/GYN, which is a shame, because I've loved this rotation. OB/GYN has, perhaps, the finest combination of medicine and surgery, of acute/emergent care (10-minute C-section, anyone?) and long-term relationships, of procedural care and big, bloody, technically challenging operations, but the fear of suits is palpable at every step of the way. My mother being a malpractice plaintiff's attorney, I see both sides of the issue. I've loved taking care of patients on this rotation, enjoyed working with the extremely talented residents and generous, energetic attendings. Nothing I've ever done in my life was quite as astouding as delivering my first baby on my first night of Labor and Delivery call. Wow.   Medical career decisions are not easy. People mistakenly think that, once you enter med school, you're just going to be a doctor, and that specialization just sort of takes care of itself. It doesn't. You're expected to decide what you want to do with your life before you've had any chance to explore your options fully. It's often based on a gestalt you get from talking to less than a dozen people, rotating on the service for a few weeks, and sniffing around the internet. There are stereotypes, which, at my institution, don't really hold up to scrutiny. I'm defying several even as I write this. Heh. I won't tell you which ones they are.  Anyway, despite how much I enjoyed this rotation, I am looking forward to being done with it. I am looking forward to sleeping more than 5 hours a night and having a break from 24 hour call. I won't say I've had enough female genitalia for a lifetime - I hope I never say that. But I certainly have had enough of them bleeding, dilated, or on the OR table for a while. Sorry to be graphic.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, as part of my OB/GYN rotation, I went to a hospital clinic that performs VTOPs, voluntary terminations of pregnancy. A young girl, who had used the morning-after pill, but unfortunately a month too late, came in at about 9 weeks. What does that mean? It means that there was a visible heart beating on transvaginal ultrasound, and that in the suction basin there was an intact little ribcage the size of a pea, a perfect hand the size of a snowflake. I nodded, staring at it. Acknowledge, move on.  The whole procedure was quick, as the attending said, "ten minutes, but five minutes of it is opening packages and getting ready." The only thing that hurt was the injection of a little local anesthetic. It was the least impressive and least invasive gynecologic procedure I had seen.   The staff was kind, professional, and despite the emotionally traumatic nature of what was being done, the whole episode was more to me like a trip to the salon. I don't think the patient will remember the experience with any pain or dissatisfaction. I don't think the experience will plague her as something she regrets. I have seen, in the past month, a hundred patients with obstetrical records that include abortions, and they seem to me to be almost par for the course, and more representative of a failure of birth control than a life mistake.   Today, we evacuated the uterus of a woman who'd tried to have babies by IVF - in vitro fertilization - only to have her fetus spontaneously die in utero. She had come in for a routine checkup, and the doctor just told her that he couldn't pick up a heartbeat. Given the option of letting the uterus clear itself naturally or having a D&C, she opted to have it taken out. I understand her feelings. When you are attached to what's in there, and what's in there dies, wouldn't you want out of you as soon as possible? This is what differentiates it from a VTOP in my mind, what places the experiences on completely different planes.   There was a great little piece in the New England Journal of Medicine about the history of the Hippocratic Oath, showing how it's changed over history. At my school, it's not worded in any way that could be construed as anti-abortion. This is true at many, if not most, american medical schools. The same little part of it, about hastening death, etc, would have applied also to euthanasia, which, during the time of Hippocrates, was a very popular practice. incidentally. Oh, it's all just a reflection of current mores, which people shout about as if those mores were unadulterable and unchanging, which is a load of crap. I'm not a political creature, but somewhat of a moral relativist stuck in a profession that professes to a moral high ground. There is so much inconsistency. What do you really believe in? What would you have your doctor believe about the sanctity of life?    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Let me give you a word of advice: never trust anything anyone ever says." - my intern, today in clinic.  She was pissed because somewhere in the chart, someone had written a pregnant patient's due date incorrectly and the patient had confirmed the incorrect due date, and the patient's entire exam was thrown off because of it and caused a shitload of problems. It took a half-hour to figure out what her actual due date was, and that's another half-hour's worth of frustration for every other completely deserving clinic patient, waiting out in the hallway, sitting uncomfortably in plastic chairs, enduring the ceaseless annoyance of not having private health care insurance.   Just one example. Thinking again - who owns the story? If I take a history, and the patient tells me something that she later recants and tells in a different way (i.e. she "remembered it wrong") to another member of the team, am I wrong, or is my history wrong? In medicine, the phrase that gets bandied about is "the patient is a poor historian." Bullshit. The person taking the history is a poor historian. The patient is a source. In the same vein, if I remember something incorrectly, or, for example, if I know that a patient's sodium was normal, having glanced at it on the computer but not having bothered to write it down because it was, in fact, normal, and the resident asks me, and I spout off a number that's close, in the normal range, but not the exact number, is that any worse than if I told the patient's history as told to me, and that history was incorrect? Does it matter that in one case the number is fabricated by the historian and in the other it's fabricated by the source and not researched or clarified properly?   We put together stories to connect disparate facts, and that the act of creating that narrative is inherently and necessarily creative; inevitably this leads to misrepresentation of objective truths, if there are objective truths to be had. Are there objective truths to be had? Doctors already use "evidence-based medicine" as a foil for the fact that our business of prognostication (which is what patients seek from their doctors when definitive treatment doesn't exist) is an uneasy melange of guesswork, experience, and pure prevarication. We work in probabilities because they don't nail us down. No one wants to be wrong, especially doctors, who are cautious and reserved, but still pride themselves on being right.  The flip side of this, refreshingly, is that I've encountered a number of excellent doctors in my training who exhibit an incredible humility. One of my mentors, my preceptor in gastroenterology, told our group of students how often his clinical judgment is wrong, and that if you have any pride left after being a doctor for five years, you're in the wrong profession. His words have stayed with me. I would love to be right in my hunches, to arrive at the correct diagnosis at the first guess, but there's a reason we don't just plug symptoms into a computer and have it spit out the diagnosis (contrary to the belief held by a friend of mine who went to medical school and then into investment banking when I first met him).  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The grading of heart murmurs is on a scale of I-VI. The official definition is that a I/VI is barely audible, II/VI is very soft, a III/VI is easily audible with a stethoscope, a IV/VI is loud, V/VI produces a palpable thrill, and VI/VI can be heard with the unaided ear. The saying goes, though, that a III/VI can be heard by the medical student, a II/VI can be heard by the resident, and only the attending physician can hear a I/VI.   If I hear a murmur in a patient, it doesn't really exist until the rest of the team has confirmed it. Every morning, I listen to the hearts, lungs, and bowels of each of my patients. When the team gets together to round, the same physical exam is repeated, in abbreviated fashion, usually by at least two residents and possibly the attending. Why? Don't they trust me? No. Okay, fine. I'm the medical student, and I can accept that, but even if I were the chief resident, the situation would be the same. We're a skeptical bunch. We rely on our own senses, and we seldom trust each other. We almost never trust the patient.  The patient, you see, may not have the vocabulary to describe her condition, her situation, her medications. She may not have the training to understand the significance of what we're asking her, so her responses to our questions could be imprecise, poorly remembered, extrapolated from her incomplete understanding.  Even as a medical student, my limited understanding of what the most important aspects of the history are predisposes me to misrepresentation and incompleteness. The medical narrative I create for my patient is fundamentally flawed and therefore must be crafted anew by each member of the team. If a tree falls in a forest and only the medical student sees it, the tree never fell, despite it being documented in the chart. If the patient tells you the tree fell, you nod politely and write it down, but you're going to request the forest record be faxed over or order a new set of complete tree counts.  The positive side of this is that there is tremendous oversight of my activities, and the patient has a number of vigorously independent and critical minds pondering her diagnosis and treatment who never take anything for granted; I get the advantage of hearing those independent and skeptical takes on the patient I am caring for, and this is the essence of my clinical education. The disadvantage is that the whole process is time-consuming, frustrating, and redundant.   I'm more interested in the inherent distrust of the patient, and the frankly political nature of the medical narrative. Who makes it, who owns it? I'm also interested in how that distrust plays into the odd doctrine of patient autonomy, where the will of the patient trumps the expertise of the doctor. The view that patients do not understand the significance of events in their medical history is widely held and not acknowledged as such, but it is the reason why we ask the questions that we do. If a young patient comes in feeling lightheaded and nauseated, we might ask them if they had been peeing, eating or drinking more than normal. Why? Becuase we're trained to immediately think of diabetes, and those are cardinal, presenting symptoms, but the patient won't give us that history unless we ask.   And along similar lines, patients who are noncompliant with medications and treatment plans hurt us, sadden us, frustrate us. Doctors are no longer in the position to impose their wills upon patients (though it happens. Take, for example, my stroke patient, half-paralyzed but fully capable of feeling pain. In order to manage his metabolic problems, we needed to agonizingly draw arterial blood every day. He screamed with his palsied face and withdrew by thrusting away those few muscles which consistently worked. We put him in restraints and went about our necessary tasks). Patients refuse blood draws, instrumentations, treatments, surgeries. We try to coax, bargain, and manipulate them into compliance. This works better in the hospital than outside.  Outside, we have AIDS patients who take antiretrovirals for just long enough to produce resistant strains of HIV, then stop taking them because they "feel good." A month later, they're in the hospital with a serious infection, utilizing vast resources, expensive equipment and medicines, and taking up the time of doctors who are already swamped with patients, all for something preventable. The waste is sad to see, but far sadder is watching self-destructive behavior in action. My attending at the time took a young AIDS patient aside after rounds and told him point blank that if he took his medicines and stayed on them, he would be healthy and live indefinitely, and if he continued to avoid taking responsibility for himself he would be dead in six months. The attending was firm - he had a look of anger on his face -  but he had been working with HIV patients since the 80's, and had seen so many similar cases, and I suspect that each case reminded him of how powerless he must have felt.  Medicine is in a power crisis. Practitioners are concerned about maintaining their autonomy and their position of respect in the face of increased workloads, decreased compensation, changing practice structures that treat physicians as shift workers in a service industry, and evolving doctrines that elevate the patient's opinion on how she should be medically managed to an exalted position. I have a theory that medical narrative is the battlefield on which this conflict between doctors and patients is being fought, that narrative is the soul of the conflict and possibly its answer. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone wanted to see it. Fine. You asked for it. Here it is, as originally published on the wonderful website, Surgery of Modern Warfare (see my list of links).  Click the link to see the poem. :)N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NICU = Neonatal Intensive Care Unit  "The goal at this institution is to support the natural drive to breathe, not to breathe for them."  A tour of duty in the hospital for the unborn, the lobster fleshed, the bruised and jaundiced, Twin A, cooking under the lamp, breathing through a thimble mask Twin B silent, no longer shuddering, red, as if he had been burned by the air of the world
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The world of the third-year medical student is not beautiful. You get bled on by your patients, shit on by your residents, ignored by your attendings, condescended to by the nurses, and graded by just about everybody, the weight of their evaluation inversely proportional to both a) how much time they've actually spent getting to know you and b) the esteem in which they hold you.  For periods of a month or so, you get thrust into a new milieu - psychiatry, surgery, medicine, OB/GYN, neurology, etc - and by the time you've started to learn how to play the game, it's time to switch. Your hours are long, your schedule capricious, variable, and often downright whimsical. You are expected to learn independently, which is manifested by the following typical encounter:  [leaving patient room] Student - How do you manage [insert patient disease]? Resident - That's a good question. Why don't you look it up tonight and give us a five minute presentation on it during rounds. Student - [mumbling while walking away] Thank you, O great one, for elucidating that important point of clinical management. I feel edified.  Resident - I'm sorry, did you say something? Student - No.  You are expected to be there before your residents, tagging along at their heels, and, if you're lucky and hard-working, they might take a few minutes to teach you something once in a while. You learn clinical management on the fly, listening, watching, working. Every piece of work you do that isn't total scut (take out that foley, draw those bloods, check how much urine she put out, run this form over to the next building, pick up coffee) is duplicated by the housestaff, so you don't even have the satisfaction of having your carefully written note having saved anyone any work. It's sad, demoralizing, difficult.  But is it _poetic_? Is it _epic_? Are there still stories worth telling? And why? Yes, yes, yes, and how.  Why? Why. Because last week I delivered a baby with my bare (well, gloved) hands. What entitled me? Paying $50,000 a year in tuition? All my diligent study of biochemistry, anatomy, pathophysiology? Honestly, everything I knew about childbirth at that point was taken from a twenty page chapter in a book called "Blueprints in Obstetrics" which I read over the course of an hour. I'm an ordinary guy thrust into extraordinary situations, given opportunities and responsibilities that most people will never have, for better or for worse. Yes, I wrote a poem about my cadaver. We don't need to go there.  Most of my third year is over, meaning that much of that initial excitement is over. It only gets harder from here, and the absolute newness of being blooded in the OR, of delivering the sort of bad news that no one ever wants to give, of bringing a baby into the world, is perhaps over. What comes next is time to chew on it, time to reflect, time to see if I can think about the way stories in medicine work, to see if I can use my experience as fodder for creative and critical work. Your mission, dear reader, should you choose to accept it, is to follow along, to ruminate with me, to tell me if I'm getting at something you want to see and read for something other than the vicarious experience of medical training.  If you want to reach me and let me know what you think of what I'm writing and saying, my email is doctorno@verticalmattress.com. If you find this blog and like it, let me know.  Much love,  Dr. No 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Look wise, say nothing, and grunt. Speech was given to conceal thought."  - Sir William Osler
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I took Isabel to see Aimee Mann in concert. I'd planned it for weeks and managed to keep it a secret until we actually entered St. Ann's Warehouse in DUMBO. I think there were signs outside, but she wasn't looking to ruin the surprise - she's a good sport. If it had been me, I would have scanned the newspapers and weeklies to figure out what possible entertainment fit what tidbits of description had accompanied the surprise. I'm a poor sport that way, doing what medical school has been training me to do: generate differential diagnoses.   When I'm not at work, I'd sort of like to be not working, but it doesn't always work out that way. Work, work, work - I can't even keep the word out of my sentences...  So we're at the concert, and there's a guy with an even worse bald spot than mine, though he's got to be around 50 years old, who's a bit disheveled and wearing a grimy thin t-shirt that says, "I won't engage in a battle of wits with an unarmed opponent" or something very similar.   ** sidenote: I can remember the Tegretol and Lithium levels of all my patients (WM: 4.3, 0.5, though 2.2 on admit, then 1.3, then 0.9); IL: 3.6, 0.2) from days ago, and I can't remember something far more clever and interesting. I can't remember people's names. I feel like medical training is bringing out or entraining some sort of autism in me **  Anyway, the guy starts talking to me, which in New York, is already a bit weird. I'm being polite, asking him what he does, and he says he's an artist and a writer, and I start paying more attention to the rhythms of his speech and they feel a little pressured to me. And I keep asking him polite questions, and he starts letting on that he's working on a book about Aimee Mann and an article that "expands and contracts" over time, that he hasn't actually talked to anyone about publishing it, etc.   So I think the guy must have been a fan of Aimee Mann for years. I ask. The first time he heard her was a year ago, and now thinks that she's the greatest musician of the 20th century, "The greatest since Wagner," on par with the only other great musicians of the century, George Gershwin and Jimi Hendrix. Okay.   So I keep talking, and he's willing to talk, and I'm fascinated, but I realize I'm essentially preoccupied with figuring out if he's actively psychotic and whether he has a mood disorder. I chide myself and then keep talking to him.  He's seen 17 Aimee Mann shows, and he's bought tickets for her entire tour. He's from New York but followed her down to Carolina for concerts last week. He's never spoken to her, and started saying that she's totally cut off from her fans, that she only puts out 10% on any given night, that she never recognizes her fans or becomes accessible to them. He chides her for this, exalting her and hating her. Really weird. He says he's been sadly disappointed with her recently because she's not being transcendent.  At one point he takes out of his pocket a flyer with a picture of Aimee Mann and a caption, "I think the greatest artist of the 20th century" or something similar (CR's complete blood count yesterday: 9.8/13.2/40.1/222 - ah, the autism again). And he's been independently plastering the neighborhood with these posters that he's made, to spread the gospel of Aimee Mann.  He also mentioned one time where he was on stage with her, where no security guard tried to get him off, where he just stood behind her and "stared at her ass." Then he shook her hand and said, "thank you," and got off the stage. I have no idea if this actually happened or not, but it was incredibly odd.  So, dear readers, that was my five-minute interview. What's your diagnosis?  My only saving grace in this was that I didn't ask him about his mood or if he'd heard voices.  I'm eager to hear what folks think...  N.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Click on the link above for a great true story about being an inpatient for a night at Bellevue by Stacy Pershall, on Mr. Beller's Neighborhood. Wow. This is exactly what it's like, except from the patient's point of view. Highly recommended.  In other news, two quotes from my Psych Attd. at a Hospital In New York, Dr. Hasan:  "If you want to see the undercarriage of any society, you need to work in the health care system."  No shit.  And, in terms of interpreting the history as told by a manic patient:  "I think the truth is somewhere between what he's saying and what I'm thinking."  Yep. Right on the nose.  Great doc. Right on the nose. N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So my best friend, Ben, is getting married this weekend. My other good friends, Matt, Gordon, and Tom, are also getting married. I'm sure all of my ex-girlfriends will be getting married soon, too, and I hope to god their husbands get them to sign pre-nups. They'll milk you dry, my friends - beware.   Sorry. They're perfectly nice people, if you get to know them, I'm sure.  Anyway, I've been busy psychoanalyzing myself, giving myself various psychiatric diagnoses, and intermittently sending off poems to be rejected by respectable journals to fill the time. After determining all of my character flaws, verging on personality disorders, I'm not surprised that the past couple of years have been trying times for the throngs of women throwing themselves, ill-advised, on my threshold.   Anyway, I've decided that, after all, I don't have any psychiatric disorder severe enough to warrant any medication other than alcohol and cigarettes, which is a relief, as I don't have enough time in the day for analysis. Can you imagine spending an hour, 3-5 times a week, lying on the couch free-associating. Though it may seem to a casual observer that this is what I do anyway, in five minute bursts, throughout most of the day, in fact my communications are part of a complex and fully articulated symbolic system which I learned from watching Animal Planet.  Okay, so it's an odd night and Psychiatry is getting to me. I have a schizophrenic patient who is just not getting better. Not at all. Probably a candidate for Rockland (and for anyone who wants to know what Rockland's like, read "Howl" by Allen Ginsberg). One of the saddest things I've experienced in medical school. Even when I had to give a patient a diagnosis of bladder cancer at the beginning of my third year, even when I saw patients dying of AIDS during my medicine rotation, at least they had their minds, at least they'd had time to be fulfilled, at least their existence wasn't a combination of confusion, doubt, and criticism of their uncontrollable behavior.  I think, every day, of how good I have it. I remember being taught about Abraham Maslow's pyramid of self-actualization by my high school guidance couselor, Sue Hershey. At the bottom of the pyramid are the needs of the id: warmth, shelter, food, water, security. The pure sustenance. Once those needs were fulfilled, then the next layer could be fulfilled, the needs of love and attachment and social support. Then came esteem needs: self-respect, respect for others, succces and empowerment in a career, fame, glory, recognition, attention, etc. At the top of the pyramid was self-actualization, the desire to grow, be independent, be at peace with the world, be creative and productive, etc. You couldn't rise to the next level if any of the lower level needs were unfulfilled. You can't worry about self-respect and self-esteem when you're unsure of your next meal, and you can't be profound and independent if you lack loving and supportive relationships. I see my psychotic patients stuck at the second level, and I see friends and loved ones stuck at a level below the top because of a lack of self-love. It's a powerful schema.   Wow. I spend hours every day thinking about this shit. When I was on Urology, I spent hours every day thinking about penises.  It's just what we do, y'know? Such a strange and diverse training. I'm scared at what med school is turning me into. In the words of the ancient hebrew sage: oy!  N.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Am I crazy? My attending thought so yesterday when I seemed to get along just a little too well with a patient who was somewhere between having a personality disorder and being certifiably loony. The patient was a kabbalist, meaning that she had studied (at an age considered by many to be far too young to handle the intensity of dedicated kabbalah study) the mystic numerology of the bible, the grand esoteric scheme of things as laid out by symbolic interpretation of the ancient hebrew text. Associated with her studies, she had had visions of the future, had experienced strange deja-vu and jamais-vu, had never heard voices but experienced the world as it was to be in no uncertain terms. She hadn't predicted 9/11 or been able to bet successfully on the world series, but she was had experienced a strange sequence of synchronicities. In the world of psychiatry, one might call them "ideas of reference," but then again they might just be synchronicities. And then we were talking and she started talking about San Diego, to a doctor she'd gone to who'd introduced her to kabbalah, and I held back from telling her that my sister lived in San Diego, fearing that she would have intuited some cosmic connection between us. Maybe we had a cosmic connection, which is why we seemed to get along so well.  So I grew up knowing a lot of people with strange beliefs, people who thought the human mind could be thought of like a computer and reprogrammed as such. I studied shamanistic religions, and even the pharmacology of their hallucinogenic potions. I had a neighbor who practiced Reiki. I sort of drew the line there. I have a limited tolerance for New Agey stuff, and absolutely reject shit like crystals and magnets and the (completely stupid) belief that herbal remedies beat out the western pharmacopeia. But I do believe in religious experience, in the collective unconscious, in the propensity of mild to moderate psychopathology to lead to creativity and wonder.   This woman confused me. So rational and so ecstatic! So willing to view the world through oddly-tinted glasses, and I was willing to go right along with her. But why the hell was she in the hospital? Some strange disconnect. I have no idea what was happening. She was a Lubavitcher jew, converted from some unknown eastern european christianity, and my father had always told me about those people ("they keep a suitcase packed with clothes in case the messiah comes in the night," he said, rolling his eyes). I am always skeptical, always rolling my eyes at the world, just like my father, but until this rotation, I rarely felt the urge to really pass judgment on people just because their beliefs were outlandish.  Now I'm making that decision - crazy or not? - as if I am qualified somehow to be the arbiter of sanity. Are you fucking kidding me?   The Fool on the Hill 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This from my sister, the busty pediatrician:  Hey Dr. No,  I just love your writing style! I'm at work, so I can't read all of your postings, but I do have a comment--- SCRUBS DO NOT FLATTER EVERY BODY TYPE.  I look terrible in scrubs!!!!!!!!! They are not built for short, busty women with length-challenged torsos! No-- they make me look like a big blue muffin! The scrubs act like a mu-mu and hit the bust then fall without, never showing the world that there is a waist below the shelf of my bust! And heaven forbid that you are big busted, short-waisted AND a bit hefty around the middle-- then there is no hope for any semblance of attractiveness or self cofidence in scrubs! No- They are built for tall, muscular men, tall lanky men or tall skinny women. Scrubs are the clothes of the devil-- scrubs be gone!!!!!!!!!!! love -Em  In response to my sister: No! You're wrong! Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong! How you like them apples?  N.  P.S. - Okay, so you're right. Scrubs only drape right on stick figures, but the big OR techs with guts big enough to serve as a tray-table somehow seem to look just fine. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was on call yesterday in the Psych ER from 8am until nearly midnight (the resident let me off a little early, kind and wonderful she is). I got to wear scrubs all fucking day. I love wearing scrubs.   1)Scrubs are excellent because they're cool and I produce heat like a furnace.  2)They're fashion classics, always appropriate, always stylish, accomodating all body types, ubiquitous but individual. In the hospital, washed-out blue is the new black. You can layer them over a t-shirt or wife-beater, under a white coat, and you can wear them home if you're feeling tired enough that you're willing to ignore how tacky it is to wear scrubs outside the hospital (so gauche). 3) You can write on them. By the end of the night, my scrub pants were covered in patient phone numbers, lab values, and record locators. 4) They are expendable. You can get them wet, bloody, shitty, pissed-on, and vomit-soaked, and it doesn't matter because there are scrub machines in every building and laundry bins in every room. Of course, the occasional shower or scrub-down helps, especially when your suicidal HIV- and Hep C-positive alcoholic psychotic decides to spew forth a combination of excrement and invective on you. 5) Super comfy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going through withdrawal.  I haven't touched a patient in almost two weeks. I've temporarily retired my stethoscope - it's hanging on a hook next to my winter coats.  I haven't worn scrubs, set foot in an OR. Oh, I miss it.   Psychiatry is riveting in its own way, but I like knives. I really do.   I think working as a restaurant cook was the first step in my transformation into a surgeon. The hours were long, the work was a combination of the physical and the finessed. In ten minutes, I'd chop up a crate of onions, carrots and celery for stock; or I'd decapitate and dismember twenty spiny little lobsters with a 10-inch chef's knife (and don't let anyone tell you length isn't important...). Then I'd spend a half-hour cutting vegetables into 1/8th inch perfect cubes for garnish. This was prep cooking. On the line, I'd be in the thick of it, managing 15 different orders at a time, stressful even if you're a fry cook or making salads.  If you find 14 hour shifts where you don't sit down once, where you emerge sweaty, bloody, dirty, and productive the most exhilarating sort of fun you can imagine, then maybe surgery is for you too. I loved every fucking minute of it. The creation of something beautiful, something real, from its bare elements. The combination of creativity, intellectualism (the subtle chemistry of cooking always appealed to the scientist in me), and physical skill suited me more than any previous endeavor. Once I got into the OR and saw the similarities, I couldn't imagine doing anything else.  Oh, and did I mention that I like knives
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing is more sad to me than patients crying. No one should leave a hospital without hope, but on certain days the ward breeds despair, when you look out the window on a sickly, overcast day and think, "it's the same out there as it is in here," when the whirr of carts, beds, machines, chatter all conspire to distract you. It's those days when I feel most ineffectual, when the patients seem most lost, when I can't imagine anyone getting better or leaving.  A patient of mine has left every conversation with me over the past week in tears. I've never had that effect on anyone. This is the same patient who was giggling and flirtatious a week before, psychotic and hearing voices. She has so much to be sad about. I guess her tears mean that she's getting better.  N.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ladies and Gentlemen of the Jury,  It seems as if there are hundreds of thousands of preventable medical deaths every year! Enough to fill three jumbo jets which would ceremoniously crash to the ground every other day for five years.  This study comes out of a company that rates hospitals called  urlLink Health Grades  . I invite you to check it out and see how woefully misleading and inadequate a study it is. I despise people who publish misleading data, because so few people actually go and read the studies to critique them, so they take figures as facts when they're actually poor estimates derived from shoddy data and asinine methodologies.  And then Forbes' HealthDay reports on it:  urlLink http://www.forbes.com/lifestyle/health/feeds/hscout/2004/07/27/hscout520330.html   The study, which I suggest you read, basically counts the dead and then sees if there were any "patient safety incidents" associated with the case. They claim hundreds of thousands of these incidents (true) and then claim that these incidents may have been responsible for these deaths. They make the point of saying "potentially" implicated in patient deaths and "potentially preventable deaths," but the implication is clear  The most common safety event they reported is called "Failure To Rescue," which, as the Forbes article weakly points out, is not accepted as a preventable cause of death. Failure to Rescue means any complication in any patient that could have been picked up and treated but which wasn't. What the category does not exclude are patients with Do Not Resuscitate orders, whose deaths are technically preventable but not the result of medical error, and patients with terminal cancer, HIV, or multi-system failure. It only excludes patients transferred from nursing homes and acute care facilities, which helps but doesn't compensate for the fact that there is not, in fact, a failure to diagnose or treat adequately these patients. It only says that patients potentially on their deathbeds potentially die. I refer you to the AHRQ PAtient Safety Indicators documentation:  urlLink http://www.qualityindicators.ahrq.gov/downloads/psi/psi_guide_rev1.pdf , which the news media seems to have neglected to read.  The study authors also think that decubitus ulcers ("bedsores") are a directly attributable cause of death, when the truth is that most hospitals actively check for them, and thus the prevalence has increased markedly, which, if you were shortsighted and irresponsible, you might confuse with a real effect.  There are so many reasons why this study is shit. I refer you to   MedPundit   for several of them.  Someone, please, stop the insanity! Yes, there are lots of medical errors, and there are lots of bad outcomes, but it's far less epidemic than these alarmists think. I believe that the Institute of Medicine study is a good one and highlights problems, but their estimates aren't all that conservative, despite the quote in the Forbes article.  Cheers, N.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a biostatistics exam tomorrow. Ever since third year ended, I've been craving the OR again, craving patients. As soon as my research studies get going, and the IRB gives me the okay, I'll be seeing patients again. I'm looking forward to being a student doctor again, writing notes and orders, yelling at nurses (just kidding. Around nurses I'm sweet, gentle, sheepish, manipulative - a pissed off nurse can and will make your life hell), talking to patients, drawing bloods. Despite being excited about my research and about several writing projects I am germinating, I think I picked the right profession after all. God, does biostats suck ass!  How grim it must be to be a statistician! Poor bastards. They probably sit at home at night, in the dark, wishing they'd been shitty at math and studied, like, cultural anthropology or something.  Missed the entire Kerry speech while studying. I hear he's developed an agenda. Some sort of plan for America. Impressive concept. Would love to see it on paper. Does one have to be a big fan of platitudes to watch the national conventions, or can you be, like, a casual fan?   Just thinking: I'm always saddened that the democrats, being so closely associated with the bar, are against tort reform in general. I don't know where the impetus for change in the way medical malpractice is handled is going to come from, despite every doctor I know (and even some malpractice attorneys, interestingly enough) throwing their hands in the air. And OB/GYN's? I hear their insurance is more than their salary - sounds like hospital economics to me.  N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Russian Square, in sepia  “A dove eats wheat from my hand,” what grain in that picture marks it as such? -- how  the possibilities of each silver crystal are reduced. Like the eye, the receipt of light foments revolution, but dead.  You can only kill more, until the suffusion of light becomes the saturation of the film.  The picture’s burnt edges are another loss entirely and with my memory fades the illusory subjects:  Akhmatova, poet of a thousand suicides; Planck, where velocity is new and the relation begins.  I thank all the builders, the makers of theory to crack whips at my dinosaur feet –   do we remember who we are when we sleep –  they beg their questions with teeth,  And Anna who feeds me words and whispers to ruffle my feathers.   (I was reminded today of an old friend I'd never actually met who said she liked Akhmatova and the other Russian suicide poets. When I read Akhmatova, I thought that each poem was a little suicide for her, which, in a way, is a certain kind of release. This is a response to her poem "Loneliness," dated Summer 1914.)
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Blog is displaying weirdly. Sorry. Scroll down if you're having trouble.  In the meantime, check out  urlLink The Lingual Nerve.  Interesting writing on medicine, and it's a collective blog. click on the title of the blog entry to go there. :) N.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Richard Selzer, from The Lancet, 1/2003:  "Every doctor is a diarist who keeps a record of his patient's illness, writing down after each visit the vital signs, physical findings, and the patient's symptoms. Such 'keeping' seems to me a higher genre of writing than mere storytelling, for the life at stake is not that of the author. Perhaps my best writing was done in hospital charts, where the patient is the hero, whose very existence is a work of art. It is the only writing I have done that is devoid of the vanity of author and the pomp of language."   I read Letters to a Young Doctor years ago, or actually, I read about ten pages and put it away because I found it to be overwrought. I just ordered Selzer's book from Alibris (as well as USMLE Step 2 review) and plan on working through it and perhaps shopping out a review. I mean, he used to be a surgeon, I'm going to be a surgeon, we both write. We've got, it seems, a lot in common.  I already am taking umbrage at the above quote, though, which I think is bullshit, the part about 'keeping.' If you think databasing, making inventories, and actuarial science trumps storytelling, then I would wory about your writing. Which is not to say that the charted medical narrative is not a place for art and skill, but to deny chart writing is a creative, narrative enterprise is to claim that the medical observer is objective and that the chart has no purpose but to record objective observations.   Think how the patient's story differs from the story recorded in the chart (if you've seen a chart). Think how the story of an illness is profoundly different when told by the patient than when told by the physician. Notions of agency come into play here in a big way - the doctor, and particularly the surgeon, pays very little attention to the subjective experience of the patient except in as much as he deems necessary to elicit a history that points towards a diagnosis and intervention. In that respect, the physician creates the story by asking pointed questions, and then he creates the story by writing it in an official record, and he creates the story through the route of intervention he chooses. The patient's story, in terms of the hospital chart and in terms of his function within the hospital, is largely passive, is limited by the scope of his interactions in the stimulus-deprived hospital environment, by a typical lack of understanding of the disease process and its management, and often by the effects of the disease itself.  I won't go down this track now.  What I object to is Selzer bantering on about lives being at stake, the patient as hero, and the wonders of the medical chart. Here is a rampant narcissist, though I mean this in a psychoanalytic way, not an inherently pejorative way, someone who derives strength from the way external objects reflect upon him, someone whose prose style is pretensiously spattered with unnecessary literary allusion, filigree and flourish (someone who uses the word "shall" when he could use "will" - he's not that old. Barely older than Updike, and younger and less dead than Hemingway). And what's nice is that he realizes how pompous his writing can be and he reflects that his chart writing has a lack of self-absorption and a lack of pomposity absent in his literary writing. But then he ruins it by elevating charts to some incredibly profound level when it's really just that the chart isn't so much about _him_. And to talk about patient as hero is to talk about the surgeon as deity in a way, and I think that's a little disingenuous.  Despite all of this, I actually like Selzer, and I get a sense that he's a thoughtful, reforming narcissist. He is someone I might learn a great deal from. The first stories in his newest book, mostly diary entries, are pretentious but charming and you can feel the nostalgia in the words. You get a sense, less of a childhood than of an older man reflecting on his childhood, a man inventorying his memories and convincing himself of the richness of the life he has led. It is sad but heartwarming.  N.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah yes, Dad brings on the pretense alert as usual. :) My father, who I've guilt-tripped into reading my blog, told me that the use of "acinar" in the poem, Breast Exam, that I posted earlier (I would link, but just scroll down - it's easier), was pretensious.  Acinar is important here. Perhaps I could have used something more like "glandular" but I don't like the feel of that.  The word means "as in a cluster of berries," like grapes or currants,  or like the small, individual rounds of a single blackberry or raspberry, but is used in medical parlance for the blind end of a secreting duct, where often the process of secretion occurs. In medicine it connotes microscopic size, and its botanical roots imply a relation to fruit, which I thought was interesting.  I chose the world to emphasize that I was looking at individual duct systems and not the breast as a whole, and if I had taken it out, it would have sounded like "flasks" was referring to the entire breast as some sort of knobbly wineskin, which is not at all what I was getting at. If you've ever looked at a mammogram, it's the structure of those duct systems and connective tissue (Cooper's Ligaments, thank god for them, and cheers to Dr. Ernest April, my mentor, who showed me many wonderful pictures of them) that form the "hidden topography" that I'm talking about.  But my point is this: I still contend that big words, unfamiliar words, and, specifically, medical words, are not only not pretensious but necessary. Without using them either out in the open, out of context, out of bounds, or somesuch, they are dead outside the hospital, and I think they're too wonderful to resign to that fate. I don't care if someone has to look it up, they're probably not going to, and they'll miss something. Half the words I see in Wallace Stevens poems, well a few of them anyway, are foreign to me, and that doesn't make him pretensious.  Oh, and for years I've never known whether to spell it "pretensious" or "pretentious." Any comments from the peanut gallery?  N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my hands they might have been limitings of a hundred scars; less a birthright  than those things acquired in your long life given to my counting, the natural heapings and torsions,  infoldings of your acinar flasks, that once held a singular wine, that once  were drunk from, that always have been in some way vessels for experience,   their stunning, hidden topography the sole diagnostic certainty.   N.  P.S. - this one, newly edited, from my first year of medical school, back when everything was new and each touch was more intimate, as if each patient were a new affair.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      _Every aspect of this operation is minimally invasive._  We know that at this very moment your language becomes concentrated in a single point, despite the now widespread recognition of the subcutaneous.   Having conducted the research, we know it is unequivocal: The natural project of the machine does not escape our attention.  As a group, our habits have lacked appropriate candor.  We apologize for your misgivings. There is no pink slip.  We do not mean to imply misdeed or redundancy.  There is, simply put, a better way with less scarring.  There is no reason not to react to a recorded voice  in the same way as you would a live one.   We have eliminated your wardrobe from our analysis as an outlier.  Our contextual imaging faithfully recapitulates your internal markings and accounts.   For you, it is certainly time to take up an alternative process of discovery. It is suggested that a sharp object, inserted obliquely to the skin will be bloodless evidence enough.   All other things can be and have been imitated by polymers.  The substitute for language in this case is a solution  of electrolytes in concentrations similar to that of seawater, itself similar to that of human blood and used, historically, for transfusion. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night I went with Isabel to a MediaBistro party, which was basically a lot of people in publishing, or struggling to get into publishing, or struggling to freelance, or somesuch. We got there late, were immediately accosted by strange and fascinating people, and by the time I had recovered from the initial shock of being let out of my cave, the drink specials were over. In any case, I got an email from the party planner, which I responded to. Names have been changed.  &nbsp; Original message: From:&nbsp;Sylvia [ urlLink mailto:sylvia@mediabistro.com ]  Sent: Thursday, July 22, 2004 2:35 PM  To:&nbsp;Doctor No&nbsp; Subject: party inquiry follow-up &nbsp;  Hi Noah: How did you like last night's party at Viscaya? I try and get some feedback from guests after the events. Cheers,&nbsp;Sylvia  My Response:&nbsp; Hi Sylvia,  Itemized Feeback on the Party:  1) The party was a great time, overall.  2) I found myself cornered only twice by scary people (one was promoting her science fiction book and was essentially hypomanic for 15 minutes, the other was just, well, scary.)  3) In 90 minutes, I met about a dozen people, talked to six of them for at least ten minutes, and ended up with one business card but also brought one person I met to Mullen's Bar for post-party drinks, which turned into a party of four MediaBistroists, which turned into a bit of a drunken party, with raucous talk and eventual infiltration by a couple of Swedes from LA, which, as we all know, is basically bound to happen at Irish pubs.  Incidentally, the way I met this person was that I came up to their group of people at about 8:45 and said, "Hi, I'm not in publishing, and I'm here with my girlfriend who's, like, talking to people in publishing, and I told myself that I was going to come and talk to at least one more group of people before I left," and it worked like a charm.  4) Venue - great space, but the drink specials didn't last very long, and at 8:30 I had a ten dollar bourbon and a seven dollar beer, which was lame for a private party.  5) Name Tags - great to have, but the company name should be bigger because otherwise you're totally obviously squinting and staring at people, mostly women, mostly at boob level. Which is something that men do, naturally, but we try to be a little more subtle about it. Also, there are lots of people who read a lot whose eyes are failing them and they have to really squint at the tiny writing and I kinda feel bad for them.   Cheers,  N.   In other news, I have been obsessed today with my new Koh-I-Noor Rapidograph pen that I started using today. I've been writing in my journal in what is approximately 6-pt font, the pen is that precise and fine. I love it. And the fact that I seem to be able to write in legible 6-pt font makes me a little more confident that I have the capacity to do microvascular surgery.  N.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Isabel was not feeling well today, and in an email she questioned the usage of the words "nauseous" versus "nauseated." In my previous career as a snarky militant grammarian, I remember spending a lot of time over a toilet bowl thinking about this. I wrote her back what I remembered, but I wanted to get an expert opinion, so I wrote two experts: William Safire, the NYT columnist, and Bill Walsh, copy chief at the Washington Post. I await their response. What I wrote to them sounded something like this:  Nauseous vs. Nauseated vs. Nauseating. I was always under the impression that "Nauseous" meant something along the lines of "inducing nausea." One could not feel nauseous, though many claim they do, but they could feel nauseated. But then "nauseating" is in seemingly broad usage as a stand-in for the proper use of "nauseous." Do you have thoughts on this?  For my own part, I like "vomitous" which, ambiguous as it is, captures that essential quality of vomit, that it is both the final common pathway of nausea as well as a potent inducer of nausea in others.   I welcome any and all thoughts. N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was the second night in a row I was out until 4am. I woke up this morning at noon barely able to walk and completely unable to keep anything down. Isabel spoon-fed me Emer'gen'C raspberry fizzy vitamin drink. I left her apartment diaphoretic and nauseous. Came very close to pulling the trigger, as they say, knowing I'd feel better if I did, but I took a shower instead and slept for another four hours, waking every few minutes to try to drink down an advil and a sip of coffee (trying to avoid caffeine withdrawal headache).  Thinking of physiology the whole time. In the shower, thinking about my headache and how, if the shower's hot, it'll cause cutaneous vasodilatation which will decrease venous return and cause a compensatory increase in heart rate which (and this is where it breaks down, my thinking) just can't be good for me right now. Worried that I'm so dehydrated I'm going into renal failure because I haven't peed in four hours, then I pee and it's all good again. Thinking about how, if I threw up, I'd eventually lose enough acid and electrolytes to go into a metabolic alkalosis, for which I would compensate by breathing slowly so as to retain carbon dioxide. Then I went to sleep and took a few advil and it was all good again.   So last night at the Fleming concert, and they headlined the Mercury Lounge, which is impressive for a band made up of mostly surgical housestaff, there were about a hundred people there, and I think most of them were either in the Neurosurgery or Orthopedics residencies at Columbia. The Neurosurgeons at Columbia are not the bowtied, gawky, severe, Harvey Cushing neurosurgeon types. Basically, they're more Ortho than Ortho, though Ortho's pretty Ortho, too, if you know what I'm saying. If you don't, fine, and no harm done. But it's, like, soooo true. Anyway, props to the resident crew for coming out in force - when was the last time sixty MD's took over the Merc? Probably never happened before.  N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a list being published in McSweeney's next month! Very minor, I assure you, but it involves the most inappropriate things I've overheard in my medical training thus far. It's amusing. Anyway, click the link above to go to the McSweeney's Lists, which are hilarious. N. &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night - out until midnight or slightly thereafter, meeting some of the MFA poets, incoming and returning. This morning, in for orthopedic grand rounds at 7:30am, and therefore up at 6am, as it takes an hour to get up to the medical school. If I had been ambitious about it, I would have been in at 6am for fracture conference.   It's a treat to be up early, working hard, knowing, somehow, that if you don't get the work done, no one's going to pick up your slack. It's fulfilling knowing that you're working hard, or harder; that you're being productive, that you're getting things done. That work ethic and sense of personal sacrifice is oddly motivating. There's a sad aspect to it, how it can be so egotistical to always want to work hard, how the expectation is foisted on those in medicine and becomes self-fulfilling and then sustaining. I read a study in one of the big orthopedic journals today evaluating psychological well-being of ortho residents and faculty. Psychiatric morbidity was directly proportional to number of hours worked. It's that simple. The word thrown out in the study more times than I can count was "depersonalization," the feeling that your sense of self is eroding, threatened, or absent, that "you" are not really "you" at all, if you're even anything. But you're there, in the hospital, working, all the time. One's sense of self seems always threatened in medicine, and the training itself dehumanizes you and makes you a walking medicine machine but at the same time makes you utterly dependent upon the approval and validation you get from your patients, your attendings, your staff. And it can be devastating to suffer disapproval - take, for example, the shock to a doctor's ego when he or she gets sued. On some rotations where the number of suits brought against doctors was higher, the ego-protections - the pure strength and recalcitrance of their defense mechanisms - were an order of magnitude greater than those of the primary care or, say, urology attendings.   I found each of my rotations fascinating in their own right, but let's just say I still have welts from a few. Don't confuse my analysis with bitterness - I love what I'm doing, but I'm scared of the way it's changing me inside, apprehensive even more of what I might become during my residency. Would I do anything different? Well, I do things a little differently anyway, and I wouldn't give up my other loves, but I would never give up on medicine.  Going back to my original thought, the French take the whole month of August off as a culture (who tends the cheese shops?). The Europeans have much more paid vacation than we do, have a vastly circumscribed work week compared to the 60+ hours habitually worked by ambitious American professionals. Residents in Europe don't work more than 50 hours a week, whereas we only recently have laws reducing our hours to 80/week.  And one of the undergrads working in the lab is looking at his fall class schedule. Classes on Tuesday and Thursday. The rest of the week free. Ah, if only I had a few weeks like that! I was talking to him about work ethic. I said, look, there are things that are important to me - having an emotional life, an intellectual life, a creative life; spending time with family; partaking in the wonderful artistic pulse of the city; my hobbies - my cooking, my running and climbing and hiking; taking time to see the world. We're going to die younger, us Americans, us doctors, and we're going to die unrequited, having only that sense of beaten-in commitment to being constantly at work to show for us, which isn't a commitment to patient care per se but a commitment to being available to all, all the time, and by the time we're in our 50's and no longer taking insurance because the reimbursements aren't high enough to justify our time, we'll be rickety old bodies trying to make up for lost time, seeking some experiential fountain of youth, licking the wounds of our disenchantment, burnout, spiritual void, and barely known families. Sounds great, right?  This has been my brief break from work to be cynical.  It's also true that as soon as I'm around patients, none of this seems to matter, which is part of its danger - if you really like helping people, you become hobnailed and hamstrung by that inclination, it becomes duty and obligation and then inescapable, even as you watch other aspects of your life spiralling downward. I've seen it happen to people close to me. I advocate a balanced life - if that's even possible in the climate of medical rhetoric and politics. We'll see soon enough, won't we?  N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Click on the above title to go to a New York Times article from yesterday by Bruce Weber. The gist is that an NEA survey of some 17,000 people, and I don't know anything about the methodology (newspaper articles make it impossible to critique research studies), said that people are reading less and less, and that people are really reading less literature, drama, and poetry, despite Oprah's book club.  A relevant excerpt:  'Still, in a world where information is more readily available than ever, where people know more than they ever have, and where visual acuity is becoming ever more crucially utilitarian, it is worth asking: What, if anything, does literature's diminished importance to Americans represent? The study has already produced conflicting reactions.  "It's not just unfortunate, it's real cause for concern," said James Shapiro, a professor of English at Columbia University. "A culture gets what it pays for, and if we think democracy depends on people who read, write, think and reflect — which is what literature advances — then we have to invest in what it takes to promote that."  On the other hand Kevin Starr, librarian emeritus for the state of California and a professor of history at the University of Southern California, said that if close to 50 percent of Americans are reading literature, "that's not bad, actually."   "In an age where there's no canon, where there are so many other forms of information, and where we're returning to medieval-like oral culture based on television," he said, "I think that's pretty impressive, quite frankly." Mr. Starr continued: "We should be alarmed, I suppose, but the horse has long since run out of the barn. There are two distinct cultures that have evolved, and by far the smaller is the one that's tied up with book and high culture. You can get through American life and be very successful without anybody ever asking you whether Shylock is an anti-Semitic character or whether `Death in Venice' is better than `The Magic Mountain.' "'  And my response here is simple: a return to culturally-valued high(er) art. We, we being readers, literary folks, those who are "socially engaged," and those in the media with any sort of influence, need to create a need for literature that wasn't previously there. It's the way advertising works - insidiously, surreptitiously, subliminally. We can't bemoan the state of affairs, because no one gives a shit. We're preaching to the chorus, and the chorus is yawning. Evidence of irrelevancy is exactly what the conservative establishment wants to use as ammunition for their constant chipping away of NEH and NEA funding for valuable projects.   It's exactly like dating, or approaching women in bars. Let me explain. Women pass over totally nice guys all the time. Why? Because they don't have that edge, because they don't present themselves as someone worth pursuing. The old truism about attractive girls going for the asshole guys - why? Because they're exciting, because they're cocky, because they're a little dismissive, that is, because their attitude adds value. You don't have to be short in supply in order to be high in demand. What I'm saying here is that literature needs to be sure of itself without being arrogant, needs to perceive itself as cool and desirable and convey that image to consumers of commerical pabulum. Genre tends to do this well, as do all niche products, but they remain, perpetually, niche market products with limited appeal.   Literature tends to be viewed as rarified, difficult stuff. Poetry even moreso. Artists perpetuate this by being aloof, inaccessable, and wedded to their own narrow cultural milieu. Sure, people will always denigrate the populist and popular writers, but the truth is that the Dan Browns, Steven Kings, Danielle Steeles, and Michael Crichtons of the world reach more people than the "writers of serious fiction" combined, even if you make allowances for breakthroughs like Franzen.  So, what am I saying to serious artists - stuff your jock straps? Wear a push-up bra? Yeah, well kinda. It's more than that, though. What I'm talking about it image elevation through attitude change. It's bootstrapping - my favorite word (ask Isabel) - change effected through a reconceptualization of the self that begets the emotional responses that you seek from others. Act the way you want to feel and people will react in a way that enforces that act and produces the feeling until the act ceases to be an act and becomes simply a manifestation of the feeling.  Poets, artists, writers, oh you marginal figures of the distressed and disenfranchised literate illuminati: you are the movie stars you always wanted to be, you are the captains of the football team, the most popular girls in school, the hip, hot supermodels of the mind and soul! Bring it on!  N.   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No one in New York slept well  in the subway it was clear the lack of buoyancy  each traveler aware of the precise distance to the place he or she was going  aware of a sudden anonymity since the beginning of the  morning commute, our ashen faces, our small rolls of fat, our pockmarks and thinning hair, shared  like we share an atmosphere like we each consume our shards of dust when the light catches an angle  what was on our collective sleepless mind? Yesterday we worked too hard Yesterday we were stretched thin Yesterday we suddenly wondered 	what planetarium was collapsing over our heads  Which is not that it was dark but that  streetlamps obscured the margins of the dark   sheet of sooty concrete, its punctuations absent in the glare. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I never made it to my point in the last entry, which was that, in the B&N, there was a decently large poetry section and there were only three books by Ashbery, none of them his best. I was dismayed. There are five thousand copies of Patricia Cornwell novels and stacks of Clinton's bloated memoir nearly the size of his ego but there are three tiny books by perhaps the greatest living poet in America!   If people read more Ashbery, they'd be better people. There were a half-dozen books by recent poetic luminaries (i.e. recent poet-laureates and those few lucky ones who have gotten some media exposure and fought back the instinct to pull a Franzen and say 'fuck off' to the establishment) such as PInksy, Collins , Gioia, Oliver, etc (though I may be mistaking a name or two) about whether poetry has meaning anymore, or silly introductions to poetry that focus, as usual, on the elements of metrics that would put anyone to sleep and only briefly acknowledge the sophisticated plays of meaning, quasi-ironies, the mouth-feel of language, the breathtaking vistas of the mind, the subtle symbolisms (as opposed to knock-you-over-the-head Eliot-isms and such) - the things that make poetry worth reading and, even more, worth writing. These heartfelt but hobbled excuses for accessible poetry books! I can just hear the editor in my head, hacking good intentions into pabulum with the hatchet of market forces.  The top selling book of poems is edited by Garrison Keillor. Wobegon poetry, where every child is above average and every poem swiftly offers up its deepest treasures like a two-bit ho.  I fucking love John Ashbery. Reading him makes me feel whole, makes me feel that a state of internal conflict, mixed signals, and curious reflection is the nature of the soul, which suits me just fine. And when I read C.D. Wright, I feel a yearning that grabs my bowels and threatens to tear them out of my body, a rending love, and also a quiet one. There are others - Jorie Graham (brings out my inner Joni Mitchell), Timothy Donnelly (jealousy, I admit it.), even, as I go back, Ginsberg, Whitman, Rimbaud, Akhmatova, Stevens. But in the reputations of the older poets gets lost the contemporary poetic soul, poorly represented in the stacks and relegated to our KGB bars and lit program touring circuits or, worse, to Yaddo. Ah, the poetic life. William Carlos Williams had it right - don't quit your day job.  And to anyone who reads this, please, for the love of whatever it is you hold as holy, read "Self-Portrait in a Convex Mirror."  N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was in the B&N the other day returning a book. What happened was this: it was a good book, William Gibson's new(ish) _Pattern Recognition_, which is, like all of his books, a hip, stylish, stylized, cyberpunky technothriller. I had gotten 120 pages into it during my trip to Southampton, and then, on the Jitney home, I was ready to curl up with it for two hours, since my girlfriend was sitting in the adjacent row from me with her school friend and there was no clandestine entertainment to be had across the aisle.   I read, and it is riveting. Mystery, suspense. Terse language. Lots of sentence fragments. Odd details. And then, as my eyes move from the bottom of the left page to the top of the right, something happens. I must have forgotten what I was just reading (happens all the time). I try it again. No go. I am confused. My eyes eventually drift to the pagination. 120 on the left. 89 on the right. Hmm. So I flip forward, and the entire next section is a repeat. And when I get to page 120, it goes to page 153. I am so pissed. Thirty perfectly good pages are missing, and they just happened to be the ones I wanted to read.  I suck it up, start poking at my girlfriend across the aisle, take out my laptop and idly browse through poems, but I am annoyed. So I take it back to the B&N where I bought it and they give me another copy for free, which is the least they could do.   But I start paging through the books, and I'm, like, wow, there are so many friggin' books in the bookstore! I go through the remainders of books that didn't sell, I look at new hardcovers that will soon be remaindered (the fate of much brilliant new writing - it falls like trees in a forest with no one around, sort of like this blog), and I start paging through architecture books by Rem Koolhaas that have explanatory books of essays about them telling you how important they are despite the fact that they're so completely inscrutable as to be gibberish. I almost bought one to use as a hip paperweight/coffee table book, but I figured I could just as well grab some piece of detritus or a plumbing fixture off the street and it would be equally hip and $75 less expensive. Of course it wouldn't have the hot yellow vinyl cover.  Tomorrow I begin my research fellowship and my biostatistics course. I'm sure my posts are going to be profound and exciting. Stay tuned for more excitement!  N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "What Condé Nast magazines do best is to democratize sophisticated, aristocratic tastes."That is what Vogue does, what Lucky does, what Gourmet and GQ do." - James Truman, editorial director of Conde Nast.  An article in the  urlLink New York Times  this morning about a new, as-yet-without-title art magazine produced by Conde Nast was the source of this quote. Truman is one of the truly powerful people in publishing, and this seems to be his baby, a sort of Lucky for the art world.  I think the quote is mostly apt but perhaps a little misguided. Yes, these magazines take luxury goods and bring awareness of them and the trends that inspire and popularize them to a large and largely non-rich, non-artistocratic audience. But by "democratizing" these trends, they reinforce and increase the exchange value of the luxury goods themselves, raising the demand, maintaining the price, keeping them largely out of reach of the buying public. I'm thinking mostly GQ and Vanity Fair here, two big glossies that hang their hats on celebrities and valuables, but also two of the three Conde Nast magazines that really publish exceptionally good journalism as well (the third being, of course, The New Yorker). Let's not get into CN Trav... Vogue, Lucky, Glamour, etc participate in the democratization to a lesser extent, perhaps, and have a completely different market. In that sense, they're not sinister. Glamour, from what I've seen (and I'll admit that I don't read  Lucky, and I just about cringe every time I come within five feet of Conde Nast Traveller), is a forum for reinforcing normative behavioral standards among young to not-so-young-but-not-old-either women, and as such it's mostly about relationships, appearance, sex, work, and health and far less materialistic than Vogue. I like that.  I'm not saying that Glamour is less about who you should be than Vogue or GQ, but the editors there espouse a more humble, more attainable ideal. In the end, the Vogues, Vanity Fairs and GQ's reinforce and maintain an elite, material culture that is made more tantalizing by its supposed availability, the seeming proximity of beauty, panache, and celebrity, and the so-called "democratization" is perhaps a repressive force. Being an arbiter of behavioral norms is a tremendous responsibility. Millions and millions of people read Conde Nast magazines to tell them what's important, what we should wear, how we should act, how we should think about ourselves. I am very curious as to how the editors view their own role in the creation of behavioral norms.  I'm no Marxist. I just call 'em like I see 'em. N.  P.S. - I will admit that Wired publishes good journalism as well, though I haven't read it in a while.  Allure, Self, Modern Bride, Arch Digest, House and Garden, Bon App, Gourmet, Teen Vogue, Bride's - judge for yourself. I happen to like Gourmet. Did I get them all? Ah, forgot Cargo - the new Lucky, profoundly materialistic, all about keeping up with the yuppie Jones -  welcome to the club.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some analysis of Sen. Kerry's approach to medical malpractice, courtesy of the excellent  urlLink Declarations and Exclusions . N.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Infirmity alone makes us take notice and learn, and enables us to analyse processes which we would otherwise know nothing about. A man who falls straight into bed every night, and ceased to live until the moment when he wakes and rises, will surely never dream of making, not necessarily great discoveries, but even minor observations about sleep. He scarcely knows that he is asleep. A little insomnia is not without its value in making us appreciate sleep, in throwing a ray of light upon that darkness. An unfailing memory is not a very powerful incentive to study the phenomena of memory." - Marcel Proust  Does this even need commentary? I could list my infirmities: sensorineural hearing loss, accomodative esotropia, migraines, a lax ACL and torn meniscus, anxiety and general moodiness which have been helped not at all by the fact that I can't hear a damn thing people say, strange and preternatural hair loss, a tendency to read and write poems, a tendency to read medical textbooks. I also see the woeful inadequacy of not only this one but the three previous cell phones I've owned as a sort of personal curse. Am I swimming in profundity with regards to these various disease states and conditions?   Well, when I got my prism glasses and realized that I had been walking around without stereopsis for years, I was shocked and amazed. It was like living in a new 3D world. I couldn't wear them all the time. Plus they don't fit quite right and hurt the backs of my ears.   Hearing aids suck, and I have newly found respect for the subtle modulations of sensitivity in the cochlea and the circuitry in the brainstem and temporal lobe that allow us to filter extraneous sounds and pick up conversation in levels of noise that vary by up to 10 orders of magnitude in intensity.  As for balding, all I think, over and over and over again, is "I'm screwed." And then I think, "Glad my girlfriend's a little nearsighted."  I ask all readers to list their own infirmities and tell me whether they have led to similar personal discovery. N. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Any readers out there into alchemy? N.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Instead of spending my day reading the Sunday Times, I woke up at 1:30pm, didn't get out of bed until 3pm, and didn't leave the house until 4pm, at which point I picked up last minute foodstuffs for my dinner with Anna and Patrick. The gravlax came out really well. I had made it many times before, but this was the first time I'd actually fed it to a real Swede, and a Swedish foodie at that.   Saturday night props go out to Bourne, Debbie, and, the surprise of the night, BK. Saturday afternoon shout-outs to Somerville, Huddleston, Dave W. and the Gap Band, courtesy of Somerville. Nublu on Avenue C was hot, though Wax Poetic were a bit weak that time out.  In other news, I got the cutest book ever from the Lancet to review. If they pay me, it'll cover my relatively minimal (for the family members reading this) gambling losses from TJ's bachelor party at Foxwoods.  Sunday's Menu:  Gravlax with mustard sauce (home-cured, of course) --- Cherry tomato salad Fresh cranberry beans with peppermint and red onion dressing Roast leg of lamb with spicy pink grapefruit jam --- Selection of cheeses --- Fresh fruit with Creme Anglaise  Free gravlax and mustard sauce recipes to the first two non-anonymous commenters. For the poets and doctors in the audience, I apologize for writing a post completely without substance. Scroll down. Scroll down.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>