<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THEY'RE BAAAACK! Friday night was the first official boogie men show of the summer!!! It was out in Racine but we figured why not drive out there!!! After the Zoo with the family Katie Haas, Katie funk, noodles, Manda and I headed out for the first glimpse at summer life! "cackle jacks" wasn't too hot that night but we turned it into a party of our own!!! I was so exited to see the guys after a long drought of boogie! JJ was happy to see us and so were the rest of the guys...JJ ran over and gave us hugs and Dr. D aka Tony was hugging us too! Luke let us sing white lines with him and everyone was just partying!!!! It was so much fun to see everyone again! Then tonight after all the grad parties and pictures and other random stuff funk, Manda, and I hit up another show! A little church festival! We showed up just before they were playing the 2nd half! We were so exited, once again, to see the guys!!! It's so great Manda and I jumped on the stage in the middle of some song...idk which one...But we were up there all alone in the middle of the stage dancing all by ourselves!!!!! It's funny to think that after 7 months of not going to their shows that we still know all the words! IT WAS SO MUCH FUN!!! Then one again all the guys were great (as usual) and rocked my SOCKS OFF!!!  I even got to see Annie, who I haven't seen since like September!!!hah I can't wait for more summer shows and just rockin' out!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was my graduation ceremony! It is officially all over now!!! I'm looking forward to summer more than anyone knows! So the service was really short it seemed to me...The speeches that were given were really good and not too sappy! I'M FINALLY OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL! YIPEE!!! so I have graduation parties up the yin yang this month at least two every weekend date and even some on Mondays! How crazy is that!!! But I cried!!! Not as much as I thought that I would...But I definitely cried! Afterwards I went outside to get pictures with everyone...I USED 2 and 1/2 cameras that's like 50 some pictures!!! But then I had to get some with the family so I DID! Then it was off to the graduation parties...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW! Two days of finals down...Only one more to go! I had chemistry theology and Spanish...And I passed them all without even studying...I guess I was pretty lucky though! But tomorrow is my last day of high school! I'm so sad that it's all over!!! It's going to be so odd to not see everyone every day! But I guess I'll get used to it! Yeah so I thought I failed my chem final but turns out I got an 83%! I almost died when I looked at the post!!! No more ML forever!!! BTW my grad party is the 19th!!! So if anyone wants to stop by feel free!!! YEAH!!! SUMMER IS ALMOST HERE!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was student help day (BLAH!) and tomorrow finals start! The last finals in my high school career! Well at least they aren't too hard I guess! Well only 3 days left and I'm gonna graduate!!! I'm so exited but I know that I'm going to cry! Well last night Katie F., Dan, Noodles, Liz, Manda and I went out to pizza hut and then to funks for a little Mario kart session then on to Kopps for ULTIMATE COOKIE DOUGH! Can you say YUM!?!?! haha anyways it was a really fun night...Except I burned my tongue on the pizza sauce :( then I went over to Ashley's for a little fun!!! Tracy K, Manda flash, Michelle, Ashley and I were crazy! Then tom and Marc decide to show up!!! WHAT A NIGHT THAT WAS!!! Wish me luck on my finals!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Thursday! Last day of school this week! School's almost out! YIPEE! I went over to noods's at like 10:30...It was crazy! We had a little Mario tennis tourney! Senior skip day was awesome on Friday...Me Katie Katie and manda went downtown to the safehouse...That place is SO COOL! And we had the awesomest waitress ever! We even had a few extra surprises in the corridor! Then we went down to the lakefront and walked a little bit! NEMO URGE! We went back to Haas's and watched nemo...It was great fun...I had a party to go to at my house...And then back to Haas's where I played cards with Mrs. Haas and 2 of the raatz boys! Andrea and I then drove around till 1:30... And we left at 10:30! We got lost 2 times...Ran into a few obnoxious 12 yr. Olds that don't know where they live...And stalked a freshman who thought we were drunk! WHAT A NIGHT! Yesterday I had Ashley Wade's graduation party! It turns out the punch that I had been drinking was spiked and no one told me...I couldn't taste a thing!!! Then off to Allen's to babysit...I was up till 4 am...It rained almost the whole weekend! I think there was a total of 4 hours when it wasn't lol...But today was just a hang out day...Church...Cleaning...Studying...Napping...Watching movies...You know...The normal Sunday stuff! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... I hope you like the title! I wasn't sure what to call it, so I just made up an unusual name.  Today was alright I guess.  I found out that Carly, after coming up from Florida was only here for the weekend. I didn't get to see her once!!! I cried...I was so mad that I didn't get to see her!!! so that wasn't too much fun.  School sucked as usual...but I only have 6 days left YIPEEE for me! I skipped drivers ed! Andrea and I went to coffee with Ben.  I ordered an Iced Vanilla Latte!!! and of course Ben drank half of it! He's known for drink stealing!!!He was a little preoccupied with his job applications though...so Andrea and I had a good time lol! mmm STARBUCKS! Going out with those two made my day so much better!!! And speaking of job applications...I NEED TO GET A JOB...I'm really poor! But yeah...I ended up going back to school and going to 10 minutes of drivers ed and still getting credit for the class! so now I still have a perfect record! WHOO HOO! but now I'm working on Theology project! I'm almost done though so it shouldn't take me too long! but I shall finish now...BYE!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was crazy! I have so much stuff to do in 4 days and it's driving me insane! I can't wait to graduate and get out of school! At least I have one major project down...Spanish video! Now I have my senior theology project! This is what determines if I graduate or not! All that hard work in school for a project on a insane religion that thinks singing is the way to the Holy Spirit! nutcases I tell you! But anyways...School's winding down...The weather is nice...WAIT I lied...Its 40 degrees! ONLY WISCONSIN...I SWEAR WE HAVE THE CRAPPIEST WEATHER EVER! But life still kinda sucks...Schools always sucks...and college doesn't look like it's going to be fun just because I have to live at home! I hate it there what am I going to do!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend started off great...All the people that went off to college were coming back on Saturday and Friday morning @ 6 I get a call from my best friend from Florida...She says she'll be in town in about 6 hours... I was so exited  nothing bothered me all day long! Then I was supposed to get picked up @ 3...Not 4...My mom was an hour late...I called her to ask where she was and she snapped on me...So after she freaked out I had to go to the spring concert at school...Manda picked me up, we talked the whole way to school about everything...I was going insane!!!! I was crying and angry. It wasn't the best mood to be in when I had to go on stage in an hour! So after that everyone kept asking me what's wrong, it got pretty annoying...and then Ashley and Nathan and I had an awesome time running around backstage and almost dying from the gun shots...It was great! Then I talked with Nathan for a while... All that made my night so much better! We were gonna hang out with Sam or Nathan we didn't know yet and then I stayed @ Tracy's with Ashley and we were up until 3 talking...It was great...Then that morning we went out to FREE breakfast with her dad! Then I went back to the hell-hole aka my house...And the crap started all over again...So once again I went to school all upset...But luckily ash and I were gonna hang out. We were gonna go listen to Andy's band, but the 1st band didn't show up...So our plans changed dramatically in an hour...After calling like 10 people and talking to Tom, we went to kopps to meet a bunch of people...We ended up going back to her house and watching the Lakers game with josh and Sam...It was a lot of fun...Lets just say the journey was 90% of the fun...All my friends turned the worst weekend ever into one of the greatest!!! THANKS p.s. the escort is hott!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got this cool lil Bloggy thing...idk how it works quite yet but uhm...check it out I guess...So this is the 2nd last week of school and I can't wait to get out! 4 years in one place is WAY too long! All the college people are going to be comin' back...I'm totally psyched! I miss everyone so much! But there is so much to look forward too...LIKE SUMMERFEST! Rock on!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow...So 4 days later a lot of stuff has happened!   (June 27th, 2004) It turns out that we didn't go see Big Boi and Ludacris! Why you ask...Well, I'll tell you! Noodles got sick with an Ear Infection...(poor Noodle!) and then DJ didn't want to go...She wanted to sleep...And then Amanda didn't want to go because Noodles and DJ weren't...So I was screwed...But that's OK! I called Al and her and I went down to Summerfest to see Jason Mraz! We had "lunch" (which consisted of Hawaiian Shaved Ice!) with Katie Haas and "Baker" (this kid that's playing baker in Into the Woods!) anyways...It was fun! Then, We sat at the Harley stage for 6 hours!!! So after sitting there for a while and watching this insanely crazy band that played flutes and sang we got hungry...So I ventured off into the crowd to buy food of some sort...1st I wanted Wong's Wok!!! YUMMY! But then I realized it was almost $7 to eat...I was like WTF! So I just got fries from Culver's instead! So on my way over to Culver's I'm walking...And Walking...And I look up...And It's Dr. D of the Boogie Men with his wife...So I waved and kept walking!!! Then Still walking...I run into Boyfriend and His Girlfriend...I almost died...It was so funny! So I stared at him until he smiled...Then I smiled back and kept walking! It was really funny that I ran into them both within 5 minutes!!! So on my way back for another few hours of sitting...I run into JJ and Nicole...Turns out they were there to see Jason too!!! So they came and sat by us!!! Ari Hest...The opener for Jason was good...Maybe I'll order a CD online or something! Then all hell broke loose with torrential downpour of rain! I pulled out my trusty emergency poncho and ripped it so it would cover Al, Me, JJ and Nicole...It only worked for like 10 minutes...Then I gave up because I was already soaked! So Jason came on!!! It was one of the most awesomest concerts I'd ever been to!!! And Just think...It was free!!! So I recorded the WHOLE concert in my phone!  And It POURED the whole time!!!   (July 28th, 2004) Monday Allison and I went down to summerfest around 2! We sat at the miller stage and waited for something corporate!(which is one of my favorite bands!!!) We were there and we wanted to see Steriogram @ the Mt. Dew stage @ 5...DJ, DA, Manda, Kate and Jill came and sat by us for a while.  Al and I were totally bored so we asked the people next to us if they would save our FRONT ROW spot so we could go walk around! We went down to Steriogram...WHICH WAS FRICKEN AWESOME...ANOTHER NEW FAV BAND TO ADD TO THE LIST!!! lol and then we walked around some more...Got a band to see Blink 182...Which we weren't going to anyways...Got a little food...And went back to sit at the stage...We ran into BB...(oh joy!) and then sat down again!!! Only a few more hours!!! ok...So we were sitting there...And the security guard from the B-men show was there and started talking to us again! It was really funny! Annie was also down there! I saw her and went over and talked to her for like 10 minutes...It's always nice to chat with her!!! But I was still waiting to S.C.!!! So then there was these 3 guys behind us...They were really funny...So I started talking to one of them...His name was Nick...He was from Kewaskum...Or something...But he was SO funny!!! Allison and I were DYING! So then Andrew...Her bro came and met us down there with the ZOOM camera! It would be awesome!!! Ok...So then after listening to more retarded bands! It was almost time to go...Nick Lachey came on stage and started talking to the crowd it was awesome!!! HE'S SO SEXY!!! MMM...NICK!!!!  He was backstage...Drinking his beer...And I waved at him...And he winked and waved back at me!!! OMG NICK LACHEY WAVED @ ME!!!! LOL So finally they came on...I've never screamed so loud! I almost cried during the show because it was so good and because I LOVE THEM! So during the show the Lead singer/Piano Player Jumped off the stage and came over the crowd and shook my hand it was awesome! Then they pulled a whole bunch of people on stage...But of course I wasn't one of them...But Oh well! Then the Guys from Steriogram were on stage too! It was a 3 for one deal! Nick, Something Corporate, and Steriogram!!!! So after listening to one of the most AMAZING concerts ever...(even better than Jason Mraz!) I went to see if I could meet the guys backstage...AND I DID!!! I got their autographs on their picture...They signed my beater and I got a pic with the SUPER SEXY DRUMMER!!! THEY WERE AWESOME!!! The bus-ride home was a little festive!!! There was a fight ON THE BUS...ON THE FREEWAY! It was insane...And a little scary...I felt bad for the bus driver!!! Oh well!!! I had an awesome time...And I took a MILLION PICS!!! Can't wait to get those back!!!  (June 29th, 2004) Jessica Simpson in concert night! Monica, Noodles, Al, DJ, Manda, and I went down to go see her @ the Marcus with our cool little bracelets for grass seats!!! Woo Hoo...Or not so much woo hoo! lol...The concert wasn't too bad...But since I had never been inside the Marcus...I didn't know we had to climb a million stairs...And then we weren't in the grass, we were in the bleachers which was a plus...But the concert started an hour and a half late! But Ryan Cabrera, the opening act, was amazing! He's so good! I can't wait for him album in the fall!!! Cheesecake show was really good too...But I had been sitting and standing way too much this past week and I was super tired because I got up @ 7, moved 100 chairs and 5 tables, 2 hours of drivers ed, which was my last one, and cleaned a little bit...So I was tired...I liked it...But it was way too much work to not fall asleep! So after that Al and I were waiting for everyone to get out of the damn bathroom which took them like 10 minutes...No joke! And I was super thirsty!!! So we were all walking to get Hawaiian Shaved Ice...Which has basically been my diet for the past week! lol...We saw Nathan and trista...It was so good to see those two!!! Anyways we talked for a while and everyone else decided to keep going to get Hawaiian shaved ice!!! But as Al and I were talking to them...RYAN CABRERA...THE OPENING ACT FOR JESSICA SIMPSON WALKED BY!!! I ALMOST DIED! I RAN OVER AND TAPPED HIM ON THE SHOULDER AND WAS LIKE "HI...YOU WERE SO AWESOME TONIGHT! I LOVED THE SHOW!" AND THEN HE LEFT! I ALMOST DIED BECAUSE I DIDN'T HAVE A CAMERA AND HE'S SO HOT AND FAMOUS! But yeah I am still mad at myself for not having a camera!!! But that night was good... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I'm taking off from Summerfest...I think we shouldn't get MORE annoyed with each other...And maybe get some sleep! Ashes grad party was today so I stopped at that for a while...And then went home to do nothing...Which is good cuz I'm tired anyways...I drove to Menard's to buy a MAILBOX...Why you ask? Well I'll tell you...For the past week we had our house re-sided...A nice shade of TAN! With Hunter green trim haha ok but...Every morning this week a HUGE group of Polish men would ring our doorbell @ 8 am and say "we here for your siding" EVERY DAY! And then they would take out very large hammers and start banging on my house... So underneath our old rose-colored siding was a lovely shade of BARN RED! Our house looked like a barn for 2 days! And then on top of that...The siding company sent a huge industrial size RED garbage can! So now the ark sized garbage can matched the house! It was kinda retarded! So then anyways...Every morning when I was getting ready I realized that there was a Polish man staring in my window...HOW LOVELY!!!! So now I'm paranoid that someone is staring in my window...But yeah...That was exiting...So tonight I'm Chillaxing in front of the TV and getting a good night's sleep for tomorrow...BIG BOI AND LUDACRIS @ THE MARCUS!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DJ picked up Al and I and we listened to CATS on the way to meet up @ Manda's! We went down to SF at about 1:30...We used our NIFTY little "Big Gig Value Cards" to get in! lol...We checked out the HP tent again, and walked around, Ate, saw people we knew, and pretty much just checked out HOT guys!!! It was lots of fun! We went to see Chevelle @ the Mt. Dew stage at 10 pm. We met up with Katie again and watched Pat McCurdy! It's amazing how many people have never heard of him before!!! I was shocked...But anyways...Al was a "pat-virgin" so she got a lap song LOL...Anyways...We saw some more ML people and went and got a signing from Pat! It was fun...Then we walked around..And saw some more people...And then we met up with BB and Candice... Then we sat by the rocks and met like 40 people ...SERIOUSLY! I'm just gonna name all the people we ran into...Tom, Marc, Andrew, Joey, Dan, Manda, Jessy, Amie, Andrea, Gabe, Jacque, Abby, Brenna, Christina, Kim, Sarah, Ashley, Nicole, Brandon, Steve, D-$, Megan, Matt, Austin, Jessy, Justin, Andy, Micheala, Brittney, Bekki, Trisha, Nikki, Adam, Lindsey, Erin, Mike and lots of  others that I don't even remember!...So yeah...There were a lot of people there last night that we knew!!! It was crazy!...So then...We watched Chevelle, got in a fight, cussed each other out, yelled, made up, walked around, tried to find Katie, and Meet up with people for the rest of the night! So yeah it was crazy...Then...On the bus ride home...There was this really hot guy standing in front of me...cuz I was sitting...And I was being dumb and staring @ him...And then he asked me if I knew what a wallaby was... 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is now officially summer because Summerfest "The Big Gig" 2004 has started!!! Thursday June 24th, 2004 was awesome!!! It was rainy @ 11 when we were supposed to meet @ manda's...Then we decided to wait until 2 to go because it was crappy outside...But we knew that no matter what we were going down to see the Boogie Men @ North Shore...8:30!!! So it turns out that when we were down there it got insanely nice outside...Sunny, Warm, and Blue Skies!!! We walked around for a while, stopped at the HP tent and took some cool pics, got a few free pins from the Sobe tent, stopped at the Gibson, and Fender stands, and just sat at a few random stages...We saw this band called Saturday Morning @ the Mt. Dew stage...Cover band of course...But we decided to leave when they butchered Blink 182's "All the Small Things" then we met up with one of DJ's friends @ the Miller Oasis around 3:30!!! On the way there we ran into Michelle S. And Manda F.!!! We invited them to the boogie men tonight too!!! But anyways, EXIT (which was the band that was playing @ Miller, some covers but mostly original)was AWESOME! And they were super hot!!! I could've listened to them all day! We met up with Katie Haas, who works admissions for the Marcus, and had lunch @ Saz's and went to another stage around 6 (MMMM SAZ'S!!!!!!!) Then off to meet up with ANOTHER ONE of DJ's friends, Candice, at the Harley Davidson Stage...."The Groove Hogs" were playing...Never heard of them and would've never guessed that they weren't all that bad! A different kind of music than I'm used to but I figured what the hell!!! After DROOLING over the lead singer (who I also got a picture of!)we went down to North Shore around 7 for THE BOOGIE MEN!!!!! We got there and waited to meet up with Noodles, then Al called and Her, Andrew, and Natalie F. Were on their way to meet up with us too!!! After everyone got there around 7:30...It was a HUGE boogie party!!! We saw Tipper, Kemo, Tony, Luke, and Randy and waved at all of them...And of course they smiled and waved back! Then Tony came over and talked to us for like 10 mins. And then Joe came over and talked to us for like 10 mins.! JJ was like..."Hey Guys! You're here..But I shouldn't've expected any less!" it was funny!   strong> I SAW ANNIE @ THE SHOW!!! I WAVED AT HER BECAUSE SHE'S SO AWESOME AND SHE'S THE BEST BOOGIE BUDDY EVER!!!    So we waited for the show to get started!!! We were all exited!!! Then BOYFRIEND came out and announced the guys!!! HE LOOKED HOT (AS USUAL!) Then the show began!!! Dr. D (aka dad, Tony) came out in White Platforms and a HUGE fur coat! JJ came out in this huge fur coat too! Of course I GOT PICS! They should be good ones!!! lol the show was really funny and awesome as usual, especially with lots of people! They were throwing stuff out into the crowd! It was nuts...Then afterwards we went over to the "TOUR SHIRTS" tent and got pictured signed and took a picture with the whole group...And after talking to everyone and getting a really weird "tattoo" from Kemo we watched the Big Bang 2004 right on the lake...It was amazing!!! We walked around...And headed for the Miller Oasis to go see The Darkness! There were so many drunk people everywhere you couldn't even breathe so we left...Al, Andrew, and Natalie had to go home so we split us...We ended up running into Steve, and a few other ML people... But then we headed back to the North Shore to meet Noodles and we saw these guys who were like "HEY! You guys are going the wrong way...Were going this way!" it was really funny, probably more funny if you were there but anyways... Then a few minutes later Kemo, His Girlfriend/Wife (we don't know if they're married or not LOL!) and a few other people walked by us and Kemo's Gf/Wife was like "HEY!" and kinda bumped me...She recognized us from the show and then we talked for a little bit and went to go meet up with Noodles by the Ferris Wheel! We ran into the rest of the boogie men but really didn't get to talk! But then we left...We rode home on the BUS! It was funny...This guys said..."Hey who'd you meet" and I answered "the boogie men" and he replied..."That's cool...For the first year and a half I thought they were black!" that basically ended the night! what a quote to finish off the evening!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a little overview of the past 4 days...Chris's Grad party was the 20th, and so was Brittney's! So manda and I stopped @ those...NINJA TURTLES 1 & 2 Movie nights!!! #1) @ My house with Me, Noodles, Greg, and Manda #2) @ Manda's with Greg and Me, 50 First Dates movie night @ My house with Greg, Rob, Manda, and of course, ME! Summerfest Shopping trip and Dinner @ The O.G. (aka The Olive Garden)With Manda!!! Noodles, Manda, and I went Party store hopping looking for Beads to wear to summerfest...It was quite an adventure because when Noodles dropped us off so she could go to work Manda realized that she locked her keys in her house and had no way of getting in...Leave it to Manda...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At the show on Saturday The Boyfriend was there! lol...He's not really a boyfriend...But he's just always around so we nicknamed him that!!!...Anyways he was totally HOTT! And he was dancing crazy...Then he came up on stage and was like "What's up Bitches!" DJ and I almost died...We were the only ones that caught that!!! And then during the show JJ said that we should all vote to Legalize Freeway Sex! I almost died!...That's our new theme for the summer!!! LEGALIZE FREEWAY SEX! Wow I love those guys...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW!!!!!!! It's been such a long time since I've written so much fun stuff has happened in 2 weeks...Let me think...hmm....We'll start from the beginning... Well the 12th was Manda's grad party which was a lot of fun...Some pretty crazy stuff happened with some pretty crazy people...Steve and Greg attempted to "skip-it" it was one of the funniest things that I have ever seen and every time Greg put it on it got stuck and I was the only person who could get it off!!! Anyways...And then Sunday was Greg's grad party!!! That was CRAZY-FUN!!!!!! After getting drenched with ICE WATER by Greg and His bro noodles, manda, and I went to my house to dry our clothes...We watched DAVID BLAINE...He's a fun guy! lol then we went on a scavenger hunt...Created by Becchi(greg's sis) and Robb.. That was so much fun! Even though it ended up in major conflict we had an awesome time driving around Milwaukee for some Lake Sludge and singing CAROLINE!!! hmm...Then Monday night(14th) I had to go to the End of the Year Troubs Party...It was a lot of fun and the picture that Jess gave me as the senior gift was adorable!!! I love it! Ok...Well then...(I can't even remember what Happened!) Ohhh...Noodles, Monica, Manda, and I went to see Stepford Wives...It was an awesome movie...I recommend it!!! Then we just went and hung out @ Amanda's!!! The 16th (Wednesday) was my Grandpa's Funeral and then we had lunch @ my house afterward...It was crazy. Thursday I cleaned for my Party and went Shopping for all the food and stuff...Friday I cleaned for my party which wasn't too much work! BUT THEN THE FUN BEGAN! uhm...Allison, DJ, Manda, Katie F., Noodles, and I went to the Boogie Men show @ St. Joe's!!! It was so much fun!!! JJ let Manda wear the Big clock and let Noodles wear the hat during "I Like Big Butts"!!! And JJ gave Manda and Me tattoos!!! lol It was a really fun show...But then this crazy kid with a drumstick kept pushing us and acted like he was part of the band...We all wanted to hit him! lol It was Al's first show and she had an awesome time!!! She was just as crazy and the rest of us...She just has to learn all the dances!!! haha Then Saturday was my grad party...It was fun...I got some crazy gifts like...Band-aids, shoe laces, and a birthday card! But of course they were from one of the craziest people I know...AL! So after that "lovely party" A bunch of us decided to drive out to Okauchee and see none other than The Boogie Men!!!!!! Steve, Manda, Noodles, DJ, Al, Andrew, and I went out to see them...After driving 30 minutes to see them, park about a 1/2 mile away, and walk all the way to the gates we find out you have to be 21 to get in!!!!! We almost died!!! We arrived just after Band X so when they came off the stage JJ (Joe) noticed us waving from the corner!!! He came over and said..."What are you guys doing out there" and we explained the whole thing...And he said "WTF" and called over the the manager...And said "Hey...These are our greatest, best, fans ever do you think we could let them in the back door?" and he counted us and was like "hell yeah" so he snuck us in the back door behind the stage!!! It was great!!! So we stood backstage for a while and talked to everyone!!! Then Joe was like "If a security guard comes over just tell them your with the band and walk backstage!" Then Later we were talking with Dr. D. And he said..."Just tell them that you are all my adopted Children" So we were officially adopted by JJ and Dr. D. Dr. D. Said that even though we're his kids that we're not supposed to ask him for money! lol that was funny and then he said "if you tell them you're all adopted they'll believe you!" it was funny!!! Then we just mingled backstage until The Boogie Men came on! We were out in the front and it was a normal show...A lot of dancing and singing!!! Especially White Lines!!! :-D It was one of the best shows so far this summer!!! So when it was over we had to leave out the back again...So we walked backstage and said thanks to all the guys and said happy fathers day to our new dads!!! And they hugged us all  and said "ok, bye kids! Drive Safe! See you on Thursday!" it was an awesome ending to an already great day!!! And this reminds me...One of the last shows we went to last weekend was all the way in PLYMOUTH! It was a 2 hour drive and we went to see them! I think they were all a little shocked and amazed that we came all the way out there just for them!!! On the B-Men website they wrote that they were so happy that we all came out to see them!!! It's so awesome...!!!!! But Anyways...That's enough for now...BYE!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night/this morning Katie Funk, Manda, Liz, Katie Haas, and I stayed up all night so we could go see Noodles at the airport when she flew in from California @ 5 am!!! We all met at Katie Funk's @ around 10 pm and since we were all STARVING we called like 5 restaurants to see how late they were open.  We ended up going to Denny's because it's open 24 hours! So We walk into Denny's and the whole restaurant was filled with tables full of guys! They were all staring at us, it was kinda weird! So we ate and while we were eating and talking this couple at the table next to us decides to listen in! They laughed at what we were saying so I said "wow it's pretty pathetic that 30 year olds sit and listen to some teenagers talk about stuff!" they turned around and didn't listen anymore! I thought it was pretty funny! So then we were starting to get tired and it was only 12! So we went over to Kris's. We snuck in the house and tried our best to be quiet! We watched clips from Chappelle's Show for like 45 minutes! I've never laughed so hard in my life!!! Manda and I were freaking out because he played the R.Kelly one! :-D then manda and I wanted to go relax so we jumped on his water bed and the rest of the gang followed! It was funny because there was 5 girls in his bed @ 2 am!!! Just think if someone in his family came downstairs!?!?!?! It would've been crazy! So a bunch of giggles and a dozen pictures later we decided to go to Katie's and make the Signs for Noods!!!! Anyways...We ended up staying there until 3 am! Back at Katie's we took Mt. Dew shots!!! We got pictures of that too!!! HAHA! We made our signs and before we knew it it was 4 am! Time to go to the airport!!! We were all in PJ's and had a sheet of colored paper...We waited for like 45 minutes and then we saw Noods and her family coming up the ramp!!! We all stood in order spelling "Noods" with our signs!!! It was by far one of the most hilarious, most fun nights ever!!! So after going home and falling asleep at 8 and waking up @ 11 I don't even feel tired at all! Now I have to clean...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night was so much fun! Dan, Scott, Jared, Katie F., Manda, Kaitlin, Greg, Kris, and I went to the drive in to go see Harry Potter and Troy!!! turned out that it wasn't troy it was NY minute w/ the olson twins!!! Harry Potter was really good! and besides...he's hot! but after that the guys decided to leave because they weren't all to facsinated that Troy wasn't showing! the rest of us decided to stay to make fun of the movie!  It was horrible...i've never laughed so hard at somthing that stupid! i don't recommend it!!! we didn't get home until 2:30 am...tonight there are a few grauation parties i have to go to...Katie Haas and Andy Q. ohhh... tracy key's! I'll let you know how the go!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night Manda and I made plans to go down to Rochambo's with Ben and Mike...It turns out that we went with them and Met up with Steve and Bona...This other guy that he knew...What a fun name! So before we went downtown...We called mike and Ben like a thousand times! We were only trying to figure out when we were going to meet! Finally we talked to Mike...But he told us, after telling us 4 different stories, he couldn't go b/c he had a "date" with his ex.  So anyways...Turns out he convinced her to go to Rochambo's just so he could see us! How fun!!! Anyways...Mike dyed his hair black!(not at the coffee shop...At home!) ahhah and then Steve bought manda and me a rose! awwwwww isn't that cute!!!  I finally got to meet Greg's sister Becky (that's not how you really spell it either...Its got a different spelling!) she's so awesome...After Ben ditched us to go with the other guys Manda and I went to go hang out with Greg and Rob!!! Manda got a parking ticket too! We went to scare Becky @ the movie theater and then went on a little shopping trip @ Wal-Mart!!! We stayed out until 2 with them! It was the craziest time ever! Now it's off to the drive in!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love Summer!!! I'm so glad it's here...I get to hang out with my friends all the time!!!! I hung out with Ben and Steve and Nick a few days ago...It was lots of fun...A night out @ rochambo's, a little Moulin Rouge, and driving for food @ 12:30 at night! It was pretty funny...We stopped @ McDonald's and then Nick got heartburn lol! Anyways...That was a fun night!!! Last night I went over to Manda's with Steve Raatz, Katie, Katie, Manda, Greg, and later...Liz! It was a good time! We went to the park to play a little basketball and football...But we ended up just throwing the ball over the fence and then going home! We played a few games and Katie F. Thinks a baby moose is called a Mooselet! hahaha...But the night ended in a TGI Fridays dinner and about 11 games of ...idk the game...Something with a neighbor..But it was fun!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been to 11 graduation parties! I've had a blast at all of them! But I'm sick of food!!! Memorial day I went to Joe's and Brandon's! Those were the 2 most fun parties so far!!! There was so many people at joe's and everyone was just hanging out! It was so much fun! Tom, Andrew, Julia, Amanda, Marc and Me all went outside to have a cigar! mmm.....Cherry flavored! We took some pictures of that! I'm sure those will turn out great! And before that we were staring @ some pretty hot guys in the area! lol It was a pretty crazy night! To bad it had to end...But there will be more parties and the whole summer ahead!!! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>