<Blog>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We get to open this page.  After one year of promises, the world shall see the thoughts of a very brilliant mind.  How d'ya feel 'bout that mate? 

						
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						         I'm thinking, I should let the whole thing with &quot;J&quot; go. If anything did happen between us, it could blow up in my face. What if &quot;La Prieta&quot; goes nuts and has a fit. I'm the one that has the most years to loose, here at Hellhole Inc. (as my best friend refers to our work place), and Hellhole Inc. does pay the bills. Besides &quot;J&quot; doesn't seem very discreet, and I don't want people I work with to know my business. It has to be a midlife crisis. Maybe, I should just get a new car! :)     

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						         Finally, was able to talk to the girl all alone. She kept giggling. She kept asking me questions, and when I mentioned that I was doing most of the talking. She said &quot;I'm kind of shy until I feel comfortable and then I talk a lot&quot;.She is going out with &quot;La Prieta&quot; I told her I wasn't sure since she keeps staring. She giggled again. She said &quot;we are going on two months, for as long is that will last since we work together&quot; I'm guessing that little piece of information was for my benefit. I did tell her I was with someone, but that I was still attracted to her. Maybe a gave to much information, but I've never been one to hold back. I told her that I won't be staring at her when her girlfriend is around because I don't want to cause any problems. Then she tells me oh no that doesn't bother she's not like that. Does that mean I'm supposed to keep staring? Hmm&#8230;I'm starting to get a little frustrated. I wish I could just flip a little switch, and place her back into the crowds of faces I see at work every day, and don't pay any attention to. Those honey brown eyes and those full lips, are not easy to forget.      

						
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						         &nbsp;It's a beautiful Saturday, and I'm stuck at work. On the good side I'm filling in for my boss, so I'll have slack. That will allow me ample opportunity to be on &quot;The Hunt&quot;! So, far we've only stared at each other, from afar, a few lame halos. I'm sure she is half my age or close to it. I must be crazy. Maybe it's a mid life crisis (I've been thinking of changing my car as well). I don't really know. Really, for all practical purposes it's a waste of time, nothing could come of it. Of course I haven't always been very practical. Who knows, maybe by the time we do talk and she opens her mouth, I'll be thinking &quot;just shut up and look pretty&quot;...     

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   work bitch!   

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Yes! Wrong! So, I thought I was over it. I haven't tried hard enough to get over the girl. To snap out of it! (maybe someone needs to slap me,  and  hard). I see her with "La Prieta" and I look forward to the day they break up. Maybe, because in the back of my head, I think well maybe then she'll start talking, and flirting, and … The reality is, she knows I have a girlfriend. So more than likely, she won't. I still find her so cute. I've been making a point of looking for the defects, (that always help get over the hump) so far that's not working very well. She still says, hi, waves even from far away, and with her girlfriend. I'm not sure I know what that's all about. Maybe the jokes on me!   

						
</post>


</Blog>