<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got this idea that I could make a life sized cowboy with empty pill bottles. That doesn't bode well for my new ideas about getting a life.  I'm in the really early stages of planning to move far, far away. I've been looking at classifieds for the states I'm interested in and I guess it'll work out real well if I'm willing to work about three jobs. I'm not. So I guess I gotta stay here till I think of something else. I REALLY don't want to stay here.  But maybe having three jobs would be better than sitting here drinking Diet Coke, smoking Marlboro Lights and surfing the internet half the night.  It's something I'm going to consider.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Kathleen's Second Site   It's my website. It's woefully unfinished because I never work on it unless I feel like it and obviously that doesn't happen often.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Starting a blog today instead of some other day. Some other day when I'm feeling shiny and happy. It could happen.  Watching VH1 at 3:30 in the morning. Or any other time as far as I can tell.  Wearing false fingernails.  Getting really tired of false fingernails and tearing them off instead of removing them properly.  Letting my desk get so dusty I'm starting to sneeze.  Trying to write my first post in a damn blog while I'm watching VH1 at 3 in the morning.  Kathleen
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink      The test is which fantsy/sci-fi character are you. Funny that I've never seen any of the Star Wars movies.  Don't plan to, either. I was hoping for someone far cooler.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't know who wrote this song, but I just heard Lucinda's version and I like it a lot.     &nbsp;   I changed the lock on my front door    so you can't see me anymore    And you can't come inside my house,    and you can't lie down on my couch    I changed the lock on my front door    I changed the number on my phone    so you can't call me up at home    And you can't say those things to me    that make me fall down on my knees    I changed the number on my phone    I changed the kind of car   I drive    so you can't see me when I go by    And you can't chase me up the street,    and you can't knock me off of my feet    I changed the kind of car I drive    I changed the kind of clothes I wear    so you can't see me anywhere    And you can't spot me in a crowd,    &nbsp;and you can't call my name out loud    I changed the kind of clothes I wear    I changed the tracks underneath the train    &nbsp;so you can't find me again    And you can't trace my path,    and you can't hear my laugh    I changed the tracks underneath the train    I changed the name of this town    so you can't follow me down    And you can't touch me like before,    and you can't make me want you more    I changed the name of this town    I changed the lock on my front door,    I changed the number on my phone    I changed the kind of car I drive,    I changed the kind of clothes   I wear   I changed the tracks underneath the train,    I changed the name of this town    I changed the name of this town    I changed the name of this town     &nbsp;   Maybe Tom Petty wrote it?    
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I went to California on vacation and it was the coolest thing I've done in years.    &nbsp;  I met a longtime internet friend who is now a real-life friend.    &nbsp;  I went to a Gram Parsons Tribute concert in Santa Barbara.    &nbsp;  I went to a Gram Parsons Tribute concert in Los Angeles.    &nbsp;  I went to Morro Bay in a convertible with the top down.    &nbsp;  I went to Joshua Tree.    &nbsp;  I went to the beach a couple of times.    &nbsp;  I sat on the deck watching the fine looking construction worker working next door.    &nbsp;  I went to see Fahrenheit 911 which was awesome, a movie everyone should see, and caused me to like Michael Moore even more than I already did.    &nbsp;  Back off, it's my blog, I say what I want.    &nbsp;  I've decided that my goal in life is to move to California. Once I get there I'll decide on my next goal.    &nbsp;  Kathleen  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            urlLink  Which is "your" holiday?      St. Patrick's Day   It's been months since New Year's and it's still months until Memorial Day.  Not as if you needed an excuse to party hardy in between...but there *IS* something appealing about green beer.  urlLink        urlLink   Click Here to Take This Quiz     Brought to you by  urlLink  YouThink.com   quizzes and personality tests.     
     
    
</post>


</Blog>