<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Haven't had a lot of time to sit and write.  Got a nice surprise on Sunday night, out of the blue M calls and asked if I wanted to go to the lake overnight with him, so I hopped in the shower, and he came over and picked me up.  We talked a lot as we drove out to his place.  A beautiful electrical storm was off in the distance as we drove closer to his place.  We arrived and it was an awesome little place.  It was a really great night and I enjoyed the time we spent together.  Last night I went to see a play at the Latenight Theatre on Grand and the troupe was hilarious.  What a talented bunch of guys.  Linda and I laughed a lot and had a great time.    Its another rainy day, but its better than the terrible tornado type storms that went through the area last night.  Wish I could just stay in bed and sleep for a few more hours, but oh well, its off to work I go, hi ho hi ho LOL  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ick....I have to go to work today.  I am getting so excited about going to Wichita and seeing everyone.  Found out last night that P was going to cook instead of us all going out someplace.  It will be a strange feeling being in Wichita and knowing of the awful memories that surround that city.  I am hoping to make some new and much more positive memories this weekend.  L and I have been thinking of such devilish things to do **weg**  She and I surely will be into some kind of trouble this weekend LOL  Feeling better and having a new outlook is allowing me to really take life on a totally different level.    Well, I am going to get going....and go to work :)  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a great day.  Went riding with G for most of the afternoon.  I always enjoy my time with him.  I always feel very relaxed and safe when I am with G.  As we rode today, my mind wandered and thoughts of many things came bouncing about.  The freedom of the open road helped me realize how much better my life is without BV in my life.  I just never knew how much of a negative force he was in my life.  I don't hold a lot of resentment towards BV anymore, but what he did to my daughter is going to take some time to get over.  He used her to get to me, and he was very sly about it all.  He would have never gotten his foot in the door if I had not been vunerable and heartbroken from another relationship.  He had only been asking me out for 3 years, and I wanted no part of his life.  He just wasn't my type.  Very manipulative, smooth, and always looking for the next sexual score.  Then when I became down and weak, he swooped down and hit me hard.  But as we were out riding today, I realized it all is over now, and such good riddens too.  I am not bitter, but I do have a lot of unanswered questions, but when those questions pop up I just say to myself...."It just is".  And so chapter closed, and so things are as they are, or It just is!!!    Well its getting late, and I think I am going to go meditate and go read for awhile.  ~~spirit~~ 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a great day...the sun is shining, the birds singing, its just breathtaking.  Had a great night out with M last night, and as always I enjoy my time with him.  We seem to share a lot of great stories and have the right amount of chemistry to enjoy a great evening.  I haven't got much accomplished today, but I am going to get moving and get out and enjoy this beautiful day.  Meeting up with a friend for dinner tonight, and then where? No one knows.    Talked to L today, and she and I had a great talk.  We made a pact about next weekend, that there would be no talk of the subboy.  It will be great to meet up with other lifestylers and enjoy great conversation and hopefully some naughty (or knotty) fun.  Although Wichita holds a lot of bad memories, I hope to make some new and much MUCH better memories next weekend.    Well I am off to enjoy the rest of this beautiful Saturday.  ~~spirit~~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yippppppeeeee its Friday!!  I am in a great mood.  Life is good.  I thought I would start this blog because sometimes it is good to just vent a little, and I am sure my friends get tired of hearing it from me LOL.  Looks like a busy weekend ahead of me.  Going out tonight, hopefully do some dancing and romancing **weg**  The rest of the weekend should be pretty decent too, with some tentative plans bouncing about.    Well its off to work I go....hi ho hi ho LOL  s
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Just Like You  (lyrics by Three Days Grace)  I could be mean I could be angry You know I could be just like you  I could be fake I could be stupid You know I could be just like you  You thought you were standing beside me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you  You thought you were there to guide me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you You thought you were there to guide me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you  I could be cold I could be ruthless You know I could be just like you  I could be weak I could be senseless You know I could be just like you  You thought you were standing beside me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you  You thought you were there to guide me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you You thought you were there to guide me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you  On my own, cause I can’t take liven with you I’m alone, so I won’t turn out like you want me to  You thought you were standing beside me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you  You thought you were there to guide me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you You thought you were there to guide me You were only in my way You’re wrong if you think that I’ll be just like you  I could be mean I could be angry You know I could be just like you  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has come to my attention that some people think I am spreading lies and making up stories.  Well let me state here and now, what I write here is MY opinion, and that is the bottom line.  The truth, what the hell is the truth?  Does anyone know, its just a perception we see and make judgment on and then we alone decide if it is true.  What I express here in my rants are my feelings and MY opinions.  If I believe something, that is my business, not YOURS.  If you don't like what I wrote, then so be it, its not meant to appeal to the masses, but for me to say what I feel, to expel some negative energies as well as some positive ones.  Things in my past still haunt me today, and sometimes I just need to let them out, and let the demons of those past memories fade just a little more.  I have been through a pretty rough year, but life is getting better and I am happier now than I have ever been.  If you want to think of me as a liar, well that is your choice, I alone have to face myself in the mirror, just as those I accuse of lying have to do.  I try very hard to release the things I have harbored inside from the past, but when someone is played and lied to, its hard to understand the biggest question and that question is WHY?  I am a very passionate person and with that my passion for the positive is just as strong as my passion for the negative.  Its the balance of my spirit.  I love and I hate with a great intensity, but the hate feelings will eat a person alive.  I have mended some bridges and I have also let go of some old pains and actually even rekindled a friendship from the past that I thought would never be again, and its very refreshing.  I will admit my pains and hurts from Wichita have me bound a bit, as the situation still to this day makes no sense to me.  Why is the question that can't seem to be answered.  I have moved on, and my life is great now, but the why's still haunt me from time to time.  My opinions, my feelings, my thoughts and so forth here, are MINE, and I am entitled to express them.  If you have a question or a disagreement, please feel free to contact me anytime.  I know there are a few people out there that love to see me hurt and want to think I am miserable here, but it just isn't the case.  The winds of yesterday are gone, the residue of such may still dust our today's, but I know tomorrow a new and better breeze will be sunning down upon me.  I will bask in the positive rays of today's sunshine.    So **ck off if you think my opinions are lies, they are what they are, so move the hell on, cry baby mutha fookers.  Off to enjoy my day!!!  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Don't I look sweet? lol&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Red is my favorite color &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Just being ornery **giggle**&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a glorious day.  I have been busy running errands, having lunch with a very sexy man, and now I am home and going to rest for awhile.  Reading a great book called the Ethical Slut.  It is a great book on alternative ideas on sexuality.    23 more days until I go to Denver.  I can't wait.  It will be a great time seeing old friends and maybe making some new ones as well.  I am also looking forward to spending some time with G and MsRK **beaming smile**    Well I am off to drink some coffee and read out on the patio.  Later...  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another work day **sigh** Oh well, life goes on.  Went and saw the new Tom Hanks movie The Terminal last night with M, good flick.  I haven't wrote as much here lately because it seems some people have nothing better to do than to jump to conclusions about what I write here as if it pertained to them.  For the  most part my life is very happy.  I am working two jobs, dating some great guys, enjoying my daughter, attending fetish events, and basically just having a great time.  Things have changed a lot for me over the last few months and all for the better.  Getting rid of the B & B baggage has helped more than I ever thought possible.  Although the first B is involved (loosely) stated with a friend of mine, it is good, because at least I know what a low-life he really is because he is treating her the same way he treated me.  As far as the 2nd B, well that is just a blip in the system now and means nothing to me other than he is like a pesky fly that I wish he would just leave people alone.    Well I need to go upstairs and wake M up so we can both go to work.    Until then....  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This song sums up my last "relationship" to a tee!!  FACE TO FACE (lyrics by Sevendust)   Don't tell me now with a smile on your face  That you're lost - down and out  When there was nothing left in me    You can't stop fuckin’ with my head  Stop fucking with my head  My silence you break  The smile that you fake (you fake)    CHORUS:  There's not one thing   That you can say to make it right   Unless you say "I'm leavin’"  And if your not - then please tell me why   Please tell me why you can't     Save face   Say it to my face    Can I take all the filth in your head   All the words that you said (that you said)  And throw it away (throw it out)    You can't stop fuckin’ with my head  Stop fucking with my head  My silence you break   The smile that you take away    CHORUS (x2)    That shit you're talkin’ don't mean nothing to me anymore   Limp dick - you fuck stick - let's settle the score   Run and hide you know I'll find you anywhere   Motherfucker - two faced prick with hell to pay   What's real is real - it's time to step up to the plate again   Swing batter-batter, swing batter-batter, swing…..  What's real is real - it's time to step up to the plate again  Swing batter-batter…….  Fucked me for the last time!     Just take a swing…..  C’mon – you should’ve taken that swing…  Just take your swing…..    CHORUS (x2)    Swing…..  Just take your swing…..  Fuck you!     Just take your swing…..  You can't stop fuckin’ with my head  Stop fucking with my head    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It seems at times that our ex's seem to continue to haunt us in ways we aren't even aware of at times.  It seems that my dumbass ex submissive Dominant from Wichita has nothing better to do then to read my blog and jump to conclusions.  It seems he can't take a hint from people when they tell him to booger off, but then he wasn't the brightest bulb in the pack that is for sure.  I will give him the most stubborn award though, in that he can't just let things go and move on.  Friends of his have walked away from their friendship with him, and he just can't seem to figure out that when people are done they are done.  Well of course he has no clue what that is like considering he never closes doors and so forth, and has several women around to torment with his lies and deceptions at the same time.  He considers ex's women that he can have sex with when its convenient.  I do wish him all the happiness in the world, but until he quits his lies and stops hurting people with his deceptive manner he will never find the warmth of happiness.  Perhaps he and T are perfect for one another afterall, two peas in a pod.    I will say that most of my ex's are still friends of mine, only a few have I shut the door on completely, but lying is the nail that shuts that door forever.    So RV if you are reading this, why don't you just move the hell on and leave me and your ex friends alone!!!!  No one has any use for your lies and lame attempts of maintaining friendships!!!!!  :::stepping down off the soapbox:::  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Rose Artist: Bette Midler Words & Lyrics by: Amanda McBroom    Some say love, it is a river that drowns the tender reed. Some say love, it is a razor that leaves your soul to bleed. Some say love, it is a hunger, an endless aching need. I say love, it is a flower, and You its only seed.  It's the heart, afraid of breaking, that never learns to dance. It's the dream, afraid of waking, that never takes a chance. It's the one who won't be taken, who cannot seem to give. And the soul, afraid of dyin', that never learns to live.  When the night has been too lonely,      and the road has been too long, And you think that love is only for the lucky and the strong, Just remember in the winter far beneath the bitter snows, Lies the seed, that with the sun's love, in the spring becomes The Rose.       
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a hurried and exciting weeekend.  I drove to OKC for a short visit.  Left Saturday morning and returned Sunday evening.  It was a nice getaway although it took quite a toll on me physically.  Driving for 5 hours is not my idea of a fun thing, but I did have a great time.  As I drove by Wichita I did think of how I don't miss visiting my ex there and how happy I am to have put so much of that time behind me.  Living and loving life is a wonderful thing.  I have been so busy lately with my daughter in Europe that I haven't really had a lot of time to just sit back and relax.  Tomorrow is going to be a busy busy day and I am so looking forward to my little one coming home.  Well I have to go get ready for a date, so I better get moving.  spirit   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Redefine (Lyrics) by Soil  FIRST SIGHT Turns me around again Brings me face to face with my sin I've got it, always had it A reason to look within now TAKE FLIGHT To your sun again Burns the sin straight from my hands I've got it, always had it A reason to live within now Every time I fall You catch me And every time I lose control You help me, you save me And every time I lose myself You find me, redefine me MY GOD How stained my hands have been Makes me sick from inside out again I've got it, always had it A reason to look within now STAND CLOSE To my side again Never stuck a knife in my back, friend I've got it, always had it A reason to live within now Somebody to make me feel whole again (better) Somebody to make me want to love again (my life gets better) Somebody to make me see the sun again (my life gets better) Somebody to hold me, hold me Until this life feels better Every time I fall And every time I lose control You help me, you save me And every time I lose myself You find me, redefine me And every time I hate myself You love me, forgive me And every time I lose myself You find me, redefine me 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Memorial Day weekend was a nice relaxing weekend.  I had a lot of time to get caught up on things, spend time with my daughter and basically have a great weekend.  I did have some to reflect a lot and that sometimes is good and sometimes is bad.  I have enjoyed the last 4 months of dating, and I find myself at a place I have never been, and that is not wanting to date just one person.  I am enjoying different aspects of the different people I have met over the last several months, and can't see myself just dating one person right now.  The last person I dated was such a pathetic loser, that I guess I am very guarded right now.  I just can't believe that someone I had known for so long could have turned out to be such a liar.  Why can't people just be honest and straight forward?  I hold no anger towards him any longer, and in fact wish him to find all the happiness in the world.  I have given up on the pursuit of a D/s relationship, but have been enjoying dating the vanilla guys.  I believe I will find what I need in the most unlikely places.  I have found that most people in the lifestyle are clueless as to what its all about, and use it mostly as a way to manipulate and control situations in an unhealthy way.  I have even began to talk to submissive men again, and there is one that kind of brings a sparkle to my eye, and so perhaps I will enjoy having a male submissive again.  I have much to do today getting my daughter ready for her big trip to Europe tomorrow.  I just hope I can survive a week without her (LOL).    I am off to get some things done...  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is the day, we are heading out on the highway, looking for adventures, and whatever comes our way (yes I stole that from John Kay..lol).    Thunder in the Mountains, here we come!!!  See you next week.  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love how people hide and can't even come forward to who they really are.  Mystery person had the nerve to write on my post about cyber communication.  How can you compare a well written book, love letter, or a well written post to a simple and often times not well written instant messages?  Hardly the same.    As far as the mystery poster not revealing their identity, well I would say its very lame.  I am not hiding from anyone.  As far as RV, I am sure I have touched more people than his sorry excuse for a human being.  And just for the record, all these posts are logged by their IP addresses, so yes I am more than aware that things are not as hidden as a lot of people are aware.  In fact I have many things in place to keep track of who contacts me and so forth.    Don't post to my site unless you want to reveal your identity, as from this day forward such posts will be ignored and deleted!!  Okay lurking chickens, stay the heck away and go play in the dark by yourself!!!  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wooohooo its Friday and a great weekend is about to unfold **smiles**  The weather is gloomy but I am beaming sunshine within!!!  So much to do, and so little time.   No time to post, I am off to lunch with a "friend" **sly grin**  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      With the age of computers, cell phones, and so forth, one would think the world has come closer together, but in reality, these objects seem to have put up invisible walls around us.  The use of computers or cell phones give one the opportunity to communicate without any face to face contact hence making it very cold sometimes and without feeling.  Especially the use of computers.  We don't have to see people's faces or care if their feelings are intact, just sign off if we don't care to talk any longer.  I also think its a chicken shit way to communicate, because you don't have to have feelings, just throw some words down on a screen and wahlah instant conversation.  Well much is lost in the computer communication, mostly human feelings and concern.  So I would say people who use this as their main focus of conversation are people who really don't care about anyone else but theirsevles.  We truly have lost the art of conversation, no face to face conversation can ever be replaced by the lonely cold screen of a computer.  The phone, well at least you hear their voice and their emotions to a degree, but I firmly believe that it shouldn't be used as a media for important or possibly emotional conversations.  If you are miles apart, maybe I understand that, but if you are just across town, well what a selfish idea of talking to someone where you don't have to deal with the emotions and concerns of another.  Just my opinion here mind you, but seems to be quite the epidemic these days with all our convenient electrical devices.  Real people talk real conversations, not cyber scripted cold letters thrown on a screen, or a phone conversation that one can easily just hang up on or cut short because one doesn't want to deal with the communication with another.  Oh well, as far as we have come in this world, the farther we have gotten away from one another and built are own little cubicles.  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes I am counting down the days to Thunder in the Mountains.  Its going to be so much fun.  Spending time with G will be great as well as seeing some old friends too.  I have heard such good things about this event that I am giddy with anticipation.  I am off my blood thinners, and by that time should be fine to play **weg**    DENVER HERE I COME!!!!  spirit
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The funniest thing about liars are they will be the first to point fingers everywhere but to where the source of the lies lie and that is with themselves.  We all lie, we all have deceptions, but when it hurts people and are used to manipulate, then lies become destructive.  Delusional people will make up scenarios and try to take the blame off of themselves.  I fully take responsibility for my faults, for I know I am far from being perfect.  I have made mistakes, and will continue to do so, that is part of the growing process.  Those who feel they are so perfect and are without any faults, really need to have a lobotomy or at least electrical shock therapy (and not the fun kind...lol).    Okay, I am off to clean the house and get ready for my weekend :)  spirit
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>