<Blog>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me, Helen and Jo with our finished didgeridoos&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me at didgeridoo making workshop, Darwin, Australia.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Helen preparing to work on her didgeridoo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Strating material for our Didgeridoos&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Our new car, Mitch, at the Pinnacles, Western Australia.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jo and Helen at the Pinnacles, Western Australia.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jo and Helen, Kings Park, Perth, Australia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Pink Dolphin show, Sentosa, Singapore&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Merlion, Singapore&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Patronas Twin Towers, the tallest building in the world, KL, Malaysia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My new phone&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Helen, Dame and Kat, KL, Malaysia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cable car to Genting Highlands, Malaysia.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and a couple of birds I picked up on Langkawi.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Crocodile Park, Langkawi.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Warning sign at the Langkawi crocodile park&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Our home on Koh Samui, Thailand.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Helen feeding the elephants&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me with our hire car on Langkawi&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Helen in traditional farmers hat during our ox cart ride, Thailand. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Helen and our guide Nancy on the boat cruise in Bangkok. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Helen and me trying to avoid trees while elephant riding in Thailand. Note the lack of driver. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Barn Thai restaurant, Langkawi. Wooden path through mangrove swamp.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are some pictures of our trip so far.
     
    
</post>


<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having decided that Bangkok could no longer offer us anything else, (the stone is still in the ring by the way), we booked a flight from Bangkok to the island of Koh Samui. In order to get the cheapest flight we had to get the one at 8 pm ish but the check out time for the hotel was at 12 noon. After having managed to convey the message that we wanted our bags to be stored for collection later on (not an easy task when you are as completely inept at speaking Thai as Helen and me are), we went out in to Bangkok one last time to see what last treasures we could unearth. To our pure delight we discovered that said treasure took the form of Shrek 2 playing at the nearest cinema, (wasn't out yet in England). Having bought our tickets we went in and sat down in the rocking type chairs and waited for the fun to begin. However something Helen had neglected to mention to me was that in one of our guide books she had read that at the beginning of all films there is a section which says please be upstanding (or something like that) for his majesty the King, at which point a little film comes on showing the King of Thailand and his family and playing the national anthem. So there I was, sat down looking round when the whole audience stands up, including Helen who was expecting it, and so not completely sure of what is happening I also stand through this film while simultaneously feeling like a complete tit, thank you Helen. We arrived at the airport slightly early, by about 2 hours, and so had a bit of a wait till check in. The plane was subsequently delayed but we managed to pass the time by pointing out all the old westeners with Thai girlfriends (of which there are many) and whispering / screeching to each other "I your wife, I YOUR WIFE". When we finally boarded the plane it was one of the smaller variety, the type Eddie Izzard would describe as a VW Beetle with wings. An hour later and a lot of turbulence we descend to Koh Samui airport, which is basically two thatched huts with no walls, one of which has a sign saying terminal 1, the other terminal 2. We had arranged with the resort we were staying in to be collected from the airport so we reached our resort in no time. We were staying in a little 'terrace' hut with twin beds a bathroom and that glory of the modern technological world that is air conditioning.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having had our fill of the smog filled city, we decided to book another tour, but this time in the local national park, (not sure of name, you will have to look it up on a map, just west of Bangkok). At 7am our tour guide walked in to the hotel lobby to see two extremely tired English people (was going to put English men, but thought it wouldn't be very pc, on account of Helen being a woman), once he had introduced him,self as Winnie (yes as in the Pooh), he told us that due to space in the van we were going to have to travel separately, looking over to catch Helens eye I could see the same thoughts of kidnap attempts filtering through her mind. However with our breaths held we followed Winnie out of the lobby to the awaiting van. To our immense relief something had got lost in the translation and we were in the same van but just not sat together. With the relief visibly washing over us we climbed in to the van and met our fellow travelers for the day. There was a Canadian couple (almost made the mistake of asking if they were American), another couple (he was Australian but working in Cambodia and she was from Ecuador, still didn't manage to find out how they met) and three Irish lads sat at the back (who admittedly were more difficult to understand than the Thai's). So off we set out of the smog filled pit that is Bangkok, (quite liked it there actually) straight away Winnie pick up his microphone and starts the tour itinerary. Apparently our first stop was in about an hours time and we were to visit the happy room, an hour later the van stops at a petrol station which Winnie tells us is the happy stop, by this point I think I was the only one who hadn't realised what the Happy room / stop was. Back in the van we head off to a local market, again me and Helen exchange dubious looks as we had experienced the pressures of the markets in Bangkok (the stone is still in the ring by the way), however to our great delight the market here was not like the ones in Bangkok which are aimed at tourists, here was a market aimed at Thai people and so taking the pressure of us. Winnie went through many of the stalls with us describing what was on offer (live catfish and frogs were just some of the delights on offer), all the way round I couldn't help but think how stupid I would feel if I had to show a bunch of ignorant tourist around the veritable delights of Bury market. Once Winnie had done his bit he left us to roam round on our own and to meet back at the van. Back in the van once more we head of to a local village to meet up with a farmer who will take us for a ride in his ox carts. Up on arrival the rain starts and we are all handed those silly plastic sheet stings that go over your head to keep all the water in (out sorry), as well as plastic sheets we are handed traditional Thai style farmers hats (like the straw hat things you see Chinese people wearing in films) to keep the sun off our heads, the same sun which was currently behind a rain cloud. Having climbed aboard the carts (4 people in one cart) we set out across the field, the sun came out and we could see the jungle covered hills in the distance, all in all the ox cart riding not matter how much I make fun of it was enjoyable, about a 40 min round trip altogether. Back in the van once more and we head in to the national park (please see map, your own that is, I haven't attatched one). We pull into the car park as once again it begins to rain, and surrounding us is the jungle. Once out of the van Winnie advises that anyone in sandals or shorts should go to him to get a pair of anti-leech socks. Of course being the wimp that I am I rush to the front of the queue. Sporting my new sexy leech socks we set off through the jungle in search of a waterfall. The "path" we were on led to the river and after a bit of scrambling over the rocks and boulders we emerged at the top of the waterfall, of course by this point the heavens opened and it absolutely poured down, Helen at this point decided she needed a bit of help as she slipped on the rocks, Winnie to the rescue to help our damsel in distress, (unfortunately for Helen, as she was hoping one of the Irish guys would come to her aid). So there we all were stood on slippery boulders at the top of this spectacular waterfall when Winnie, (a.k.a crazy Thai dude) declares that we can climb down to the bottom if we wish (in the rain). Much to our relief he shows us where the steps are and declares he will go back to the van to await our return. Thinking, 'how hard can a few steps be' Helen and me set off down. On the way down we found out exactly how hard steps can be, especially when they were at the angles of these particular stairs. Upon reaching the bottom we shakily turn round to view the falls and realised it had been well worth it. If not for the rain it would have been just like a scene from the Beach, which coincidently some of the scenes were shot in the national park. After a laborious trip back up the stairs of doom we head back to the van and Winnie. Our next stop is for lunch, the "restaurant" was a thatched style hut with no walls but the food was welcome and good. Although part way through lunch I felt something bite my toe, looking under the table I discovered about 7 chickens wondering about. After lunch came the most exciting part of the trip, the elephant riding. Standing on a platform in the rain we awaited the elephants. Climbing on was not exactly an easy task, a bench for two people was strapped on the elephants back and so the first person to get on has to step further than the next across the elephants back. Obviously being the perfect gentleman I let Helen go first. Once everyone was seated we set of down an extremely muddy hill coming out at the bottom onto a concrete path, thinking that this was it for the journey, concrete paths all the way we settled back in to the chair.  The elephants however had different plans to the rest of us and veered of the path into the jungle, now faced with the task of trying not to get slapped in the face by the excess amount of foliage, we didn't have much time to spare to admire the view. The elephants then decided to descend in to the river which came up to the tops of their legs. As not so much foliage in the river we could relax slightly and began to enjoy the ride. Looking down in to the river we noticed some strange fruits floating on the surface, however, looking up we saw that the elephant in front of us was busy visiting the happy room. While getting out of the river we decided we would like photo evidence of our ride and so passed the cameras to our mahood (elephant driver) who subsequently jumped elephant and ran on ahead to take pictures for us leaving Helen and me in charge of the elephant. You no doubt saw the results on the news. All in all an absolutely tremendous day.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After the adventures of our first day in Bangkok we decided to take it easy and go for a leisurely stroll in to Bangkok city centre. However being that it was me and Helen we set off without directions and at around midday (what was that saying about mad dogs and English men?) after wondering around aimlessly we stumbled across a small franchise of a recognisable restaurant, that's right McDonald's (McThai). After having a drink there (about 30p) we set off again, once more we had no directions but were content to just wonder. By now we had the knack of refusing what ever anyone offered us, be it taxi, bags, and even a prostitute. After wondering aimlessly for a hour or so we came across the World Shopping Center, where after a brief stop in Starbucks we set out to see the goods on offer. Fortunately we were left alone to wonder the shops with out being hassled left, right and center. Not much else happened that day, apart from taking part in a survey by a lovely little chap by the name of "Bum"
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am again, to continue my tale of travels with a numpty (Helen for those of you who haven't met her, before any of you accuse me of being cruel it was her auntie who suggested the title). So where was I, ah yes the airport tour agency, they arranged a taxi for us to the Bangkok Palace Hotel which contrary to it's seedy sounding name turns out to be quite pleasant, unlike the taxi ride. Apparently there are no road traffic laws here or if there are only a minority has heard of them. Cars jumping in and out of lanes, undertaking when there is no room  motorcycles again are a law unto themselves weaving in and out of traffic carrying up to as many as 4 people only some of which have helmets. But hey traffic rant over, time to carry on. Once we had checked in we had a little nap (from which it was hard to recover) and then headed down to the hotel restaurant for some authentic Thai cooking (or Chinese if you are me and Helen). The following day we were eagerly waiting in the hotel lobby for our tour guide at 9pm, surprising both of us she did actually turn up and introduced herself as Nancy (which isn't her real name, just the one the company gave her so as not to confuse the tourists)so once again we are bundled in to the back of another taxi, the driver for which looked about 12, (Helen and me are still debating the sex of the driver) and off we set in to the sprawling smog filled city that is Bangkok, and straight in to the traffic jams. Just a normal jam though the super jams are reserved just for rush hour. Admittedly our new driver was not quite as crazy as the first, which is bringing me to believe that it was a she as Helen originally suggested (thank God she can tell the difference). The first temple we stopped at had a 5.5 ton Buddha made from solid gold, which was quite impressive until you looked about and saw the high levels of poverty around the city. We then decided to be slightly more adventurous and went on a flat bottomed boat trip down the river and through the canals of Bangkok, again an excellent time however the poverty stricken areas were depressing to say the least. Back in the taxi again and off to what we thought would be the hotel, Nancy had other ideas however and took us off to a jewelry makers/shop where Helen was subsequently bullied in to buying a ring with a "topaz" stone set in. This was achieved by the use of the following clever sales speech,  "I been your country, I been Marks Spencer, you come my country you buy topaz" Will keep you updated on how long the stone stays in. Seeing her obvious success Nancy then proceeded to take us to another jewelry shop and a tailors, however this time we were strong and managed to stay the attempts of the several sales persons. After escaping the voracious clutches of many sales people we eventually made it back to the Hotel where we hid for the remainder of the day, free from the attempts of the taxi drivers, tuk tuk drivers, and motorcycle taxis plus the numerous sales people all of which are sure they have exactly what you are after (even if you are not sure yourself). So day 1 ended, will keep you informed of further developments
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello everyone and greeting from Thailand. Finally arrived after a grueling 13 hour flight to Singapore, 2.5 hour wait in Singapore then a 3 hour flight up to Bangkok. Was absolutely knackered, but who can blame me when they are showing all three Lord of the Ring films on the flight, however Helen the wimp that she is decided that sleep might be the better option, more fool her. Arrived at Bangkok airport feeling a little worse for ware and were captured by a travel agency dealing in tours round Bangkok, and in our sleep befuddled states we eagerly signed up for the Temple and City tour for the following day. They also arranged a taxi for us to the hotel and prob charged over the odds, but at the time we didn't care. Am running out of time now so will update again at another time to let you all know about the tour etc.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finished packing today, (started packing in fact), have just about got everything in but have had to leave some stuff behind, which I will no doubt need in the near future. Don't think I will be able to sleep at all tonight, so will probably fall asleep at 4am and need to be leaving for the airport at 6:30 ish, so lucky Helen will have to listen to me snoring for the whole 13 hour plane journey. Got to go now as have some last minute phone calls to make. Next entry will prob be from Bangkok, Thailand.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Leaving Langkawi we arrived at the airport to be told that the flight was free seating, which I think is the nice way of saying it's every man for himself, and there seemed to be a thousand children all running about and screaming, not a happy situation to be in.  Seeing as we had only booked our hotel in Kuala Lumpur (KL) that morning, they said that if we were not there by 8pm they would give our room to someone else, so once we landed we decided to pay the extra and get a taxi instead of the train. Fortunately we arrived with about 20 minutes to spare. The hotel itself was in Mid Valley which is about a 5 - 10 journey on the LRT (some train thing, not sure what it stands for) or the monorail, and was built on to the side of the Mid Valley Mega Mall. Not much to say about KL apart from that it was fantastic, there seemed to be more shopping malls than people and the prices while still not as cheap as Thailand were cheaper than home. Unfortunately we didn't have any room in our bags to fit extra stuff in, although Helen decided not to let this stop her. On our second day we decided to book a tour with the agency in the hotel, and so the next day we were off to the Genting Highlands. The highlands are basically on top of a mountain \ big hill, where some guy decided to clear the forests and build Malaysia's only casino, obviously the hotels followed and now he is one of the richest guys in Malaysia. On our way to the highlands the tour guide turned to us and said it is very unusual for westeners to go there and it is mainly Asians, especially the Chinese, who enjoy gambling, and the last time he took westeners there was about a year ago. Deciding not to let this stop us we continued on. Once at the bottom of the hill / mountain we boarded the cable car which they proudly told us was the longest in South East Asia and the fastest in the world. Gripping my seat nervously we set off over the tropical jungle, only loosening my hold when we were informed that the cable car was actually built by the Swiss. Once at the top you could notice a considerable drop in the temperature and it was now a mere 20 degrees Celsius. At the top there was an indoor and outdoor theme park, few thousand Asians and about 5 westeners. Despite thinking that if we had known what to expect we probably wouldn't have gone, we decided that it was all worth it for the view and the cable car. One day we decided to go up the KL tower (KL equivalent of BT tower only bigger) and got the monorail to what we thought was the correct station, following the signs we set off to find the tower. After about a 30 minute walk, up and down hill, through jungle in the sweltering heat and humidity, we finally found the tower, and the road leading up to it. The views from the top of the tower were outstanding and the entrance fee included an audio tour so we could know what we were looking at. The other towers that we tried to climb included the Patronas Twin Towers, which are the tallest buildings in the world, unfortunately they had no tickets left for that day so we though we would come back when the school holidays were finished. Later on that day we met up with Kat (from the Art Gallery) and her husband Dame, who were on holiday visiting Kats family. Was great to meet up with them especially as they could show us all the places we would never have found without them, unfortunately this also included a Cantonese Techno Club (Canto Techno) which we went to one night with Kats auntie and uncle, (who referred to us as the Caucasians, but in a nice way), this was on our last night in KL and by the time we got back to the hotel the paper had already been delivered and they were starting to set up for breakfast, however we had a great night and Kats uncle and auntie were fantastic, if not slightly crazy, and offered us lots of advice on where to go and what to see. We never did get to go up the Twin Towers as every time we tried we were told they had no more tickets and in order to get them we would have to come at 8:30 am, in the end I decided that seeing as the tickets only allow you access to the Sky Bridge, which links the towers and is only half way up, it wasn't worth it and it probably wasn't the tallest building in the world, I'm sure it only goes up to the Sky Bridge and from then on it is done with mirrors.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As usual being the ever forward thinking people that we are we managed to arrive in Langkawi during the school holidays so everywhere was fully booked. Fortunately we managed to get accommodation at the Helang Hotel which is right next to Langkawi's airport. It was a bit out of the main town, about half an hour, but it looked nice enough and it was reasonably priced. Walking in to our room, carrying our own bags, the news of our non tipping seems to have spread to all of Malaysia, we were amazed that the room was so cheap, it had two queen sized beds marble slate floor, writing desk, table and chairs by the window looking out over the pool. The bathroom had a toilet, bath with shower and another separate shower cubicle and a sink with a notice to say that if it was damaged it would cost 2000 ringgits to replace, however after taking a closer look we realised that beneath the plush looking decor things were not as they seemed. The sheets on Helens bed were dirty and looked like they hadn't been washed and there was a general air of uncleanness. We didn't let this stop us from enjoying the island though and so we set out to see what we could discover, inevitably we ended up at the airport as this was the only building within walking distance. After enquiring about tickets to Kuala Lumpur we ended up buying two, which gave us five days to enjoy the island.  Leafing through the may brochures we had  picked up from the ferry terminal we decided to go for a trip to the crocodile park. After getting a taxi there it started to rain but the ingenious business minds of the Malaysian people didn't let the rain affect the visitors, they achieved this by handing out umbrellas as you entered. We are still not sure if the park was set up to help crocodiles or just for entertainment, unfortunately the entertainment argument was fuelled by the gift shop which sold everything you could imagine that could be made from crocodile skin. Further evidence was supplied by the show that they put on, which involved dragging one poor crocodile round by it's tail and standing on another one, at which point we both hoped the crocodile would try it's luck and bite them. The other down side to the crocodile park was that every time we walked past a particular family the old Chinese grandmother would just look at me, smile and then laugh, still not sure why. After the success of the crocodile park we decided on the bird park which was a big improvement, and the aquarium as well, the only down side to the aquarium was that after getting a taxi there we had no way of getting back again, after asking at the ticket counter if they could phone a taxi for us the woman behind the counter called to someone who then directed us to his car, at first we thought he was a taxi driver but after a while we realised that he was just some bloke who happened to have his car with him, not even sure if he worked for the aquarium. After a couple of days of having to get taxis we decided to look into hiring a car so we would be more free to roam the island and it's golden sandy beaches. We hired a car from the ferry terminal and after refusing all the top of the range vehicles he offered us we settled on a small Malaysian car, which actually turned out to be excellent and not what we expected at all. The only bad point about it was that the front window and the back had a red stripe across the top which was not transparent and so you could only see out of the bottom half of the window, the only answer to this was to practice biddy driving. Helen decided to drive also, which she hasn't done for 2 years, I was a bit nervous at first, white knuckle is one way to describe it, but she was actually quite good and only ran over one chicken which had already been hit by someone else. Our last night on the island we decided to go to a restaurant called Barn Thai which is located in the middle of a mangrove swamp and so you have to walk on the wooded pathway to the restaurant which is lit by fairy lights, the food and the surroundings were fantastic. The following day we had to return the car and so we headed back to the ferry terminal once more, when we got there the guy we had rented it off wasn't in his office and so after a few attempts by other people to locate him for us one of them gave us our 50 Ringgit deposit back and we handed him the keys, still not sure if he was being nice or had just bought a car for 50 ringgits.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Arriving at our hotel on Penang we seemed to confuse the check in staff, still not sure why, and so they asked us to sit in the lobby till the room was ready. Not long after the porter came over and placed our bags on his trolley and proceeded to show us to our room, telling us every useful piece of information about Penang. Arriving in our room we said thank you to the porter and only afterwards realised that we had completely ignored all of his hints for a tip. Looking round the room we noticed that there was only a double bed when we had booked two singles, letting Helen go to sort things out I relaxed and waited. Five minutes later we were walking down the corridor to our new room, carrying our own bags, the porter seemed to take his lack of tip personally. The next morning we descended to breakfast, while trying to avoid the porter, and I couldn't help but notice a few pitying looks from the hotel staff, news of our move from a double bed to two single beds had obviously spread. The hotel we were in was in George Town, the main town on Penang, left over from the colonial days. Wondering about in the midday sun once more we discovered a shopping mall and decided to pop in to have a look. It is amazing the high levels of tack that is available over here, and I think we bought most of it even though our backs are braking already under the strain of our bags. By this point in our trip I had got fed up with wearing creased clothes and so decided to buy a travel iron, it worked twice, once in the shop and once in the hotel, but for some obscure reason I am still carrying it round with me, think its in the hope that it will miraculously start working again. Feeling a bit cultural we decided to head for the museum and art gallery, which is dedicated to the Malaysian people and their origins, know it sound bit boring but was actually very good, they had a few interactive exhibits as well. Obviously when I say interactive exhibits I mean powerpoint and a projector. After feeling that we had exhausted George Town we booked two tickets on the express ferry, we were actually looking for tourist information but the Malaysians are experts in sales, from Penang to Langkawi, which is another island further north than Penang. Two more handy travel tip for you all now,  1) don't just get the express ferry because it is quick, as it rides up and down every single wave,  and 2) if you do book an express ferry, don't have scambled eggs for breakfast.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spending a few days in Hat Yai we decided to move on as there wasn't that much to do there and we had already exhausted the shopping mall across the road from the hotel. We booked a coach to take us south across the Thai boarder in to Malaysia to the island of Penang. The following morning, after discovering that Helen had had some of her Malaysian, Singapore and Australian currency stolen, we suspect while in Bangkok, we went to the coach pickup point feeling a little bit bitter about Thailand now, and looking forward to Malaysia. The coach pulled up and Helen and me climbed in, note the Helen and me part, we were the only ones on the coach. So we set off to Penang with the whole of the coach to Helen, me and the driver, who didn't look like the kidnapper type, so feeling safe we sat back and enjoyed the scenery as we sped through the remains of Thailand. Thankfully the coach driver didn't take us to any jewelry shops, (ring and stone still ok), so we weren't coerced in to buying any more Thai rubbish,no offence meant to Helens purchase, looks nice actually (for glass). Arriving at the boarder we sat on the coach not knowing what to do as neither of us have ever crossed a land boarder before. Seeing our lack of movement the coach driver pointed towards a hut and grunted, which due to my varied language skills I interpreted as "you need to see the person in the customs hut to get your passports checked and stamped, and don't forget your Thailand exit forms and the Malaysian arrivals form." After going through the necessary procedures of more grunting and stamping we boarded the coach and set off once more in to what we thought was Malaysia. Apparently though it was just a strip of land between the two boarders as 5 minutes later we pulled up at another set of buildings and had to do all the grunting and stamping again. Once we were in Malaysia, properly this time, we pulled up a roadside cafe type thing, where we had our first taste of traditional Malaysian drinks and cuisine (coke, sprite and BBQ flavoured crisps). On the coach again and we seemed to have picked up two extra passengers, one of which I suspect was the drivers mothers who had his laundry with her. About an hour and a half later we arrived in Butterworth, a coastal town which is connected to Penang by bridge. Our first glimps of Penang was as we drove across the bridge at night with a lightning storm playing out above, fantastic.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having decided that we had been round the island too many times, literally, we checked out of the resort and in typical fashion didn't have a clue what to do next. So we started to walk along the road with our heavy bags on our back, heading in the direction of the ferry terminal, about at 15-20 minute drive. Fortunately after about 2 minutes a songthaew (cross between taxi and bus, basically fit as many people in as possible and take them exactly where they want to go), dubiously climbing in to the back we decided that kidnap was the easier option than walking in the baking heat with our bags. Arriving at the ferry terminal we paid the driver, about twice as much as the locals, and no sooner had we done this there was somebody there trying to sell us a ticket. This time however we took them up on the offer and bought two tickets for the bus, which sounds odd I know but the bus goes on the ferry and then from the ferry terminal on the main land it takes you to Surrat Thani, about an hour away, which is where the main train station is. So feeling thoroughly pleased with ourselves we set off to Surrat Thani. Once we arrived in Surrat Thani we planned to get a train a.s.a.p to Hat Yai as our guide book says that a stay in Surrat Thani is only recommended if death is the alternative, or along those lines anyway. This is where our luck ran out, on arriving in Surrat Thani we headed straight for the train station only to find that the next train was at 12.55 that night and the following train at 6.40 am the next morning. Feeling a bit tired and dejected we walked back to where the coach had dropped us off, which coincidently also turned out to be a guesthouse. Sitting down and having a bit of lunch, we decided to book a night at the guesthouse and get the 6.40 am train. After paying for our room, about 50p each, we were escorted upstairs while our host showed us the amenities on the way. Said amenities took the form of a drop down toilet which glancing over at Helen I could see neither of us had a clue how to use. Silently praying that I wouldn't need the loo till we got to the train station we continued up the stairs, which I couldn't help but think held our doom at the top. Our "room" was one of three on our level, it was partitioned from the other two by the clever use of fiberboard. The bed was a double with mattress which felt like it was stuffed with concrete and two pillows which I suspect were filled with sawdust. Lying awake in our sleeping bags, trying not to make contact with anything, we admired the local insect life which also seems to have booked our room for the night. After a restless night in what would make the scummiest ming pit in Bury look positively palacial we headed straight for the station. A little tip for you all now, while booking a train ticket in a foreign country don't just say yes to a question because you don't understand what they are trying to say and you don't want to appear an ignorant foreigner. The result of such a mishap would be to sit in third class on solid wooden benches for a six hour twenty minute train ride. Arriving in Hat Yai a bit sore we immediately spot our prize for enduring the past couple of days. Rising majestically above the bustling streets of Hat Yai like a shining monolith symbolising all that is good and right with the world, lay the Novotel. Exiting the train station to the calls of "Teksi" coming in at every angle we headed off to the Novotel hoping that they would have a room available for us. Obviously when we decided to ignore the taxis we didn't take in to account the size of the hotel and what that would do to our distance perception (bit like standing in Paris and walking to the Eiffel Tower just because you can see it). Fortunately a room was available, bit more expensive than the other hotels we had stayed in but still very reasonable. God only knows what they thought when we entered the lobby, after our train ride and sleepless night, but they let us in all the same and provided us with a drink, which I can only describe as purple, while we checked in.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having arrived late on the island we collapsed on our beds turned on the fan, tried to turn on the air conditioning but failed, and subsequently drifted of to an unbelievably uncomfortable roasting nights sleep. Waking in the morning both a bit tired, understatement really, we drag ourselves off to find the restaurant and breakfast. The restaurant was of the same fashion of the airport, thatched roof open walls. However unlike the airport the restaurant was situated by the pool which was just above the white tropical sandy beach. Having consulted the ten maps we seemed to have accumulated overnight we decided to ignore them all and never learning from our mistakes we set off for a walk in the midday sun. About an hour later having not got anywhere we were back in our room, fortunately though we notice that the air conditioning is now working and all it had needed was batteries in the remote. Seeing how bad our attempt to walk the island turned out we looked in to hiring a jeep for the day, neither of us were brave enough to try the motorbike, which actually tuned out quite cheap, about 350 Bahts each, about 5 pounds. So the following day we hired the jeep and went on our own tour of the island with me driving and Helen navigating. Inevitably the main conversation in the car was as follows: Helen - There's a scenic look out point just coming up Peter - Where? Helen - We just past it. Peter - It's ok it's an island we'll be coming back past it in about an hour. Eventually my responses to Helens direction improved and we turned off to go look at a waterfall that was marked out on one of the maps. However once we arrived I pulled in to the car park and realised that I didn't know where reverse was as nowhere or the gear stick did it mention which gears were where. Luckily I had parked with enough space to be able to do a u-turn and so we thought we could go look at the waterfall then sort out the jeep. Turning off the engine we then realise that we can't get the keys out of the ignition. After sitting there for about 5 minutes we decided to head on back to the resort to ask the guy what to do. As you might guess when we pulled up back at the resort I accidentally nudged the gear stick and it popped in to reverse, so now having solved that dilemma all that was left was to ask the guy how to remove the key. Looking at us as if we were stupid (no comments) he simply put his hand through the open window and removed the key. Handing it back to me he just smiled and walked away. Feeling like a numpty I got back in the jeep, slightly more embarrassed as I hadn't actually seen how he had managed it, not wanting to go back to ask again I had a play around and eventually realised that you have to push the key in in order to get it out. Having solved all our car dilemmas, for now, we set off once more round the island, passing a lot of scenic lookout spots on the way. We finally managed to find a beach where a parculiar set of rock formations can be found, they are called grandfather and grandmother. After looking up and down the beach for some time we finally notice which rocks the names referred to, and five minutes later we were back in the jeep feeling a parculiar mixture of revulsion and the giggles. I will leave it to you to try to form the images, I would rather not go in to detail. Later that night we set off in the jeep to find a restaurant called The Cliff that we had heard about. After driving past it a few times I eventually managed to park and in we went. The restaurant was magnificent, you got to sit on a balcony over the cliffs looking down at the ocean below, fantastic food well worth a visit. Sticking to the food theme, the following night we found another little restaurant called the Five Island which was located on the beach, again an excellent restaurant. Helen felt a bit on edge at first due to the lizard climbing the wall near our table, but as the wine kept flowing she seemed to forget about it, or at least not care anymore. The only down side to the evening was Helen feeling a bit ill as we drove back to the resort, which was apparently the fault of the bumpy roads and not the wine.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't got that much to say about our journey round Australia so far, so will do a quick summary. Leaving Kalbarri we headed on up the coast to Monkey Mia, which is one of many golden sandy beaches on the Australian coast. Still camping, although we can get the tent up in just a matter of minutes now, instead of hours. While there we got the chance to see some dolphins, which swim right up to the beach almost. Back in the car and the next planned stop was to be Coral Bay, however once we got there we couldn't find anywhere to stay as it was school holidays. So we continued up the coast to Exmouth and managed to get in at a campsite there. While in Exmouth we hired snorkeling gear and went to Turquoise Bay. Was fantastic, there were hundreds of fish swimming about you, and some coral to admire as well. Broome was our next stop and fed up of camping by this point we stayed in a hostel. Not much to report from Broome, except that it is a really nice town and very good for relaxing, especially if you have spent the past week in tents and driving. Broome to Darwin was a long slog, and can't remember now how long it took us to get there. Anyway while in Darwin we decided to treat ourselves and so booked a didgeridoo making course. Mike, our teacher, picked us up in the morning and took us to the bosses house and the workshop. We then picked out our didgeridoos from a wood pile outside and proceeded to shave them down. Helen and Jo being clever had only picked small pieces and so didn't have much to shave off theirs. Me on the other hand picked one that weighed 6kg and needed to get it down to 3 or 4 kg. A lot of blisters later and it was finally at 3.5kg. A lot of sanding and treating then took place, followed by lunch and didge playing lessons. Helen found this quite difficult but only because she kept giggling. The finished didgeridoos can be seen at holdenpix.blogspot.com From Darwin we planned to head to Cairns which would have been about a 5 day drive. After 1 day we decided to go to Alice Springs instead, which took us 2 days from Darwin, although on the last day we did do just over 1000km (600 miles) in the one day. We camped the night in Alice and then the following day went to see Uluru (Ayers Rock), which wasn't as close to Alice as we had thought, it is about 500km away. Camping again at Uluru we set off to the rock a couple of hours before sunset. It is amazing, at first I was thinking I was only going because it was expected of you when going to Australia, and people at home would shout if we didn't go, however as I said it was amazing to see and to watch people trying to climb up and down it. Out of respect for the Aboriginal people we didn't climb all over their sacred sight, and the fact that 35 people have died doing so. We also went to the special sunset viewing point and waited, looking at the rock as the sun set. Think I was expecting some fantastic light show and the rock to change through the colours of the rainbow, instead it just went dark. Think it would have been much more impressive if it was cloudless. Bit more travel advice for you all now, when driving in Australia be on the look out for wandering livestock, there are stretches of road that have no fences, the result of which is as Helen found out, having to do an emergency stop for a cow, only missing it because at the last second the cow ran out of the way. Think we did clip its tail as we screeched passed, doing a little skid on the road as we went. Other dangers also include camels, again when Helen was driving, this time however she managed to stop the car safely at a couple of meters from the camels, who then refused to move off the road. Kangaroos are the other things to look out for as evidence that they don't survive many impacts are everywhere, as is the evidence of the cows. Back in Alice Springs we sold the car to Mingo Motors, who gave us $700 for him, although $300 less than we had originally paid for him, it's still not bad seeing as we had cracked the windscreen, the tape player still didn't work, he was quite rusty in places, and the day before fourth gear kept popping out while you were driving. From Alice we boarded a coach bound for Cairns, and 36hours later we arrived. This country has too much space.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Setting out from Perth in our car we realised after about an hour of driving aimlessly that maybe we should buy a map. One map purchase later and we set out once more. We had decided to head up the West Coast and our first stop was Cervantes. Finally arriving after nightfall we booked in to the local hostel and were advised to view the Pinnacles (rocks in a desert, see pictures at holdenpix.blogspot.com) at sunrise. Waking up the next morning we looked out of the window, saw the clouds, and went back to sleep. Later that morning, once we had checked out we decided to pay a visit to the Pinnacles after all, especially as the weather had cleared and we now had a bright blue sky. Driving round the Pinnacles was fun, especially because Jo was driving at the time, and we successfully managed to avoid smashing the car in to a rock. Sharing the driving we set off to our next stop, Kalbarri, a few hundred kilometres north. The roads are incredibly straight, long and boring, especially with no tape player, the result was a sort of madness induced warbling we liked to think of as singing harmoniously. Arriving in Kalbarri we booked in at the campsite and set about trying to put up our tent in a full Carry On style. About an hour later, with the light fading, I got fed up and walked to the nearest tent to us and asked if they knew what to do. Fortunately they were experts and soon figured out what went where and in no time our tent was standing proud. Feeling a bit stupid we went to the bottle store and bought Mark and Linda, our tent experts, a pack of beers to say thank you, and a box of wine for our selves. That night we sat up looking at the stars sharing our drinks with Mark and Linda. While in Kalbarri we booked a river cruise, yes another, and as we set off up the river we were treated to champagne, a cup of tea, and a cream scone, thoroughly British. While out on the river it was approaching sunset, and so the temperature was dropping, which led to Jo and Helen striking their pensioner poses, huddling underneath a blanket.   Now for a couple of things I have forgotten to mention.   While in KL with Kat and Dame we were in the Times Square shopping mall, the biggest in South East Asia, when we were asked to pose at the information desk, so they could take our picture and use it for their magazine. Fortunately I think I managed to hide behind the others.   In Singapore we were walking down the street when Jo was approached by a lady who we think was from Indonesia. The lady asked her about a photograph, thinking she wanted Jo to take their picture she agreed, the next minute the lady had her daughters surrounding Jo and then dragged Helen and me over to pose with them all as she proceeded to take our picture with her daughters. Think it was Helen and Jo's blond hair they wanted a picture of and me because they felt sorry.    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Leaving the humid shores of south east Asia behind we set off to Perth, Australia, (after a brief stop at duty free). Forward planning once again we arrived in Australia with no place booked to stay, we did however have a name of a hostel that had been recommended to us. Getting on the bus we set off to the Witches Hat hostel, in Northbridge, Perth. Walking in I was a bit depressed, as I was in a separate dorm from Helen and Jo for the first night and by now I was used to living in Hotels. However by the second night we were all in the same dorm and things didn't look so bad after a descent nights sleep. Perth it self is a great city with free public transport in the inner city zones. While in Perth we also met up with Kate, a friend of ours that we used to work with and has been in Perth for almost a year. We also got invited to a party at her house, and I have been banned from reporting anymore than that about the party.  We didn't actually do much in Perth apart from wander the city and the parks, but was good to have a week of relaxing and not having to get up early every morning with the feeling that we should do something.  Perth is also where we purchased our car, Mitch, with the hope of it getting around Australia and to Sydney. As per usual we looked hard in to finding the perfect machine for our travels, and so bought the first car off the first dealer we went to, saying that however he hasn't failed us yet, apart from the tape player, which may not seem major but while driving on endless straight roads for miles at a time with no radio as you are nowhere near any form of civilization, it would come in handy. After we bought the car we also set about buying camping equipment, which would save us money on accommodation, we also bought 32 cheap batteries which we later discovered didn't work.  While in Perth I also took the opportunity of having my tongue pierced, while my mother isn't about to shout at me.   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had arrived in Singapore about three days before Jo was due to arrive, so we spent most of our time wondering around the streets looking at the sights we didn't have to pay for, so when Jo arrived we wouldn't have to pay again. One afternoon after running out of ideas we went on a boat trip up and down the river on a bum boat. The ride was good, if a bit choppy, and we were shown the sights, such as the merlion statue, which is some sort of mythological Singaporean creature. Singapore is fantastic and I would strongly recommend it to anyone, the public transport is great and the underground network is years ahead of Londons. You can purchase a travel card that can be topped up at machines at all the stations and can also be used on the busses, taxis and even to pay for your McDonald's. We were slightly disappointed in the Raffles hotel as we were expecting something spectacular, which I am sure it would have been if it hadn't been for all the skyscraper's surrounding it. On the day that Jo was due to arrive Helen and me had to get up at stupid o'clock in the morning and catch the first MRT train (mass rapid transport), underground thingy, to the airport. By the time we had arrived Jo was already through customs and was stood waiting for us. We all headed back to the hotel Helen and me were staying in, to pack and move to the YMCA which we had booked a few months back. Thinking that our luck was in it turned out that the International YMCA was only a short walk round the corner from our hotel, so we carried our bags round in the unbearable heat and humidity. Approaching reception we handed over our booking confirmation slip to the receptionist, only to be told that our booking was actually for the Metropolitan YMCA which was a taxi ride away. Exiting the building feeling like idiots we hailed a taxi to take us to the right place, which turned out to be quite far out and not as handily located as the other YMCA. When we arrived we were told that we were too early to check in, but they would store our bags for us, so we could go out and to come back at 12 noon. Getting another taxi back to Orchard road we showed Jo the sights and went for some lunch. Returning back to the YMCA at 12:30 pm we checked in and sat and waited for our room to be ready, they had to stop the cleaners from having their lunch so they could prepare our room, about an hour later we were told that due to overbooking they had upgraded us (first time I have ever been upgraded) to an apartment. Entering the apartment we were slightly in shock as it had two bedrooms, both en-suite, a kitchen, lounge area with TV and more importantly a washing machine and dryer. We spent the next few days doing everything that we had wanted to do, but needed money spending on. We got on the cable car to Sentosa Island, actually we got on the wrong side so ended going up to the top of some hill in the opposite direction of Sentosa. Eventually getting on the right side we headed across the water to Sentosa. On the island we went to the underwater world there, which was good but would have been better if not for the 10,000 other people trying to look around as well, we also went to a pink dolphin show down by the beach which was great, but couldn't get any pictures because I wasn't fast enough, do have lots of pictures of splashes and ripples in the water. We also went to the night safari at the Singapore zoo which was spectacular, the animals aren't caged but are separated from the public. You could walk round the place or get on the tram, we did both and were pleased we did as you got a commentary on the tram also, and got slightly closer to the animals. The only down side was that we thought we would find somewhere to eat once we got there, so when we turned up to find only KFC, we were slightly disappointed, especially as Jo is vegetarian. What was even more disappointing is that KFC had no chicken left and had just sold their last portion of fries. Once we passed through the gates of the night safari though we noticed a large amount of restaurants and realised that KFC was on the normal zoo side, which had closed for the night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Leaving Malacca behind us we sped off to the bus station and boarded a coach to Johor Barhu, which is on the Malaysian, Singapore boarder. We were warned against staying there, by Kats Uncle and Auntie, as there is not much there, however we still had a few days left to get to Singapore to meet Helens friend Jo from home, who was flying out to join us. Not much to say about Johur apart from the information we had gathered about the place was true and there really was nothing to do there, so we spent one day roaming around malls and then decided that we would continue to Singapore the following day. We had already decided to travel over the boarder by train, so the following day we got the receptionist at the hotel to phone a taxi for us to go to the train station. The receptionist informed us that if we were traveling to Singapore we would have to go to customs first. The taxi then showed up and dropped us off at the customs shack, for want of a better word. Passing through customs we had no trouble and emerged on the other side of the fence looking for the train station to take us over the bridge to Singapore. The strangest part was that we kept seeing road signs saying Singapore, it's the first time I had seen a road sign pointing to a country. After about five minutes of looking we gave up and boarded the public bus, less than a pound to cross to another country is not bad at all. I was expecting the bridge to be an amazing feat of engineering, something to rival the Sidney Harbour Bridge, as it turned out it would be a hard push to rival a hump back bridge over a stream. It was just a flat bridge not even a suspension cable in sight. Arriving in Singapore slightly disappointed I soon discovered that Singapore had a lot more to offer. It's amazing to see the difference between two countries that are only separated by a small stretch of water (and a crappy bridge). Passing through customs on the Singapore side, and getting another stamp in our passports, (why do they always stamp it on a page where you already have a stamp by the way?), we headed to the taxi rank and asked him to take us to the Hotel 81 classic, which we had seen on the internet and was quite cheap. Pulling up at the Bencoolen 81 Hotel we decided that it was good enough, if not the one we had asked to go to. As it turned out it was better than what we had chosen, as it was just off Orchard road, the main shopping road in Singapore.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having recovered from our night out, we packed up our things and checked out of the hotel. A quick taxi ride later and we were at the bus station in KL, where the previous day, with help from Kat and Dame, we had bought two tickets to Malacca. As soon as we got out of the taxi we were being asked where we were going and then being offered cheap prices to take us there, non however could compete with the RM8 (8 ringgits) we got the coach for. About 1 pound for a 2.5 hour coach journey. The bus station in KL is not the most luxuriant of bus stations and even manages to make Bury Bus station look positively pleasant. After a short wait, while trying not to breath, we climb on board our coach and set off south. A couple of stops and hours later we arrive in Malacca and our hotel. While trying to pay for the hotel using my credit card, which is a chip and pin card, the receptionist asked me to enter my PIN, which obviously I had in my phone cleverly disguised as a phone number. However it seems it was a bit too cleverly disguised as I couldn't remember which bit was the PIN and which were just random numbers. An embarrassing couple of tries later and Helen ended up paying. The following day we booked a river cruise which was nice, although we were slightly put off by the lizards in the water, which we were informed were closely related to the Komodo Dragons. The rest of our days in Malacca were spent wandering the streets and malls and trying to avoid the river and it's dragon kin.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>