<Blog>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just went to do a new post here. Nothin' different, really... And when I clicked on title, one of the previous ones was "porn". >  >     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Every time I go to school, I end up seeing someone on a computer doing OMG ILEGLE ACTEVETYS. Or maybe just in the library.  These people are doing stuff like looking up lyrics to rap and looking at shoes. ... ... ... What the fuck? Shoes and rap?   I was in a chat the other day, as well, and a guy kept linking me to his computer. -_-  Anyway, I'm out. This'll probably be rewritten next time I'm all overfocused...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My name's Arcane Cossack. ^^   I got this name quite a while back, in the Bob and George chatroom. (www.bobandgeorge.com, or #bobandgeorge in irc.darkmyst.org). I was switching names a lot, never staying with one because I'm odd like that.   Someone got pissed at me and ranted at me, so I stayed with RavenZero. Then I had to leave for, like, 5 months, thus losing the love of my life at the time, Yaka.  I left the name RavenZero and took up Arcane. Then later I RPed, and got Cossack added on to it, after my character's creator.  The "Veliz Ralonious Kaledemon" in the middle of it is from a great inspiration, named Myrmadon. His comic's up at bobandgeorge, as well. It's funny.  Thanks for the idea for a post, bro. (You know who ya are.)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Family people aren't included here...  [] Trinam. [] Ellie. [] PDmon. [] Steve. [] Juke. [] Vile. [] Yaka. [] A certain Ex of mine. [] Milly. [] Docks. >>" [] Pishi [] Geemer  (And, in a friendly way)  [] Allen [] Matt [] Brittany [] Beth [] My mexican homie peoples out in my neighborhood  Well, anyway. I didn't include some because they might take offense at being on a list like that...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Normally I don't do sentimental stuff like this, but this is a dedication to someone who affected my life a bit.  A while ago, I was in a class called Library Media. A while after, when I finally talked, I met a girl. I know, most people reading this are going to say "OMG TEH ROMNANCE STORY", but no. All those people please report to the giant cliff of doom now. >>"   Anyway. We talked. A lot. She was really nice, but had depression and all that and I learned a strange amount about the phases of teenageness. I also learned people at my school don't neccesarily suck. >>" I was all happy 'n stuff die to the evils of having a girlfriend then...   After that girl left to the wilds of Texas, I was dumped by my girlfriend. I went into depression and all, missed a lot of sleep, and memories of that class cheered me up 'n stuff.  Cheers to ya.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The reason behind that phrase is because my ex-girlfriend disagreed with me about it. It was silly. I mean, she'd argue for a hour against me about it.   Nobody agrees with me about it, and if anyone does, I'll glomp them. Completely. 'cept if they're already taken by someone else. ;_;
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      People at my school always rant about everything sucking that I like, and then saying that the XBox pwnz0rz or whatever the hell the cool kids say nowadays. -_-  I rant about people at my school too much. x.x Next post is about something good, really.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today in class, a girl near me decided she was bored with class. So she slammed a book down full force on the ground. This didn't get the teacher's attention, so she did it -again-. x.x And I'm all noise-sensitive. Others decided to go use the computer and marvel at such things as www.google.com and such. -_-  Ever have this homicidal urge? : Anyway... Docks go out in the water.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>