<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Where's everyone?  Holidays. I used to look forward to holidays a lot. Holidays then represented the only time I could stop studying and just sit around the whole day doing nothing but popping of German soldiers like a bunch of daisies in a WWII game. Now? Erhhh.... Let's face it. I mix with a lot of high-achievers. Unfortunately, I ain't one of them.   All   my best friends are truly very busy people. One's got camp, the other's probably involved in some church thing, while another is always off on jamming sessions in town. Fact is, everyone's got something to do. Everyone, that is, except for ME! I'm stuck at home, always pondering my next move. Sleep, eat or do homework. Is it any wonder why I look like a rugby player? At this rate, I'll be a sumo wrestler soon...Terrible. There isn't even anything to do in the chatrooms. It's so lame in there. Everyone's either hitting on another person or playing with the trivia bot. No perverts for me to kick or ban. Damn! I remember how I used to look forward to banning those clowns. Problem is, those clown's aren't even around anymore!!  At least there's been a FEW happenings around to keep me alive. The most interesting of all, an interestling skirmish between my mum and eight other women which happened after an accident occurred. Would've been a hit-and-run, if it wasn't for my mum's sudden switch to Maniac Mode. Sincerely, for once, I think my mum could've taken on all eight of them and thrashed the hell out of 'em, thanks to the rage she was in. Hmm, makes me wonder what my dad would've done...  Amusing. I think this blog will be seeing a lot of me these holidays. Well, at least until my comp comes back. Then I'll get on with popping more enemy soldiers...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's been a mixed week. Funny how I can experience so many different feelings throughout one week.  Happy -  Skipping class, as per usual, and finding out I haven't failed my Mod Maths...  Excited -  Manchester United signing Alan Smith  Puzzled -  Danny Pugh's move to Leeds  Nervous -  caused by something requiring oratory skills beginning with the letter 'D'  Sad -  Won't be seeing my dad for the next month  Annoyed -  Finding out that the entire holiday is about to become one big joke  Peeved -  Sitting through 3 hours of tuition  Pissed -  Hell, hardly a week which passes without feeling pissed   Tiredness seems to be a usual condition of mine nowadays. Whatever happened to those days when I could sleep at 3am, wake up at 5am and keep going until 3am the next day? Heck, wouldn't be surprised, with all the load of crap that's been happening in school. I mean, has anyone heard of a four-hour duty duration for prefects? That is ludicrous, but yeah, that's what I did, and most other prefects too. This was followed by a rather aimless compilation which, by the time it ended, was time for me to go to the mosque.  Crumzz, life goes on...  Now onto more serious stuff....the Alan Smith transfer. Sincerely, as a very, very, very loyal MU fan since the age of 11, who really cares where Alan Smith came from? Who really cares if Smith had shown real commitment to the Leeds United cause previously? He's a good player, and that's all that matters. Seeing MU finish third this season was painful. Painful because it was caused by silly mistakes. Silly losses to Wolves and Leicester, and an even sillier and embarassing loss to Liverpool. Silly because Sir F decided to go an entire season with only SIX tried and tested defenders, one of whom was eventually banned for missing a drugs test (real clown, that guy), while another had just returned from an eight-month injury. Wow, I see the sense in that. And now, with all the frailties in defence, Sir F lets Danny Pugh move to Leeds as part of the Smith deal. Great. I sincerely hope Gabriel Heinze or some other able defender switches over to MU soon. Almost every MU member fan is bemoaning the fact that the Smith move is a cross-Pennine one, an almost  haram  type of transfer. Gee, if it was me, I wouldn't mind even if it was cross-Titiwangsa... Well, here's to Smith and to Fred the Red. To Liverpool fans, we're gonna get Gerrard (:P)! To Leeds fans, thanks to your club for being our feeder club (hope none of you beat me up after this)!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        What's On My Mind?   When I first started thinking of having a blog, I decided that if I were to eventually have a blog, I would be honest. Brutally honest. And I won't care who the hell reads my blog and I won't care if no one reads my blog at all. Today, for some reason or the other, one thing has been bothering me. A LOT! The connection between Malaysians and English, is a terrible one. I'm not criticizing all Malaysians here, but these past few weeks, I've come to realize a fact. All Malaysians are really "stuck-up" and they are even more so if they have a fair command of English. I'm not accusing all Malaysians of being so, but it is true. Just because a person can speak proper English, he or she will look down on others like the other person is not worthy of living in the same world as him or herself.  Hell, I don't know where I got the inspiration for this blog entry. Just came into my mind, and bang, I start writing! It is a sad reality (to quote the debate teacher of mine).  Speaking of debates, I don't really know if I really enjoy it. Just read a blog of one of my best friends who said something about passion and what not. No disrespect here, but I sincerely do not gain anything from putting myself through this endless torture. I'll be the first to admit, I love skipping classes. I love sneaking off to play games whenever teacher gets out of the library. I like hanging out with my "bestest" friends all day doing virtually nothing but talk crap. And I guess the best thing of all is to win... But, then again, I feel stupid and silly. I'm a virtual unknown in the team. Not that I care, but I just feel left out. It is real crappy. It also ain't very pleasing when I feel like I'm a damn liability to the team. This is stupid. Whoever came up with the rule that at least one bumiputra speaker must be in a debate team is an idiot. Heh, for once I feel glad I have a blog to just let go of some stuff I probably won't in real life...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Introduction  First things first...the name's Khael.  Khael bin Abdul Malik , that's what my parents named me. Not spectacular, not ordinary, definitely not Malay. Dad's half-Malay half-Chinese, Mum's full Chinese...guess that makes me three-quarters Chinese,  eh ? So, I guess it's understandable why so many Malay people raise their eyebrows when they hear my name. " Hah? Itu jer? Tak der Mohamad kat depan ke? " Sweet.  I'm 16, born in Ipoh on the 16th of March 1988. Can't speak a damn word of Malay...well, can  lar , but damn lousy. Used to speak Cantonese well, but now...can understand but don't want to speak for fear of making mistakes. Used to speak Hokkien well, but now...can understand but don't want to speak for fear of making myself look like an idiot. So, perhaps now anyone reading this blog will understand why a perfectly normal Malay guy is using English...  Studied in Sri Lanka for a period of three years. Two of those years were horrible years in which I grew fat, had lots of problems with girl classmates who were obsessed with the Spice Girls, but managed to learn how to swim, do lots of tricks in the water, learn the initially boring but interesting cricket game and improve my English and experience life as a House Captain. The last year there was definitely the most memorable one, where I spoiled my eyes completely by reading a whole stack of novels in near complete darkness every night, grew even fatter but managed to become Head Boy.  It was those years which has shaped me the way I am today. Mostly blur. Partly blind. Still quite fat. Can't kick a football straight. Have a poor command of the Malay language.   And that's all you need to know about me.  That's who Khael is....... 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am not a deep-thinking person. I have come to that conclusion just now as I was gaining an insight into the life of another person. That guy thinks a lot about life and how he inteprets the happenings around his life is indeed very interesting. In shorter words: everything is probably from his soul. Me? I’m a gutless, soulless, Russian-trained clown who has no emotions. This blog is effectively a place for me to get rid of tensions, which is why a majority of the posts before this centered on anger, frustration, depression, death and doomsday ( er, all true save the last two ). I am a happy-go-lucky person. And when I say lucky, I mean very, very lucky. Life has been generous to me. Or should I say Allah? Hmm...  1997 : Fusion16 enrols in an international school at a god forsaken city called Colombo in Sri Lanka. His parents could chosen to send him to an American one which was far away, but decided to settle on a British one – closer to home. It so happened that the blogger (that’s me) failed – or did badly – in an entrance exam and was enrolled in a lower class. How does that make me lucky? Well, that year was the only year which lacked a potential future Sri Lankan prime minister. So, who gets the top job and the honour of being the first ever foreign Head Boy?  Me . ( Insert cynical laugh here !)  2001 : Fusion16 gets his bum into the scout den with hopes of becoming a top scout. Never gets past his Tenderfoot test and quits. Joins Kadet Remaja Sekolah a few months later.  Lucky?  Well, KRS happens to be one of the more “inactive” uniformed units around. No work, no play, nothing. More free Saturdays for me! ( Raise eyebrows here !)  2004 : Fusion16 is miraculously in the debate team. He is blessed with a brilliant third-speaker and a shining Scottish-born first speaker.  Lucky?  Gee, their Sri Lankan bred second-speaker rides along and gets a piece of whatever they earn for cryin’ out loud! ( Insert another cynical laugh here !)  Still in 2004 : Fusion16 shoots up to the top post in KRS.  Lucky?  Very, very lucky. Why? Coz' there aren't anymore seniors around, no more Malay leaders who have gone off to MRSM, and look, it’s that same clown who’s suddenly inherited a whole bunch of stuff. ( Don’t have to laugh cynically here, just grin maliciously )  So, the conclusion is? I am one hell of a lucky son-of-a-gun and I intend to stop that from happening. Makes you feel uneasy wondering when all this graciousness will end. Fusion16 now officially proclaims his desire to try his utmost best to get something ( well, anything ) based on his OWN merit! Well, actually, being lucky ain’t that bad, come to think of it (;P) Thank you great God. I’ll repay you in any way you see fit if I get upstairs ( or even downstairs, for that matter ) when I die. ( Insert the final cynical laugh here!)    
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I feel depressed.  I feel sad, angry, pissed, tired, sick and a whole lot of other things. Something tells me I need to take anti-depressent medications soon to avoid a repeat (or to prevent) of many stupid things I've done, like the way I almost massacred my computer after some Haitian gangster pulled the plug on me in a game. Or the way I don't feel the need to say anything serious to anyone anymore. Or the way I'm now sleeping extremely early at night which I would've considered absolutely ludicrous only two or three weeks ago. I need to find out what's causing all this. Anyone out there who knows a good shrink, do recommend him/her to me...... Certain friends have been great, though. The best of all is a very close friend of mine. I've known him since Std. 1, we've fought each other, we've triumphed over and failed a lot of things together and we've done a lot of crazy stuff together. Good thing is, we can get along fine even though we have our own set of friends, own set of likes and dislikes and he supports Liverpool (I think football loyalty is worthy of mention here. Haha). I need some diversions. Anything other than the only thing I'm doing now is good. The last time I even graced our school field with my presence (hahahaha!) was four months ago. I haven't played football that long! Good god! Looks like I'm giving Rio Ferdinand a run for his money. I had a VERY strong urge of just whacking a very, very tempting football that was lying in my Principal's office this morning.... Also, as in the previous post, I'd like to take this opportunity to thank a few more people. > 3 Doors Down for Away From The Sun, which is keeping me from going insane as I write this... > David Sneddon for his, uh, inspirational songs (??!?!) > And finally to U2 for rocking......
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       What !?  No break !? That was my initial reaction after finding out that there wouldn't be a break between the State-level and Regional-level debates. Looks like the five of us are going to see the library a lot again next week. That library will always be remembered as a second home to me. We practically live in it. We know how to check library books out using the comp system, we know all the passwords to everything, we get access to the librarian's exco room.... We get to do all the stuff even some librarians can only wish of doing... (snicker!) Back 2 the debate. I managed to make a fool out of myself, which is nothing new really. Got mad on stage, swore in Chinese, Hokkien, English and Malay for a full 20 seconds after I finished my speech and then set my mind to muddle their third speaker up, which I didn't successfully do either... But anyway, who cares? We won! Who cares if we had to spend the next three hours doing nothing waiting for the results? Who cares if some dumbass teacher was so intent on telling a whole crowd that I was stupid for arguing the way I did in my speech? (Course, I wish that teacher the worst of luck in his Salehhudin debate competition. May his team lose in the first round so I can snicker some more!) It is a pity that Euro 2004 is going on now, coz I can't seem to stay awake long enough to watch matches anymore. How I wish to be able to stay up until the ungodly hours of 4am again! I've read that wives have divorced from husbands because they felt ignored thanks to football. Hmm..........let's just hope my future wife is more patient than that...  Well, here's to me debate teammates and to Yoke Teng, who has been kind enuff to do a  LOT  of things for me even though I don't really know him that well... 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some silly faggot wrote earlier that he wouldn't have much to do these holidays. For the record, that clown is completely, truthfully, brutally and embarassingly WRONG. Holidays have taken on a new meaning for me. I mean, since when does a 14-day holiday involve 7 days of debate training? Since when did holidays involve 12 days of endless tuition? Add to that, the blistering amounts of homework, and what do you have? A great holiday.  Yeeahhh right . I still intend to enjoy. I've stopped caring about my homework. Let it take care of itself. I'm sick and tired of working my ass off finishing it and all I get in return is a full-scale blasting in front of 39 other 16-year olds by my confounded History teacher. Come on, a guy like me, who is so used to not having a life, suddenly has a 1,000 things to do, another 3,000 things to complete and about 40,000 things I've forgotten to do sometime ago and have to catch up with now. My circle of friends seem to have shrunk as well. My social life now is limited entirely to five other people. The debate teacher and the other debaters. Don't get me wrong. Those guys are great. But their social circles seem to be growing, while my social circle seems to be struggling to even stay a circle.  I need social healing, if there ever was such a thing. Apparently, people nowadays have handphones so they can leave it to rot at home. Can't even have a chat with ANYONE anymore. It's pretty pathetic, when you consider the fact that the only person I'm currently actively messaging with is a person I haven't even seen in my life. Forget seeing that person, I barely even know her name! If this person (who claims she is a girl and insists on calling me her litte bro), turns out to be er, something else, I'm screwed. Come on guyz, put those h/ps to use!!!   "The Darkness is a great band"    Fusion16 , giving another of his useless quotes.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       The Others...  I spent quite some time reading a whole lot of other people's blogs last night. People have blogs for all sorts of reasons. Some of the blogs were really cool, like one particular person's one which kept track of his bike journey across some country. But, after extensive, er, research, I think it's safe to assume that blogs fall into three different types of categories:  a)  The Inspiring Blog : These are the blogs which really get you thinking. These blogs amused me for all sorts of reasons, be it for the pictures they included in it, or the descriptive manner in which they wrote it.  b)  The Who, What, Where Blog : A normal type of blog. I guess a good example of it would be mine, where a whole bunch of crap is the main topic. They DON'T encourage any thinking. :-)  c)  The Are You For Real? Blog : These blogs had crap as their main topic too. The difference is, these blogs emphasize exaggeration until the line between fact and myth is sooo blurred...    My Blog?  So, how does my blog stack up against all the others that I've read so far? Well, don't know... I know for one thing that I my language isn't deep. There's no technical jargons involved. Just normal English. There aren't any outpourings of feelings in my blog either. I don't really talk about feelings stuff coz of two reasons: 1) Don't wanna sound like a teenage drama queen... 2) I don't have feelings...(well, actually I'm a mean person...so all I feel is pissed, most of the time anyway)    Fan Factor, not to be confused with Fear Factor  That's another factor... Check out the Blogger website blogs. The best are usually the one's which don't have a whole bunch of loyal supporters viewing them all the time. The ones which do have loyal readers meanwhile, tend to sound more magazine-like than, well, a blog...  And that concludes this edition of "Blog Weekly". Thank you.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I’ve just come to realize, not for the first time in my life, that I am –  weird...  And I think -  just think, but I’m not sure  - that I’m glad that I’m weird, because it makes me different from everyone else in this world.   Let’s take for example, the military. I’m absolutely nuts about it. At age 9, I memorized all the names and codes for the bombs U.S. used on the Iraqis. At age 11, I managed to remember all the abbreviations and nicknames for fighter jets and bombers. At age 13, I embarked on a journey to know every single rank in the military, from Private to Field Marshal. At age 15, I moved back an era and went back to WWII to see how the Allied forces moved through Europe starting with D-Day itself. Why exactly did I do all this? I’m not sure myself. Even my personality is weird. I can be extremely quiet if I want to. If I'm not in the mood, I can be really, really quiet. When I'm tired, I look like a street thug - especially when I'm on the public bus. If I'm in good spirits, then all hell will break loose. I will do all sorts of funny things, even if I'm in the middle of a convention, or when everyone else is having a farewell for another friend. Let’s move on to computer games. Some years back, everyone else were getting engrossed in Counter Strike and Half-Life. Me? I found those two a bore, and entertained myself building cities in Sim City and managing my own football teams in CM. Talking about football, most other people watch football and enjoy it. I, on the other hand, loved to make it a point to remember every player - first team or reserve - and their positions. Now it makes me wonder, why in the world can’t I do this when it comes to things like History and Agama??! Lack of interest? Perhaps. Somehow I find it easier to remember Francesc Fabregas than Maharaja Lela and Operation Market Garden than Prophet Muhammad’s  hijrah . But that’s beside the point. The point here is that – I am weird. :-P Do I ever wonder what people might think of me? Yeah, I do. Sometime’s I’m afraid people might think I’m a freak. Maybe I am a freak. But I’m not really bothered. Am I going to stop doing these funny things? Probably not. So, why have I decided to write about this in my blog? Have no idea. See what I mean? I am  weird... 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The handover is looming. This Monday, our seniors will cease to be prefects and our batch will take over the running of the board. I’m not entirely sure though if I’d like the board minus the seniors, some of whom are really cool guys and are people I respect. Of course, there are also some seniors who are not that great, but I have to say, Discipline Commission has the best, the most hip and the most "happening" (to borrow a phrase from a friend) of all prefects. As I type this, I’ve just returned from a farewell outing. A brilliant farewell outing which, although beset by petty problems such as lack of food ( hehe !), could be considered an overall success, thanks to the stuff we did and the crap we talked. First of all, there was the “affirmation” time, where everyone could just say anything they liked about the commission. Naturally, I thanked my senior, who was also mentioned in almost every single prefect's affirmation speech. I personally feel glad I did get the senior I got, coz’ he was without a shadow of doubt the absolute, single most “lepak” prefect in the entire Form 5. He took everything with an easy attitude, and we talked about anything and everything ( even when there wasn’t really anything to talk about ). He also had hopes of me to be among those to pass the first batch. He also got me out of the “ragging” business after telling his buddies not to disturb me and covered my back over a whole lot of less than flattering things about me. Thanks again, Adrian. Owe you a lot. Disco will also be remembered for a personal reason. The first time I've ever managed to complete conversations with females in many, many, many years was during compilation meetings (yes, I am that pathetic). Of course, what outing would be complete without the traditional bombing of other commission outings? Why, none, of course. Our commission went over to a rival commission’s outing spot in a couple of cars right smack at 10.30pm and started chucking a whole lot of water balloons at them. Two minutes later, we realized they had a nice, powerful water pipe. At three minutes, the retaliations kept coming in fast and hard. At the fourth minute, we realized we were out of ammo (another thing caused by lack of organization) while the enemy was just beginning. At four and a half minutes, the entire Discipline Commission was effectively retreating. At five minutes, we were dying… More weapons were brought out. Eggs. Flours. At about ten minutes, half of all Disco members were busy being blur outside the war zone, while the other half were busy being hit by a whole lot of soapy water and flour. At fifteen minutes, the reinforcements from the Cleanliness Commission came in.  Disco  charged in again. After half-an-hour, war was over. Peace reigned once again (heheh!). I do not doubt that the various car drivers that passed the war zone, actually a house compound, thought a gangfight was in progress. I mean, it isn’t often you see a whole bunch of people gathering outside a house, busy chucking things in and out while running all over the neighbourhood, yelling and screaming. The end of a generation... We’ll never see the same seniors in our Commission again. It was fun while they were around and unfortunately, the future of Disco’s status as being the most “happening” commission around doesn’t look so bright. Well, no matter… anyone for a water balloon war? I like it...   -Discipline Commission 2004-  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, there will be no talk about how life has been treating me unfairly. There will be no rants about how things always go against me. Today, I will attempt to “relive” my “painful” moments. Head… This will have to be the time a South Korean boy whacked a ball straight at my face. It especially hurt my nose because I was bespectacled that time. All I remember was going in for the challenge and the next thing I know, I was on the ground clutching my face with a specs a few metres away from me. Backbone… Ahh, this one happened recently enough. Sitting on a railing and being at peace with the world has some consequences in this modern era. (Snort!) Somehow or the other, I slip and fall over backwards head first. There was a nice little thud when my head connected with the concrete floor. I flipped over and sat there without moving for the next ten minutes because I sincerely thought I had broken my back. Until today, when I sit up straight, my backbone hurts. No prizes for guessing who’ll be a hunchback by the age of 30. Left Hand… Another Sri Lankan moment. Our old apartment had a very solid and thick black door. A solid wooden one. As we lived near the sea, the wind was always ferocious. And once, the wind was about the blow the door shut. An 11-year old me kindly stuck out his left hand to stop it from slamming, but apparently I miscalculated the strength of the wind, and the door slammed shut on my fingers. Right Hand... Playing goalkeeper, for a few moments I thought I was in the boots of Peter Schmeichel. While saving (or attempting to save, anyway) a shot, some clown managed to hook the ball away using all his might. Trouble is, that particular clown hooked my hand along with it. The hand swelled to twice it’s normal size, and this was during my LTC. I spent the rest of that LTC with a bandaged right hand. Leg… Nope, nothing serious here I can recall. I’m having a minor one right now which was, again, caused while playing goalkeeper (is God trying to tell me I’m not meant to be keeper?). Collided with a classmate of mine then landed awkwardly. Foot… This happened when I was a little kid. My sis was having fun pressing the stapler, watching the staples fly here and there. I was unaware, and I jumped off a table right onto one of those staples, which went and stuck itself on my foot. Mind you, there was some trouble getting it out, and even harder to walk with two holes on my foot… I will keep this blog posted if I get seriously injured anytime soon… 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      That’s a thing I have to watch seriously if I want to get anywhere in life. My temper. It’s bad. And when I say bad, I mean very, very, very bad. I don’t know what made me get so blinking angry that morning during assembly. It goes something like this:  Somehow that morning, I was very peeved because I had to walk all the way to the scout den, which is at one end of the school, when my duty area was at the front gate, which was at another end of the school. A senior had sent me to get the watchman to get the gate open, and I was given the honour to wake the guy up. Anyways, that’s beside the point.  The point is, when I got back, then only does that senior tell me I was on flag duty, and that I’d better look for the Head Prefect because he’ll probably be pissed at me for not doing it. Off I go looking for the HP. Soon as I find him, as expected, he screws me upside down for not doing flag duty. OK. That’s the end of the problem.  The thing is, for some reason or the other, I didn’t think that was the end of anything. I got extremely hot. And he’s still screwing me sometime later when it’s time to raise the school flag. I get even more pissed.  After HQ, I see that a few cadets are missing from the Guard of Honour line. Temper reaches boiling point. And what do I do? Ohh, nothing much. As the HP and several cadets were standing right in front of me, I slid my bag off my shoulder, threw it as hard as I could to the ground, took my bottle flung it away and starting swearing while putting on a savage face. Whether the HP saw me or heard me or not, I wasn’t really bothered that time. Hell, I wouldn’t have given a rat’s piss even if it was Sultan Azlan Shah himself standing right there.  I was in a bad mood for the entire morning, shrugging off friends who tried to approach me. Went up all the way to recess. Barely uttered a word for almost three hours. Must’ve set a new record for frowning.  Is it any surprise I didn’t pass first batch? Well, actually, if truth be told (and I don’t mean any disrespect to the guys who got first batch – coz I respect the pants out of those guys), the ones who got it were the timid ones. The yes-men. If that’s what those guys are looking for, then I’m probably the wrong guy for it, because I’m all for speaking up. Something like Shahrir Samad in UMNO, but&nbsp;mind you, I hate that guy.  Maybe I’ve just become the person I’ve been avoiding to become ever since I joined the debate team. I remember telling myself every single debater I knew was arrogant. I remember I could never get along with any debaters last time, because I hated them and they felt they were too good for everything else. Maybe I’ve become that. But if I have, then I’m glad at least I realize that fact. It’s time for self-discovery. (ß hahaha).  It’s time for me to feel my inner me. (ß What the hell am I talking about here?)  Well, time to sign off now.   The Hulk    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I’m not very happy with myself at the moment. Failure to make the first batch of prefects to pass probation makes for a very lousy week. And unfortunately, that set the tone for my mood throughout the week, after a soothing break down south in Singapore. And look! It’s Thursday night. This confounded mood is probably going to carry on into the weekend. God! I think I’m going to sleep this entire weekend and save the trouble of feeling moody and sulky. Well, shit happens... I’m also pretty peeved that a certain senior prefect decided to run his mouth at me for being a statue while doing duty. He can ( this part has been censored to safeguard the “U” rating of this blog ). I’ve been threatened, intimidated, stared down and laughed at by students of that class and yet I have the guts to walk up to them and talk to them. And even if I am a statue, it’s as if he’s any better. All he does is stand at the back. Walk up. Walk down. Walk up. Walk down. You get the picture... And since my row has eight prefects on duty, which makes a ratio of one prefect for every ten students, I don’t understand why about five are always at the back. Am I missing something there? Is the view the better? Is the air there fresher? Blinking prefectorial board. And in other highlights, yours truly has managed to stay two periods of Biology without falling asleep!! A record has been set! If I can keep it up again tomorrow, it’ll be the longest continuous time awake for Biology lessons gone through by me. Anyways, Singapore is a nice country. Although I’ve supposedly been there loads of times ( the only thing I can remember is the airport for some reason or the other ), this definitely will change my mind a lil’ teeny bit about that country. (Note: Prior to this, I was always of the opinion of stationing a couple of tanks in Johor Bahru to invade them). Everything there is efficiently run, such as their MRT’s, and the system for everything works just fine ( except for their immigration checkpoint ). And everyone there is loaded! I mean, who has heard of 26 bucks for a bloody cup of coffee? Who else can boast of seeing a Rolls-Royce, Ferrari and ten Maserati’s parked in one row all in the space of three minutes? And I was just in a car park, not at a car show! Ahh, I feel much lighter now................   Norwich City 3 MPPJ 2. (Hmm…something’s not right with that score!!!)  Fusion16/2331hrs
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I am lost.  That’s all I can say about me after barely three days back in class. I can safely assume that I now know what Lord Cardigan went through during the charge of the Light Brigade, when he bravely led about 600 British troops right into the paths of three different Russian cannons much to the dismay of Lord Raglan. The order to march right into those cannons was apparently never issued, and much of the Light Brigade were massacred. In my case, I haven’t the faintest idea what I am doing most of the time ( or what I’m supposed to be doing anyway ), but I still go along as if I bought the whole outfit.  Mwah ha ha ! That’s me! I live by the principles: act smart even though you ain't that bright. And yet, for some reason or the other, I do not feel the need to “educate” myself. To unlose myself from this maze. To work harder so I finally understand these confounded things. Instead, I find myself getting totally engrossed in a spectacular 125cc race in which the tussle for the lead involved six bikes. I find myself rooting for Greece in the Euro 2004 Finals as if it was my country. I find myself having fun bashing people up all day. It hasn’t really helped to find that I had an accumulated points total of more than 30 in my recent exams ( boosted by a 9G for my Add Maths – don’t ask me how I managed to do that ). If I manage to reproduce that sensational form for my SPM exams, let’s just safely assume that I won’t be top of the list for admission into the University of Skopje – let alone University Malaya. Well, can’t be perfect. As my good friend Andre Benjamin once said ( or sang ), “But mighty fine only got you somewhere half the time, and the other half either got you cursed out or coming up short.” Sarcasm aside, I know I have to buck up. I know I have to work. I know have to put away the urge of staying up nights to watch A.J. Foyt IV lose control on Turn 4 and narrowly miss smashing into Sarah Fischer. I know I have to stop my fingers from double-clicking the enticing gun icon on my desktop. I have to stop plotting my next move in a bid to unseat Celtic from the Scottish Premiership using some obscure team like Partick Thistle or Dundee United. Aaahhh! The temptations of life... And will some kind hearted Hollywood director come up with a good war movie soon? I’m getting fits just thinking about the lack of action! This year, the only thing I’ve seen which comes close to a GOOD war flick is some silly movie in which a dude charged straight at a whole platoon of Germans armed with mortars and machine guns with a flame thrower. And unlike the poor Light Brigade, this guy actually made it through. Heavens! You’d think the director would have a sense of reality to accompany his obviously magnificent imagination. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The end of the journey... After two years of misery, four months of not going for classes, moments of joy, moments of anger, moments of grief (!), moments of boredom and moments of sheer insanity, the “debate” part of my life is finally over. I may sound relieved, and in a way, I am, but when I consider the fact that had we won I would have been a mere sixteen minutes away from being part of a National-level champion team, disappointment sinks in. Anyways, I am not going to wallow in disappointment. Going back to class was amusing. The more rational-headed ones welcomed us back nicely, which was great. The brick-headed ones have yet to stop asking us what in the blue blazes made us lose, which is not so great. Whatever it is, “debate” definitely lives on (in my memory anyway)...   Quarantine  Quarantines were one of the more “colourful” aspects of debates, especially for us. Did we work? Well, to say we didn’t would be an understatement. But in the early stages of the competition, we would sneak food in and start playing around while in quarantine. Later on, it was more serious stuff, although I had the opportunity of having a go on a drum set that was in that Taiping school...   Identity Crisis  Well, that only applies for me. Till this very day, my Principal thinks my surname is Khaled, for some reason or the other. Every single time he’s called the team out during assembly, he’s called me that, and I’ve had to stifle torrents of laughter as I stand there thinking “who’s Khaled”. I think he’s been reading too many reports on those terrorists.   Wild Goats  Our journies to and from the debate venues have always been eventful. On the way home from Parit Buntar, a teammate of mine had something going on about wild goats. Must’ve been high on something. In Taiping, our teacher had the misfortune of confusing her left and her right…go figure!   Training  By far the best part of debates. Aww, c’mon, we needed to have some sort of distractions during training, didn’t we? And having access to a whole bunch of computers was really tempting anyway. Here’s to Unreal Tournament and World Cup 2002! Those were two great games...   The King And I  Thanks to the time-wasting training sessions during the hols, I have practically watched the entire school play – well, the unrefined version anyway.   Homework  I still have lots of these...no comments.   Tim, Andrew, Josh, Sheng Yuen  Four great guys who have been great teammates. Cheers to them!  (And J-X deserves it too, I guess, as he got us through the first round before he had to leave for good ol' Kay-El) 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>