<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey ya'll! i'm in earth science and we have a free period so yeah.... michael & megan were over here with me but then they left b/c i was still typing the stupid shit that didn't publish before! grrr. well i'd just like to say i'm so glad all my drama is over with from like the past few days... ha ha i'm sure some of you had to hear all about it and well i'm sorry. well class' bout over so i gotta bounce yo. ha  peace, bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok well i just typed like a ton of shit and well it didn't work i'm in earth science right now thogh. anyways let me see if this one will work. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey! well i kinda forgot i had a blog for a while. life's kinda been a blur over the past few days... congrats to EVERYONE at saint mary's who got confirmed! that was really fun to just see all of you. i wish i'd been up there with you tho. leah congrats on your jewish confirmation too! hah that was soo much fun! ok for those of you who weren't there tho... there were these ppl in front of us in the temple i might add, MAKING OUT! the whole time. and not like teenagers, like fat old ugly ppl! it was soooo wierd. i mean during a service. it would be the equivalent of me making out w/ someone during mass ! it pissed me off actually. haa well i have so much more to say but i gg peace 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well hello hello everyone! today was lot's of fun for me. although rather uneventful.... sort of. school as usual, running, as usual. well not quite as usual, i ran at home today since track is over... and oh wait i'm still running! oh yeah and i forgot tho... i have a C in curtis' class! is that not crazy, too bad i'm like awesome in his class but ok let's give me a "C"! haha oh well. i'm kinda giving up on this whole school thing. it's getting old. oh man and guitar concert tomorrow! dont forget, come watch me 3rd period, tell you teacher to take the whole class! ok well i gg eat sum dinner. peace~bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well today was just normal pretty much, except it's so hard to believe track's over! i was so lost after school today. actually justine and i had a fun time though. ha ha she and i and ryan started the " ckwgdttgsawiatabs" club. and for all you non members... that is the "cool kids who walk down to the gas station and walk in a triangle and buy slushies" club. yeah it's just that awesome. then justine and i thought it would be a good idea to hop in the back of mark's truck and not tell him we were in there, which in case you're wondering.... really scary thing to do! too bad i really think they knew we were in there all along though. anyways, they drove like insanely and scared the shit outta me, but it was all in good fun.   sooo too bad i'm about to go running even though tracks over, but it's all good. i get to go swimming anyways. yess! ok well bye guys. peace 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well today was a pretty good day... (i can't help but think to myself dude why does anyone care about how well my day went...) haha  oh well i enjoy writing it. i just got back not too long ago from jenny's house, b/c we had our end of the year track party! pretty much everyone came, including ryan cav! which was so fun b/c i mean he doesn't even run track! we got to hang out which i mean is always a fun time. then i ate like 1000 taco thingys, which were really good. it was kinda bittersweet tho, b/c i don't know what i'm gonna do w/o jenny and all the seniors next year. it'll be so different. but it's cool tho chris williams is gonna join and so is ryan cav, seriously.... football? anyway, that was fun.      ok and on an entirely different note, i have to get something off my chest. what's going on in iraq is sick, and our country is seriously screwed up sometimes. we have to work to stop all the violence and craziness people! i was getting so mad in world history the other day, because some people are just so uneducated, and so unaware about what's going on. i mean we bombed a hospital, we are killing innocent people non-stop. we're an imperialist nation, it's sad. anyway, that's my 2 cents.      i gotta go do my earth science homework from last friday so i'm out. i love you all a ton! peace, bernie 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well anyway you're probably getting bored of reading this by now, but i've just got a lot on my mind that i need to let out. so as i was saying we won states, and my dad was like wow bernadette you didn't race... but then a few minutes ago i was talking about how i ran like complete shit and he was like "coming in 5th in the state isn't bad bernadette" so i guess he's over it.... i mean i did run really well yesterday so, i suppose he's proud about that. anyway winning states was absolutely amazing... the last race, the 4x4 decided whether we win or lost states to FORSYTH the insanely good team.... and well we won in an absolutely amazing race.  i'm never gonna forget jenny just crying tears of joy as we finished, so overwhelmed.... and everyone just screaming insanely. as emily said "it's an amazing feeling bernadette!" and well brianna came and saw everyone for the first time since xmas when my dad and her got in a huge fight, so i couldn't be happier. *sigh* well i hafta go shower i'm disgusting, and really really really sunburned. i love you all! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh my gosh! i'm so excited i actually have a blog now! i feel like a raleigh charter person.... anyway today was an amazing day. first of all we had our state track meet today and yesterday. it was amazing. just let me say i LOVE all you people on track, and i'm so proud of everyone. our girls team won states for the first time ever in gibbons history, which gibbons has been around a LONG time. anyways, my coach said i scored 10 percent of the team's points.. so that's really exciting. i ran my fastest times ever. in the 2 mile i came in 3rd in the whole state, and i ran it in 11:35. and then i ran the mile today which SUCKED. i dunno what my time was but i really don't wanna know. i came in 5th in the state. my dad's words were "bernadette you had it right there in your fucking hands and you just didn't race." which i mean was true, i could have come in 2nd in the state if i'd run hard. oh well it's over now i suppose. well i have more to say but mom calls so i'll post another in a min or so. love you all sooo much! peace 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey hey hey,       I'm at ariels house right now, for her graduation par-tay. moira and ariel and ellen headed out to the pool but laura and i weren't really in swimming moods sooo uh we're in here. yeah kinda bored..  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Two nights ago I went to a memorial for Don Clark Pearson, and it was a good experiance. Don was the cross country coach at East Chapel Hill high school, and went to Chapel Hill high school when he was younger. My Dad used to write about him in the Chapel Hill News. Don commited sucicide last summer. So, 2 days ago would have been Don's birthday, so we celebrated, had cake and told stories about Don. Now, as corny as it may sound it made me realize that life is short and you never relize when you are going to lose someone.   Also I was thinking about seeing as life is short, I should write about things that are more meaningful... If something were ever to happen to me and you were to read my journals,. you would find worthless shit about like guys I had crushes on in the 6th grade. Where as I want to let everyone know how much they mean to me, and about my life.    So, I"m gonna publish this and write the rest later because I already wrote everything out and it was erased when the computer messed up. :-( ok well peace, bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's the first day of summer I suppose. I mean it's the first Monday that we're not at school. Yay! My day was rather uneventful though. I went to practice this morning, and wow we had 17 girls show up, which is insane! That's so many girls. Plus we have these kind of new coaches like Joe, and Nick Mangum. We did out and back course just on the main road, which was alright. I actually kind of like the little sophomores who joined our team. They're alright.  Let's see so I get back from practice, and my Dad is like let's get mad at Bernadette for everything she's ever done! I dunno like he just all of the sudden started yelling at me. Eventually I just started crying, and then he was like I guess I'm sorry, or whatever. So, I dunno... that sucked. He says that I don't appriciate him. Which I don't think he understands just how much I do for him. Like, let's think, why am I a runner? Oh yeah that's right because of my Dad. Why am I doing the newspaper? Oh that's right, because of my Dad. Why do I call my parents constantly whenever I spend the night with people, oh yeah to make them happy. And, why do I like never do crazy shit, oh yeah because of my parents. Oh well I'm over it. i gg peace, bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       sweet that exam just dominated me.... and i'm so pissed that i still have a "C" in spanish, even though i studied my ass of for the exam and got an 88 on it. yeah, that's awesome. I've made straight A's in spanish my whole life and all of the sudden i have a "C"... that rocks. wow, bernadette's life seems really interesting...not.... um, me and bernadette def just failed our earth science exam ( megan)  anyway i guess i'm out, gotta study for english so that i don't fail that too.  peace, bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so 2 more days, nothing I can't handle. Spanish exam was alright too actually, I suppose all this studying is actually paying off. Oh and just a note to everyone at my lunch table from this year, I love all of you, each one. Even if I was mean sometimes, or add, or annoyed you to death with my talking I still love you all. I really hope we have a good lunch again next year like we had this one.    you know looking back on this year, it really has been a good one. Melissa and I were talking ( how unusual) and we were just saying how we've really accomplished everything we wanted to accomplish this year. I mean it all started back with Operation Orange, which some of you might remember, and then there was the ever changing thousands of OPP's after that. Although some of them did work, and are kind of still going on. Plus we won states for the first time ever, and I became editor for next year, and mastered the guitar. Plus I think I really figured out who my friends are this year, and I'm so happy about that. The people I've surrounded myself with this year, have been amazing. I don't know what I would have done without all my friends.    Lunch at IHOP rocked my life! ha ha Everyone the waitress at the IHOP on Capital Blvd. Is sooo nice, yay free sundaes! I'm gonna miss everyone this summer, and we have to get together and just do lunch like we did today, if not more. Peace b/c I've gotta study! Love, Bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       sooo 2 hardest exams are over.. thank God! curtis's theo exam wasn't as bad as i thought it would be. if you studied you'll be fine. geometry was alright too i think. i was proud of myself on my mid-term for geo.. yay A! and i beat certain really smart ppl in my class. geo what a great class, i'm gonna miss all you add mother fuckers. ha ha not it was really good tho. speaking of ppl in goe.. brian i love your hair! i think i wanna cut mine, although not buzzed like brian's. tomorrow i have spanish w/ krull.. omg, i think i'll be fine as long as i study, but i'm procrastinating on that one at the moment. i'll probably go do it in a few.    omg i'm so glad it's almost summer tho! my summer is going to rock! i can't believe i leave for nicaragua in like 2 weeks. i'm soooo excited. it should be amazing.   oh man and sorry i have to brag about myself real quick, i'd just like to say.. most valuable reporter, news editor for next year! yay! and also all conference in the mile, conference champion for the 2, all state for the 2- mile, 5th for the mile! 11:35 for the 2, 5:25 for the mile. holla! oh and some guitar award, that i'm pretty sure everyone got haha. still it's an award. ha ok well i better go study. bye! wish me luck... 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so let me just say leaving anonymous&nbsp;comments is pretty cool.... not! like if you're going to make a comment at least have the gut to say who left it.. coward.    
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hello hello, well i just got in from seeing "Anchorman" with walt and his dad... i thought it was really good, plus walt works at the theather so i got in free..yay! i'm bummed i can't make it to practice tomorrow, too bad i'm supposed to be running 54 miles this week, yeah that's right 54 miles! ha ha even the NC State girls said that was a lot of mileage. I dunno how I feel about doing high mileage, i mean on the one hand we have high goals that we wanna reach as a team and individually so I mean I wanna do what it takes, but on the other hand, 1. how much is too much.. eg. overtraining...shin splints you know 2. running like 10 mile runs by yourself sucks balls. oh well i'll quit complaining. i went over to justine's last night for her "not a birthday party/hangout" which i mean i guess was pretty cool. things got pretty hectic, michael thompson cracks me up though, i never knew he was so crazy. and i really liked giving melissa and justine their birthday presents. ha ha my card cracked me up. sara riggs you're the best girlie! and so are you melissa, it was so good to get to hang out, after soo long. ha ha ok well i guess i'm gonna go to sleep or something since i went to bed at like 5 am this morning and then had to wake up for church.... nite!  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wow so i'm at work and 8 hours a day in one house w/ three little kids is not so fun....  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       HEY! Wow, I missed my blog! So, I just got back about a week ago from my delegation to Nicaragua! Let me just say, it was incredible. I can't even begin to describe everything that happened. First of all let me just say, Nicaragua is the most beautiful place, the scenery is amazing, the people are welcoming and kind, and it's sad that they have so many problems. Also the people I went with were awesome... I love everyone on my delegation!  There are a few main problems in Nicaragua, the debt they can never pay off, the IMF and WTO's "structural adjustment programs", & the immense poverty. Nicaragua seriously is in the middle of an economic war. It's sad that country's like the US spend billions of dollars on war and weapons that kill when Nicaraguan people can't afford the necessities to live. Anyway, it was an experience I will never ever forget... More on it later I suppose. It's nice to be home, but I kind of miss all my friends... Although Sara I had fun yesterday. :-) Hmmm, so now that I'm back, here's my life as of now, running, working ( which I'm doing right now), hanging out. I would like to say that I was invited to go to the beach, Hershey Park, Ohio twice, but I had to say no to a lot of those options.... Boo hoo Alright and now for the random shallow part about my Nicaraguan trip.... I SAW JA RULE at the airport, and got a picture with him... YAY... haha  alright that's all for now, because I should be checking on the kids I'm babysitting.... haha, oh and Harry potter 3... What a good movie, and I'm dying to see farinheight 911! Peace, Bernadette 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        wut up.... i'm at laura and ellen's right now b/c we're having our "reunion" w/ the yonkes who i haven't seen in sooo long. let's see, what've i been up to... well cfl and camp for the past 2 weeks. let me just say both= sooooo much fun. john and alice are the coolest even tho i haven't seen them in like 5 years, so i thought it would be awkward. anyway, cfl, seamus you are the best, doug you're so funny... ummm camp cypress bay i love you guys.... kev,lee,doran,billy you guys are great. well i gg so much more i could say. peace, bernadette   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>