<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bev had to go into surgery again, she had developed an infection in the previous surgical site that they were unable to stop with antibiotics.  The surgery went well, but she may also have pneumonia, so she will be going to the ICU on a breathing tube after Postop.  The surgeon is confident he got all the infection.  Other than that, things are going well.  Lyn and I got back from a business trip that I took to Santa Cruz as part of my new position at work.  I snuck her into the motel room, it was fun!  It was good to see the place again, it had been a long time since I had been there.  That's it for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Test Pic&nbsp; urlLink    This is my first picture upload, using Hello from Picasa and BloggerBot.  I'll figure out how to let others post to it and post directions.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm changing this blog to Family, I want to try to create a new way to stay in touch with family spread out all over the place.  Lyn and I usually try to put together a Christmas Newsletter to send out with cards, but we didn't make it in time last one, so here is our recent history.  We have been living in Sacramento, in our current apartment for 2 years now, its a little small, but we get by.  Lyn has not been able to teach, with the recent layoffs of teachers, the ranks of the substitute pool have swelled larger than is practical to even attempt to get work.  Lately she has been helping her dad take care of her mom, who has been feeling a little under the weather.  Bev broke her ankle trying to get out of bed, then got a bowl obstruction.  She was scheduled for surgery Sunday, it wasn't supposed to be as involved as Lyn's was, they should be able to keep it to cauterizing adhesions laproscopicly.  Unfortunately, the surgeon couldn't keep it laproscopic, and ended up having to do a full resection.  We don't have all the details yet, but we'll update when we do.  I have been handed a change at work.  I had been working at Mercy San Juan Hospital for over 4 years, when I got the call that I was moving to our Regional office in Rancho Cordova to work in a new position as Tier 3 support.  What this means is I will be mostly working on projects, and Helpdesk tickets that have been escalated beyond the site support technicians.  I will have a service area over much of northern California.  Well, that's it for now, I'm still getting a handle on what I will do with this bloc, I suppose the first thing I should do is tell people about it !!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have never blogged and I'm not sure how much time I will have to put into it, but I have always thought there was much potential for this medium.  I hope to use this to crystalize my ideas, and provide a forum for feedback.  I'm going to create my profile now, so more to come later.  James
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Well, Lyn couldn't let her mom be the only one in the hospital, she had to get herself admitted too.  She had another intestinal episode, it took her a week to clear it up, she came home with a few more meds than when she left.  She plans on going back down to Waterford to continue to help her dad get her mom out of the hospital.  She is getting better, the cast is off, but is not getting up as much as she should. Lyn is going to try to motivate her to get moving.  I, on the other hand, spent last week in Santa Cruz, on business.  I had to go back to continue what I did last time, I might even get another trip.  I didn't want to leave, but Lyn insisted.  I took a disposable camera with me, we'll see how the pics came out.
     

    
</post>



</Blog>