<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Immortality, take it, it's yours!"  -Brad Pitt, TROY  Watch Troy yesterday. I'll put a movie review later. Anyway, I did nothing but play RYL. But I manage to upgrade 2 levels up! MUAHAHAHA! Thank god for parties and helpful players. Anyway, went to TM to eat at Bali Thai. The restaurant was a cuisine made of Balinese and Thai [Thainese?] dishes. I ate these fish that look like a preserved mummy. But then it was yummy. Yeah, went to TRU and played at E-Zone then went on to watch TROY.   Anyway, during dinner, my mum was talking bout masterbation. Yes, masterbation. It was embarrasing when she said  "You know, when Hakim was small, he use to go on the floor and masterbate. " Gawd. I was so embarrased.-hides face-  Will put a movie review later. Ciao my peeps!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling: Lonely  Yeah, it's a Saturday night. And I'm staying in my house all alone. I'm not sure what I'm gonna do tonight. Maybe cut my hair [my hair is like weeds growing on a garden. And everytime you cut, it just grow faster which is frustrating.] But I'm always too lazy to cut. Anyway, maybe I should play RYL and become a geek. Ah. What to do on a Saturday night?   Yeah, I think the June holi's are gonna be boring. Maybe boring enough to wish that school was back.-JENG JENG JENG JENG- But damn my Rugby coach for have long hours of training during the holidays! I want to go to K.L.! Fuck you coach! Just because your not going on holiday dosen't mean you can hold us back! REBEL AGAINST THE SYSTEM! -Grabs pitchfork and torch-  Yeah, maybe going to watch a movie with Daryl, Kevin, Lisa, Tasha and Audrey. Maybe watch The Day After Tomorrow. I'll be a movie critic and tell you is it worth your 8 bucks.   HaZ out.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man. I feel bored. Really bored. I'm so bored that maybe I'll do some housework. But not now. Cause I'm feeling lazy. Why lazy? Maybe because I'm sleepy. Why sleepy? Because I slept at 2.30am playing  Risk Your Life [R.Y.L.] That game is fun man, and now I just turned into a warrior. A warrior with two sabers! Yeah! Okay, screw that topic up to Jupiter. Anyway, woke up at about 11.00am. Watch Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles. TMNT is now my favourite cartoon show. I'm happy that they all got new  look injected into them. Allrightie then, let's pick up a topic from the box of HaZ.  -puts hand in the box and picks up a paper which says  MINAHS -.  Hmm... Intresting.    Minahs   Well, today I'm gonna talk about the stereotype malay girl. The Minah. It's the same as mats, as they have many different type of minah species[examples are minah hip-hop, minah hobi(something like that.), pash minah etc.].  Okay, back to topic. The most common Minah is the uhm.. Actually, I do not know. I'm not a minah-o-logist okay?   Let's call the steretype minah, minah fugly. Oh well, the minah fugly likes to hang out in the malls with their boyfriends who treat them like shit. Yeah, they will go into the bus, with their boyfriends, talk loudly, say who is a flirt and whatever. I have my experiences with them. They keep on looking at me. Eeee... Yeah, and this Damai Secondary bumped her ass on mine and I nearly fell off. Thank god for railings.  How to spot a minah: 1. Wears short skirts. 2. Speaks Malay frequently. 3. Has very arched eyebrows. 4. Tapered skirts.  If your girlfriend has two of these signs, than she is a minah. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not into loud music these days. Maybe I'm feeling sentimental. Oh well.  311 - Love Song  Whenever I'm alone with you  You make me feel like I am home again  Whenever I'm alone with you  You make me feel like I am whole again   Whenever I'm alone with you  You make me feel like I am young again  Whenever I'm alone with you  You make me feel like I am fun again   However far away, I will always love you  However long I stay, I will always love you  Whatever words I say, I will always love you  I will always love you   Whenever I'm alone with you  You make me feel like I am free again  Whenever I'm alone with you  You make me feel like I am clean again   However far away, I will always love you  However long I stay, I will always love you  Whatever words I say, I will always love you  I will always love you   Man I feel gay.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to 311- Love Song  Feeling: Sentimental  Just came back from Kevin's house. I tought Kevin stayed in a HDB flat! But he lived in a terrace home,which has like three stories of uhm...stories. Yeah, back to Kevin's home. He has like two computers man! He has two webcams too. And has like this flat screen TV which can be used as a computer screen and a normal TV! Great huh?!   Anyway, Daryl gave a major booster to K&L relationship. It's sweet to do that kind of thing. Anyway, I went to Siglap Centre and saw her. I was like, "hey yeah bye". And she looked kinda sad, but she blocked me. So fuck it.  At Siglap, I met this guy, let's call him  War . He's a sadistic, idiotic jerk. Seriously. He threw away a cage full of hamsters[two are dead, one is still alive], sawdust and hamster poo into the dustbin. Being an animal lover, I picked up the surviving hamster, and decided to maybe give to somebody who loves hamsters. I decided to give it to Taralyn, and she has a cute name for it.  Daddy DJ . I was laughing my ass off, but it was a cute name for a hamster. But it was an oringal name for a hamster.  Who would call a hamster Daddy DJ ?  Anyway, thank god she board the bus before War took it and threw it onto the road. I was like "Go Tara, before that bastard takes the hamster!" Thank god and earth as she went into the bus.  Phew.    It looks like it's gonna rain. Oh well, HaZ out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling: Confused  I really suck at blogger dammit. I've been trying to put my pic up so you guys can see my face. Damn the devil for creating html. Oh well, you can see my face here. I'll be doing some works. If it dosen't work, I got a secret weapon. DARYL!     
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came back from school with my mum. We went there to take my report book. I came 4th in class! And 17/83 people! Woot! It was surpising however, as I failed two subjects. But I got 2 A's! WOO! Litreature and Design and Technology are my best subjects. Oh well, I guess I'm looking forward to Home Economics next month. See how I'll do next semester. Well, Miss Kaur seems she was quite proud. Who is Miss Kaur? She's my form teacher. Oh well, I passed 60% overall. That's good. Well, goodbye school books, and hello K.L.! Yeah, that's great. Oh well, HaZ out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a lot of things on my mind. I'm not exactly sure on what to blog about. Maybe I shall take random current things and speak my mind on it.    "I was an atheist untill I found out I was God."   This is a beautiful quote. Very nice one in fact. Thanks to Rubin, my mum's boyfriend's son for that beautiful quote.   Now, I shall speak my 2 cents on the following topics.   Miss Singapore Universe   Sandy Chua. She is the ugliest Miss Singapore winner of  all  time. Firstly, she has a brain of an imbecile. Secondly, she is not sophisicated enough to give judges the "Singaporean modern woman". But somehow, She won that competition maybe because she blowed that Daryl and Stephanie president guy. You know, that short freaky guy. And speaking about Miss Universe, she will so not win the competition. If she does, I'm gonna shave my head and become a monk.    Old Folk's Home   I went to the Old Folk's Home just now. I had to act for the oldies. But the act was meant to aim at the younger crowd, cause it's a parody on mafias. So I think I screwed it up cause I did not rehearse with my fellow actors. So that was it I guess. But as I always expect, the CIP work wasn't a bed of roses. We gotta do cleaning, talking to the folks, made their bed set up the chairs from them to seat etc. But the old folk's was rather jolly actually. But some of em' are also cranky.   Mat  Tapered    The most  "kental"  mat species of them all. Their sense of fashion is as bad as Bill Pullman's speech in Independence Day. For god's sakes man, YOUR LEGS ARE NOT NICE! ANYBODY WHO WEARS TAPERED PANTS LOOKS WORSE THAN BOZO THE FUCKING CLOWN! And don't give me that  "heran tak heran"  crap. I hate those fucking songs.   Movies in 2004   In my opinion, 2004 has the 3rd best movie year I have watch. (1st was 2000, which has the very cool Spiderman, Gladiator. 2nd was 1999 which has the Blair Witch Project and the Matrix) It's possible that 2004 can also be the best movie year if there are more hits in the next 7 months. The movie of the year could be Spiderman 2.   Well, these are my 2 cents on a few topics. HaZ out.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Shrek II         What is it about:  The movie is about Shrek, the angry and cranky ogre, who have just came back with his princess Fiona(who turned into an ogre after her first kiss with Shrek) after their honeymoon. They were summoned to the Kingdom Far Far Away (that's the name of the kingdom) to get the blessings of Fiona's parents, Mum and Dad. Dad gets into a fit when he sees the ogre.   Cast:  Mike Myers, Cameron Diaz, Antonio Banderas, Rupert Evert and some actors only god knows.   Who stole the movie: Puss In Boots i.e. Antonio Bandras character. The voice acting was great as he charmed us with that cute puss face.   Rating:   * * * * /* * * * *  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes! I finally stole Yusli's paper 2 maths! MUHAHAHAHHAHA!~ I can't wait to see your face when Miss Kaur asks you for the paper. Anyway, sorry for the abscence over the weekend. Watch Shrek 2 which I will put a review. Didn't get to watch Troy though.  I have notice that she has blocked me on MSN. I do not know what I did, but I'm sorry. Please stop blocking me.   My computer has crash and now I have to download things all by scratch. DANG BALLS OF JUPITER!  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not bad actually. My mum didn't punish me that bad! HAHA! YES! Only tuition more and that's it. Great eh? Hahaha. But I better massage my mum when she gets home. Good day people. It's 6:18. Gotta play soccer.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I AM SICK OF YOU SON OF A BITCH! Fuck, what the hell did I do? You just  kuti  me on the neck for no apperant reason? Asking me to fuck off? WHO THE HELL YOU THINK YOU ARE?! Talking bout' porn, molesting people, punching Idris for no apperant reason? Idris is a nice guy man. He's ugly, but hell, he's nice. He never did anything wrong to oppose you. BUT YOU, THE SO-CALLED "GANGSTER" IN THE CLASS JUST DON'T LIKE HIM CAUSE HE'S UGLY! FUCK, HAVE YOU LOOKED IN THE MIRROR?! HELL, YOU'RE IN TAF CLUB! AND YOU'RE A FUCKING RETAIN STUDENT TOO! Hell, have you smell yourself? Man, you stink like cheese and ogre. I see people suffering because of you son of a bitch. Hell, I'm suffering myself cause I hate to see you terrorise people. So, this is the last straw. YOU ARE GOING DOWN! SAY BYE-BYE TO ONE OF YOUR EXAM PAPERS BITCH! BY THE TIME YOU'LL READ THIS, YOU PROBABLY LOSE YOUR MATHS PAPER.   And, Syamil, you maybe fucking good-looking, but hell, your attitude stinks like cheese and rotten milk. YOU THINK YOU ARE A BIG SHOT EH? YOU'RE GOING DOWN.  To the girl whose name is Germaine, you terrosie Nathalie. You bullied her. You even call her a flirt! WELL, WELL, WELL! I MAY NOT KNOW YOU, BUT HELL YOU MUST BEEN A FUCKING FAT SLUT!   I'm feeling much better steaming off like this. Just five words for you bitches;  Don't mess with The HaZ.   I got to do some planning on how to sabotaged them. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn it. I gotta give my mum my results. I delayed yesterday. So, these are some way to slightly lighten the punishment.  1. Put the best results on top. This will make her happy first and slowly goes down to anger. You can do it vice-versa if you want to.  2. Sweet talk your mum. Before she breifs you about what punishment you are gonna get, try to sweet talk your mum after that. [Examples are How are you? Have you eaten? Have I ever told you that you look like Cindy Crawford?]  3. Tell her about how the whole class fail. This is a good way to do it. Say that there were only 4 passes in the class of 40.  4. Give her that sad face. Don't try to talk back to her. Always work.  5. Don't give her empty promises. She will be mad the next time she remembers. [Provided that your mum does not have short-term memory]  6. Also, fake tears will be a plus. When your mum scolds you, try to cry madly.  7. Don't talk back. Very important.  8. If the all of the above fails, then try to revenge her. Not really a good choice unless you love your mama.  So, pray for me peeps. Hoefully this works for me.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my good ass. I just got back my results. I tought I did okay for some of it, but some people know that my malay and maths sucks like a bitch. These are my results.  Geography- 64 Maths- 43 Malay- 43 Science- 67  So far, these are the only results I got. So, stay tune to this blog people if you wanna know how well I did.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh damn the next whole week. I'm also trying to get the sickness from my mum and Tasha(heard that she got a cold). Somehow, I'm immune to it. I'll be getting my Mid-Year results. Pretty scary. Cause what i heared from my teacher that only 9 peeps passed Maths and there were loads of single-digit numbers in the Science paper which is over a 100. Damn! And my malay! AHH! But this is what i predict I will get.  English-60 to 75 Maths-40 to 60 Malay-30 to 60 Geography-50 to 65 Science-50 to 70 Litreature-65 to 75 D & T-50 to 65  Well, that's my predictions. Hopefully i'll pass em'. It's about 9.13 pm. Goodnight people.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You should be dating a Virgo. 23 August - 22 September This mate is known for his/her ability to work with the helpless, to evoke strong feelings of empathy and to keep a household strictly organized.  Though the virgin can sometimes be scathingly critical of others, cranky and irritable, he/she will seduce their partner with finesse, charm and subtlety.    urlLink   What Zodiac Sign Are You Attracted To?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Oh my god. And she's a Virgo! :O    Ghost or spirit: You are a lost soul. Very calm and sweet, you are often the one who asks: What if? With a clever mind, you want to explore the world on a different level. Without the answers, you aren't ready to move on. You are most likely very creative and find yourself thinking things through on a different level. (please rate my quiz)    urlLink   **Where will you go when you die?**(now with pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You are most likely to be the Vampire Chevalier!   The Chevalier personifies the vampire that acts with noble intentions, despite what it is capable of. Taking a conflicting nature and resolving its issues, the chevalier both embraces and yet keeps the vampiristic nature in check; the hunt and taking of blood is enjoyed greatly, yet is restricted to those who willingly give, 'wrong-doers,' or is taken in self-defense; its powers are also embraced willingly, yet while it blatantly and proudly uses them, those that harm are only used in self-defense or in the defense of others. The vampire charm is used in full, and the chevalier appears as one of the most alluring of all vampires, often lordly in appearance as well. Because of the open embrace of its powers and seemingly royal stature, the chevalier often is an immensely powerful vampire.   Dominant personality trait: Pride  Dominant color: Gold  Fictional Vampire Examples: Meier Link ('Vampire Hunter D: Bloodlust'), Jean-Claude ('Anita Blake: Vampire Hunter')   Curious to see how you would fare as a creature of the night? Come this way...     urlLink   Vampire Classification Quiz (w/ Pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    DRACULA! FEAR ME AS I AM A CHEVALIER!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blah. Doing chores and all. It just makes me feel flustered. Anyway. I wanna watch TROY. Heard that it was good. I just watch the amercian behading. It is so not right. Seriously. Not right. At least if they wanna kill him, just shoot him! Not cut his head. Oh yeah, they didn't cut his head with just one slice. They cut his head with like a kitchen knife and cut it with a to and fro motion. Damn painful to watch.   Hopefully, I'll get to see her tomorrow. But my mum is not feeling well. Hiaz. She's like the nicest girl I have ever met without a single flaw. She's nice, sweet, and beautiful. I seriously like this girl.   Anyway, I will post up reviews on TROY and blah dee dah.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Somehow, on Mondays, I usually get the worst bad luck. I just got into a fight with my whole family, talking about sensitive issues about my dad. Then, I happen to come across Daryl's blog and there was this issue about me. If he want's it to end this way, then I can't stop him.  Sometimes, I feel suicide maybe the best way to solve problems.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey peeps. Back again. Sorry I didn't update for a while. Was real busy [yeah right]. I went to Wild Wild Wet [WWW] yesterday. Pretty dissapointing. Esp the wave pool. Got scratches because of the stupid wall and got bumped in the head by other floats.Just go to Escape. The rides were dissapointing too. GAH.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came bacn from the St. Pat's fair. Man, I'm feeling pooped. I was quiet tired. Anyway, came at 12 noon [I was suppose to come at 11]and made my grand entrance. Met up with Lis and Audrey [two hot girls]. Than with Kevin. I promised Audrey I won't act like a jerk. So I didn't most of the time. I was pretty dehydrated during the fair because of two reasons.  1. The weather is fucking humid 2. I was wearing black.[Everything]  So I end up sweating. Sweating untill I get Lisa all wet with my sweat [eew.]Lisa squeezed my cheeks. Yay! Okay, better not say it cause later somebody will get jealous.*cough*KE*cough*Vi*cough*n  Anyway, just went there to meet up with my old friends and then I met Keith Arriola! My Montfort rugby friend. He was with Roshan. Anyway, there were lots of hot girls around there[except for Shrek's wife, Germaine]. Like everybody there was hot! Anyway, Fuz hit my arm when I was talking so I was pretty surprised.   We then buy helium baloons and suck in the helium. Man, we talked like Donald Duck! Totally!  Went to talk to Fuz when going home. I was sad that I never bought her ketchup. I'm sorry! Really I am! Going to sleep peeps.  HaZ out.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came back from my datuk's house[again]. Played with my cousins. They are just so adorable. Haris, the 2nd child who is only like 2 years old, is quite smart. He can do those things which I can't do! Like say Spiderman! But in the baby way like Ahh-Man! Played the PS2 than went home and buy some donuts. Lazy to update.  HaZ out.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came back from Changi Village for dinner. Changi has a good point and a bad point. The good point is that the food there is terrific. The bad point is that there are too many transvestites hanging around there. Eww. Yeah. Anyway, ate fish & chips. One of the best fish & chips I ever had. The best was Fish & Co. Had dinner with my dad, sis and mum. After that we went to buy some breakfast for tomorrow.  As my dad was driving out of the carpark, we saw one of the most well-built [as in plastic surgery] transvestites ever. And may any man, woman, or shemale would have their eyes on her. Her V-neckline top was so low that I was afraid that Mary-Kate, Ashley [I name boobs after them] and little Timmy might pop out[You know what I'm refering to]. But there was another transvestite around and she was one of the ugliest one ever.  But then, after we went out of the carpark, my ever-so cheeky mum ask my dad to go into that carpark again to see the bosom wonder of the world. And my dad pass her and even slow down beside her! I, the ever so embarrased one [for the transvestite and myself] pushed the pedal to the metal and we quickly zoomed out of the carpark.   Went to fetch my sister from work. She asked me a question, and that question was; do you have any friends who are Singapore Idol fanatics? My answer was no. But she will interview the guy who is an addict. So do my sister a favour. If you are going for the audition in two days time, and you want to be interviewed for TODAY newspaper, please leave me a comment yah?  I had my haircut about two days ago. It was the same haircut for like for the past 5 years of my life. Somehow, I had the same haircut, but my hair is like David Beckham's mohawk. Not bad eh? I got a pervert's hairstyle!  Going to sleep soon. My back's killing me. Arse. Anyway, see ya tomorrow.  HaZ out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came back from my Grandad's house. Went to eat for lunch/dinner. Every of my cousins are there. Played the PS2 and kicked the hell out of my uncle's creation called Mandrake. What kind of stupid name is Mandrake? So that guy deserves to be beaten up for a stupid name. So beat him up than watch miss universe. Blah. Lazy to update.  HaZ out.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        TROY          The Movie is about: Two countries, Greek and Troy, had a peace treaty untill Paris[Orlando Bloom] falls in love with Helen[Diane Krueger] and she runs away with him back to Troy and that sparked a war between the two countries. The King of Greeks[I forgot his name] asks Achilles[Brad Pitt] to kick some royal Trojan ass.   Cast: Brad Pitt, Diane Krueger, Orlando Bloom, Eric Bana   Opinion on the movie:  Basically, it's just a love story with a war element inside. The first 20 minutes was boring, but than when the war starts, see Brad in action! Man, he has the body of what everybody wants man. Great. Diane Krueger shouldn't be as Helen Of Troy. The reason is that her beauty isn't enough. They call her the Face That Launch A Thousand Ships. I call her The Face That Could Only Launch Five Sampans [boat in malay].   Who steals the movie:  Brad Pitt. The war kicks major ass. He was like superman in there. He kills people easily like a master warrior.    Rating:   * * * *[1/2] /* * * * * 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a friggin' busy day for me. I woke 8.40am and started doing errands for the whole friggin' day. First we went to Tampines, went to transfer $30 bucks into my T-X account [How many of you have one? :p]. Yeah, went to CPF to do some maid shit then went to go to Parkway Parade to cut my hair than went to MOM. Ministry Of Manpower building. Went over there to do some stuff and than we went to my mum's office to do my mum's stuff. Blah.  But then when I went in, everybody recgonize my mum and say "Wah, who is this boy? So big ah? So handsome." I was like blushing my ass off. I just smile and ran away then. Played the computer at my mother's office and I just found out that Daryl has defected to the  merkhadians [monster side of R.Y.L.]! Dang! But he say that I copied him cause there was another server and I started a monster side there. So yeah, I did not copy him.   As I was using the comp, aunty Sally heard me talking and she said that she felt sorry cause of my voice. WTF?! She say that like when I have a cough, I cannot clear my throat. But Aunty Sally is cute cause I was bored to death over there and she messaged my mum on MSN that I'm dying slowly. Sigh. I love her cause she's like a mum to me too.  After finishing some stuff at me mum's office, we walked through Arab Street. As we come to Baghdad Street, my mum started to come across old neighbours of my father's shop. She being the social person, ask how was buisness. But as always, there's always a common answer.  Bad .  Walked to Seiyu to see if there was the rare Phantom Stikfas. But damn the balls of the devil. There was none! Aiyee! Gonna play RYL. I'm already level 17. Muahahaha!  HaZ out.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Three Days Grace - [I Hate] Everything About You  Every time we lie awake  After every hit we take  Every feeling that I get But I haven't missed you yet  Every roommate kept awake by  Every sigh and scream we make  All the feelings that I get  But I still don't miss you yet   Only when I start to think about it...   I hate everything about you  Why do I love you  I hate everything about you  Why do I love you   Every time I lie awake  After every hit we take  Every feeling that I get  But I haven't missed you yet   Only when I start to think about it...   I hate everything about you  Why do I love you  I hate everything about you  Why do I love you   Only when I start to think about you I know  Only when you start to think about me do you know   I hate everything about you  Why do I love you  You hate everything about me  Why do you love me  I hate  You hate  I hate  You love me  I hate everything about you  Why do I love you  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey peeps. Yeah, I know it's been quite a while since I update this junk. But I've been  "busy".   Anyway, I've been pretty down and depressed. But what's new eh? But usaully, you'll know that after all this crap has happened, it'll probably turn brighter right?    Wrong. It's getting worse and worse-rer [is there such a word?].   Apperantly, I heard I'm on one to the "wanted" list. Well, not one, but a couple now. I lost my chairman badge, I&nbsp;called an ah-beng a fucking retard, and apperantly, the class hates me. But no surprise on the "class-hates-me" issue. People think I'm gay, but well, I'm not. I just act gay. I'm a full-pledge metrosexual. I am loyal to the females even though I just got out of a bad relationship.   Yeah, as for the ah-beng guy, he hit me knee and I shouted in the library, "Fucking retard!" And somehow, he says I'm insulting his parents. Outside, I was calm and cool. On the inside, I was saying "What the hell are you smoking?" And then comes Gerald, the real homosexual in my class, said this to me. "Eh, you better watch out. Later, Robin will beat you up"   Oh ho ho. Some short fuck gonna beat me up? HAH! At 1.7 m and 58 kg, do you think a small 1.5 guy can kick my ass? Well, yeah. I'm a gentle giant, and I don't like to bully peeps. So maybe he'll kick my ass.   I wonder what will Miss Kaur will do when she finds out I lost my badge. Probably she'll say&nbsp;this. "It's okay sweetie, we'll just make a new one!" Yeah, my form teacher has a crush on me. When she, a thing that Godzilla would fear, has a crush on a pansy&nbsp; like me. Bah, I prefer to rape Ashley. -winks-   Anyway, my sister has not been switching off the air-con in my home. But the good thing is that I can relax in my room after school. *smiles*   HaZ out.   &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey peeps. I'm sick now. Got a damn high fever. 40 degrees man! That's like high. I'll tell you the timeline from yesterday to today.  5.30 am-6.21am Woke up and went to school.  6.30am-7.30am Reach school and touched Ashley's tits. :)  9.30am-10.45am I got dressed up as some Singaporean retardo who looks like a retarded version of I, Robot.  10.45am-11.00am Went back home with Idris. Poor guy. From Hougang he travels to Clementi when going home. He's a nice guy, but erm...let's just say his face is related to The Beast.  11.00am-12.42pm Departure at Bedok MRT. Went back home.  12.45pm-1.00pm Came back home tired, and sick.  1.00pm-3.00pm Gets the fever lagi worse. Slept till 5.oopm.  5.00pm-6.30pm Just slept in my room. I put on my sweater and hence, my fever get's higher.  7.00pm-8.00pm Mum came back. She was worried why the lights weren't on.  8.01pm to 8.30pm Went to two clinics and they were closed. So we went to the clinic near the 7/11 store. The doctor is a nice guy man.  8.35pm-9.45pm Watched Starsky and Hutch on DVD. Damn fun! Ate lots of cream puffs and a snicker bar.  10.00pm-10.30pm Slept to 1.00 am cause my sister was sponging me. I don't know why she must sponge me at that time. Geesus!  1.00am-3.00am Watched boat trip after I was sponged. Dman cold.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An interesting "urban legend" reaches my mailbox. Amusing and hopefully worthy of sharing with you :  Eating Sperm is another old n ancient "Urban Legend" dating back to the Biblical times. The fact is there are countless women the world over who love consuming sperm than anyone cares to imagine.  French women are the most avid sperm-eater in Europe, having learned from the Arab females whose Arab husbands believed that by 'eating' his sperm on both 'mouths', the wife can be addicted to be faithful. In fact in Algeria n in many other Arab countries the husbands penis is, must be for the first time, be inserted in the wife's month n thus the first drop of sperm on a wife is consumed by the mouth before the pussy had the chance. (If the woman displeased the husband, sodomy is the punishment, but strangely some women loves this rear entry after a few 'punishments') And so the legend just lives on. In fact it is a secret craving and culture among almost all females. In the old days, a Chinese family will always appoint "an adviser" to the bride on the secret arts of sex, the do’s and don’ts, and it's various articulations, rewards and consequences. The adviser will always get a fat angpow when a baby boy is born and a smaller one or nothing if a daughter is born in the first year of marriage.  One of these 'teachings' is the male sperm is the "core" of the males' (thus family's) health n essence of life. Too much of it 'spewed' must be replaced almost immediately by simple consumption of "Essence of Chicken' or consuming Chinese herbs regularly. The Cantonese and the Hakkas are champions in this concept and so we can safely say they are the greatest sperm-eaters among the Chinese. The Japanese women are not far behind. Since so much value is placed on the sperm, the consumption of it is "discouraged" as it drains the husband's youth and vigor. So it is considered a 'selfish' act by the wife. But if the husband is hale and healthy, then it is OK but still, it must be 'replaced'. Sperm-eating is "dangerous" if the husband is sick or ill. Besides, consuming the sperm is just transferring the sickness or disease to the woman. But the smarter women 'steal' sperm regularly as long as she 'replace' it. Otherwise over a period of time if the husband is noticed to be suffering from ill-health, she woull be blamed for draining away his youth, vigors and general 'wellness'.  Just remember the old Chinese adage "Chiak Shi Hock, Hock Shi Chiak" in refined translation it means :- "To Eat is Luck n Blessing and Food itself is Luck n Blessing too" Woman are great sperm connoisseurs - 100 percent- all of them. The only difference is more or less, regularly or once in a while. Some do it with ginseng drinks or other nutritious drinks as 'chasers'. Great and famous beauties Like Cleopatra were reputed to be living on a regular daily dosage of male human sperms. The list extends to vicious demons like Empress Dowager of China (Manchu Dynasty) even to Queen Victoria of Great Britain, even perhaps to the present QE2.  Celebrities like Marilyn Monroe, Mae West, Elizabeth Taylor, etc. are also said to be regular consumers. Helping them keep young and youthful, improve their sexual prowess and all that spout from the "Fountain of Youth"  There is low-profile but highly profitable companies from Texas to Tasmania selling to women all over the world capsules deep-frozen Male Bull's sperms and that of other Exotic wild animals at very high prices.  Personally, I know a woman who actually paid young Bangladeshi contract worker to eat their sperm "fresh from the cow". She is an 'old' woman now (62) but in her youthful hey days as a night-club dance hostess, she was red-hot or super 'red-label'. I knew of this because she was caught "milking sperm" directly by the supervisor (a woman too) whom I also know. She pleaded to my friend to keep mum thus keeping her reputation and her job but her supervisor pitied her, warned her not to do it at the work-place (in the seldom used darken stairways). When I ask her one day why she did it, she said that without the 'dosage' she felt old, 'pain n wind all over'. She had always preferred sperm in her mouth rather than in her pussy and she never had sex with any "hak yean" or 'blackies' which is hard to believe. This sperm 'secret' she told me was passed on to her by a "Mummy" who also happened to be her "adopted" Mum, who in earlier days used to work as a 'Ah Mah' for some rich Chinese family, and "sometimes" as mistress to the boss n boss's friends. (This is interesting because she said she born in Malaysia and when I suggested that for all she knew, her Mum could have been pregnant and sent over there to give birth.) Her Mum's house-keeping duties included taking care of the employer children and in the process, Mum milked the young boys almost everyday. Her Mum is now pass 80s but look a lot younger facially and still relatively healthy.  So what the real truth ?  Sperms or spermatozoa of male mammals contains a high proportion of testosterones or male sex hormones. Medical professionals are perplexed how this ingredient can be believed to boost a woman's youth and sexual prowess. If there's any link at all, then it should have better result for male consumers rather than on the females. The legend goes on.  In some islands of the Philippines, Indonesia and the whole Pacific Indo-Pacific region, some females believe that by smearing fresh sperm from young virgin boys on their face will somehow make them attractive n thus improve their chances of snarling a man of their liking.  -from "fukyuman" in Sammyboy's alfresco coffee shop [forum] 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Movie Review: 13 going on 30   Rating:  *[1/2]/*****  This piece of crap comedy, about a girl turning into an ugly 30 year old [Jeniffer Garner] belongs to the toilet. I bought the DVD [pirated of course] and it's really crappy. There is one scene where Jeniffer Garner took the house from fugly actor what'shisnamecauseheistoofugly and there were still the "Wishing Dust" from the house. 17 years and there is still wishing dust? What the fuck. Not worth your money.  Who steals the movie: Nah-dah, no one. Not enjoyable. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey peeps. Whassup? Anyway, school was okay. Manage to go on the 6.30 bus and watched Vandread. :) I realised that it was a clear blue sky. So i tought to myself, what can go wrong?  Many things. MANY.  Apperantly, during the national anthem, Mr Rama [the suppose to be police-cum-teacher] caught me singing the song in a monotonous voice. Cause who bothers to sing the national anthem? I just well, talk the national anthem. He cause a comotion in class. Oh whoop-dee-doo.  Met Ashley, Aaron and Anthony [the three A's!] and talked crap before school. At recesss met Jude [the HAMSOMEST guy in whole of sec 1] and Jeremy Noel a.l.a. J.No! I tell you, Jude said, what Aaron said,  "If you were a girl I would fuck you.". In return, I said, "If I was a girl, I'll rape you." I tell you, Jude is DAMN good looking. Eventhough he's not the smartest guy [he's in NT], he's sarcastic. He reminds me of Audrey if Audrey was a boy. =p  The funny thing is that, Jude says that he wanted to go to SPS! I was like "OMFG!" A person who wanted to go to St. Pats! That's a first! And I can sense the Patricians blood in him. He really wanted to go St. Pats but his mother said it was too far. Deja Vu.  After school, went to the 2nd level and met with Jude, J. No and Simon. Simon wacked me in the balls and I  kena  punched by everybody. Then I go kuti Aaron untill he nearly cried. Simon tried to grab my balls, but I grab his and he fell down like a duck. Lol.  All right peeps. Gotta go. My latest movie review is gonna be 13 going on 30. Ciao!  HaZ out.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>