<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think that people who are in love are actually terrible egoists. At least I am. I am afraid that I am having a terrible crush. HOpe it works out.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am listening to Asleep From Day ( Hope Sandoval & Chemial brothers) and dont understand how I have never heard it before. Anyway, before I forget, here s my update on my graduation.  I arrived on Friday, met Linda and Angel (the guy who is studying for the M Juris this year) for a dinner and then we went to the pub for a few drinks. Then it was time to get to the college and get asleep. I was very lucky coz Linda's college mate let me use her room coz she went home for that weekend. I was a bit nervous about how the whole graduation thing will go, coz I have never really enjoyed the stiff and formal dinners/lunches at my college. Anyway, on Saturday morning I picked up my graduate gown (long, black with blue hood, lined with white fur)from one of the shops (30 pounds...not cheap...but then, I did not have to buy a dress). Then me and Linda had a leisurely breakfast at the News caffee. Then it was time to get to my college to pick up the graduation tickets and fill out a few papers). The porter could not pronounce my name (surprise), but I managed to get the tickets. Then I had to give my graduant gown (the one with the hood) to the person who d took it to Sheldonian and help me change the gown after the first part of the ceremony. Since every degree has a different gown, all gowns are labelled, so that you d get the right one.  I was very very happy to meet one of my British course  mates I studied EU law with. Luckily, he turned out to be my table mate also. (I ve had a few NIGHTMARE experiences with table mates who dont talk...and then you have to spend 2 h dinner smiling idiotically). I actually caught the guy and rather assertively asked if he might perhaps been in my class...and of course he did not remember, but then his mother came to his resque saying that if I am graduating, I must be on the seating plan...and then I left to fill in the papers and let the guy to regain his composture. When we met next time, he said he now remembers me, and mixes up the courses:) Anyway, he was an ok mate, and I had a bulgarian girl on the other side, so it was a delightful lunch all together.  However, before the lunch we had a briefing on how the ceremony will happen. and there came the surprise. Since Oxf is a classical Uni, lawyers, doctors and philosophers are first to get the conferral. Lawyers are THE first, actually. And since I was the ONLY law student graduating, I was first to be presented to the Vice Chancellor...and had to do it ALONE. A bit scary, huh? Also, I mislaid my academic hat somewhere...so I had to look for it...but I luckily found it. Anyway, after the lunch we formed a procession and went to the Sheldonian.  When we got to the Sheldonian, we got seated according to the sequence of presentation. Namely, the graduation ceremony consists of being presented to the Vice Chancellor of the Uni, receiving a formulae of disharge announcing that one has received the degree, then getting out of the Sheldonian, changing the gown to the graduants gown with the hood and then going by the Vice Chancellor once more.   The first three degrees to receive the discharge are law, medicine and philosophy - the three degrees that were awarded by the historical universities.   The ceremony starts with the Vice-Chancellor and Proctors entering and then the Vice-Chancellor opens the Congregation by saying "Causa huius Congregationis est ut Gratia concedantur, ut gradus conferantur, necnon ut alia peragantur quae ad hanc Venerabilem Domum spectant".  Then the Registrar reads out a statement saying that all these students have been granted graces by their colleges to receive the degrees. This has been important as in Middle Ages Colleges sometimes imposed conditions on graces.   One of the Proctors reads out a list of all people asking for the degrees, mentioning their colleges and names, and the degree they are asking for. Then the two Proctors walk amidst the COngregation and back and then states that "Hae Gratiae concessae sunt et sic pronuntiamus concessas". Originaly they took the votes of the congregation, and, if somebody plucked on their gowns, somebody did not receive the degree.   Then the candidates for various degrees are presented to the Vice - Chancellor and Proctors either by the Dean of the respective College or by a professor. As I said, I was the only M Jur graduant, so I was the only one wearing a blue and white hood. Also, I was the first of the persons who was presented to the Vice Chancellor. I was presented by the Regius Professor of Civil law. I had to stand on his right side, and, while holing my right hand he read out a formula of presentation something to the lines of me being a great scholar etc:) The formula used for BA is "Insignissime Vice-Cancellarie, vosque egregii Procuratores, prasento vobis hos meos scholares in facultate Artium, ut admittantur ad Gradum Baccalaurei in Artibus."
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Several people have wondered how come I am going for my graduation this week, while I have been boasting about my Oxon law degree for half a year or more already.   It is all because in Oxford graduation ceremonies can only take place in the Sheldonian theatre, and its tiny.  Therefore, graduation ceremonies take place throughout the year, and in each ceremony each college is allocated a few places. You have to book the ceremony in advance, for instance, I booked mine some time in December! As a result, person does not really graduate together with his or her course mates. Moreover, some people graduate 10 or more years after they have done their exams!  My main reason for booking ceremony on 22nd of May was to have a graduation ceremony in a period when the weather is nice (albeit I am told its gonna be ghastly this weekend), so I could go punting together with my friends and make a lot of pictures. I am also pretty lucky, coz Linda, a girl who was in Oxford in my year and who became a very close friend, decided to go visit her Oxford tutor during the week of my graduation. Also, I will meet a Latvian law student who is doing a M Jur at Oxford University this year. Btw, he is one of the crazy guys who is doing the rowing:)  Anyway, the graduation itself differs significantly from graduations in other Universities. First, as I mentioned, you dont graduate with your classmates. Instead, you have a nice lunch at your college, chatting with people and drinking sherry.  Then, you dont get a diploma. For example, I already have mine, although I ll order some more as my new diplomas will have the date of graduation on them. Diplomas are ordered and students receive them in mail.  All the ceremony takes place in Latin . And all students wear subfusc, gowns and hoods.  urlLink Description of subfusc  has been a constant source of entertainment for Krommenaas, so I thought you might enjoy it as well. However, all that fun aside, it also looks very impressive when all the students and other members of the univeristy gather in the Sheldonian. What makes M Jur people especially happy is the fact that lawyers and doctors (medicine students) have the same gown (blue hoods). And only these two, and masters in theology and the DPhil graduates sit behind the Chancellor as a part of the Oxford congregation.  Graduands enter the Sheldonian wearing the old gown (no hood), then during the ceremony they go and change, and then  and enter again for the "blessing". Also, after the graduation, I can finally wear my academic hat, that, as some of you might remember, I had to take to all of my exams.  After the ceremony, I ll go for the tea with my friends and then, if the weather is good, we will go punting. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Apparently, in Glasgow, “It’s pure baltic man” means "Brrrrr it’s frightfully chilly":)  urlLink Glaswegian  Its not really that bad here, honest!    urlLink London pubs     For those of you who are wondering what I speak sometimes:   urlLink Crazy Latvian  And dont ask me what the VERY ADVANCED K is:)  I hoped to make use of  urlLink Oxon Society     Crazy Russians...have posted the whole  urlLink stories   by Kuttner in Russian.... . And  urlLink five stories on Galagher    mmmm. Oh well, copyright is not an advanced concept there I guess:)  I know brits tend to be a bit on the  urlLink lustful   side...but my Uni??? OMG  :D  What  urlLink country  are you?   On penguines being thrown and my favourite page on internet culture:   urlLink Scotsman internet       I was told that this  urlLink link    might take my mind of guys. Well it did for a very short time, but then I found a lot of advice on snogging. And that did it:)  However, I ve also found a cool article on betting and WMD from my Alma mater  urlLink here , enjoy:)    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, its a Sunday morning and I am starting my third blog. Thanks for nothing, people, in relation to choosing its name. Apart from various comments that "this sounds as a liver desease", ''hopeless'', ''whats that supposed to mean'' and "that reminds me of a beefsteak" I did not get any feedback. Ah, yes, one suggestion referred to Belle de Jeur's blog. Thanks. A quick update, I am turning into a frequent flyer those days, am going to my graduation on 21st of May, then to Bxl for my EU civil service final interview from 5th-8th (the exam itself will be 45 mins) and then moving to Luxembourg on 15th of June. Since I am investing ALL the money in plane tickets and hotels, I expect to live on pasta until September afterwards.  Am doing a bit of revising of my German, and pretending to be listening to French lessons tapes that were kindly sent to me. Also, stressing about managing to finish up my two current jobs. So, as you see, very busy. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have been a bit busy, but here s a short update.  I attended my oral exam for the work as a civil servant of the EU on Tuesday the 8th of June. I arrived to Brussels on Saturday and stayed in a sorta yout hotel   urlLink http://www.sleepwell.be&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; with my would-be roomie.  On Saturday we went for a dinner and then pretended to be revising. On Sunday we revised a bit and then I called my friend in Luxembourg to arrange meeting on Monday evening. I tried phoning my Belgian friend in Antwerp, but upon reaching him and asking if I could speak to him, I got a reply that I have reached a wrong number. Ruined my (non-existant) self confiednce as I had to conclude he does not want to talk with me.  My roomie had her exam on Monday afternoon. In the morning we phoned somebody who had the exam at 10:00 and heard what the questions are and they wer awful. I waited for my roomie &amp; she came out of her exam not entirely happy with it. I also managed to finally reach my Belgian friend, as I guess he thought its somebody else calling that time.  Anyway, my Luxembourg residing friend had exam on Monday too, but afterwards h drove all the way to Brussels to meet me for a casual dinner. Sweet, aint it?:) I met him at 17:00 and we walked around a bit, then had a dinner.  I had my exam on Tuesday morning. I have no idea whether it went ok. I ll have me results by the end of September. However, there were two people from the European Parliament Legal service and they were not entirely happy that I had only given Commission, Council and Court as the institutions I would like to work for. To quote "Parliament has a great legal service and there are so nice people working ther, why nobody wants to work for us".  TBH, I think I was not at my best. I had slept poorly, and was too busy thinking about something else. Well, we ll see. There ll be another competition announced in December. Besides, at this particular moment I dont have an idea as to what I would like to do. Well, I *THINK* I would rather live in Bxl than Lux.  After exam I went to the Gare Central and met my Belgian friend there. He had *gasp* had to get up in the morning to come over to Bxl and meet me, for which I am very very thankful. He showed me around a bit and we discussed something ( I dont really remember what) but I am afraid I was too wrapped up in my post exam trauma to leave a good impression. Oh well, thats life:)  This weekend I had my most favourite teacher visiting. Unfortunately I was terribly terribly busy:(  Anyway, I am moving to Lux on Tuesday. I have nearly packed. The only thing bothering me is that the EU has not reimbursed me the previous trips, so I am completely broke. But I am meeting my Luxembourg residing friend, so I hope all will work out well:)  I am not taking my PC with me, so I will only rarely be on yahoo msg or icq. However, I will be more than happy to receive emails from all of you. Also, if you are somewhere nearby, give me a call and I will be more than happy to meet you.  As to the EU, play this: http://www.europaquiz.org/.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had my French exam (for level 1) about an hour ago and will know if I have passed by 3 pm. I need 60% but I am not quite certain if I will pass, as I have not studied enough the last two weeks.  One of the reasons for this was the weekend trip to Brussels and Brugge to meet Len's brother and brother' s fiance. (Btw, if I wrote ''his'' fiance would you think&nbsp;that she is&nbsp;brother' s fiance or Len' s fiance?)?  Anyway, the first night we stayed in what probably was the worst hostel I have ever stayed in. It was noisy, bleak and did not have hot water. Len had earplugs, so he blissfully slept and added to my misery by snoring. There was no hot water in the morning either, so by 10 AM on Saturday morning I was angry, hurt, miserable and&nbsp;felt like screaming. When I went downstairs to ask why there s no hot water I was told the problem will be fixed in an&nbsp;hour. Len's brother, however, was told that&nbsp;the hostel is just saving the money.:)&nbsp; The hostel in Brugge was in a very pictoresque place and it had hot water. However, we&nbsp;had to&nbsp;share the bathrooms. In addition, when we arrived, we were told that the rooms will be ready in an hour, but when we returned about 4 hours later, they still were not cleaned. To sum up....I think I am too old (and like comfort too much) to stay in hostels.  Brugge was very pretty (though not as pretty as Luxembourg of course :)). However, its too full of tourists. Like with Prague, you cannot meet a single local, its just people who go there for a day trip. The buildings dont serve their original purposes and the service is not very good coz the business persons are certain you are just there once.  Len and his brother speak fluent French, so its sometimes annoying that they speak this to people around and I dont understand what they are saying. However, in the restaurant in Brugge Len' s brother tried to order in French and the waitress pretended she did not understand. YAY, I SO related to that ;). When I think of that moment, it reminds me of the Latvian and Russian situation in Riga a lot. At one moment I felt a bit strange - when Len asked an owner of a restaurant if there are any free tables, and the owner turned to me and explained that he is really sorry but there are no places etc., etc., etc. I am not quite certain if that was coz Len as well as&nbsp;Len's brother and his fiance are of asian origin, but that is how it appared to me. Apart from that, I have got my tickets for Croatia trip (Aug 28 - Sep 05) and I am also going to Riga (Aug 20 - Aug 22).  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a lazy weekend, mostly coz the weather was terrible. Yesterday I went to a film, ''Just a kiss''(Ae Fond Kiss), directed by  urlLink Ken Loach , and set in, guess, Glasgow.&nbsp; urlLink http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0380366/ . It was quite good. It is a story about a Pakistani guy falling in love with an Irish girl, having a look at the way cultures clush in private life and decisions people&nbsp;face as a result thereof. I am not very religious, but I still cherish religion as something that helps people to find who they are in this world. However, having seen this film, I guess I might be more reluctant to see the positive things about such identification as it probably does require that some people take the hard line protecting the so called core values. And if they have the power to decide, it can ruin a person' s life. Then of course, I have always been the great position of being able to follow my religious beliefs mostly as my code of ethics.  &nbsp; Then I did some shopping, so now I am a proud owner of a hedgren backpack ( urlLink www.hedgren.be ) and several books, including two Terry Pratchet books, one of these entitled The Wee Free Men. And, no, the guy I am dating DOES&nbsp;NOT wear kilt:). &nbsp; Today I started my French classes - they will go on for two weeks, 6 h per day. Let me tell you, French is an awful language. I personally speak 5 languages, and all of these are logical, compared to French. Oh well:( I could learn either to read it or to speak it, but definately not both.  &nbsp; As to the vacation, seems that the decision is finalised, and we are going to Croatia AUG 28 - SEP05. A week seems to not be a long time, but I have no idea what I will do if we start fighting... &nbsp; 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am trying to book a few beauty procedures (dont ask), and feel as an idiot coz no person speaks anything but French. Also, my idea of a great hear dresser is not a 22 year old Italian guy shouting bella! at me (*wink wink*). Besides, I can hardly take my friend to a beaty salon, and ask to conduct the translating service during the waxing, can I? I am starting my intensif French course next Monday, and its definately not too soon! Apart from these worries, I have been working quite hard this week, and the results should be coming out soon.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks to a recent article in the Sunday Times (thank you, thank you thank you), it seems that my British friend has overcome his intitial distrust towards the Eastern Europe, so, if it works out, we are going to Croatia in the end of the August/ begining of September! Mapping out our trip, do you think I should take a ferry from Italy? :D 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I spent the weekend with my Lithuanian course mate from Oxford. She is currently a lawyer at the European Court of Human Rights.  Generally, I liked Strasbourg a lot. I lived in a great hotel in the very centre of the town, and the price of my room striked me as very very low (well, I guess I am getting used to Luxembourg prices). We chatted a lot about Oxford, about our current jobs and how people leave Baltics:( I also did a lot of sightseeing and some shopping. Contrary to Luxembourg that is nearly empty during the weekend and with ALL the shops closed on Sunday, Starsbourg was very lively.  I had a bit of shock, though, when I got on the train and found out that there is some scheme for the reservation of seats on these trains. Hence, on my way to Strasbourg, I had to change my seat about three times (It was a Bxl-Lux-Strasbourg-Bern-Milano train). And I was really worried that I wont get a seat on my way back to Luxembourg. HOwever, I also found out, that the key is to sit in the seats that dont have these silly yellow reservation notes over them...there are a few seats like that:) Oh, well, another lesson of life.  Len - the guy I am sorta --hmmmm?-- dating??? -- is in Breton, spending a week with his family. And, I hate to say that, but it appears, that I *GASP* actually miss him. Not good news, this.  Anyway, I am not certain if he was serious be he ha sbeen asking me about holidays for some time now, so I came up with the idea of going to Coratia -   urlLink http://www.croatia.hr/home/Default.aspx    urlLink http://www.dubrovnik-online.com/english/touristboards.php   Its a bit less touristy that the other two destinations I am considering (Greece and Malta) and it has about the right mixture of historic places I would like to visit and places to just chill out. Also, its about the right size. Finally, I need a bit less of the crowds, just to think over what I would like to do in about a year and whether I feel like taking another exam to secure a permanent position at my current work.  Anyway, we looked at the Europe' s map...and realised that we have travelled around completely different places. Whereas I have travelled around East Central Europe and Scandinavia, he has done all the Western Europe, as well as places like Egypt, Marocco,Turkey. So, wherever we go, one of us has been to the place:(  And, finally...who can understand men? I mean, I am supposed to be the one trying to bring the relationship further, whereas it seems that I am the one dragging my feet here...Mind, its partly due to the fact that, considering my abnormally low self confidence, I think its just a terrible joke:( 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have not really managed to keep up with the initial idea of this blog, namely, to fix my first days in Luxembourg. However, these two weeks have been both fun and a bit nightmarish.  I did not have a place to stay and finding an apartment with my roomies has not worked out as well as we had hoped. Hence I have been on a move all the time, changing places on average every three days or so. Twice I stayed in a hotel, lived with my former class mate for a few days, then in a house of a collegue who went home for a few days. However, I have spent some time at my British friends place.  In my first week I fell from the stairs. I was ok for a few days. Then headaches started a week later. I also feel nauseaus all the time. I did the pregnancy test that frightened me witless! Namely, the instructions (that were in flEmish and french only) did not say that the bloody purple line indicating pregnancy will first appear in the ''results'' part of the test and will thereafter MOVE to the control part. You can probably imagine how I felt realising that the test says I am about to become a single mum in 9 months:) Anyway, since the headaches did not disappear, I went to see a doctor today and also had brain scan. There was nothing abnormal, so the doctor told me to drink paracetamol. No idea what to do about feeling sick all the time. I also moved in in a small room in a house where one of my potential roomies is renting a room. Its for two weeks, but at least I have a place to slep a bit. The lady renitng out the rooms is a bit of psycho, but I think I can hold out for two weeks. Will buy earplugs, though:) Also, I have arranged to have a look at a studio apartment on saturday, but I overheard another person saying he ll be looking at it today:( So keep fingers crossed that I get it. It would mean living alone of course (and I dont really enjoy it), but I need my own space SOON.  As to the British person in my life, all in all, he has taken quite a good care of me, except that he never gives me any breakfast. I have complained about this a few times, so its gradually improving. He also snores. However, I am still waiting for that TERRIBLE trait to appear (the one why he s still single at the age of 29). 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have passed the EU civil service exam. I applied for it last June. Yesterday there was the following letter in my profile. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "I am pleased to inform you that the Selection Board for the above mentioned competition and field has now completed its work and, on the basis of your results, your name has been placed on the reserve list. This reserve list is divided into 4 merit groups, and your name is included in merit group nº 2.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The list will shortly be transmitted to the Institutions which are solely responsible for recruitment. Each Institution will select successful candidates from the list according to its needs and with a view to filling posts which have become vacant. As soon as a suitable position arises, you could be invited for an interview with a representative of a department of any of the institutions interested in your application. Depending on the outcome of the interviews you may receive a formal offer of employment. For practical reasons, you may be asked at the same time to undergo the medical examination which is required before any decision can be taken on appointment. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I should point out, however, that it could be several weeks or months before you are contacted." So now I ll be waiting for the offers. I dont know what I will do if I receive a really good offer. My salary in that post would decrease by about 800 EUR per month. Also, atm I would hate to leave Luxembourg and Len. But I will cross that bridge when I get there, that is, when I receive a really really good offer. I and my two roomies moved in into our new flat. Since my (very stylish) bed will be delivered in about 6 weeks, Len lent me a bed. MIne, however, will be just great, I ordered it from Mowo Lifestyle. See their (a bit useless homesite)  urlLink www.mowo.lu . I am doing some more furniture shopping this weekend, but the rest of my furniture will be in a very classical style. ON a bit of a nerves wreching note, my parents seem to have been fighting lately, so seems that they will get separated. Oh, well.  &nbsp; 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>