<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Nothing can heat up quite as much debate in religious circles as new medical breakthroughs—be they in the creation (cloning) or ending of life (abortion, euthanasia), or anywhere in between. So when Life published a special issue focusing on 21 breakthroughs in medical science for the 21st century, we knew we had to review these with a focus on how they would affect religious faith. All of these are now in existence under clinical trials which could be complete around the middle of the next century.   1. Memory drugs. Scientists have discovered a method for manipulating the gene responsible in part for long-term memory. They’ve been able to give fruit flies a photographic memory, and are hard at work on a drug for humans based on this discovery.   2. Attacking schizophrenia. E. Fuller Torrey has developed a ‘brain bank’ of more than 100 brains from schizophrenic and manic-depressives. Samples are being studied by groups around the world searching for the cause of the schizophrenia. Some are hunting for genetic clues, others for traces of a virus or a faulty neurotransmitter.    3. Edible vaccines. Researchers have developed a method for infusing potatoes with a vaccination for traveler’s diarrhea. The potatoes become living, low-cost vaccine factories, but because they contain no virulent agents they can’t cause an infection. This could become a low-cost way of delivering vaccines to the Third World.   4. Treating age-related blindness. Researchers have developed a new method for treating severe age-related macular degeneration (blindness in old age) by a two-step process involving a light-sensitive drug and very cool laser beams. This process is less dangerous than the previous one using ‘hot’ laser beams.   5. Blocking angiogenesis. Tumors are fueled by their ability to spark the construction of new blood vessels (angiogenesis). A new antiangiogenetic therapy halts this process, causing tumors to practically melt away. In a few years this could represent a cure for cancer, but it has further applications with more than 75 other diseases, including coronary artery disease, strokes, and AIDS.   6. The Smart Shirt. Scientists have developed a smart T-shirt with embedded sensors (like electrocardiograms to monitor the heart) which can transmit their signals to a satellite and thence to any location on Earth. These are useful for monitoring at home patients, police officers, athletes, or soldiers on a battlefield.   7. Herceptin therapy. Traditional cancer therapy is to throw as much poison into the body and hope it doesn’t kill good cells as well as bad ones. Herceptin is a ‘smart bomb’: it directly attacks the message system used to tell cancer cells to replicate wildly, and has few side effects. It’s been successful with some breast cancers.   8. Artificial retina. An implantable computer chip translates image information from a camera mounted on an eyeglass frame into electrical impulses which it passes through the retina to the brain. Early test patients have been able to detect motion and shapes. Others are working on a hybrid electronic-biological artificial retina.   9. Gene therapy. Scientists are using ‘suicide genes’ to attack glioblastoma, a fatal brain tumor. A modified leukemia virus (able to enter human cells but not cause the disease) carries a herpes simplex virus which produces cold sores. These infect the tumor, and are then killed using an antiviral drug. Since the virus infects only dividing cells, normal healthy brain cells aren’t affected. Genetic therapies are in development for more than 200 individual diseases, and are anticipated to be worth $3.5 billion in sales by 2005.   10. Eradicate polio. A global campaign led by the World Health Organization, UNICEF, Rotary International and the USCDC could eradicate polio in the next 4 years. The next target will be measles, which despite an effective vaccine kills 1 million annually.   11. Designer hormones. Tamoxifen was originally developed as a contraceptive, but failed (it actually almost guaranteed a woman would become pregnant). It’s estrogen-binding properties, however, have enabled scientists to revive it as a drug to ward off breast cancer. Other ‘designer hormones’ could prove useful against Alzheimer’s and hearing loss.   12. AIDS vaccine. There are seven different vaccines in process (AIDSVAX is the most advanced). The AIDS epidemic is taking a terrible toll on Africa and Asia, and the UN anticipates a large population decrease in those areas. More than 21 million Africans and 4 million Indians are infected—unless a cure is found, some whole countries could simply cease to exist.   13. Stem cells. One of the most controversial researches involves fetal brain stem cells, which can be used to grow virtually any organ or tissue without the problems of rejection. A US ban on fetal research limited the availability of cells for study; but a recent experiment has led to the ability to multiply fetal brain stem cells in a laboratory, leading to a potentially endless supply and avoiding the ethical problem that led to the ban.   14. Cancer vaccines. A new process is underway to develop vaccines that teach the body to cure its own cancers. New research is making it possible to develop more accurate vaccines. In some trials, patients have showed tumor regression of more than 50%.   15. Holograms. A computer can now be used to generate three-dimensional pictures of the brain: useful for precise measurement of tumors and anatomic relationships: important when neurosurgery cases can fail over a difference as small as a millimeter.   16. Aging. Researchers have discovered more than 20 genes implicated in longevity. They anticipate tremendous strides in the biochemistry of aging in the next five years, and a thorough understanding by the middle of the next century.   17. Stress management. The National Institutes of Health is funding a $30 million research study into stress management after finding that depression and isolation can kill cardiac patients and that stress-reduction techniques can lower blood pressure and heart rate.   18. Genetic screening. Some day you may be given a genetic ID card which knows everything about you—including what diseases you are susceptible to. This could eliminate privacy but could be useful in discovering and stopping genetic diseases: a miniscule blood sample could reveal the presence of a tumor in time to treat it.   19. Asthma drugs. New drugs are being designed to cure the faulty immune system of asthmatics. Applications for FDA approval are expected by AD 2000. Asthma afflicts as many as 15 million Americans—one third of them children.   20. Artificial heart. Surgical teams at US hospitals are preparing for a new trial: replacing failing hearts with battery-powered mechanical pumps made of plastic and titanium. (The first candidates are cows, but doctors hope to be conducting human trials by 2000).   21. Spinal cord repair. New drugs may soon win FDA approval and be used as the first treatment for spinal cord injury. These medicines are useful only in the regenerative phase of recovery, but will lead to new advances in getting the spinal cord to repair itself.   Most of these advances will be welcomed by religious faiths. Two lines of debate will likely open. The first, of course, is ‘who gets to take advantage of them?’ An artificial heart, for example, can cost about $125,000. Many of these will be beyond the reach of the average American, let alone someone in the Third World. Some, of course, won’t be critical—people in the Third World tend to take old-age blindness and heart failure with a grain of salt. But others—like vaccinations for AIDS or polio—are crucial. That’s why advances like potatoe-delivered vaccines are important. They lessen the cost of the overall treatment.   Other advances will be fraught with controversy. Many religious extremists will see sinister monitoring conspiracies in the ‘Smart Shirt,’ for example. Some will be opposed to technological implants like artificial hearts and eyes. And debates over the use of fetal stem cells and antiaging drugs will be vicious indeed.   Religion has an important place in these matters, though. Religious leaders can lend to the medical debate the argument of ethics; further, they must speak to the spiritual implications of these discoveries. For example, if mankind were to live on average to 150 years, what would it mean for our development as a civilization?  ___________________________  The discoveries listed were essayed in Life, October 1998. 

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The current church growth rate coupled with the rate of growth in discipleship and teaching centers suggests China will become a majority Christian nation—eventually.  As Christianity takes in a greater percentage of the population, the government will certainly lighten its restrictions. In fact, we may very well see officers in the government who are publicly Christians (right now, many of the Communist Party are secret believers). However, it's not likely that total religious freedom will be available before 2025—perhaps not before 2050. It’s doubtful that the majority of China’s residents will be Christians any time in the next century.  The likeliest obstacle holding up church growth isn’t government repression—it’s materialism. Economic growth is the principle goal of the country, and its achievement has already begun to have an impact on the church. Several Christian workers who labor on behalf of the Chinese church have reported cases of ecclesiastical crime and apathy toward the church due to greater interest in material gains. As economic gains filter down to more and more of China’s people, it’s probable that materialism will dampen church growth, just as it has in the West.  Christian activists need to begin working on discipleship and training programs that teach Chinese believers the proper role of money in their life, and how not to make an idol of it. This could be one of the greatest contributions Christians make to the culture of the world over the next century. More than a billion Chinese people attempting to live a life of Western consumerism could quickly strip the Earth of most of its natural resources; principles of self-discipline could keep this from happening.  

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink HoustonChronicle.com - Catholics advised not to marry Muslims . The Vatican releases a warning over the profound cultural and religious differences between the two faiths. The article doesn't mention the fact that often when a non-Muslim woman marries a Muslim man, she ends up converting. This is one of the factors in the growth of Islam around the world. 

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Muslims plan new mosque in Rochester Hills - 04/30/04 . The Detroit area is home to one of the largest Muslim populations in the United States. Recently a suburb of Detroit voted to allow Muslims to broadcast the Call to Prayer via amplified speakers so it can be heard over a wide area. Some Americans reacted out of fear, wanting to quash it, rather than faithfully reaching out with friendship and love. 

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink The Birmingham Post-Herald  has an article on the shallowness of American Christianity. It examines some of the things that happen when we view Christianity as a market that we belong to rather than citizenship in a Heavenly Kingdom whose rules we must hold up. 

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink People point to discipleship as top need, survey shows - (BP) . This is unsurprising given the evangelism techniques of the past generation. After WW2, most of the big names in evangelism looked to mass manufacturing for evangelism models. Thus we had mass crusades, mass door-to-door campaigns, mass broadcasting, mass radio. These systems focused mostly on getting converts, but less on followup and discipleship. The result: in 2000, 235 million people said they were Christians but only 191 million were part of a church. That leaves 34 million, at least, as "nominal" believers who confess Christ with their mouth but fail to be part of a body of believers. Now there is a new trend toward personal discipleship, in answer to this problem. Optimally I think the future should combine relational evangelism with relational discipleship; but many people would probably rather leave evangelism to "professionals" and absolve themselves of personal responsibility. 

						
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Religion News Service  has a new article detailing the construction of a temple to Shiva in Atlanta, Ga. Hindus in America number about 1 million but are growing twice as fast as the population as a whole--faster than Christians, Muslims or Jews, and the 2nd fastest growing religion in America with more than 1 million adherents (top religion is Buddhism, with 2.5 million members and an annual growth rate of 3.2%). 

						
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For decades, religious leaders, particularly Christians, have been targeted by terrorist groups for persecution, harassment, and even assassination. Now, terrorism against religious groups has entered the electronic world. ‘Two unidentified women set up Internet accounts that were used in a three-day automated attack [in early September] on religious Usenet newsgroups. The attackers used familiar newsgroup member names in sending thousands of off-subject, often vulgar, posts to a number of alt.religion groups on the Internet.’ (Wired News, 18 September 1998).  Many of the messages came with forged identities purporting to be from regular posters to the group. Reviewing the alt.religion.christianity newsgroup at the time, one could see several messages with the headers, ‘Stop using my name!’ With more than 10,000 forged messages flooding the group, the problem eventually became so rampant that posters began digitally ‘signing’ their messages using encryption software in order to verify their identity.  A similar sort of cyberterrorism was exemplified by an attack on the web site edition of the New York Times, when hackers replaced the front page of the Times with a hacked version. Security experts suggest a more subtle hack—the alteration of a few smaller pieces of less-public pages on the Times’ web site—would have been virtually undetectable and could have done a significant amount of damage.  This illustrates just how deadly electronic forgeries can be. Messages supposedly from Bill Gates abound on the Internet, promising free vacations if people pass the message on so an e-mail tracking program can be tested. Most people know these messages to be fakes, and would probably be suspicious of an e-mail message supposedly from Billy Graham or the Pope. On the other hand, an e-mail message forged from a local pastor carrying a solicitation for drugs or pornography could do horrific damage to one’s reputation.  In fact, by 2004, an updated version of this kind of attack became widespread. New computer viruses were forging the "From" addresses, making themselves appear to be messages from authentic religious websites (as well as many other large websites).   Today, the only ones to be immediately affected by this would be individuals in the West, where such technology is most prevalent. However, as the technology becomes more useful in northern Africa and Asia, elements hostile to Christianity may very well adapt such a technique in order to drum up false charges against Christian leaders or to sully their reputation. Religious conferences being held in the East were beginning to feel the problem this year.  How to avoid such a future? Individuals regularly corresponding by e-mail could begin ‘signing’ their name using electronic signatures such as those offered by PGP Encryption or through Microsoft Outlook. News sites can similarly use digital ‘wrappers’ to sign and secure their web stories. The only other real route is to maintain a life of integrity and to quickly respond to any forgeries with evidence—which is exactly what participants in the alt.religion.christianity forum did.  

						
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   http://www.churchcentral.com/nw/s/template/Article.html/id/19253 has an article about youth churches: "According to the New York Times News Service this new 'alt-evangelism' attracts a young generation seeking an authentic, intimate and personal religious experience, different from their 'media-intensified lives.'". For a reader of the 4th Turning (www.fourthturning.com) generational cycles in America, this is unsurprising and has been developing for some time. Religion for nomads (30s/40s) and young heroes (20s, teens) is likely to be driven more toward spirituality, inner experiences, community, and ritual than to large corporation-style churches. 

						
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Religion - faith, or belief in God or gods - is a key part of the life of most of the people on our planet. My interest in the future of faith on our world has been a long time developing. As an Associate Editor of the World Christian Encyclopedia, I was part of a project to develop a world-scale picture of religious beliefs on our planet. I have also written many other articles on this subject. This blog is the beginnings of a semi-regular posting on the topic. 

						
</post>


<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Translated version of http://www.rasscass.com/templ/te_bio.php?PID=26&RID=1  - Who is Karl Albrecht, the 5th richest person in the world? The two retailers (Karl & Theo) developed one of the largest trading ventures of Europe from a food shop in the Essener suburb. Theo and Karl Albrecht generated the phenomenon with uniform, cheap and nevertheless qualitatively substantial goods offered and their undemandingly equipped branches?Aldi?, under its convinced clientele in the meantime also representatives of middle and income-strong social classes are...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink News   Paul Allen, the co-founder of Microsoft, became the first person in 2003 to own three private yachts measuring more than 200ft. His flagship is the 413ft Octopus, which is swathed in secrecy and is thought to have cost £113m. But Mr Allen is facing stiff opposition as admiral of the fleet from another computing tycoon.  Oracle's chief executive, Larry Ellison, has commissioned a 460ft vessel - also his third yacht. The whisper is that it will be called Rising Sun and will be launched by the end of 2004.  Analysts say the yachts are part of a revolution in the industry in recent years. There are more and more luxury yachts, growing ever bigger and increasingly sumptuous. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink mcall.com - Paul Allen charting new course : "Billionaire Paul Allen's appearance at the annual cable-industry convention this month had tongues wagging. And not just because the reclusive mogul arrived aboard the world's largest privately owned yacht, a 413-foot stunner that Allen docked on the Mississippi River."  ... Touring cable executives said the 8-month-old vessel cost Allen $200 million and had a permanent crew of 60 people, including several former Navy Seals. It has two helicopters, seven boats and a remote-controlled vehicle for crawling on the ocean floor. An accompanying submarine, under construction, will have the capacity to sleep eight people for up to two weeks underwater.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink AP Wire | 04/30/2004 | Warren Buffett Living Humbly in Nebraska  - The world's second richest man lives humbly in the Midwest city where he grew up, driving his own car, paying $12 for a haircut and stopping by his local drug store for newspapers. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Bill Gates' Web Site - Speech Transcript: Microsoft CEO Summit 2004 . Bill spoke to over 100 top international business leaders about how technology advances emerging today can help organizations use IT to drive business value through improved productivity and optimized business processes to take advantage of emerging digital technology. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>