<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      since my last entry, i was studying the script again..  AT LAST, I FOUND THE PART TO CHANGE!! with the new changes, it will no longer jump to the end of the page with every command of the console(YESH!!) haha..
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last nite slp late... morning woke late... got to run to meet the ppl for CIP... tired like hell.. FINALLY!!, CIP over liao, can go home lor:) got home only to find out got to go EXPO for meal.. ARGH... TIRED!!.. nobody cares.. i still had to go... go there, crowded like hell, food tasted like hell... sumore is all can be found and Causeway Point de... just that it is cheaper and tasted worse... was DaMn BoReD.. then rem that SK is there too.. sms chat lor.. haha... she saw me very soon, but i like took 1 min to spot her.. haha.. but today is a wasted day lor.. sianz..  Blog(update): still changing;p
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read Slowly...   Have you ever wondered which hurts the most?  Saying something and wishing you hadn't?  or Saying nothing and wishing you had?   I guess the most important things are the hardest things to say.   Don't be afraid to tell someone you love them. If you do, they might  break your heart...if you don't, you might break theirs.   Have u ever decided not to become a couple because you were so afraid of losing what you already had with that person?   Your heart decides whom it likes and whom it doesn't.   You can't tell your heart what to do.   It does it on its own.... when you least suspect it, or even when you  don't want it to.   Have you ever wanted to love someone with everything you had, but that other perso n was too afraid to let you?   Too many of us stay walled up because we are too afraid to care too much...for fear that the other person does not care as much, or even at all.   Have you ever denied your feelings for someone because your fear of rejection was too hard to handle?   We tell lies when we are afraid...   afraid of what we don't know,   afraid of what others will think,  afraid of what will be found out about us.   But every time we tell a lie, the thing we fear grows stronger.   Life is all about risks and it requires you to jump.   Don't be a person who has to look back and wonder what they would have done, or could have had.   *What would you do if every time you fell in love you had to say   good-bye?   *What would you do if every time you wanted someone they would never be there?   *What would you do if your best friend died tomorrow and you  never got to tell them how you felt?    (even if it is that you don't care anymore)   *What would you do if you loved someone  more than ever and you couldn't have them?   *What would you do if you never got the chance to say I am friends with all of my family and they know I love them?  People live, but people die.  And I want to tell you DO NOT make any decisions that you will regret about...
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      say play pool then when reach there, ended up chatting.. ok lah.. quite fun oso.. got to c sum stars.. BeEn a long time since i actually sat down to c stars.. tok lots with lele and SK and XIGua.. played true or dare:s(for slightly more details, read lele's blog :s)   got to know them better.. some SECRETs not to be shared with others.. haha..  that's bt it i guess..  OH YA!! i got 30buck voucher for kinokuniya... but no use.. sianz.. gif DaJie.. haha..
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today boring sia... Morning nv go MC test, go back secondary school to take prize.. 2 only.. sianz..  then later say go play.. then play play until not much to play.. go all the way to Bukit Timah, play 2 rounds and go home liao... ARGH!  reach home liao, then got ppl sms say wanna play.. sianz.. me home liao.. but okay lah.. can play can liao.. haha. ;p
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my blog will be done soon..:)
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blog like very popular nowadays huh? hehe.. me also cum and get a leg in it.. haha... Let's see how i fair ;p
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now is 4.45am of 29/06/2004...  i got woke up by the heat wave that can't seem to leave me alone to sleep.. very tired.. slept at 11am+ and has been sleeping in intervals of 2hours?  now can't take it liao.. drinking iced water.. a jug of it.. double iced.. ice in both glass and jug.. haha.. tired.. :s
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is the world so crude...  Today i had my Chi tests.. didn't study but think can reach my aim of 50/100 + - 2 ba.. the world so crude to me.. don't let me get accurate every time..  Then i go teach my friends Maths... then teach until very good.. why are they not blessed with the talent i have?? WHY??!! why the world so crude to them??!!  Then, becoz i very good, my friends called me Maths God... why so crude?? why can't they let me off.. it's such an insult to me.. comparing me to Maths God.. the Maths Gods will probably think they are very talented in Maths if they heard about it.. why so crude to me.. i help you, still insult me.. then also make the Maths Gods happy for something that they are not.. they will crippled if they know they suck lor..  why so crude.. WHy?!!!  (An attempt to write in the 'pattern' of Yun Song.. HAHA..)    In my 'pattern' :  Today went for test.. then study.. then bball.. then home.. tml is maths test.. 
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      past week has not really been studying well.. today really studied.. think bt 5-7 hours? haha..  got me, kelvin, meiying and clarresa.. at Woodlands Mart's Mcdonald..  studied maths and a few page of chemistry(2-3?) haha..  mostly maths.. APGP.. abit inequalities.. and stuff..  then after that went to tiong bahru with kelvin to do something.. then home sweet home.. haha.. quite sian today.. but stuff done.. haha..
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Msg with no error:  According to a research at an English university, it doesn't mater in what order the letters in a word are, the only important thing is that first and last letter is at the right place. The rest can be a total mess and you can still read it without problem. This is because we do not read every letter by itself but the word as a whole.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aoccdrnig to a rscheearch at an Elingsh uinervtisy, it deosn't mttaer in waht oredr the ltteers in a wrod are, the olny iprmoetnt tihng is taht frist and lsat ltteer is at the rghit pclae. The rset can be a toatl mses and you can sitll raed it wouthit porbelm. Tihs is bcuseae we do not raed ervey lteter by itslef but the wrod as a wlohe.
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      since i got back from chalet, i've been slacking.. trying hard to do my work, but didn't do much.. haha.. practically nothing? haha..  hmm... just to let you all know if you guys thinking of catching a movie.. The Chronicles of Riddick and Best Bet not nice de.. of the two, the first is better.. if you really desperate for movie, then watch the first.. the second, dun.. if not you see until, cant find kenny, you may find find the second movie a suffering experience...  ha..
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm.. got lots of fun.. especially the second day.. first day a little sian.. haha.. hmm.. did lots of stuff.. played lots of stuff.. eat not a lot of stuff.. always looking for food :s haha..  paiseh ar.. i kinda lazy to write... but, thanks to a friend who was not lazy, you can get the details from his site.. wahaha.. just go yuh shin's blog to find out ;p haha.. paiseh ar..  BTW, the footprints is mingzong take one right? not keen hong? or izzit i kanna gui block eye??? c wrongly :s can someone tell me :s
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just an email i got.. some thoughts for you guys.. since many of you are falling into it..  For all you people who say, "I love you" when you have no clue what love is exactly!!!  Something to ponder upon...   Are your palms sweaty, is your heart racing and is your voice caught within your chest??  -It isn't love, it's LIKE.   You can't keep your eyes or hands off of her/him  -It isn't love, it's LUST.   Are you proud, and eager to show her/him off??  -It isn't love, it's LUCK.   Do you want her because you know she's/he's there??  -It isn't love, it's LONELINESS.   Are you with her/him because it's what everyone wants??  -It isn't love, it's LOYALTY.   Are you with her because she/he kissed you, or held your hand?  -It isn't love, it's LOW CONFIDENCE.   Do you stay for her/him confessions of love, because you don't want to hurt her/him?  -It isn't love, it's PITY.   Do you belong to her/him because the sight of her/him makes your heart skip a beat??  -It isn't love, it's INFATUATION.   Do you pardon her faults because you care about her/him?  -It isn't love, it's FRIENDSHIP.   Do you tell her/him every day she is the only one you think of?  -It isn't love, it's a LIE.   Are you willing to give up all of your favorite things for her sake? -It isn't love, it's CHARITY.   =================================================  Does your heart ache and break when she's sad?  -Then it's LOVE.   Do you cry for her/his pain, even when she's/he's strong?  -Then it's LOVE.   Do her/his eyes see your true heart, and touch your soul so deeply it hurts? -Then it's LOVE.   Do you stay because a blinding, incomprehensible mix of pain and relation pulls you close and holds you to her/him?  -Then it's LOVE.   Do you accept her/his faults because it's a part of who she/he is?  -Then it's LOVE.   Are you attracted to others, but stay with her/him faithfully without regret??  -Then it's LOVE.   Would you give her/him your heart, your life, your death??  -Then it's LOVE.   Now, if love is painful, and tortures us so, why do we love? Why is it all we search for in life?  This pain, this agony?  Why is it all we long for?  This torture, this powerful death of self?  Why?  The answer is so simple cause it's...LOVE.  It is such an addictive thing that even people who are not having it wish to experience it and share it with others as well.
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... just got back from the NaCLi camp , a.k.a SC camp, yesterday.. wanted to meet sam for bball.. but got to go home.. got home liao, realize i was very tired... so sleep early..  today actually planned to stay in bed the whole day de.. long time since i did that.. BUT!, my parent's room accidentally got locked up and coincidentally, both my parents' keys are in the room...  Here's where SPIDERMAN comes to save the day.. haha.. i had to climb from the window of one toilet, to the toilet of my parents' room...  (first, screw out the grills, then remove the glass panels, climb out, climb over to the other toilet on the 'roof', remove the glass panels of the other toilet, screw out the other grill and climb in to open the door from inside.) but, the screws of the grill in my parent's room's toilet were stuck and couldn't be unscrewed... HoW WaS I SuPpOsEd To EnTeR If ThE WinDoW Is GrIlLeD??!!!   so in the end, i had to 'fish' my mum's handbag with a pole while sitting on the 'aircon-generator?'... imagine the force i had to apply at 20cm from the pivot to produce a moment strong enough to lift my mum's handbag of weight about 3N at a distance of about 3m!  let the weight be 3N. 3N X 3m = ?N X 0.2m ? = 45N (about the weight of a thin person?)  haiz.. anyway, it was kinda fun lor.. since i like climbing around.. like rock-climbing.. haha.. so it was tiring and fun.. haha...  IN THE END: I got the keys from my mum's handbag as it was hung on the other side of the grill for my mum and th door is OPEN!!  My dad immediately took the keys and made a copy to be placed in 3 rooms.. haha.. over-cautious sia..
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Be careful of your thoughts, For your thoughts would become your words.  Be careful of your words, For your words would become your actions.  Be careful of your actions, For your actions would become your habits.  Be careful of your habits, For your habits would become your character.  Be careful of your character, For your character would become your destiny.                                           AuthorUnknown
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Moods of a Woman    An angel of truth and a dream of fiction, A woman is a bundle of contradiction, She's afraid of a wasp, will scream at a mouse, But will tackle a stranger alone in the house. Sour as vinegar, sweet as a rose, She'll kiss you one minute, then turn up her nose, She'll win you in rage, enchant you in silk, She'll be stronger than brandy, milder than milk, At times she'll be vengeful, merry and sad, She'll hate you like poison, and love you like mad.     The Moods of a Man    Hungry. Horny. Sleepy. 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke late.. missed the wedding.. sianz...  but went for the dinner.. haha.. food tasted good..;p wanna know what i had? dun say... haha...   hmm... then back here (Genting) for the night.. tml dad gotta meet some developer then can go home... like the climate here at genting.. but it ain't the same without friends lor.. haha... AWWW... haha...   hmm... by tue should be home if nothing goes wrong...
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was wasted.. sleep, eat and play was all i did.. and the things i played SUCKS...   i wanted to give the arcade a chance.. but all the game was old and the machines are spoilt..   then it was pool.. all full or in the worse condition u can find..   done nothing worthwhile today...sianz...   P.S: i am still at Genting now cause dad want to gamble more... :s 
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm.. set off at bout 3+.. reach Genting just.. slept the whole way here.. haha... no choice.. cause i get car sick easily.. :s  sian.. reach here liao, was very happy.. but all spoilt by an argument about a rude waitress..  In my dad's view, the waitress was damn rude and the manager got involved..  In my view, she was just doing her job.. just a little.. rude.. but not that bad that the manager has to be involved..   Anyway, i just find it very selfish/stingy/self-centred to actually make things hard for others just becoz you dun feel good about sth and want to make youself feel good, by making others feel bad, EG: get the waitress into trouble?  i just find it selfish.. i hate it..
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm.. you may notice that this is the only entry i have in the morning.. well, i wrote this in the morning today at the school lib.. cause i just rem i have yet to tell most of you guys/gals that i will be going to malaysia for my cousin's WEDDING!!  haha.. go there got good food and can have fun.. but kinda :( cause you guys cant have fun with me.. haha.. going half-hearted... prefer to stay, cause if go, i gonna miss 2 SC meeting and cant play with you guys/gals... but i also wanna go lah.. cause long long loonng~~ time never see them liao.. (bt half a year??)..   so that's about it.. just to let ya guys/gals know i will not be in SG from today afternoon till monday night i think.. bye bye.. haha..
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today, i went to sch for physics lecture... luckily aidi never come.. saved from the dare for now.. haha.. then play bball at sch.. .. .. then go lot1 walk walk.. then they go watch harry potter.. me nothing to do liao...  so i took my time to scroll back to sch.. BUT sth catch my attention..i ended up playing 1hr+ of bball at CCK community centre there.. was as lousy as before in shooting.. sianzzzzzz... but my lay-up still quite fun to me.. haha..  go back sch for the MEETING! i was made the editor;p i got ppl under me sia.. haha.. but actually not much diff.. still got to work.. just that i compile and edit what the photographer, journalist and creative designers give me...  after that, i went to play pool with sam.. SAM!! i said i gonna write this, so here it is!! I WON SAM IN A MATCH OF 1-HAND POOL!!!! haha... but i kinda lost the rest off the matches.. except one that he suicided.. haha...  Had fun today.. :) the meeting bonded me closer to them.. i believe i gonna start liking SC liao.. quiting SC will not be in my mind liao:)
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was a bored day.. woke at bt 6am despite slping late.. but nothing do.. went back to slp.. can't slp.. toss and turn till 11+ then got off my bed..   been a long long loonng time since i meet FeiFEI!! haha.. meet up with some old friends and went orchard jalan jalan.. nothing to do.. ended up at arcade of cineleisure.. one word: sucks.. not nice to play de.. but had fun playing soccer, the one you control with a joystick and kick with your leg.. haha.. damn fun..  den..den.. we ate dinner and walked to Plaza Singapura to play arcade again.. haha.. then go home.. alone.. sian.. they all go bugis that way, while i go woodlands this way.. sianz.. alone.. hp spoilt sumore.. can't chat with anyone.. luckily i got bring Discman, so i enjoyed the Daniel Bedingfield CD on my way home;p  sianz.. bt my hp.. i left home and got on the train.. on the train, as i was smsing, my hp HANGED!!! dunno y.. so i switched off my hp(illegally) and on it again.. eRoRr.. tried again.. same.. can't use liao.. SIAN!!! haiz..  what to do? no hp liao.. gonna miz all the sms chats... 
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i was at the Physic Enrichment Camp yesterday and today.. hoping that it would be fun.. but.. SIANZ!!! all lectures.. no interaction de.. slp through almost all of it.. sianz..  today, i left halfway, at bt 2 to go sch for PW.. at least not so sianz.. more enriching sumore.. haha.. anyway, today i cut my hair.. looked quite nice.. but when i got home and bathe liao, realized that one side longer than the other side..HELP!!! sianzz... cut hair hoping no need comb hair.. but with the hair like that, can only comb one way(muz comb..) sianz..
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i  realized  sth today.. suddenly..  i come online everyday to look through the blogs.. once or even twice a day.. hoping to see new entries each time.. but each time, i see no new entries.. then i suddenly sub-conciously looked at it in another prospective.. i was thinking :" could the others be doing the same and that i, not writing entries disappoint them?" lol.. sudden tot made me make a decision!!!!  I decided to write at least 1 entry every 2 days.. if can, once a DAY!! :)  Hope those who rarely write entries, like me, and checks other's blogs for entries daily, like me, can see in the  PrOsPeCtIvE  i looked in,  AnD~~~ WRITE MoRe ENtRiEs!!!!  haha.. that's bt it on my  Realization ..   ha...
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm.. past few days not really in good mood.. though anyone knows.. &nbsp; couple of reasons :  &nbsp; 1. schoolwork.. things are piling up real bad and i can't seem to do anything about it.. &nbsp; 2. was sick since last wed.. starting cold then ... then migraine...&nbsp;mind kinda hay-wired.. then last night a little fever sumore.. &nbsp; 3. something cropped up that spoilt my mood.. not gonna say.. only few people know.. haha.. wanna know? dun say.. haha.. but what i can say is that i kinda sort it out.. so it won't be much of a prob now lor.. &nbsp; -This is for people who noticed that i seemed tired.. sth bt myself.. i tend to look tired when i am in a bad mood.. cause when bad mood, i play lots of bball (actually good bad mood also play de lor.. but when bad mood more) + i think a lot.. think lot, mental stress, so will tired lor.. haha.. but  i'm still the same me lar .. so never lor.. haha.. 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      READ  Message: Lady : Why do you like me..? Why do you  love  me?&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; Man : I can't tell the reason.. but I really  like you..&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;  Lady : You can't even tell me the reason... how  can you say you like me? How can you say you  love me?&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;  Man : I really don't know the reason, but I  can prove that I love you.   Lady : Proof? No! I want you to tell me the  reason. My friend's boyfriend can tell her why  he loves her but not you!&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; Man : Ok..ok!!! Erm... because you are  beautiful,&nbsp;   because your voice is sweet,&nbsp;  because you are caring,&nbsp;  because you are loving,&nbsp;  because you are thoughtful,&nbsp;  because of your smile,  because of your every movements.&nbsp;&nbsp;  The lady felt very satisfied with the man’s  answer. Unfortunately, a few days later, the  Lady met with an accident and became comma.  The Guy then placed a letter by her side, and  here is the content:&nbsp;&nbsp;  Darling,&nbsp;&nbsp;  Because of your sweet voice that I love you...&nbsp;  Now can you talk? No! Therefore I cannot love  you.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; Because of your care and concern that I like  you..&nbsp;  Now that you cannot show them, therefore I  cannot love you.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; Because of your smile,&nbsp;  because of your every movements that I love you..&nbsp;  Now can you smile? Now can you move?&nbsp;  No, therefore I cannot love you...&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; If love needs a reason, like now, there is no  reason for me to love you anymore.&nbsp;   Do love need a reason? NO!&nbsp;   Therefore, I still love you...&nbsp;   And love doesn't need a reason&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;  Sometimes the best and the most beautiful  things in the world  cannot be seen, cannot be touched, but can be  felt in the heart      
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today, go sch, then SC meeting then go watch show..  nothing real interesting.. bt the first 2.. the show was great.. The Woman In Black..  interesting cast, interesting setting, interesting storyline with nice sound and light effects.  hmm.. had plans for secret activities.. but wasn't very fruitful :s sianz.. how?how?how?  my secret training's result is unknown :s :(  HaHa..
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like what yuh shin has said... nobodies blogging nowadays... i gonna delete my blog liao... haha... kidding... instead, i will keep it.. just to type what i wanna type every now and then.. hmm.. but now that yuh shin deleted his blog, it's really bored liao lor.. no thing to read le...  hmm.. exams results... not that bad.. kinda expected.. could have been better had i put in more effort... or should i say put in effort.. haha.. as usual, language prob lor.. sianz... haha...  hmm.. what else... played bball more often now =p hehe.. gdgd lor.. me shooting better a bit.. tiny bit.. then realise many many mistakes i have.. pointed by sam.. thx! i will work on it.. really!! haha... EG: passing, shooting, lay-up, blablabla..  then... got secret activity.. improving with the help of a secret person.. those who know what it is, good... those who dun, you will know someday..   then..then..then... got lots of work to do.. to catch up.. wanna do, but always no mood to do.. sianz.. SC got work cuming in liao.. pw.. blablabla.. only thing that i have mood to do is Accounting stuff :s cause it is more interesting.. sianz.. dunno how to get my work done..  think that's bt it ba.. long long time, one long long blog... haha..
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i removed some extra stuff like the BlogUpdates and Jokes.. then i updated quite some stuff..  err.. feel free to give me some suggestions or comments or views or thoughts or ... you get the idea lor.. 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm.. exams has been over since fri morning.. HAPPY! and sad.. cause dun think will do well.. especially fm.. sianz.. chinese and eng, no aim so dun have to think.. haha..  hmm.. had a game of bball after exams.. then go watch WindStruck.. Nice nIce niCe nicE show.. haha.. funny with romance... just the kind of show i like.. haha.. then.. then.. go home, change and go to night class at FTC.. for those who have no idea what it is/ no i dea i got night class, now you know! It is an accounting night class i am taking at FTC, financial training centre.. Dun ask me why i took up the course.. i would say, i was a decision i made a little implusively.. :x   i would rather guitar lessons.. but anyway, what's done has to be finished.. i would get my CAT by either end of next year or mid 2006.. then, i will get BSc of Applied Accounting (Hon) in bt 1 to 1.5 years time.. sounds good? well, that will keep me studying hard for Accountancy ;p  anyway, after lessons, i went to yuh shin house.. played fatal frame... ... then kinda bored... sleep late next morning.. met friend.. suppose to help him with Amaths but got back late.. SORRY!!~~... haha.. in the end, i just meet him to pass him his time table..  then got back home.. Sleep slEep sleeP until bt 1am.. woke up.. watch tv, eat, slack.. till now.. bt 4am+.. check email and now blogging lor..  quite long liao.. think gonna end here.. wanna sleep again le.. at least i nv eat and sleep, eat and sleep... i still go exercise my fingers.. haha.. okok.. i will upload kenny face to save you all the trouble... haha.. lame~ :s haha...
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, after a session of Interesting DISC assembly, and a Long Tiring day in school, i had a Fun game of bball which caused the Painful injury of my thumb...   DISC... for those who dunno my personality and wanna know it, i am a S/C... in the first 3 mths was C/S... but almost the same lor.. CS or SC... just a little difference in priority.. In fact, i decided this change.. sound unreal.. but it is so..   I used to be one who would always be there to prove that i am right, making many conflicts and stuff like that... i realized that such arguments are redundant.. so i made the decision to give in more often.. which probably lead to this change..  Then the long day nothing much lor..   Now, the game!! hehe.. I think i have improved.. dunno how dunno why... but today was like WooHoo!!! haha.. but that's what i think only.. dunno what others think.. Overall, i had a great game lor.. =P though we lost, i still happy =) er.. anyway, paiseh wor.. if i did not fooled ard at the end.. we would surely have won.. sorry ar :s  hmm.. Painful thumb.. thx to _______ lor.. use ball hit until my thumb.. inner bleeding.. pain sian.. now thumb cannot press stuff normally.. sianz...  Then end of day, go home, i read comic read until like in the comic like that... i missed my stop.. had to get off, cross the platform, take train back.. sianz.. but funny..   ha...
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i had my meet the parent session.. all was well.. until the end.. i thought my mum would be understanding about my dozing off very rarely and understand my GP failure.. but..  she threaten to stop my Accounting lessons if by end of the year i dun get a pass in my GP... :(    ARGH!!! HOW?! HOW CAN SHE DO THAT TO ME??!!!   so anyway, i got to work hard liao.. can't doze off in class nor dun hand in work.. if she know, she gonna.. *you know what* ...   sianz..  Guess can't go ard playing all day liao.. haha.. at least she never complain my hair.. no need cut..   ha..
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today, i wok3 lat3.. very lat3.. at about.. 2+?  k3lvin and sam want3d to m33t m3 to study.. but stiff n3ck.. dun f33l like going out.. now still stiff n3ck.. wors3..   PJ P3OPL3!! If Lucky, Monday You All Still Can S33 M3 Stiff N3ck!!  haha..  the wors3 thing is, i did no work.. slack3d the whole day lying ard to l3t my n3ck b3 in a comfortabl3 position... play com..  watch NARUTO ;p   anyway, tml sure di3 liao lor.. work not done.. :x  ha...
    
</post>


</Blog>