<Blog>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Shoppers flock to Midway Wal-Mart opening   Walmart!!!  Cheap products that I need.  As a joke I had overheard, went something like this, "Where else can you go in to buy some laundry detergant and toilet paper and come out with motor oil and a shotgun?"  Awesome.  **** 8 more days until "Riverfest 2004" (aka X-Fest).
      
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Wolves win 83-80 thriller to set up date with Lakers   They did it!!!  Won Game 7 to go on to the to Conference Finals.    It's been a good time for drinking, although, my diet has failed.  I am determined to lose some weight before July, which is the 1st of 7 weddings I have to attend this summer.  The 1st one, my childhood sweeheart, is marrying an airforce pilot.  I'll never forget the times when we would play "glow-in-the-dark" sticks in my basement.  I love you, Emily.
      
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My sleeping bag is getting aired out (someone borrowed it lately), my tent is ready to go, my cooler needs ice, and my lantern is at my friend's house.  I have to remember my swiss army knife (for creating marshmellow sticks) and my lockpad (to lock up my tent when I go look for Limabean).  I did a lot of off-season drinking (training), I am ready for the 3 days of continuous beer guzzing.   RE:  Riverfest 2004 (old 93x X-fest) View Pete's website for much more info on one of the best weekends of the year.
      
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What the crap is up with Sunday afternoons?  There are no good shows on, going to the bar is almost depressing, and Monday is only a few hours away.
      
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Very entertaining site.  Mostly about drinking and concerts that deal with drinking.  urlLink giencke.net :: View topic - Official 2004 Riverfest (was 93X X-Fest) @ Somerset Thread 
      
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, this is a start.  Not sure what to write, so for now I'll just say, "Here we go!!!"
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Can't think of anything to write right now, so i decided to just paste a scene from one of the best Seinfeld episodes of all time. ------------------------------------------------------------  George: The sea was angry that day my friends, like an old man trying to return soap at a deli!  (Jerry gives Kramer a "what the h-" glance)  George: I got about fifty-feet out and then suddenly the great beast appeared before me. I tell ya he was ten stories high if he was a foot. As if sensing my presence he gave out a big bellow. I said, "Easy big fella!" And then as I watched him struggling I reliezed something was obstructing his breathing. From where I was standing I could see directly into the eye of the great fish!  Jerry: Mammal.  George: Whatever.  Kramer: Well, what did you do next?  George: Then from out of nowhere a huge title wave lifted, tossed like a quark and I found myself on top of him face to face with the blow-hole. I could barely see from all of the waves crashing down on top of me but I knew something was there so I reached my hand and pulled out the obstruction!  (George pulls out of the inside pocket a golfball)  (Jerry and George just stare at Kramer)  Kramer: What is that a Titleist? A hole in one eh.  Jerry: Well the crowd most have gone wild!  George: Oh yes they did Jerry they were all over me. It was like Rocky 1.  Diane came up to me, threw her arms around me, and kissed me. We both had tears streaming down our faces. I never saw anyone so beautiful. It was at that moment I decided to tell her I was not a marine biologist!  Jerry: Wow! What'd she say?  George: She told me to "Go to hell!" and I took the bus home.
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dirty's birthday...that is the night, and what happens is incredible and unpredictable.  Contents include "Dynamite Hack"....awesome song, Texas Holdem Poker, Drinking lots of Coors Light, Guiness, Miller Light, and Bud Light.  Billy's On Grand includes "Woodbury's Class of 99" 5 year reunion, in which, I, pretend to be a fellow student of this class.  The most asked question for me is, who are you?  I don't remember you...and are you sure you are from Woodbury?  Of course, I couldn't lie for long.  As usual, I am a magnet towards girls of all ages, as a result, I obtain a relationship with a '99 graduate of Woodbury High School.  What was funny, is that Denise and I pretended to be dating, and she was introducing me to her fellow classmates.  Its odd, and awesome, that her best friend has a boyfriend (or husband or fiancee) that has the same name as me.  How cool is that?  So, before leaving the bar, I attend to my ultimate goal....get her number...which does happen.  But, not as easy as said, I have to borrow Dirty's cell phone to insert the number.  What is really bad, is that I don't know how to save the number in his phone.  Therefore, luckily, and coincidently, my girl, Dinese, has the same exact phone.  Final result equals she put the phone number in his phone for me, and she saved it.  Tomorrow is the ultimate determiner of what the conclusion is.  Was this a true phone number???  Was this her phone number???  Will we ever see each other again???  Of course, as there is no answer yet, I will wait patiently, and realistically, as most drunk girls you met, while you are drunk, are not a sure thing.  But, if all is good, how awesome is that.....And, as time passes by, on Dirty's birthday, I feel good.
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And it is now Friday night......so what does a single guy of almost 25 to do???  If you guessed get drunk at the bars and stare at girls...you're wrong.  I decided that a wild night in front of the movie set was the perfect option.  In retrospect, it wasn't that bad of a night.  I didn't drink, (didn't get more fat), I didn't inhale any smoke from the bars (save my self from second hand smoke cancer), and I didn't fall flat on my face after drinking myself silly (save my self from embarrassment).  "Identity," the movie I started to watch after my Seinfeld watching, was starting to get a little too spooky.  It wouldn't have been too bad if someone else was here, but -man alive- my heart jumping out of my chest, it was soo suspenseful.  I usually like suspense or horror movies, but it gets a little too much whenever I watch them alone on my living room floor in the dark.  Yea, I don't have a couch yet, so I lay on my air mattress whenever I want to lie down while watching tv.  "Dipity Due Dah, Dipity Day, my oh my, what a wonderful day."  I like that song, it’s from my old record set from when I was a kid.  It is sung by Donald Duck and Friends,,,,,,they Rock!!!  As for work....I guess today wasn't that bad.  My emails were very slim today, which meant less problems to conquer, and more time for me to associate with my fellow co-workers and associates.  That's all folks..... 
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And then there was....  I finally bought a new tv.  The old one died about 5 weeks ago, and I've been living off a 13 incher since then.  I decided with a 27" Flat Screen, which offers plenty of quality viewing angles and capabilities.  I decided against the HDTV large screen until I move into a new place in September, I thought I would decrease any extra moving I would have had to do with the large tv.  In addition, I signed up for Time Warner's digital cable service with DVR service.  DVR is like TIVO, therefore, I'm able to record up to 40 hours of tv programs and watch them later.  Yeppie!!!  Now on to last night.... I guess Shaggy decided we should drink since he retained his scholarship for Law School for another year.  I decided I should celebrate me buying my new TV, and Dirty was celebrating his first day of work at Best Buy.  It was the perfect reasoning and a celebration was an excellent idea for a Tuesday night.  We drank for awhile, then we got hungry.  So, we headed off towards McDonalds, Burger King, and Taco Bell.  Half way there we made a pit stop, did something very sneaky to a friend of ours, caused us to be very happy as our proud minds pulled off a stunt so mystifying.  Ahhh, fun-ness.  We arrived at the destination (food), and realized that only the drive-thru was open.  However, as our bodies were not in a vehicle, we were denied the right of passage to cheap food.  As a last resort, we skipped over to Rainbow and took avail to many many options.  The final result... (3 cartons of snack packs, 2 packs of pop tarts, 2 Tombstone pizzas, and 1 box of Scooby Doo cereal).  We continued on home, we cooked the pizzas, Smallz made the trip over to hang with us for awhile, Dirty passed out in the bunk bed, I passed out on the floor, Smallz went home, and Shaggy hit the hay.  ......Let the recordings of Seinfeld and Friends begin. 
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't formally gone to bed yet.  Fell asleep in Smallz apt after a long, devious, extraordinary, extraneous, critically acclaimed, somber drinking night.  First thing I can think of is "I'm Tired."  Whenever I have liquor, other than beer, I am assured to have an extraordinary night.  More than drunk, I become devious to my own inhibitions, sometimes creating stories of .... ahh, whatever, I'm just tired.  I think I'll get some sleep soon, I wish I had McDonald's breakfast, which is "oh" so tasty.  Good Night.
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Played b-ball last night, bought a shirt at Target, visited Famous Dave's in Uptown where  I ate, drank and listened to Blues.  Drank a few, then went back to Minnehaha.  Had a couple Milwaukee Ice (from the 30-pack priced at $10), then Dino drove me to where the party was.  Drank a few more from the 30-pack, sang a few "made up" songs while Dino guitared, then called a taxi at 5:00 AM.  What I learned last night:  Famous Dave's has really good potato skins.  All cab companies hate me.  Cab companies take credit cards, however, cabbies hate filling out the credit card slip, and would rather get stabbed before taking the time to process them with a happy face.  Justin (Dino's friend) is a good cook for drunk people at 3:30 AM.  White castle serves a "non good" sausage egg and cheese muffin.
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just got back from the ACME Comedy Company where Nick Swardson, St. Paul native, was headlining the night.  The best part would have to be the "Gay Robot" routine, which features Nick moving (arms stiff, jerky movements) and "gay like" talking.  The only thing missing from this bit was "Robot Balls," but maybe he'll think of it sometime soon, which would almost certainly boost his laugh-o-meter.  I am not a comedy critic, so I will not try to critique or review his comedy.  One thing I would have to say is that Nick has an excellent impression of "old people," "drunk people," and "babies."  Put those three together, and you'll be bound to find many people in the audience who can relate.
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went running for the first time in almost 2 months.  Holy crap, where has the time gone.  I guess I'll have to blame work that one.  I've been really busy at work, which had caused me to work way past 6:00, and with the gym closing at 8:00, I never had enough time to get to the gym and jump on the treadmill.  I would run outside, but I'm also very picky in what kind of weather I will run in.  Today, the weather was awesome, so I made the run.  I am going to try and leave work earlier from now on (workload pending) and continue running for at least 1 month, after that we'll see what happens.  1 month until my birthday (yikes, grrr, sad, olddd???, boooo).  I am going to have to drink a lot, I'm thinking of getting a keg.....yeee haaa!!!!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Strange movie.  I watched it for the first time today, and found it to be a relatively decent movie, with some good (great) acting.  I like mysteries, so this one went up to the top of my mystery movie watching list.  There wasn't too much fowl language, so that is always a boost for me and my sensitive ears.
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pete's party made out to be one crazy and long night.  I haven't stayed up this long partying since I was 21.  I was in bed by 7:40 AM, and could not sleep past Noon.  I haven't talked to anyone today, which is probably a good thing since my voice is a little sore from the various late-night activities.  Dan is one scary driver, I mean, crazy!!!  I have partial memories of Dan driving the car backwards down a One Way street going probably around 60 mph, and doing some crazy ass turns which made me think I was going to die.  All I can say is "awesome."  I hope Dirty didn't get too mad at him for that, if he remembers.  I found an old house lamp in the garbage and stored it in Dirty's car until we got to the next house.  It was going to be used as my coat rack, that was, until Pete (I think) took care of the lamp (my date) and threw it on the ground, breaking it around the pelvis region.  It was too flimsy to stand up, so Dan threw it over some fence.  I walked into the neighbor's house, of the house we were at, and they were having a little get-together with loud music.  They thought I was coming to complain about the noise, but I told them I was just their to party, and they said "come on in."  It was pretty fun, they had an old piano, which didn't work at all.  I tried to play Beethoven's Moonlight Sonata, but only 7 out of the 88 keys worked.  Hence, I had to settle for Crouton's Overture, which only uses 6 1/2 keys.  We ended up at Perkins somehow at around 5:00 AM, and I ordered some blueberry pancake thing, which Dirty had ordered.  He got pissed that I wanted the same thing he wanted, so he changed his order and got the strawberry pancakes instead.  Someone told Amy that I thought she was cute, and so everyone had fun with that.  I never got her number, maybe she'll IM me or something.  She seemed pretty nice.
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I did it, I finally have a job.  Well, not really, but it feels like it.  My year of being a temp and ten months of being a team lead are paying off.  I accepted the supervisor position last week, after being the interim supervisor since May.  The paperwork is in, and I will soon be wreaking the benefits of corporate america.  Work has been getting busier too since this spring.  We have hired 4 more people, which brings my staff to 15 spread among 2 shifts.
      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Kick His Ass Sea Bass
      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I finally had the job interview today with my manager.  The interview was for a supervisor position, which basically was given to me 3 weeks ago.  Although, company policies were dumb as always, they had to interview 3 people for the job, or 2 other people.  So, I was kinda nervous before the interview since I had no idea what to expect, and I suck the crap house at trying to convince someone I'm good for the job.  Even though I've already had 2 years experience in the department I'm in, I still have minor management experience.  Oh well, what the hell, life goes on, then we drink.  I played with my racket after work.  Devo met me at the courts and was pissed completely since I was 10 minutes late.  Anyone who knows me, knows I will probably be on time for something about.....9% of the time.  And, anyone who knows Devo, he is on time 99.999% of the time, and if he is going to be late, he will feel so bad that he'll consist on buying you a beer or keg of beer.  I dunnoh, maybe I'm exaggerrating a bit.  Swinging the racket is quite the funnest thing I love to do, besides golf and sex with my neighbor.  I have played golf with my neighbor, we used to play in my backyard back in the hood.  Once, she didn't even use a golf club and just threw the ball directly at my head.  I pouted exponetionally, since I knew the more I looked hurt, the more action I could probably receive on the later part of the day.  Stomach is hungry, off to eat.   Peace.
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just another Friday night, containing fun and adventure, summarizes last evenings events. Dan, Tom, Pete and I made our way to Grandma's "Fun Time Saloon." Here, we are introduced to various ladies who our absolutely glorified by our looks and style. One exception, I did get the cold shoulder from a cute short girl from Blaine. But, that wouldn't stop the fun from succeeding, for our group, "the handsome gang," was looking to have a good time. There was much "lifting the roof" on the dance floor, and girls grinding on eachother. Which points out the obvious, these are the girls to talk to.  Pete and Tom macked on the girls, while I watched in astonishment. Sometime after bar close, we end up in a hotel room at the Holiday Inn, where I found myself on the 14th floor, trying to break-in to the swimming pool. Being unseccessful, I wandered back to room "520," to reunite with the gang so we could head home.  On the way home, we get the idea for McDonalds and decide the best way to get there is to drive through the 15th avenue construction zone....Not a good idea....here we almost die, as the car is forced through 2 feet deep potholes of mud. Competely shocked that we got through that, we made it to the McDonalds - which is closed. So, we speed on over to the Quarry. While waiting in line at the drive thru, some guy in the car ahead of us, "drunk as a French donkey," gets out of the car and wanders around the parking lot. As I see the car door ahead of us wide open, I don't hessitate to think, and jump out of the car and head straight for the car ahead of us. I get in their car and close the door. Holy crap, were they surprised to see me!! Of course, they couldn't help but laugh at this most mystifying event. I said, "oh crap, wrong car again," opened the door, and left for Tom's car. We tend to our Double Cheeseburgers and McChickens, and head for home. 
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OK, so it's been awhile...&nbsp; I've been so upset lately over my cable internet service.&nbsp; It hasn't worked since last Friday, and today, I had a genius idea...hook up the cable modem to the computer through USB, without connecting it to the cable cord.&nbsp; "Holy Cow," it worked!!!&nbsp; So, that brings me here, finally.  I've spent this entire week watching the Democratic National Convention.&nbsp; It is very exciting, compared to my normal boring week.&nbsp; I really enjoyed Clinton's speech on Monday.&nbsp; On Tuesday, I was extremely impressed by Barack Obama and Teresa Heinz Kerry.&nbsp; Wednesday, John Edwards gave a very powerful speech about "Hope."&nbsp; Now, tonight I'm sitting through John Kerry's speech, and although he is my favorite presidential candidate, I can't help but be a  little  bored.  Last weekend brought about many funness in Madison for Brodie's bachelor party.&nbsp; Events included hanging out with Amy on Friday night, where her parents made me a bed in their basement, which was awesome!!!&nbsp; I had my own TV, and a fan right next to my bed.&nbsp; We made it down to the Madison Union Terrace, where we visited for awhile before meeting up with Todd, Wilson, Brodie, Josh and Dino.&nbsp; Amy and I made it home around 3:00 or something and went to bed.&nbsp; Sometime around 3:30, the calls started to come in from the drunk guys, "hey dustin, are you awake?"&nbsp;...&nbsp; "hey, where does Amy live, we'll pick you up."&nbsp;... "dude, where you at?"&nbsp; Ah, yea, needless to say, I put my phone on silent, and went to bed.  Saturday brought about paintball, where we were the laziest troops of all time.&nbsp; I think we played the same course 5 times because we were too lazy to walk to&nbsp;another one.&nbsp; Now, the fun continues.&nbsp; We get drunk at the hotel, and head for State Street.&nbsp; Here, we come across many people who enjoy our crazyness.&nbsp; I was fairly drunk, at which one point, I was introducing myself as "Hi, I'm Crouton, I'm running for Senate."&nbsp; The ladies really seemed to love that one.&nbsp; Also, since we had Wilson there in a Cow Suit, I was asking everyone, "have you seen a cow?"&nbsp; I got a lot of strange looks, which I dismissed as normal behavior.&nbsp; Sometime during the night, I found myself holding hands and mutually&nbsp;grabbing a nice 5' 3" blonde lady, and telling her she and I were meant to be together.&nbsp; However, what happens next is super crazy, she shows me her license and says, "see, im 36 years old."&nbsp; HUH???&nbsp; I was shocked to hear such a thing, but very proud, as the whole night she was saying how funny I was.&nbsp; I seemed to calm down a little, but then her friend goes, "she's married."&nbsp; WHAT???&nbsp; She shows me her ring, and I almost faint, except, I knew it was time to get back to my duty of being (fake bouncer guy), yea, I sit at the entrance on a stool&nbsp;and put my hand out when people open the door.&nbsp; They start to give me their ID, and they go, "Again??"&nbsp; - since they just got through one bouncer up the stairs.&nbsp; Ha Ha, I was so happy to be such a fooler.&nbsp; I found myself alone and lost at around 3:00, and walking around downtown asking people if they've seen a cow....I didn't think they would recognize anyone else.&nbsp; They said "No?".... later on, Wilson calls me, I'm like "Wilson, where are you?&nbsp; I'm lost, alone and scare."&nbsp; Anyways, we end up meeting at the state capital, and eventually find the rest of the gang.&nbsp; Somehow, we get in a cab, get back to the hotel, and go to Perkins.&nbsp; Here, I'm involved in a stabbing, my hand gets cut by a butter knife, and Goose (i think) starts putting salt on the wound.&nbsp; (Is this normal??)&nbsp; I think I was hurting then, so I got angry and pout.&nbsp; The night ends soon after this, and the sleep began.  I'm leaving out a lot of details, as the pact of bachelor parties, is not to devulge.&nbsp; Therefore, my stories only include some of my fun. 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I bought my first book&nbsp;since the&nbsp;4th grade, today.&nbsp; I had a conversation with someone at the wedding over the weekend about how I don't really read books, and that I only read things such as news, and business stuff.&nbsp; Feeling stupid talking to the girl, I figured I should really start-up reading again.&nbsp; I mentioned I should just go and get a "Harry Potter" book, thinking to myself those books must not be hard to read, as kids read them and such.&nbsp; She said that those are awesome books, but that if I get one, I should start with book one, even though the the third one is the best.&nbsp; So, today I walked into Barnes and Nobel, lost as a zebra in a K-mart, and headed towards the Children's Section.&nbsp; About 20 minutes later, I found the "Harry Potter" section.&nbsp; First thing I did, after finding "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone," was&nbsp;looked at the price.&nbsp; HOLY CRAP, why so expensive???&nbsp; $20, when I can buy the dvd for $10.&nbsp; Oh well, I guess it must be worth it, taking into account the competitive market, if it is twice as much as the DVD, it must be twice as good, right?&nbsp; Well, I guess we'll see about that...  I have my final interview tomorrow with " some big mortgage company"  for the same job I have now, it's just that &nbsp;"some big mortgage company"  bought out the contract of my company, which was operating the Document Imaging department for the past year.&nbsp; I am not too worried, and&nbsp;I'm just getting anxious to get this whole transition process over with.&nbsp; If all goes well, I'm going to be car shopping soon, for something other than a "rusty, purple cavalier."&nbsp; I keep dreaming of the day when I'm driving some really neet car down the road, and the chicks are like, "wow, that guy is very datable since he is driving a really neet car."&nbsp; Ahhh, Dreams...  Has anyone driven through the Burger King drive-thru at the Querry lately?&nbsp; What the crap,,,???&nbsp;&nbsp; For Pete's Sake, it took 14 minutes to get my whopper value meal, now that is just down-right slow. 
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a crap load of stress at work last week...mostly caused by lack of employees coming to work.&nbsp; In fact, last Friday, 5 out of 14 people were gone in my department.&nbsp; I think I should do something about this, maybe&nbsp;I should give them the Chris Farley "Motivational Speaker" speech.  &nbsp;  On Wednesday, my real birthday, I visited Squirt, my longtime friend.&nbsp;&nbsp;She had baked me a cake that day,&nbsp;which made me feel happy and special.&nbsp;&nbsp;Homemade presents are always&nbsp;awesome.&nbsp; She didn't think it looked&nbsp;good, but&nbsp;I think the&nbsp;homemade frosting was just perfect.&nbsp;&nbsp;I left&nbsp;there, and bounced on over to Psycho Susies as&nbsp;Shaggy and Rachel were dining with some friends.&nbsp; I had&nbsp;the "Pirate" drink, which is basically 151 in a&nbsp;Pirate mug, Argh!!&nbsp; It's got a nice kick, which helps when eating the scrumptious cheese curds.&nbsp; So, after getting drunk, I can go to cute girls and go "Arrren't you cute."&nbsp;- With a pirate grin&nbsp;and wink.  &nbsp;  That night I got totally wasted, which was my goal.  &nbsp;  Thursday was really rough at work.&nbsp; I got in about 2:00 PM, and felt a little guilty, but then I ended up staying there until 10:00, so it's allll good.  &nbsp;  This weekend was Emily's wedding, my first "real kiss" neighbor girlfriend, and longtime friend.&nbsp; Needless to say, it was very strange to see her get married, I was kinda sad, but maybe it was because I kept thinking about the time she through a golf ball at my head.&nbsp; That night, my arm was twisted into drinking the free beer at the bar, therefore, leading me into Croutonish ways, and chatting away with people, including the girl I had a crush on for over 6 years.&nbsp; We ended up in Downtown La Crosse, where Smallz and I played a game of pool - he won :-(&nbsp; ... and more talking with friends from high school.&nbsp; Somehow I got home around 3:30, and that's about it.  &nbsp;  6 more weddings to go this summer.&nbsp; Yee ha!!!   
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Keg Stands @ 1698 Minnehaha Ave" was a success.  Results include, buying my first keg, doing my first keg stand, drinking lots of beer, running after and catching a runaway puppy, donuts and energy drink run to SuperAmerica, Friends triva persuit, Psycho Susies, and Bobby Z's.  The keg was tapped around 6:30, which is followed by Bag-O and Papa Johns.  Subsequent events follow, including chasing after a runaway puppy, where quickness and a good pouncing effect are needed and produced to take ahold of the little bugger.  The dog, weighing a whopping 3 pounds, was missing a colar and an owner.  We couldn't find an owner, therefore, the only resonable thing to do was to take it home, and wait fot the owners to come by some day.  Since there was no colar, we ganked the color from Monkey (the cat), and used an ethernet cable as a leash.  This produced such easy naming capabilites for the dog (our mascot), including normal names such as...."Modem," and "Router."  Modem was the name that stuck, so as we played Bag-O, Modem was drinking water, tied to the ethernet cable, and trying to drink random glasses of beer.  Melancholy took over a little while later, when 2 older guys in a big-ass van came by and said the dog was theirs.  Very sad time for us, as our mascot was being taken away from us, leaving us with a colar, and an ethernet cord attached to nothing. :-(  Later on, we caught up with Pete and Tom at Psycho Susies.  Not much happened there, just finished off a pitcher, then left for Bobby Z's.  On the way in, I see a leaf on a bush and decide to ghank it as a suvenior.  The bouncer is like, "What's the leaf for?"  Ha Ha.  At Bobby Z's we drink more beers, and get more drunker.  As the night is almost done, and are about to leave.  Someone goes to me, "Crouton, give the girl [slutty girl] the leaf."  Being non-shy at the moment, I do the obvious and lay the 3 inch long leaf on the table in front of slutty girl.  I go, "This [the leaf] has your name written all over it."  I quickly left, leaving no room for a response.  On the way down the stairs I hear "Here's your leaf back fag."  while seeing the leaf floating down towards the floor.  I am justifiablly shocked by what I heard, am I getting into another fight???  Over a leaf???  Holy crap, is there something on me that says "fight me, i am leaf boy?"  Well, funness only starts when, outside the bar someone goes "hey crouton, there's that guy who wanted to fight you."  So, fag-boy starts coming after the gang and I, while slutty girl trys to stop him from committing suicide.  I would have to say this was the strangest and funniest thing that has happened in awhile, and I'm sure the leaf story will stick around for ages.  Thanks fag-boy!!!  
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tonight's activities included Basilica Block party, where the "Main Event" was "O.A.R."  Which is the best, and only band I ever paid to see in concert.  I saw them at the Target Center last year, where they opened for 311.  I did leave after "O.A.R" was done playing, therefore, I consider myself an "O.A.R Head."  Screw you hippies, I'm goin home.  To start out, I left work at 6:00 PM, fairly early, since I didn't get into work until 1:35 PM.  I decided that I needed some time away, therefore, deciding on playing Golf with my friends up in Andover.  I did fairly crappy, as this is the first time playing in at least a year.  The results included, 5 over par on the first hole.  Par on the 2nd Hole, and hitting a goose in the head on the 3rd Hole.  I was very upset that I hit the goose, since I was trying to hit the ball over the flock, but then, Oops!!!, I hit the ball too low, and watching gravity take it's turn, I saw the ball go straight down towards the flock of 200 geese.  I thought, "OH God, please find a way to get through the geese without hitting them, but Nope, it was not going to happen today.  Sadness took over me as I saw the goose that I hit, start walloping, and running away.  The rest of the flock followed, and I felt like a "Thug," who punched some innocent person at an "I love Lucy" Convention.  OK, on to the Basilica Block Party.....  I took the #6 bus from my apt down hennepin ave to the big church on 16th street.  The bus was loaded with chicks, all of which were under 23 years old, which is basically, Incredible!!!  Of course, I did my part and didn't speak a word to anyone.  At the O.A.R concert, I met an annoying girl, who I found to be very interesting, and attainable.  Therefore, I played nice cute guy, and spoke very few words, including "wow, is that a video camera?"  And, she was like, "hmm, I don't know" (she gives me the camera), I look at it very closely and say, "nope, it's just digital."  Yes, I know I am an awesome conversationalist.  Later on I go, "Hey, nice pink toenail polish."  She goes, "thanks, what color do you have?"  I go, "they are tan."  Anyways, later on, she comes up to me and says she thinks we should go on a date.  I'm like, "OK?," don't you have a boyfriend?, (because she was talking to a guy the whole night), and she goes, no, "we are just friends."  ...my head is like OK?...So, she gives me her digits, which I am doubtful I will call at anytime during my life.  I'm having a Keg tomorrow to celebrate my birthday (which is actually July 14).  Anyone who thinks I'm cool is invited,....if you're reading this, I guess you can come too.  The location is probably going to be my apt, but if you want up-to-date info, email me, or call Devo, Dirty or Shaggy....(my bitches).  Later...... 
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The 4th of July activities included Dan's house in Woodbury, where bag-o was in play, swimming was in operation, along with volleyball with random girls.  I made it to the party around 6:15, which caused me to be way behind on drinking.  I cracked open the 18-pack of La Crosse City Light, and began the journey of fun times.  Mom had packed 3 cooked brats, some potato salad, and green salad.  This was eaten during the night, and was super good.  After downing around 3 beers, we skipped on over to Woodbury Park and joined 3 girls to play sand volleyball.  This was very fun, however, I was disappointed in my effort...I think it was hot chick (black shirt girl) that was making me nervous.  She had bootylicious tan shorts on, and was a pretty good kicker (she said it was because she was a dancer).  Man alive, she could punt the ball.  Creepy guy was watching us play from afar, and when I volunteered to sit out of the game, I was forced to answer questions, which I felt very uncomfortable.  He is like, "the cops won't let me shoot off my fireworks."  And, I'm like, "yea, isn't there a sign that says there is a $700 fine?"  He was like, "yea, but I thought since I bought them, I might as well try to light them off."  -----  What the crap is he thinking???  Oh well, he was home schooled throughout high school, maybe that's why it was incredibly awkward.   Josh came by later and was saddenly introduced to him as well, I was much relieved, as now I could play the quiet shy kid who doesn't like to socialize much.  (hmm, sound familiar?)  After volleyball, we went back to the house.  There was swimming and fireworks by the pool, and me talking to a girl from Steven's Point, crap, I'm really bad with names,,,but she was really nice.  The Woodbury Fireworks came on for a little bit, then after that, 3 hot chicks came by in short skirts and nice shirts.  They were in the pool about to get naked, when "cry baby hot chick" said she couldn't continue stripping her clothes since her panties were attached to her skirt.  What the hell, almost the awesomest thing in the world was about to happen, but NO, i was shot down by the stupid "Panty-Skirt In One" deal, again!!!  I had conversations with Susie as she remembered what had happened the last time we were together (@ Perkins @ Pete's party).  And I kept saying, "i'm so sorry" and "i was a jerk" and "i think you are cool."  Which is all true.  I was laughing at her when she was trying to get the CD player to work, it was very funny. 
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I will be attending Dan's "kick ass" party on July 4.  I'll be in La Crosse Friday night through Sunday mid-afternoon, and I'll drive back to Dan's for Intoxication and Fireworks (my two favorite activities,,,,, besides getting laid).  Last night produced another fine fine night, involving St. Paul Saints, hot girls with nice ass pants, and a Saints schedule magnet for my fridge.  Shaggy, Dirty and I sat in the left field bleachers.  We had an excellent view of "hot girl" and "devil girl."  Shaggy kept his mouth shut while Dirty and I had a blast telepathing with "hot chick."  I said "Stand Up Hot Chick,"  and, she stood up..."Awesome."  I said "Touch Your Boob Hot Chick," And, nothing happened.  I'm disappointed in my telepathing abilities.  Dirty and I went to the ATM, and as I was getting cash from the merchandising shop since the ATM was broken, Dirty spied on the ATM maintenance people and saw them put in the combination for the lock.  He jotted it down in his memory, of which was translated into my cell phone later.  We joked about stealing money or selling the combination to the Mob, but we're pretty much all talk.  I got 2 cell phone numbers yesterday.  Two people had lost their phones at the game, for which the announcer repeated the numbers over the loudspeaker, and using quick thinking and finesse, the numbers were stored in my cell phone as "Lost Phone" and "Lost Phone #2."  I called one of them, and asked for Bill (bill murray), but they said "Jill?" and I said "yes."  They said wrong number, then I hung up.  Fun Stuff!!!  Rachel joined us later in the 5th inning.  She drank with us, and then we decided to go get a brat.  Rachel ordered first, and I hear the brat guy go "no more brats."  I was exasperated to hear such a thing.  I had to settle for a burnt hotdog with a crappy bun….Yee Ha.  I woke up at 11:30 today, therefore, late to work as always. 
      
</post>


</Blog>