<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Peace. What does that mean?  1)The absence of war or other hostilities.  2)An agreement or a treaty to end hostilities.  3)Freedom from quarrels and disagreement; harmonious relations: roommates living in peace with each other.  4)Public security and order: was arrested for disturbing the peace.  5)Inner contentment; serenity: peace of mind.   The first definition is "the absence of war or other hostilities". I think that our society would agree that that is what peace is. So when you see the anti-Iraq-war rallies, they hold up signs that say peace first. Or you've seen the bumper stickers that say peace is patriotic. People think that peace is as easy as not going to war. That's a joke. Do you notice how easy it is to say that you're for peace? It sounds terrible to say you are SUPPORTIVE of a war, but it sounds great to say you are for peace.   Question:  Are the people who are for "peace" that are against the war really supporting peace as we know it?  Answer:  NO .  Let me tell you why. When you are against America taking militant action against terrorist regimes or terrorist groups that have ATTACKED AMERICA before and have plans to do it again then you are permitting violence against America. On September 11th, 2001, terrorists hijacked planes and drove them into American buildings. How many people died? "On the hijacked planes, 266 people were killed. For the combined attacks, more than 3,000 people are dead or still missing and presumed dead. More than 300 firefighters and 23 policemen died in the towers as they ran up to help others escape." (http://www.aynrand.org/medialink/fortheyoung1b.html) That is the largest terrorist attack against America, but there have been many other small operations against Americans over the past 10 years.   So when you are against taking militant action against the people who want to slit our womens throats you are giving them permission to do so. Thats the bottom line. When you aren't willing to defend this country and to disable our enemies from attacking us again, then you don't love this country.  YOU ARE ALLOWING AMERICA TO BE ATTACKED . You are anti-American. So if being against America defending herself against her attackers is peace, then peace is not patriotic in that sense. Peace in that sense is quite the opposite.   What is the real peace? Where can I find peace? The real peace is a constant relationship with Jesus Christ our Lord. You can find that peace in leading a life that worships Him. "He will wipe every tear from their eyes. There will be no more death or mourning or crying or pain, for the old order of things has passed away." -Revelation 21:4. If that is not peace then I don't know what is.   In  Christ 's Name Amen.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "The Islamic guerrilla group Hezbollah is airing a promotional TV spot comparing the abuse of Iraqi prisoners to the suffering of Jesus, based on a trailer for Mel Gibson's movie The Passion of the Christ. The 40-second spot, made by Hezbollah's satellite TV station, Al-Manar, shows images of a coalition soldier kicking an Iraqi prisoner and a man and woman cowering in terror as troops burst into their home. The words 'no mercy' and 'no compassion' flash on the screen. The soundtrack for Gibson's film plays in the background as the title, 'The Passion of the Iraqis,' appears next to the infamous photo of a hooded Iraqi prisoner standing on a box with wires attached to his outstretched arms."   Read that through. Now read it again. If what is discussed in the article above is not insane to you than I don't know what is.   Lets get one thing clear here. The torture of Iraqi prisoners is not even comparable to the sufferring and crucifixion of Christ. Christ endured being beaten by the Jews, being beaten by the Romans, being whipped 39 times with a cat of nine tails, having a crown made of thick thorns shoved into his head, nails the size of hammers being driven into his hands and feet, and the shame of being naked on a cross for hours in front of everyone. How is that at all like the torture that has been going on in Iraq?   First of all, Christ was tortured like that because it had to be done. Christ had to be beaten and killed because that is the sacrifice He made for us. He had to rise again because that is the salvation he gave to us.   About the torture that was going on in Iraq... I personally disagree with the entire concept of incarcerating terrorists because I dont think we should let them live if we are at war with them (read my post: what do we about terrorists?). But about this torture: I agree with some of the interrogation methods used by the American Military but not all. I agree with anything used that is non-sexual and does not draw blood. For example, the Military will put someone who is known as a terrorist in an extremely cold or hot room for long periods of time, or they will tie them in a weird position and make them keep it for a long time. The entire goal of those precedures is to brake down their will so they will give the information. The people who would be interrogated by the military are known terrorists or criminals of some sort. How is it wrong to do something like that in order to get information to save lives? How do you expect our Military Intelligence to gain the knowledge of where other terrorists are or other necessary information to win a war? Thats exactly what most liberals out there will do. They will complain about not "winning" the war, but will not let us use the methods that it takes to win a war. You cannot battle evil (like we are doing in Iraq) and be "nice" about it. When it becomes wrong is when the interrogation procedures become extremely abusive or sexual.  I disagree with any sexual method of interrogation. I disagree with it because I would say that doing that is bringing it to a level of debauchery that is like mingling with Satan. As for that woman in the pictures, she belongs in some dirty porno theater in the Weimar Republic. She is an abomination to the U.S. Military and should be thrown out immediately. That porn-toting jezebel is a parasite to our military. How can you say that this harlot and her chronies represent the American Military in its entirety? Thats just blatant foolishness.   The fact that people are comparing the slaughtering of Nicholas Berg to the torturing of Iraqi terrorists is absolutely maniacal. A few disgusting American soldiers put underwear on peoples heads, drag them around on leashes, and/or sexually abuse them. Yah thats pretty terrible. Seriously, like I said before I believe that most of that is wrong. But to compare that to a group of blood-thirsty murderers surrounding a man saying "God is great" as they slit his throat and slowly cut off his head, that is just absurd. That is apostasy in the First Degree.  These men (if you can call them that) and other leaders of radical-Islamic terrorist groups have declared a Holy War against Christianity and Judaism.  Thats right. I said it. Its the truth. Do you think its just a mere coincidence that Nick Berg and Daniel Pearl (both men beheaded by Al-Quada oriented terrorists on video) were both Jews? NO. The terrorists even said that they killed Daniel Pearl because he was a Jew. They hate America because it represents a few things they believe are evil in the purest form: Christianity, Judaism, and Freedom. We can all see that cutting off a mans head well you say "God is great" is EVIL. How can someone doubt that? If you do doubt that, then I question whether you are on the right eating habits. Maybe its the Ritalin the libs perscribe to silence the "enemy" aka Masculinity. Then again thats another topic. I will discuss that soon.   Dear Lord Jesus Christ , I pray that you would give President Bush wisdom. I pray for America. I pray for the world. I pray for the souls that do not see truth. And I also pray for the souls that have seen the truth but still deny it. We love you Lord. I pray that you would help everyone of us to lead a life worthy of the calling we have received (Ephesians 4). In your Son's Name,  AMEN . 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Romans 12:9 - "Love must be sincere- Hate what is evil and cling to what is good."   Love must be sincere. This verse is saying that if you don't hate evil than you CANNOT love good and vice versa. If you do not believe that there is Good and Evil out there than you are a fool and have no verifieable evidence to support your claim. Anyways, I love this verse because its so true (then again it is the Word of God), if you do not see the evil out there and hate it, than your love is no longer sincere. There would be no love if there is no hate. It is philosophical fact that if you love something than you hate its opposite. That is why the liberal idea of only love is a joke. If all you have is love than that love isn't actually love because you dont have any hate for the opposite. And from this day forth, I pray to God that He would help me see the Good and recognize it as good and to see the Evil and recognize it as evil. And I pray that my hate would not be misdirected towards Good but only towards Evil and that my love would not be misdirected towards Evil but only towards Good.   This all relates to politics somehow. Recently my dear friend and colleague Taylor Straton told me that someone said to him that we need to show the terrorists the love of Christ. In response to this, my friend made a great point. It is the love of Christ that makes them Hate us. They hate good and we hate evil. You cannot compare our two hates. You can't say that all hate is bad, because hate for evil is good. But don't get me wrong, hate is a tool of Satan almost all of the time. That is why through daily devotion in the Word and through leading a worshipful lifestyle God will give us the wisdom to discern. If we show the terrorists more love, then they will kill us more. I do not want my people to be led to the slaughter. I would rather hand these terrorists to Satan because they are so evil that they will never be able to overcome it (1 Corinthians 5:5).   Once again I will say that the only way to make this stuff stop is to eliminate the enemy. Liberals will tell you, "You cannot drive out hate with hate." Well let me tell you something, You can't compare a hate for evil with a hate for good, a hate for evil is a love for good and a hate for good is a love for evil. They are not even subject to comparison, the only way to drive out a hate for good is a hate for evil and the only way to drive out a love for evil is a love for good. Therefore,  THE ONLY WAY TO DRIVE OUT A LOVE FOR EVIL (MODERN-DAY TERRORISM) IS A HATE FOR EVIL !  The Love of Christ is the ultimate pure love of good. Therefore the ultimate pure hate of evil.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many of you are wondering, what do we have to do to get this terrorism to stop? Well let me tell you a little story.   While the Nazi Army was in it's prime, Heinrich Himmler (the creator of Concentration Camps) created a radical group of the Nazi Army called the Werewolves. After Hitler committed suicide, the Werewolves consisted of barely 1,500 people. The majority of the men in this group were old men and young boys. So after the fall of Nazi Germany, Russia tried to go into Berlin and clear out all the Nazis that were still there. The Nazis that were left were Werewolves and they used terroristic methods such as bombing train stations, giving grenades to children, pretending like you are hurt so you can blow up the oppossing country's medic, etc. So this huge Russian army goes in against about 1,500 people. It seems easy right? Not when you are fighting against die-hard Nazis like the werewolves. The werewolves were SO committed to their cause that once they were captured they would NOT give up. They would find any way to end their life or the lives of those around them. Russia lost over 500,000 men to these terrorists. No joke. The Russians had this policy that when they would find these Nazis they would not kill them if they did not have to. But the nazis that they ended up holding captive in hospitals, etc. usually ended up killing somebody of killing themselves somehow. They were SOOO brainwashed that they wouldn't even stop if their life was on the line. So Russia was losing tremendously to these guys (keep in mind its a bunch of old men and young boys) and then America steps in. America had a different policy. When we would find a nazi, we would tie him to a tree and shoot him in the forehead, no questions asked. Everyone knew that this was the only way to eliminate the chance of the Nazi party ever rising again. America succeeded with this policy and we quickly killed off all of the Nazis.  Back then they had it a little easier, they had ONE party they were dealing with. Today we have a lot of different groups of terrorists that are attacking us in the Middle East. But they all have a few things in common. They are based on radical Islam and they are ALL terrorists. The only way to get rid of terrorism is to KILL everyone of those terrorist. Not keep them in prison. Not give them medical attention. This is an unconventional war against unconventional people. They slaughter innocent men and praise God while they are doing it. That is inhumane and they  DO NOT DESERVE LIFE . HOW CAN NO ONE SEE THIS?! If we let them live, they will not change and this terrorism will continue. These terrorists are parasites to this Earth. I am not being close-minded in saying this. I am saying that they have made the  CHOICE  to draw innocent blood in the name of Allah. They have made the  CHOICE  to gas thousands of innocent Iraqi people. They have made the  CHOICE  to ATTACK US ON OUR OWN SOIL!!  THATS RIGHT!! THEY HAVE ATTACKED US ON OUR OWN SOIL!! THE SAME PEOPLE THAT SLICED THE THROAT OF NICK BERG ATTACKED AMERICA ON SEPTEMBER 11th, 2001! HOW CAN NO ONE SEE THIS?!?!  And because of those  CHOICES  they deserve death.  The libs scream "End the violence!". Well, you cannot end the violence with peace. I will tell you that. If America just stopped and said "Peace, please we really want peace with the world and well stop killing terrorists because its violent" the terrorists would rape Lady Liberty once again and would attack more. Conclusion: these terrorists are sons of hell and deserve nothing but death. The people that we have incarcerated that we know are Al-Quada and/or Hamas or affiliated with any other terrorist group should be taken outside and shot in the head. That is the only way to defeat the enemy. If the terrorists see that we let these people live they will keep attacking. We have to ELIMINATE ALL OF THE ENEMY! Just like America did with the nazis in WWII, we have to totally eliminate everyone of those terrorists. Many historians say that if America hadn't killed every last one of those Werewolves, the Nazi party would have slowly gained power again and they would probably be the leading power in Europe at this point. If we don't kill every one of these terrorists and show them death then they will take over. The Al-Quada had plans to  TAKE OVER AMERICA  and make it an Islamic nation by the year 2020. DID U READ THAT CORRECTLY?!?! thats 16 years from now! They want to take over the world. We HAVE to stop them NOW!!  YOUR LIBERTIES ARE AT STAKE !!  Romans 13: 2-4 "Do you want to be free from fear of the one in authority? Then do what is right and he will commend you. For he is God's servant to do you good. But if you do wrong, be afraid, for he does not bear the sword for nothing. He is God's servant,  an agent of wrath to bring punishment on the wrongdoer ." 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You deserve nothing but death and that eternally. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You are a DOG, John Kerry. You lover and practice of falsehood! You are nothing but a double-talking two-timing parasite to America! You defend the mutilators of flesh and are nothing more than them!&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am sorry I have not updated my blog lately. I leave for Mexico tomorrow to share the gospel of Jesus Christ. Please keep me and my team in your prayers. Once I get back I will further update this blog.     "Watch out for those dogs, those men who do evil, those mutilators of the flesh." Philippians 3:2  "Blessed are those who wash their robes, that they may have the right to the tree of life and may go through the gates into the city. Outside are the dogs, those who practice magic arts, the sexually immoral, the murderers, the idolaters and everyone who loves and practices falsehood."  Revelation 22: 14-15   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>