<Blog>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Changed the Template - the other one wasn't 'doing it' for me.  So to address the only two comments I recieved:  Kris - no, I did not check this out.  I came across this after searching for 'quack docs and their theories' and thought, "Wow, that sounds like a fun!!".  Of course I have checked this out.  I even talked to my OWN doctor about this.  He says that a de-tox cleanse every once in a while isn't a bad idea, and there is a possiblity of better health and function afterwards so blah on you.  Amber - ENOUGH with the In-N-Out.  We are strong, sexy, motivated bi-a-tches and the benefits of these 10 days far outweigh any burger or any other piece of over processed fatty piece of crap we can put in our bodies.  So now to recap day number one.  I, like Amber, cannot feel my lips or my tongue due to the large amounts of cayanne pepper I put in my drink.  I think tomorrow's batch will have to have less pepper, and more lemon juice.  Today wasn't really that bad -- I never felt 'hungry'.  There were many times when I wanted to chew something, or just eat because that is what I usually do at that time of day, etc etc, but not hunger pains, no dizziness or crabiness yet.  Well, no more than normal.  As far as the actual 'cleansing' part, nothing exciting to report.  I think that is because the cleansing tea I drink isn't strong, so I bought a new brand called "Smooth Move" so I'm sure that will be enjoyable.  Amber is excited as well!!  I have lost 4 lbs in one day (Water weight I'm sure - but it's still kind of fun!).  I'm not any more air-heady than normal, and I actually got a lot of work done today.    So far so good - about to drink my tea and kill Marcus -- the wonderful boy that he is has decided that ordering a pizza and eating in front of Amber and I is a good form of entertainment.  If he does I will kill him, slowly and painfully.  So that is day one - nine more to go & I'm sure much more fun and excitment!! Ha! right.........    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so as some of you know, and some of you might not, I have decided to undergo a cleanse of my body - using Stanley Burrough's method from the early 1940's I believe.  You can read his book here: http://www.supernatural.com/Wavelengths/Ebooks/TheMasterCleanse.pdf.  My main reason for trying this cleanse is not only because I have had some pretty horrible allergies this year, as well as other not fun ailments, but I have had a couple of stressful and emotionally-jumbling weeks.  I was trying to find a way to clear my thoughts and gain physical strength to make myself feel better and I then remembered a girl I worked with at my old agency did this cleanse and raved about it.  She felt healthier, more emotionally clarity, and not to mention she dropped about 10lbs and kept it off.  So I figured I had nothing else to loose, so why not.  I am only in Day One of what I am hoping will be a 15 day cleanse - but seeing as how this is my first attempt, I should let my body tell me if I can keep going or if enough is enough.  I have read a lot about the diet, the effects it has on your body, and what I can expect.  Without getting too explicit, I've heard the restroom trips aren't the funnest, but that after all is said and done the cleanse is well worth it.  I'm excited and a little scared, and seeing as how my friend Marcus has put money up against the fact that I won't last 3 days, I would have to say I am motivated.  One of my girlfriends Amber is going to try and do this with me, so that is exciting to have her support as well.  So the cleanse started last night after a bowl of cheerio's.  I drank some slimming tea - which tasted nasty if you must know - I HATE peppermint tea.  Work up this morning, had another cup and drank my first class of the lemonade.  I think I added too much cayanne pepper cause it's a little spicy, but then again, I'm a wuss so who knows.  Seeing as how I am only about 5 hours deep into this thing, of course I have nothing to talk about, but at least I haven't given up yet, right?  I'll keep the updates coming :).
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so Day 3 is done, and today was awesome.  Felt good all day, had a ton of energy, and even more mental clarity.  Even managed to sit through a lunch meeting while everyone else what seemed to be all of my favorite foods without attacking anyone or having any cravings.  I was totally surprised how I felt today, and am crossing my fingers that I am able to feel this way throughout, but I kind of doubt it. I even ran 3 miles tonight (at a slow pace mind you) and felt fine - so I think I might try a run tomorrow morning and see how that goes.  Went over to my friend Rachael's to play with Silvia and her sister Nelly, and had some discussion with Rach that stirred up more emotional unrest, so I'm thinking even though I'm trying to gain control over some things, this cleanse really isn't the way to do it...dammit.  But maybe my butt will be firmer when all is said and done, who knows......  The true test will be at my girlfriend Tessa's bridal shower Sunday -- too much good food and good friends make for a hungry Ann, but at least I'm preparing myself now for it.  Amber is doing fab as well -- no more close quesadilla episodes from what I hear.  We've decided to go out tomorrow night with a couple of her friends from back in the college day, so that should break the monotany and be fun :)
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so here we are on the beginning of Day 3.  With how badly Day 2 ended, I really didn't know if I would be able to keep this up -- if I was going to feel that SICK for the next 7 days, I didn't know if I would be able to handle it.  Well, I woke up this morning, with energy, feeling great, like yesterday never happened. Not sure what the change was, but so far so good.  Dropped my dog off at her Aunt & Uncle's (Josh and Rachael) to play with Nelly, her sister, so hopefully she will be feeling better too.  I have been no fun to her or anyone else for the past 2 days...  So Day 3 is off to a great start, still not feeling hungry, the drooling has subsided :), and I feel about 100% better than how yesterday ended, I just hope that keeps up!  OH, and big thanks to everyone for thier support.  Oh, and Eric, my garden gnomes would like to say good morning.......  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, sorry this wasn't posted last night, to update on Day 2 - but I felt like CRAP and went to bed at 9pm.    Day 2 started fine - I went running and did pilates in the morning as always, only on a much lighter scale.  I felt fine as I went to work.  Then when at work, I started sneezing a lot, my nose was running, and my throat was SO sore.  And my right gland in my throat was swollen, so that wasn't fun.  Then I noticed that my tongue was coated with this white fuzzy stuff, that I have since found out is normal, and once it clears up I am supposedly 'clean'.  On top of that, ALL I want to do is chew on something.  I thought about Jason's Chew and Spit idea of eating, but I didn't want to be weak and cheat, so I didn't.  Then I noticed that I was drooling worse than Silvia.  Seriously.  My mouth was ALWAYS full, it was so strange.  Then around 3pm I developed an awful headache.  I read that this too, is normal.  Basicially, the theory is that the reason I am feeling sick is because the toxins are being released and are now circulated in my blood, making me feel sick.  I went home after a client meeting and went straight to bed and took an hour nap. I woke up feeling better, but not great.  It felt like I had just undergone a night of heavy drinking, and that I had to clean myself out, go running, eat fresh fruit, or something like that, ya know?  I didn't know what to do, so I went over to Amber's and we went for a light walk to clear my head, which did help.  Then the drama began.  Mr. Marcus came home and made fun of me for feeling like crap and made fun of Amber for asking him to tell her what he ate that day - in detail.  I was making my next batch of Juice for Day 3 when I recieved a phone call of support from the wonderful Ali Thompson.  As we were talking Marcus began to talk about going to Taco Bell for dinner.  As I am talking to Ali, I hear Amber say, "Bring me back a cheese quesadilla." And she handed Marcus Money!  And all I'm thinking is hell no, this girl is NOT going to cheat on this cleanse, and especially with me in the house!  So I ran out side, chased down Marcus' car, and got her money back and threw it back in her face and called her a weakling.  So I totally destroyed her night of quesadilla heaven.  Ha!    So I went to bed, not feeling that great, and choked down another glass of the "Smooth Move" tea - and slept through the night farley well -- Silvia wanted to cuddle, so those kinds of sleep disturbances, I'll take :).
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so day four is over and done with.  I'm doing really well, I feel great, mentally stable, and physically awesome.  I have a ton of energy, have NOT felt hungry (though I really really really really want to chew on something, and ice is NOT cutting it anymore).    Ok, so now I'm going to get all philisophical and deep (and I don't think I spelled philisophical right, but oh well, this weblog thing doesn't have spell check, I'll write them a note requesting).  So today I was having a conversation with one of my most favorite people about what we can do to start 'listening' to our bodies.  Meaning how can we figure out what we need vrs what we crave, and how we strive to listen to our bodies, yada yada yada.  We both agreed that we are getting better at it, and that is exciting.  Well, one of my goals of this cleanse was to also sort myself out emotionally and mentally, and we began to discuss how easy it is for us to listen to our natural nutritional needs of our body, but how when we try to listen to our guts and our hearts we sometime ignore those and try to feed our emotions something they are telling us they don't want.  Just food for thought, as I know I am struggling with that right now.   Ok, so back to normal conversation - life is good, the cleanse is going well, and no complaints so far.  I highly recommend to anyone who is looking to challenge themselves and possibly try something to affect thier health -- but no worries, I'll keep you all posted for the duration and after to see if this is all a bunch of poo-poo.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so its on into Day #4.  So far so good, still feeling awesome.  Got up this AM, went running, and pilates (both at a little slower than normal pace).  I still have a lot of energy, and at work I've been acting like a hyper child, so that's always fun.  A little headache, but it isn't nearly as bad as Tuesday (day #2).  It's wierd because if you think about it, a week from today I'll be eating food again -- seems like a long way away, but this week has gone by so quickly that I'm hoping this weekend and early next week does too.  AND Today was the first day I haven't taken allergy meds in a while, and I feel fine.  So either:  A) I never had allergies and I have been drugging myself for no reason or B) The things I'm allergic too aren't bothering me or  C) This cleanse is maybe working?? Call me crazy, but knows??  So yes, in Day 4, almost 1/2 of the way into this thing and still going strong.  I want to say thanks to everyone for their support (even the making-fun-of-me type of support).  It means a lot and helps so much.  And just FYI - even though Jen says I do, I do not smell stale yet.  (that is supposedly one of the effects of this....looking forward to it!!!)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so we are into day 5, and again, feel good, nothing out of the ordinary to report.  Not as much drooling, and I don't think I smell.  BUT I can smell everything else, like I have a super-spidey sense of smell now.  I think its probably from lack of eating, or maybe it's all in my head, but I smell EVERYTHING.  Just this AM I realized that I can't stand the smell of my car.  It's mainly from Silvia riding around in it this past week after going running and swimming, but I'm sure it still smells from Adam last weekend.  That was awful, you could smell the whiskey trying to get out of his system.  I think his tears even contained whiskey and jager.  I'll have to clean that ASAP.  So I think this weekend will be hard for me, I won't be at work, won't be busy entertaining myself, so that is when I see myself getting weak.  AND at the Bridal Shower Sunday, that will suck, but only becuase I'll be wanting to eat.  And the thing is that I've come this far, so I want to finish.  Like I've said all along, this is either going to make me feel better or not, and either way, its only 10 days of my life.  And about last night's rant about 'body hearing', I apolgize for those who thought it was a little hippie-ish.  It was, but you have to put yourself in that mindset to survive this without going insane. Super excited for the weekend though, should be fun!  Though to add to the emotional issues, I have really started to miss Mr Mike as of late, so that isn't fun, but whatever doesn't kill us makes us stronger, right?  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm combining these two posts mainly b/c I was too tired and lazy last night to finish a follow up.  So last night was awesome, went out to Tempe with some friends, and had a great time.  Though I wasn't drinking OR eating (which was driving me nuts, big shout out to Loren for bringing up pizza about a gizzilion times) I had good coversation and met some fun new people.  Last night was a big contemplation night if I was going to finish this or not.  I was about 70% sure I was going to quit, but then when I got home, had some lemonade and woke up fresh today, I am going to try to stick with it until my body tells me not too.  That or day 10, which ever comes first.  Just got out of bed a few mins ago, so going to go swimming and relax today.  Have to run a ton of errands and work a bit from home, so that SUCKS, but I'll survive :).  So here I am, starting day 6, exciting, no?
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my goodness, 7 days.  Last night was another hard day - was fine all day, went to the movies and DIDN'T even partake in the Milk Dud fest that was going on around me.  Happily drank my water and tried to think of gross things so I didn't crave food.  I'm not hungry, but I really really really really really really want to taste something.  Really want to chew something.  But other than that, I feel fine.  Went out last night with some friends, and I snuck in a bottle of 'juice' into the joint, just in case I started feeling hungry or down at any point.  Well, about an a hour into it, I go into the bathroom, go into a stall, lock the door, and take some swigs out of my bottle o' juice.  It was so satisfying!  Then I hid it back in the bag and went out as if nothing was wrong - I felt soooo scandelous!  Ha!  But in all honesty, I am feeling good.  Mentally clear, and I have beaten the caffene habit I've had forever.  I don't find myself needing it to wake up, and I don't feel sleepy during the day, so that is awesome.  I only hope that keeps up!  I still have lots of energy and no weak for sicky feelings.  So this AM is good - went running, am avoiding doing any more work from home, and need to get myself ready for the bridal shower at 1pm.  Should be a great time though, I'm going to see a ton of ppl I haven't seen in forver.  I'm planning on going to the dog park this afternoon, maybe going to hit some golf balls, and possibly going to the Improv tonight, but that is still way up in the air....so a busy day is a good day.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so it is the morning of Day 8, and this weekend was tough.  Mindy did a fabulous job with Tessa's bridal shower, including 9 of my top 10 favorite foods.  I nearly died.  I am so ready to eat, you have no idea.  Reassurance, I'm not hungry, but really really miss food and eating and tasting and chewing...its nuts.  But only 2 more days, and I'll be SOO Happy.  Can't believe I have lasted this long, and I'm a little proud of myself!  Sorry this is short, but work is super busy, but I will write more later w/ more details.  Hugs :)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so on to day #9.  Doing well this morning, didn't sleep well at ALL last night.  I was having crazy dreams and just couldn't get settled.  So working out this morning didn't happen, so I figure I'll have to try for that tonight.  I'm not tired today, just a little sluggish.  So things have been going well, my tongue is starting to clear up, which I have read means that my initial 'cleansing' period is coming close to an end, so that is good.  I also don't smell, at least I don't think so (and I'm using extra lotion and body spray just to be safe).  My spidey sense of smell is still in effect, which is good and bad.  I was at target last night and there was a smelly guy ahead of me in line, so that was kind of gross, but I think it would have made me just as sick even with out.  So tomorrow is Day 10, and I am really really looking forward to eating / tasting something on Thursday.  I just have to remember to take is slow so that I don't kill myself or my stomach by eating too much too soon.  But knowing me, I probably will.  Thanks again for the support! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah!! Last day is finally here -- I am so glad that tomorrow at 11:30 I will be enjoying a bowl of soup and possibly a side salad at Atlanta Bread Co.  SO excited.  So on this last day I feel normal -- I can see why people who don't love food as much as I do can go for 20, 30, or even 40 days. In all honesty, my initial goal was 15 days, and at this point I could go 5 more days and be the same, but I am not about to miss out on Tessa's wedding AND Memorial Day festivities.  I'm glad that I did this though.  I just really hope this balances out my system a little more and starts me on a better path to over all health and eating better.  I was talking to Jen K this AM and telling her that I was really torn about this cleanse ending.  One part of me can't wait to get back to normal life, but on the other side, I am afraid to stop.  I really do like the way I have been feeling health wise this past week.  I don't want to loose that, so it will take a lot of work on my part to continue that.  Imagine thinking that your body is on its way to performing at a more optimal level - and then going back to life before that.  I know it's not very reasonable or easy to think that I can do that full time, but that is one of the thoughts running around my head.  As far as the emotional stuff I was trying to figure out, I had to give up trying to control those areas and realize that they will figure themselves out with time.  As much as I would like to have the answers and have everything solved NOW -- it's just not the way the real world works.  All turns out how it should in the end.  So thanks again to every one for all your support & laughs & interventions through the past 10 days.  I really do appreciate it.  Until NEXT time......  Grand total: Weight lost:  10 or 13 lbs (depends on what time of day I weigh myself) Emotional clarity gained:  not much, but did come to some realizations Health benefits:  Currently feel great, but time will tell the rest.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>