<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sorry for everything.
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So...I already have a livejournal. Now I have a blogger thingy. Hmm. I should use this blogger thingy to....post like....quiz results...or....something dumb like that! or or...random....stuff. Indeed.
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      la la la.
    
</post>


<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once upon a golden century The world had shattered into immortal debris  Battles rage upon the cold earth Her stare forced me into spiritual rebirth Many lives were laid to rest Across her chest was blessed the crest of the dead  Caring not for my own life My wings spread and I flew to her side Staring at me she spoke  "Fear not what you cannot stop  Close your eyes and feel your body drop"    Thats all for now.  I cannot seem to think at this moment, I know not why.  Enjoy.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh sweetest of angels, where art thou? I need release from this cold world, this fake world.  All I see is lies.  All we ever hear about are lies.  I wish these thoughts would just go away.  I cannot take living this way.  Oh sweet baby Jesus, do thou not hear me?
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why can I not stop this suppressed pain?  So long has it been suppressed, it wants out.  It wants to make me bleed, the blood, an ever flowing river of negativity, bleed.  I can feel it starting to pull me down, deeper and deeper into the halls of despair.    Oh saviour, I beg to thee, save me from my hell.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Death and Decay fills this land As I take hold of death's cold hand We embrace in the cold summers night I can feel upon my skin the cold ice Death, take me away from this pain It keeps whispering my unholy name I am confounded to my bed As blood slowly rushes to my head 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello fellow Renegade Angels; I have returned.  I have returned, but with no memories of anything that came to pass, nor of the terrible deeds that I might have once committed.  I, we, are now one.  I remember only but a thing, it is us we, of us.  Of me and him, Him and I, us, the demons.....
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alas, I have returned.  I could not make the razor enter my broken skin.  Its soft touch made me whisper things in my head.  So many bad memories rushed in, making me feel like as if I am nothing more but a mindless drone.  I thought of my mixture of untimely poisons, but something, or someone was holding me back from consuming its sweet taste.  What has happened to me? Why could I not enter the razor deeply within me? Why could I not carve away my life? Why could I not consume my poison?   I live now for another few days, until I regain the strength to attempt a new sacrifice.  We need the sweet touch of a crystal blade upon our open flesh.  We must be punished.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is all we shall post for the day.  Our eyes become dreary from all the tears that have fallen upon the damp plains, and we fear that death is imminent.  We shall return to you, if death does not get its way with us.  Good day, and may the forsaken heavens bless you all.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to be alone.  Forget everything about this life, just rest forever.  Forget about all my memories; forget all the possibilities that may still linger.  My soul was taken from me along time ago, I cannot even remember when it was.  My heart is lost, confused, broken and shattered.  I am so alone.  When all this had began, I hoped I was the only one feeling this pain, for it is unbelievable and unreal that someone can feel all this hurt inside.  I’ve wanted to find something I’ve wanted all my life, true love, someone that cared for me.  She came too late.  I am feeling hallow.  Often my wrists have bled there crimson tears, but never did anybody notice.  My wounds cried so many times.  Screaming for someone to heal them, my heart constantly trying to keep me breathing, but without the willingness, I cannot grant it that one wish.  The emptiness of my life, a void that has yet to be filled.  I’m paranoid.  I’m uptight.  I feel like everyone is always watching me, staring at me, waiting for me to do something wrong.  Now that I have you're full attention, you are going to hear me out, like it or not.  I hate everyone that breath's except for a chosen few.  I hate everything about this world, from the smallest bug to the biggest tree, I hate it all.  I often wonder why I hear voices, why I never put my pain on display, or ever set it free.  Instead of letting my pain, my anguish free, I let it form deep within me, let it become me.  I am my pain, and my pain is me.  It never goes away, they never leave.  Haunting me for age's it seems.  I have tried to cut them out, tried to cry them out.  I opened my sounds, bleed them out.  Nothing worked, the only way to calm them was to take pills, to feed the urges.  I am so confused; I don’t know what’s worth fighting for.  Why do I scream? Why do I breath?  I finally found a cure.  Death.  Felo-De-Se.  The act of self annihilation.  I often say things that I don’t mean, but at the same time, I mean them.  Tonight I am taking my own life, painting my pain on my walls.  Blood is the letters, crimson regret is my clarity.  I have fallen into a hopeless black void.  I cannot stop my fall; tonight I shall meet the devils advocate.  I cant trust anybody.  All truth slips through the cracks in the ground, and the lies, being bigger than the truth, and in stronger numbers, is all the stays in my lost mind.  I will no longer waste myself on you.  Who is you? You is whoever is reading this, you are hardly worth my time or breath.  If you are Jill, I love you and you are worth it.  If you are anybody else, I care not about what you think of me.  Nobody listens to me.  I told you everything there is to know about me.  All my fears that I kept well hidden, all my pain and stress I kept as a goal in life, to overcome it.  As you can see, I have also failed that.  I gave you so many warnings.  But you were not listening.  I spoke so clearly to all of you, and at one point even told you my exact feelings.  You weren’t listening.  This is my session of peace of mind.  Keeping everything silent, no more voices, no more screams, no more anger, no more hate, no more hopeless dreams, no more denial.  Everything I ever did was nothing more but another mistake to you.  I tried to make everyone happy by being what he or she wanted me to be.  It overtook my soul, and I became so afraid to be myself, that I pretended to be who I was not.  Every step that I take is too much.  To much stress that has conversed upon my black heart.  I’m tired of being what you want me to be.  Its so funny how I found myself in tears day after day, wondering why I was cursed to live in this hapless world.  Why was I created? What was my purpose? Was it just to feel all this pain in my heart? I was a waste of life, a waste of air, a waste of food, of everything.  The blood is running trough my veins still, keeping me alive long enough to write this.  To express all my hurt and anger into this one letter to the world.  Ever since that first day where I gave myself paper cuts and showed everybody, someone should have known or taken a clue from that.  I had to feed the pressure in myself.  Its under my skin, tearing at me, slowly killing me.  I fed it by giving it what it wanted, crimson regret.  I keep looking over my shoulder, thinking someone is taking to me, but all it is is a new voice inside the back of my head.  So many voices I hear now.  Anger, Hate, Love, Hope, Death, God, Satan, Angels, Demons.  It’s a whirlwind inside of my head.  You people make me sick.  All these words are ignorant.  Every time you talk to me, I take one step closer to the edge of life, treating every time to jump and die.  I want you all to shut up about life.  Shut up and quit you're bitching about the world.  You don’t know how it feel's like to be like this.  Being on the edge all you're life, and finally getting to the end of you're rope keeping you safe.  Burning it to finally fall.  No matter how hard I tried, I will never see another day.  I am not sorry for what I have done.  So much trouble in my mind, I could care less about how you think of me now.     More about myself, there is a lot to say, I cannot seem to express all my feelings, all my thoughts.    I once sought to find a meaning for my existence.  I often confused what was real, thinking things that I dreamed were real, and it ends up they were not.  There is something deep inside of me that grows and grows.  I’m finally ready to unleash it.  Let the world feel my pain.  I’m falling lower and lower and confusing everything.  My walls are closing in, I can barely breath, and I feel the shadow's dept also closing in on me.    I stare up at the neo sky some nights, thinking how it would be life to finally be in that final resting place.  How it would be to go outside of this earth, and beyond.  What is beyond? Nobody knows.  But maybe, just maybe, its better than here.  I’m always wondering why to everything, instead of asking myself how?  Soon I’m going to run away from everything, and never again wonder why.  Open up my eyes to death, then close them once I take my last breath.      I don’t know what to do.  I’m so confused and lost.  I’m crying everyday.  I’m so alone.  I’m stuck on the outside.  I once felt the hate rise up from the pit of myself.  Eventually, I will be but a distant memory.  Remembered by none.  I tried so hard to make it, but everyone was always mocking me.  You would not recognize me anymore, with my true self being revealed to the world.  You never knew me.  None of you ever knew me.    I’ve always wanted to live underground.  Its strange, and I cannot explain this urge, but it would free me of my pain.  Keeping it underground, stuck beneath the earth, and by force, over take the evil energies around me and turn them into positive.  Would never feel the heat of the sun upon my pale flesh, never have to worry about daylight or darkness, just my own hallow cave.  Hiding away from the world, keeping myself hidden from everything so that no one would know I exist.  I could hurt nobody that way now could I? That’s one of the only things I’m good at now, hurting people.  I tried to let all my pain go, let it leave me and put all my trust and love into somebody.  Too many times I was hurt, too many times my trust was turned into pain and it became forged into the very core of my soul.  And now I feel like I have to run away, escape it all.  I don’t know what I will be searching for, but I know if I try hard enough, I will find it.  The moment I feel it close to me, the moment I can touch it, I will know I found it.  Ill crawl my way to it if I must.  I’m calmer than a heartbeat that is on a flat line; I fear not death or any of its ways.  I embrace the kiss of death every night, I pray I die and that death's depth will come and will me away.  There is barely any more joy's in life for me.  But I found one, sleep.  When I sleep, I feel like, I’m dead, even though it lasts but a few minutes, I seem to be in peace.  I dream so many wonderful things.  Love and happiness find there way into my mind, and I dream them.  It is amazing how happy I am when I dream, its like, I’m in another world, another dimension.  Still, when I wake up, I am forced back to reality and see that I am forced to live another day in this horrible world.  Sleep is the closest thing to death without actually meeting death. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am writing this in fear that I may not be able to express my thoughts and values further.  I have always thrived for what others wanted me to be, for what others thought would be better, but now I have finally come to the realization that the world is hell.  Trying to see the positive only brought more pain into my already tortured soul.  What positive is there to see? Love? Light? Hope?   What hope is there? Million's die every year by diseases, famine strikes the heart of every poor country, shakes and rattles the very foundation it was based upon to the ground, killing all whom live.  What else is there? Plague.    Plague will strike at any time, any day, whenever it sees fit, and will show no pity to whoever is in its path.  1665, what happened? The Great Plague stalked all of England, killing all whom it touched.  According to reports, over 100,000 people had died in pain by the year's end.  Does this seem like a world of hope and love to you?  This is but a minor plague compared to what happened in the 1300s.  One third of Europe's population was eliminated off the face of the earth that being 20 million helpless souls laid down to rest.  How can you possibly claim that this world consists of hope? Can you not realize that there is no hope for humanity?  Every year, new diseases are being introduced. Sars, The "Bird Flu", yet still relatively new, are very dangerous disease's that humanity has yet to be able to identify, and all are quick to judge another country, when the fault is obviously there own. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Death surrounds our troubled body. We feel the razor entering out broken skin, our shattered heart cries out in horrid pain as we see all the trouble going on on this insane world. Will we live long enough to meet our angel? Thou thinks not.. for thy is quite weak now... and only days remain in our once vigile life.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is such a dark world. Everything is dying, I am dying. The tree's, nature, all things beautiful, are being destroyed by no one else but humanity. How can we stand here and do nothing? Things must be done! Things must be taken into account. We shall overcome this hated evil, we must take them all. Death to all whom oppose us. For we are the damned dead, and none shall ever question our wrath again.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is a day of which I shall always remember.  Today, I have fought the demons suppressed inside of my mind, and I have vanquished them.  It was hard, I thought I would never be able to silence their screaming voices, but alas, I have.  With the help of certain people, I have vanquished these demons from my mind and have set myself free.  I have never been so happy in my life, and from this day forth, I promise to be everything you ever wanted me to be Sarah.  From now on, I am happy.  I am free. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you remember your life as a child? Do you remember all the mistakes you did? I do not.  I hardly remember a thing.  Hope? There is hope now; I can see it.  But hope for a better future? To have everything I have always dreamed of having? Never shall I have that.  I am feeling so alone in this world.  I need the love of a gracious angel to come and touch me; I need to sense it near me.    Death, my only remaining friend, can you hear me screaming? Or are you gone, like everyone else?  Please do not leave me, please, I need you, I need you to keep hold of my sanity, please, don’t go away.  Please don't go my Savior.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You took my soul.  You killed my heart with your burning ignorance.  I need to run away from you, leave the tears behind; you know there is nothing you can do.  You have broken me in many pieces.  You can never make me stay.  I must leave these tears behind, but the pain we inflict upon each other. I… we need it; we crave it.  How can I live in a world of hatred without my one true love by my side?   Death, oh holy goddess of all whom are damned, lead me to my grave. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday is a memory. Tomorrow is a vision. What can I possibly do in this messed up world that will have any meaning to anybody?  I feel as if... as if life is slowly fading away, and every day I cry crimson tears for my beloved dead comrades.  I fear not death; I fear not the scorn of what shall come to pass.  I fear but only one thing, to die without love, to die with nothing but hate inside of my heart.  Love, what is love? Love is something fabricated by man, to make you think you need it, but really, you do not.  You may be thinking I have just contradicted myself, but really, have I?  I think not, for I once felt this so called love, but now, I do not, and I shall never feel it again.  Death's sweet embrace, take me to my grave. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They say the good die young. This is true. Tupac Shakur... Rest in piece. Kato, I still miss you.  I may not have known you all person to person, but Tupac, trough your music I've been inspired to be more than what I am. You taught me to be a man, make a plan, listen to my voice. And taught me to listen to women, and give them a choice. Respect women, respect myself. You are my hero.  Soon, I will be joining you, I know it. I feel a knife puncturing my chest, and I'm having trouble breathing. I lay here crying every night, wondering why they took your life, when you were just hitting the top of your life.  We will never forget you, and I hope, when it is my time to go, they will not forget me.  Rest In Peace Tupac Rest In Peace Lisa Left Eye Rest In Peace To My Uncle Rest In Peace To Everyone Who Is Gone The Good Die Young 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hallo, how is everyone? Good? Good. Considering no one read's this... I don't even know why I write. Lately, my life has been hell. I can't take how everything is! Everyone is so negative around me, then they have the nerves to ask why I'm so negative?  I want to die.  So much.  But no one knows that, no one cares about that.   The only place I feel comfort is in my angels sweet embrace... 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kk! The point is to copy paste this and answer the questions.&nbsp; Put them in my comment button (paste them there then post so I can see :])  Gogo, Its stupid I know, and I never do these things.. but hey, once will not kill me.  gogo!  &nbsp; 1. Who are you? 2. Are we friends? 3. When and how did we meet? 4. Do you have a crush on me? 5. Would you kiss me? 6. Give me a nickname and explain why you picked it. 7. Describe me in one word. 8. What was your first impression? 9. Do you still think that way about me now? 10. What reminds you of me? 11. If you could give me anything what would it be? 12. How well do you know me? 13. When's the last time you [missed] me? 14. Ever wanted to tell me something but couldn't?  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I tell her how I feel, and what happens? She leaves.&nbsp; Yes, leaves me again.&nbsp; I can not and will not take this anymore.&nbsp; I refuse to.&nbsp; I have ceased all contact with her, and it will take alot for me to ever speak to her again.&nbsp;   &nbsp;  I am tired of being second to her.   "Why did you leave, where did you go, and leave me here with all this pain and animosity"   &nbsp;  I'm sorry I had a fucking mental breakdown.&nbsp; How would you feel if people disrespected you and spat on you any chance they got?   Its not everyday that I get to sit down and chat.&nbsp; But now I am.&nbsp; And unless someone lets me in, helps me, I might send all this madness upon society.   Im holding my breath.   Sitting with death.   He listens, he always listens.   And I swear, when I blow my brains out, everyones going to hear me now.   &nbsp;  Why do I keep breathing? I look ahead, trying to figure out why I am aloud to carry on.   Death please take me, you listen to me, please dont close your arms to me.&nbsp; I need you.&nbsp; Embrace me.... Take me.... Release me of all this pain....   &nbsp;  "I Can't remember her face"  "No one&nbsp;can take her place"     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am back to feeling how I felt around a year ago.&nbsp; Depression is sinking in faster than when the twin towers went down.&nbsp; I don't feel as if I can take this anymore.&nbsp; I don't feel as if she cares about me anymore.&nbsp; Anytime I make reference to being depressed, she brushes it off or does nothing to help me.&nbsp; Yet if someone else tells her they are depressed, then they get so much attention, she cares about them.&nbsp; I'm sick and tired of being second and being a no one to her.&nbsp; If things don't change in the coming weeks, I will take my life.   &nbsp;  As an old philosopher once said, "To live is to die and to die is to live." (Or was it a philosopher who said that? I know not anymore).    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       If ever she reads this, she will know my truest feelings.&nbsp; My heart is being torn apart, and the feelings I once felt for her are diminishing.&nbsp; I do not know what to do to make it come back.&nbsp; I’m trying everything I can to have my feelings grow back, but I cannot.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  She is amazing; she is my angel.&nbsp; I feel for her deeply, but yet, I cannot seem to express it anymore.&nbsp; Every time we speak, she annoys me.&nbsp; I know not why, but I don’t like it.    I want us to go back to how we used to be, before I started to feel this way.&nbsp; I do love her, I know it, but it is not as strong as it once was, and I fear I will lose her soon.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is death? Death is nothing more but a blessing.  Why must we all be saddened by death? Why must we all cry when someone dies?  Dry your eyes!  Know that they are now gone to a better place, whether you accept it or not.  They are away from all the terrorism, all the rapes, all the hate, and all the racisms of this world.    Like Tupac himself said, At worst, he is in a quiet place, by himself all alone.  At best… He’s an angel.  Death is so much more than you all make it seem.  Give it a second thought, a second opinion. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>