<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not sure how the rest of you are feeling, but I'm starting to have trouble staying motivated.  I am quite sure it is because of this weather...rain, rain, and more rain.  I have done the finishing touches on my letters to WBI Feild Reps ans sent them off.  I'm looking into contact information for ACOA's Partnering For Success paper, to see about the article I mentioned.    As Sheri has suggested I am checking the local paper, and little community papers (Tiny Times, Flying Cow, etc.).  I've also been watching our local community cable chanel to see if there is any potential contacts or clients...I saw one that could be promising if only I could catch the contact info one it.  I'll let you know how it goes.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My COC presentation was a bit of a bust.  Only 6 people showed up for the meeting (they usually have 20-30).  However, the people who did show up for the meeting were very interested in our program and what we have to offer.   Kris and I have finally received our new email accounts.  So I took some time to get mine organized.  I wrote a few letter to the WBI.  I am planning to contact ACOA to see if we can get an article published in their Newspaper.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am scheduled to do a presentation on Student Connections at the next Annopolis Valley Chamber of Commerce Meeting on May 20th.  However, I have been unable to get a hold of anyone to find out the meeting place and time.  So I am getting a little frustrated.  I will try to call again in the morning.  If I do not speak to anyone then I will not be doing the presentation, since I have no idea where or when it is.  I am also working on letters to see if we can form a realationship with the WIB and Nova Scotia Business Inc.    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I came into the office to discuss our plan of action for the road.  We also have a conference call at 11.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now that the weather is getting nicer the days seem to be longer than ever.  I had a meeting with Canadian Tire Service Manager and what a waste of time that was.  CT’s service staff has all the training they require and cannot see a need for our services any time in the near future.  However, RW felt it was a great program and would be very beneficial to small and medium business.  I will not be wasting any more time or theirs trying to promote Student Connections.  Kris and I attended the WVDA Open House; I think it went fairly well.  I met a few new people and chatted with the ones I had met before.  I’ll keep you posted on what develops with my new contacts.  Also I won a gift bag from the WVDA!!!  BS from NSCC customized training sent it up to me today.  I also attended the Central Annapolis Valley Chamber of Commerce meeting last night.  I have some info to send S about the Fall Lifestyles Show they are planning for September.   I am continuing work on my Seniors and Town’s Projects.  They will become my main focus for the weeks ahead.  Finally, I will also be working with client MSF starting Tuesday June 29th.  It has taken almost 4 months to arrangements to start her training.  It sure will be nice to get out of the office. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have been getting a bunch of little things done so that I call some of my projects done…or a least done for now.  I also have started a few new things.  I have a meeting next week with a Canadian Tire Auto Centre Service Manager!  Finally we are starting to make more progress arranging meetings with potential clients.  It’s a great feeling…and best of all I get to get out of the office and hit the road!    One of my new projects is Towns Project...I have been coming up with a few ideas on marketing Student Connections in this area.  Our area covers a lot of little towns, so I am working on ways that we can work with them.  It looks promising.   That’s all I have to say for now.  Have a good weekend :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I have certainly been busy!  Not that it is a bad thing it's good that things are finally picking up down here in the Valley, but I just came to the realization that I had not posted anything here since last week.  Anyway, I am working on a number of projects Canadian Tire, Real Estate Agencies, NSBI, just to name a few.    For those projects I have been writing letters, sending out kits and making new contacts, etc., etc.  I am still trying to contact MF with regards to starting her training sessions….hopefully I will touch base with her soon.  This morning I had the privilege of attending the E-Business Breakfast Seminar at the Mid-Valley Motel.  I was hoping to meet some new contacts, but I had already meet and or made contact with most of the people there.  The others I had not met took off as soon as the seminar was over.  Oh well, there will be more opportunities 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well the time in the office is flying today.  I have a number of things I am working on this week and they include: a summary of the meeting Kris and I attended yesterday, a project to make our lives a little easier (I’ll let you know more when the project is near completion).  There is also an opportunity to do a presentation at the HRSC meeting tomorrow night in Kentville…I am hoping Kris will be interested in it since he lives closer to Kentville then I do.    I must get back to my work.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is my last day with Student Connections.&nbsp; I have finished up the projects I have been working on so that Kris can easily pick up where&nbsp; I left off.&nbsp;&nbsp;Working with Student Connections has been&nbsp;a good experience for me and I do hope it is the same for the rest of you.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Have a good one :)  Kristine 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>