<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let it be known to the internet world that I consider myself to be a great music connoisseur.  I love almost every facet of the music world, because I have different moods and tastes that require different genres to satisfy my needs.  I recently recieved an iPod for my past birthday, and I listen to it every single stinking day, because I love music that much.  Anyways, there's this blog that I read by an old friend of mine, and he posted a Summer mix tape list of songs that he's listening to.  I think his musical tastes "taste" more like elephant poop, so I'm posting the following list:   The Musical Albums of My World (For This Week or Longer)    Death in Vegas - Scorpio Rising :  I found this by accident while shopping on the iTunes store.  I loved Death in Vegas when they came out with their single "Dirt" waaay back in 1996 or 1998 (somewhere in there), and I figured I'd see what they came out with recently.  I didn't realize that they were responsible for that great opening song in "Lost in Translation" - which is known as "Girls" on this album. I wound up buying the real album for $20 at FYE (which pissed me off b/c it was a lot of money, but worth it).  Other songs worthy of my greatest praise are  Hands Around My Throat, Scorpio Rising, 23 Lies, So You Say You Lost Your Baby, and Help Yourself.    Zero 7 - Simple Things :  I listened to this album 5 times a day for 387 days, starting in the Summer of 2002 and not ending until the Summer after that.  This is one of the greatest albums of all-time.  These two guys (and their various guest vocalists) do a perfect job of creating a mellow feeling with the entire album.  To borrow from the title, it's simply beautiful to listen to.  MTV did an MTV2 preview of what was popular music on their channel in the spring of 2002, and Zero 7's  "Destiny"  caught my attention.  These are my favorite artists of all-time right now, and though I don't listen to this album as much as I used to, I can still listen to the entire CD whenever I get a chance to.  Other songs worthy of my greatest praise are:  I Have Seen, Simple Things, Likufanele, This World, Spinning, In the Waiting Line, End Theme, and Salt Water Sound.    Zero 7 - When It Falls :  This is their follow-up album, and I would dare to say that it's just as good, if not better than, their first effort.  Awesome mellow tracks include:  Warm Sound, Home, Somersault, Over Our Heads, Passing By, When it Falls, Speed Dial No. 2, and Morning Song.   Zero 7 is the perfect band to listen to when the sun is shining and the days are perfect, that's the best way I can put it.  Their music is an experience.   The Darkness - Permission To Land :  This is the best friggin' rock band to come out in years.  This album blows me away every time that I listen to it, as the guitar riffs and the vocals really make this band sound badass.  Check out  Black Shuck, I Believe in a Thing Called Love (best song on the album), Love is Only a Feeling, Friday Night, Get Your Hands Off My Woman, and Stuck in a Rut.    Beck - Midnite Vultures :  Best Beck album.  Ever.  I can't think of an artist that embraces experimentation and evolution more than this guy does.  Listen to these if you get a chance:   Sexx Laws, Nicotine & Gravy, Get Real Paid, Mixed Bizness, Peaches and Cream, Debra (best song on the album), and Pressure Zone.   That's what is playing in my car right now.   My musical taste rocks your world.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up this morning feeling a little bit guilty about my last post.  Sometimes I feel like I'm anti-mom, and I'm really not.  I really love my mom like a good son does (but you can ask anybody that knows me:  I'm not a momma's boy).  As I continue to endure the endless world of job-hunting/subbing, one of the best things that my mom has done for me is something that happens every day:  Mom:  Where did you teach today?  Me:  I taught at (school's name) for (teacher's name), in a (grade level) class.  Mom:  Who's (teacher's name)?   Author's note:  I have absolutely no idea why she asks this question.  The only teachers she knows are teachers that I or my other siblings have had.  I think that she asks this just to piss me off because I'll actually take the time to answer and explain the person that I sub for, and the only reply I get is a one-word answer that serves as my trophy for being stupid enough to think that she cares.   Mom:  Well, did you teach  quality  today?  And this is where I feel like a payoff occurs.  This is the point of the conversation where all frustration or miscommunication between myself and my mother is worth every single ounce of pain.  This one question gets me every time, because the concept of quality is something that we both place a great deal of value in.  We owe it all to a local professor over at Monroe Community College, who teaches a class designed around a single book by an author named  Robert Pirsig .  The book,   Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance  , is about a man's journey to discover himself, as well as his desire to answer the question "what is best?".  This is a very philosophical novel that requires a lot of re-reading, but I think that this book changed my life.  Now my mother and I didn't take this class together (that's creepy), but we did take it almost 13 years apart with the same teacher, and we're both amazed at how much has remained the same.    Among these deep questions and issues that the main character tries to deal with in the story, there is a concept repeated or implied throughout the story, which is that of quality and what quality actually is.  It's one thing for people to go to work and simply leave unfinished projects as soon as it's time to go home.  A 9 to 5 job for most people literally begins at 9 am and literally ends (everything is dropped) at 5pm.  On the other hand, we have people whom practice quality, people that leave work when the work is done for the day.     If you ever get an opportunity to read this book, I strongly encourage you to do so, because many of you will be changed for the better.    This book is my bible to living a good life.  That's how committed I am  to what's being said here.    Now, I may border on being crazy to some of you, but if you're interested in any sort of philosophy, or if you read to be challenged as a thinker, then this is what you need.  Too often, we forget about quality in our work as well as our personal lives.  We work for the sake of getting a paycheck and we're content to do the minimum just to get by.  If every educator simply relied on passing out worksheets, giving notes, and giving exams were the only aspects required of teaching (some would say that they already are), then anybody could truly claim to be a teacher.  To me, there aren't enough teachers that can teach quality to their students.  I am planning on re-reading this book within the coming Summer months, and I plan on writing about it more during that time.  If you have read this book and want to discuss it, please feel free to contact me.   And what is good, Phaedrus, and what is not good - Need we ask anyone to tell us these things?  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been engaged since Christmas Eve, so I've just crossed the five-month plateau, and I've only got thirteen months remaining until the big day.  Sometimes I wish that I could get married tomorrow because the wait is absolutely excruciating for the both of us.  It's during times like these that I wish that everybody with an opinion was a mute and that they were overly agreeable with any ideas presented by either myself or my fiance.    As we have planned our big day, I've noticed that there are a lot of times similar to that of a roller coaster: there are ups, downs, and crap where you get spun around, flipped upside down and left feeling very nauseous.  We've got the church (hers, and it's growing on me - I'm not the religious one anyways); we've got the reception location (a very nice golf club that will look very prestigious in June - our choice that we made together); we're doing a sit-down dinner instead of a buffet (my suggestion - and it grew on her after a while); we've got the band (again, my choice); we've got the photographer (her choice); and we've got the florist and invitations being covered by our mothers (just to keep them happy - for about five minutes).  The major point of contention right now is the actual wedding ceremony.  According to my fiance, I'd be fine showing up, exchanging our vows, and being done with the whole thing in ten minutes.  I'm also more concerned with the reception than I am with the ceremony (according to her).  We aren't Catholic, so the wedding isn't officially mandated to be longer than an episode of Law & Order without commercials.  So I guess, in a way, I am not looking to drag the ceremony out.  Look at this from my perspective.  I've dated this woman for over five years now, and by the time we get married, it will be over six.  I don't want to have a super long ceremony when I've been waiting for six years to finally marry her.  I want to get this over with relatively quickly because it's been six years of NOT living together, NOT living in the same home, and NOT being able to spend all of our down time together in the same place.  I'm tired of playing by the rules.  To make matters even worse, my mother and future mother in-law each have their own ideas about how to drag this process on even longer, as if they're secretly saying  "I want you to wait as long as you can until you take out a gun and shoot yourself in the head in the middle of the church."   With my mother (she's the worst right now - but it's died down a little), she would like to hire a soloist to sing these songs that I have NEVER EVEN HEARD OF!  It would be one thing to sing songs that have a significant meaning to us, but my Mom wants to hear "The Water is Wide".    THE WATER IS FREAKING WIDE?!?!?    My mother is from space.  That's the only answer I can come up with.  We're also in "discussions" with the apparent need for a Scottish bagpipe soloist (because Mommy's Scottish), so I guess while this lady stranger is singing songs, the bagpipe guy will really rip one on his pipes.  One thing that needs to be said about bagpipes is that the words "bagpipe" and "solo" do not go together.  It has the tendency to sound like a family of dying cats if played incorrectly.  Oh, and since I'm half Scottish, apparently it would be nice if I wore a quilt (which I thought would be cool - until my fiance shot it down).  No big deal.  Now my mother in-law has been a saint for the whole engagement.  She takes my side in every argument because I do the same for her whenever the opportunity arises.  She's been rumbling lately because she really wants us to do Communion at the ceremony.  I will not do communion, period.  I don't believe that crackers or wine/juice are adequate symbols for Jesus, and I don't care what the Bible says about it.  The church that we're getting married in doesn't provide fancy bread either.  We would get oyster crackers.  How the hell can oyster crackers even come close to representing the body of Jesus?  They don't even represent his toenails in my mind.    So there we have it.  People think that I want a ten minute wedding ceremony because I hate church and I'm more concerned with the party afterwards.  In a way, they're certainly right, but they're right for the wrong reasons.  I'll do ONE soloist, two or three readings by family/friends, exchanging of the vows, and maybe some prayers.  I'm all about class as much as the next guy, but I don't like overkill.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Welcome to My Entertainment World   I feel like talking about what I'm doing right now for entertainment.  I don't want to file entertainment entries under a different blog title, because that takes too much effort.  So, any entries that deal with movies, DVDs, videogames, or anything else of the sort will be filed under the title   My Entertainment World   (or until I come up with a better title).  First up, let's talk about what's going to be the best movie of the summer.  Go to the link above to watch the trailer for Napoleon Dynamite.  From what I can tell, the film is by a first-time director and it won the national comedy festival award for independent films.  It was also an entry into Sundance.  Now, before you dismiss this movie as a sappy drama, it isn't anything close to that.  I can't remember I saw an independent comedy movie (a legit comedy) with as much promise as this one shows.  Napoleon Dynamite is a high school nerd who is out to prove to himself that he can pick up chicks, be popular, and make friends.  Supposedly, it's a salute to the pubescent years of every member of Generation X.  Watch the trailer for yourself at the link mentioned here, and you'll go see it on June 11th too.  On the DVD front, I picked up two titles yesterday worth mentioning.  First up, we have The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King (my favorite).  So we have the best novels of the last century made into the best movie trilogy ever (thanks to George Lucas ruining the previous "best trilogy" in Star Wars).  I watched it last night, thinking to myself how I am going to watch the whole trilogy this coming weekend.  I had trouble staying awake for one movie, so I can't imagine how I would last all 11 hours watching the two extended editions and ROTK.  If the whole journey of Frodo Baggins and the Fellowship of the Ring took 13 months to complete, from the leaving of the Shire until the destruction of the ring, I wouldn't last one freaking day out there in Middle Earth, because I'd die in my sleep.  Some Orc would kill me while napping.  The other DVD I picked up was Office Space, which I realize has been out on DVD forever.  I owned the VHS version back in the day, and I loved this movie, but haven't watched it in a few years.  It still holds up against the test of time, including Samir and Michael Bolton (not THAT one).  They are hilarious and steal every scene that they appear in.  Mike Judge should make a movie about them next time.  This movie represents every working man's (and woman's) natural feelings towards hating their jobs and their bosses, and how we all ultimately desire to do nothing.  Okay, it's late and I need to finish watching Deadwood on HBO.  Best. Western. Ever.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So within the last couple of weeks, most all of the school districts in the Monroe County area of Upstate NY passed their school budgets, allowing school districts to move forward in the hiring process.  This past week, I've heard rumblings from several different schools expressing interest in me that I'm in the hunt for several positions.  Now before people start asking me to check my ego at the door, I'll stop you right there because I already have.  In my frame of mind, I try to follow the Buddhist belief of remaining in the present moment, and having expectations of the future would come at the expense of this moment (I'll save that explanation for a future post).  In short, I'm more interested in enjoying the substitute opportunities that I have for the rest of the school year.  When the Fall comes, there is nothing I can do to stop it.  Whether or not I have a job is the least of my concern.    Since the end of the school year is approaching, it's important to know that sick time for teachers does NOT roll over and accumulate from year to year.  You have something like 10 sick days and 5 personal days to use each year, period.  If you have perfect attendance for 10 years and you run into some emergency that requires a year off, you don't get to use sick days (rather, you get to benefit from tenure :) ).  So towards the end of the school year (like right around now) - teachers are taking days off left and right.    Anyways, as I am enjoying these last few weeks of school, I am encountering more and more substitute teachers.  Every time I meet one, I feel like it's easier for me to relate to them because I am also looking for a permanent job in a school.  Subbing is fun, but it sucks at the same time.  We share war stories about classes to avoid, how our job hunts are going, and things like that.  These are people that I meet maybe once or twice in my life, but we already know each other in way.  That's the nice side of me when I meet other subs.  The mean side of me wants to paint their faces with animal blood and then dunk their heads in a shark tank.  Any time I meet or even look at another sub, I feel like I'm the wife who's been cheated on by her husband and I'm sizing up the piece of trash my husband left me for.  I can honestly feel myself giving these subs the once over and passing final judgement on them within seconds.  I've judged other subs by what they wear  ("JUST A BUTTON DOWN SHIRT AND KHAKIS? WHERE IS YOUR TIE?!?!") , and I've judged by seeing them teach (don't even get me started on some of these people).  The way that I look at it, every sub that I see is both a friend and an enemy.  I want you to complain to me about your class, or about the places you've worked so that I may offer you comfort and support.  But I also want to hear about these things so that I can get a leg up on you in our "competition", which is why you will never hear a negative peep out of me when it comes to anything related to a school district.  Oh I do complain sometimes, like when I blog or when I vent to my fiance, but it never goes further than that.    So essentially, one of the biggest fundamentals of job hunting is to find out as much information from your competition as you can so that you may be able to get a leg up on them when it comes to interviewing for potential positions.  I guess the saying that you should keep your friends close and your enemies closer is more true that I thought it was.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since  I'm a teacher, I obviously have chosen a career that focuses primarily on working with young children on a daily basis.  Whenever I go to the movie theater, the happy thoughts that I have when it comes to kids are usually replaced with homicidal rage.    When I am at the movie theater, for roughly 90 minutes to a maximum of 240 minutes, I love what's on the movie screen more than anything else in the existence of the universe.  Previews?  I'd give up my fiance for them.  The movie itself?  Take my future children.  Whenever I am "graced" (and I use the term loosely) by the presence of any number of 18-month to 15 year-olds, I seriously want to rip out every one of my fingernails and bludgeon my own toes with a sledgehammer.  I purposfully avoid seeing movies any earlier than 10pm in my town, but the catch-22 is that my fiance falls asleep at 9:30 every night, which practically nullifies any sort of movie theater excursions.  The problem with any G or PG rated movie is that the little kids always have to go to the bathroom, and it's never just once.  The small families that go with mom or dad all have to go the bathroom at once because the parent thinks that coordinating bathroom trips will actually cut down on the need to go potty.  This is a parenting urban legend that is based on lies and continually spread by single people in order to make the lives of parents more miserable.  Kids will pee whenever they need to go, and they consistantly strive to go at different times from their siblings in order to gain the full attention of mom or dad.  The problem with any other type of movie is that teenagers simply go to these kinds of movies to socialize.  Gone are the sleepovers or rollerskating rinks that were popular community staples of the 70's and 80's.  Kids don't have anyplace to hang out anymore, and I can't say that I blame parents for wanting to get these kids out of their hair for the evening.  Dropping off 30 of them to ruin my evening of watching "50 First Dates" is not the solution to their problem.  Every time I see a group of teenagers at the movies, I cringe.  I literally feel myself wither up and die on the inside of my body, wanting to forget all of my previous encounters with this age group in a theater setting.  All of the loud conversations, stupid jokes, and their constant getting up to leave the movie, only to come back five minutes later makes me wish that I had a tranquilizer gun to shoot at every kid that pisses me off during a film.  People may criticize me for being too harsh on parents, or for forgetting that I too was once a teenager.  To the parents, all I can offer is that promise that I always avoid going to see a kid film during kid hours.  When my fiance told me that we were going to see Shrek 2 yesterday (Sunday) at 3:30pm, I wanted to shoot her face off with a missile laucher for not consulting me about the time.  The kids were very well behaved considering the film was sold out and there were no empty seats.  To the teenagers, I offer no sympathy for my ill-feelings towards them.  As I was once a teenager, movies served but one purpose for me back in the day: making out.  Go to the movies with someone you like, sit behind me, and kiss each other the whole time.  I won't tell anybody, I swear.  I'm not being creepy either, as I would gladly prefer the quiet subtleties of passionate kissing to the loud raunchiness of being a complete moron with no social skills.   Author's Note:  Actually, now that I think about it, making out is the absolute LAST thing that I want to see two teenagers doing at a movie theater.  There is only one thing in life that is more disgusting than watching a man having his flesh ripped from his bones by a pack of wolves, and that's watching two awkward teenagers pretending that they know how to make out in public.  Stick with silence during the movies kids. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the real world, I'd like to think of myself as somewhat of a movie buff.  I have a strong appreciation for many different films of all genres, and that's something that I take a lot of pride in.  The humbling factor about all of this is that I know that somewhere in this world, there are about two to ten million  other people whom are actually more qualified at calling themselves 'movie buffs' than I am.  Once in a while, a great movie will slip by my presence unnoticed; journeying from the screens of movie theaters, to the shelves of movie stores, and finally winding up in discounted DVD bins.  The movie that I 'discovered' this past weekend was director Richard Kelly's first effort "Donnie Darko".  I picked this up at my local FYE (For Your Entertainment) for $14.99, and I proceeded to watch it three times in a 48 hour period.  I was blown away by the content and the presentation every single time.  The last time I paid this much attention to a movie was with Sam Mendes' "American Beauty" back in 1999,   and even though I may just be in the heat of the moment, but I think that DD is as good, IF NOT BETTER THAN American Beauty.    Donnie Darko stars Jake Gyllenhaal as the title character, and the film primarily concerns itself with one major concept: time travel.  Think of the Back to the Future trilogy as you know it, but make Marty McFly a private school teenager with a lot of angst, a tendency to sleepwalk, and emotionally disturbed.  Throw in the presence/guidance of Frank the evil bunny as the replacement for Christopher Lloyd's Doc Brown, and you've got yourself a very dark Back to the Future.    I've tried to explain this movie to my fiance and to several co-workers this morning, but I just can't find the right words that do this film justice.  It's about time travel and insanity, justice and sacrifice, and what would a movie be without the classic comic book 'save the universe' dilemma?  After watching DD for the third time last night, I went to www.donniedarko.com and completed a some questions/activities to access materials that make the movie more understanding.  I love stuff like this, where I have to build a bridge between the movie and the internet (or other resources) in order to further comprehend what's going on in the film.  If there is ever an opportunity for you to at least watch this film, do not pass it up.  As I watched it, I couldn't help but be reminded of movies like Memento because they both rely so much on the precision of their plotlines.  This is a thinking-man's (or woman's) movie, and I urge you to watch it if you can.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I swear sometimes I just want to hit a wall...  As I am both a man and someone who is trying to climb a career ladder in a profession where you need to be a role-model 24 hours a day, seven days a week, I understand and accept the fact that I am bound to behave in certain ways over others.  I accept the fact that I need to model to other people (especially students) how other people should be treated, and that I can demonstrate and exemplify kindness and respect.  As a man, I understand that I have to be especially courteous to women and other gender stereotypes like that.  What I can't understand for the life of me...what makes me want to snap every time it happens (not because it happened in the first place, but because I am seeing it more and more on a daily basis) is the lack of respect or appreciation demonstrated by other people.  To me, it seems like to many other people feel like I  owe  something to them, as if I should feel priviledged for helping them out.  It seems like Upstate NY (the Rochester area) is a breeding ground for this sort of apathy, and it just makes me sick.  Case-in-point:  As a student teacher this past December, I was teaching at a school in a rough city neighborhood.  It was my first day of "solo week" (where the student teacher does literally everything on his or her own), and I spent the entire night before traveling back from Florida on an airplane only to spend the next 4 hours at a hospital with my fiance's mother, whom suffered from a pendacitis.  I get to school at 7am on a Monday morning just so I could finish planning my week and set things up.  I remember it was a cold and snowy commute that day.  Anyways, as I was walking through the cold, dark parking lot, I managed to step on an old hanger that went through my boot and into my foot.  As I tried to assess the damage of my foot (by gently pulling on it before wincing in pain), three employees managed to walk right by me without saying a word, asking if I was okay, or offering to help pick up my belongings which were at this point soaking wet in a puddle of black slush.  As far as general appreciation goes, I'd like to think of myself as an appreciative person.  I always go out of my way to thank people when they do anything for me, because I know that they don't owe me anything.  What I can't understand as why people think it's okay to just tell me to do something without asking nicely or showing a little bit of gratitude once I agree to do it.  Being a sub is only two letters away from being a scrub, and sometimes it just bugs me.  I enjoy working with so many people in the buildings that I sub for, but sometimes people will just stand in front of me and bark orders.  Even when I agree to do something, I never get a thanks, or a "Hey, I appreciate what you're doing."  Mind you, it's never the whole crowd, but there are always a few rotten apples.  I'm sorry about my rant, but I just wish that there were more opportunities for people to share their appreciation for one-another.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm substituting today at a local elementary school in this third grade class, and I'm having the best day of my short career, as these kids are behaving fantastically, and we're not having any behavior problems.  Here I am, teaching the kids, and they're soaking up everything that we do together.  It's literally perfect for me and for them, and four different students come up to me at different points of the day with cards for me or simply to tell me that I'm the best sub that they ever had.  I don't go into classrooms trying to be the best friend a student has ever had (that's what pedophiles or bad teachers do), but I'm confident that I present a likable and friendly persona that will come down on people who choose to make bad decisions.  Anyways, I heard in the news today that a few teachers in six different states across America are on some sort of leave of absence from their respective school districts after showing the full video of the Nicholas Berg's beheading to their own students.  This is the controversial video that almost every television station across the country refused to air due to its grusome content.  A man pleads for mercy as he his freaking head is cut off!  Now, it's my guess that the teachers that showed this video (made available by internet sites) must have shown this to high school students.  It's also my guess that these teachers wanted their students to think for themselves when it comes to why we are fighting the war in Iraq.  What I'm struggling with is why these teachers thought it was okay to expose these kids to this.  I've never seen a real beheading, nor have I seen somebody murdered in real life or on television (movie violence doesn't count).  I served on a jury in a murder case two Summers ago, and that was when I saw pictures of my first murder victim, as well as my first autopsy photos.  Why would a teacher want to share something so horrible with their students?  Talking about the incident would have served the same purpose, wouldn't it?  Kids would have started a dialogue on violence in the middle east and our role in this war.  What's the point of the video?  It's at times like this that I'm glad that I don't feel the need to overlap my personal beliefs with my job as an educator.  Whether I believe in this war or not, it's my job to present a balanced objective when talking about war with children.  Their will always be pros and cons to it, as there is with everything else in this universe.     However, part of me wishes that several of these teachers lost their jobs here in Rochester, so that I could apply for their jobs.  Just because I can remain objective doesn't mean that I will pass up on an opportunity to climb the ladder! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I'm sorry that these blogs have been so serious and intense.  Blogging is the best because I can gripe about the state of our country's ignorance in one post and talk about videogames in another.    Which brings me to my 4th blog today:  the biggest travesty in videogaming as I know it thusfar.  The game I'd like to talk about is   Medal of Honor: Rising Sun  .  I don't care what system you play it on (I own the PS2 version myself), but this game didn't get a fair shake from the moment that it was released.    If you check out www.gamerankings.com, type in the title of this game and check out the results for yourself.  Game Rankings is a great site that takes review scores for a certain game and averages them all together to come up with an average score.  The average score for Rising Sun was a paltry 68%; a mediocre game at best.  As a fan of the Medal of Honor games (for the Playstation 1 and Playstation 2), I eagerly waited for this game to come down to $19.99 before buying it.  Hey I'm a fan of the series, but I'm not a rich one.  I finally bought it on Ebay two weeks ago for $17 and when I played it, I was blown away by how unfairly this game was treated by the media.  They complained that the game felt too controlled by the levels in the sense that they were progressing on rails, meaning that they couldn't wander off course at any given point.  There was also a lot of flack given for the game's graphics and the AI of the enemy soldiers.  After playing this game for over a week now and as a lifelong fan of the Medal of Honor franchise, this game did not let me down by any means, and I feel that it got a bum rap.  As an unemployed and engaged teacher, my time is quite limited and I don't have time to get lost in games that take place in these huge worlds where I get to create my own path.  Not for nothing, but who the hell would want the ability to go off the beaten path while fighting in the Pacific countries during WWII, especially if you're an American solider?  If you wander around in the jungle, you're going to find more jungle...and snakes.  Big, poisonous snakes that would eat you and your family of six for breakfast after your limbs fall off from one drop of snake venom.  Thanks, but no thanks.  My army arse is going right where my commanding officer sends me.  Also, with a game that tells me where to go and what I need to do, I can eliminate a lot of the guessing games that make me wonder "what the heck do I do next" in so many games these days.  I don't have time for this crap.  Sometimes blowing up bridges and escorting tanks through hostile villages is all I really need.    This brings me to my next point as to why this game got a raw deal:  the graphics.  When you are shooting guns out in the jungle, chances are you are going to be dealing with a lot of trees and other vegetation.  Not only are trees a popular fixture of jungle culture, but dirt and rocks are too.  Sometimes the little rocks get together in a huge pile called a mountain.  In all seriousness, I don't understand how this game is faulted for trying to portray as much of these foreign environments as they can.  It's a solid effort on all levels.    You know what else I love about this game?  The multiplayer levels.  I'm not even talking about online play here, because I hate playing online and getting schooled by 12 year-olds.  I like to look my opponents in the face when I compete against them.  The multiplayer levels in Rising Sun are freaking huge, like at least a square-mile huge.  I can shoot my 10 year-old brother in the face from a mile away in this game!    So regardless of what the media may say about this game (half of the sites that reviewed this game are lucky, L-U-C-K-Y to even be associated with the word "media", this game succeeds in keeping the honor in Medal of Honor.  Thanks to EA Games for showing me what was going on on the other side of the world while we were fighting in Normandy.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like I've spent a lot of time talking about my pending nuptuals in the first two blogs, and I'd like to talk about something else that's bugging the bejesus out of me.  It seems to me that a lot of people (like the majority of America) is all up in arms about the newest fad for weddings.  Of course, I'm talking about the gay marriages that have started in Massachusetts.  According to a www.foxnews.com poll, 54,740 people feel that Mass. is  dead wrong  about their approval of gay marriage, while the 13,000 voters either approved of this (about 5,000 and change) or simply didn't care (5,000 and change as well).  Now the poll conducted at Foxnews.com states that it't nowhere near considering these results as scientific, but judging by the public outcry, I can't imagine that these percentages are terribly skewed out of proportion.   Now before I start ranting and raving, I'd like to point out that I'm a registered Republican.  Yep, I'm a proud member of the Grand Ol' Party (GOP) and I don't plan on switching affiliations anytime soon.  However, I am becoming increasingly disenfranchised with this party and where it is choosing to stand.  I hate taxes.  I hate having the government take money out of my paycheck to provide services that I don't qualify for.  While I do realize that this is a necessary evil in our society, I also accept that if my situation met the right criteria, I know that I could qualify for these services.  But it doesn't mean that I have to like them right now.  Many would say this qualifies me as being fiscally conservative, but all I'm saying is that I'd like to keep the money that I make.  When we approach the sensitive topic of morality in the USA, I feel like so many of our citizens feel that we're going to Hell and never looking back.  They cry out that God is gone from our schools and public offices and that we need to stop being a secular nation.  They feel that by allowing for two homosexuals to actually marry, our family values are futher eroding from under our feet.    While I may be a tad on the stingy side about money, I am thankful on a daily basis that I am not one of these people.  I am even more greatful that there aren't more of these people actually running the country.  Not for nothing people, but American marriage is on the rocks and it will continue to be this way until we can teach our youth how sex is about quality and not quantity, as well as the importance of commitment.    If we're looking at almost 55% of today's marriages ending within 3-5 years, I say that we let gay and lesbian couples get married.  I would give two gay men from New York City higher odds of staying  happily married  for a very long time over the white teenage trash that gets married because the kid knocks up his girlfriend.  Marriage is supposed to be a sacred vow that so many heterosexual couples have thrown to the ground and crapped on, I think it's time that we let someone else show us how it's done.  How can a culture (or sexual preference) possibly try to justify their control over the bond of love when their own people have no idea how to abide by it?  I don't know a lot of gay people, but I was thinking the other day.  For the handful of homosexual people that I know, they have had significantly fewer partners (like 1 or 2) over the past five years than most of my straight friends.  If the commitment is there, then why can't they be officially recognized as being married?  I don't like thinking about two men or two women having sex any more than the next guy, but I don't like thinking about most other couples I know having sex either.    Or maybe these finatics are just afraid of being exposed to this super-sexual lifestyle.  Obviously if you're gay, you like to have sex as often as you can,  and even in public places!   Maybe there is a fear that enough of this exposure will turn other people's wives or daugthers, husbands or sons into homosexuals themselves.  I suppose that I should be thankful that I have millions of bible-loving Christians looking out for my well-being when it comes to homosexuality, but lucky for me, I have the ability to think for myself on this one.    It's situations like this that make me thankful to live in the country that we live in today.  Even if there are laws introduced by Bush (the biggest church puppet short of the pope) or Pat Robertson and his 700 club, our system of checks and balances is good enough to overrule that sort of law within 5 years after it goes into effect.  To all people that are pro-marriage (whether you're gay or not), please know that this guy is cheering for you and your right to be married.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got engaged this past Christmas Eve to my girlfriend of five years.  I graduated with my BA in Education on 12/12 when I finished my student teaching, and the promise that I always made to my girlfriend was that I would propose to her after we were both done with college.  Anyways, my fiance said yes (obviously), and one of the most suprising things about our engagement and the planning of our future together came to me out of the blue:  I actually forced myself to say goodbye to the majority of my childhood.  You see, in college (and for most of my teenage years), I built up  quite  a collection of action figures and videogames from various systems.  Since I went to college from 1998-2003, I was fortunate enough to be able to spend all of my money on some of the coolest toys and game systems around.  On the toy front, I had a formidable Todd McFarlane Spawn action figure collection that got up to around 50-60 figures.  I collected those, along with many other McFarlane brands for about 3 or 4 years, ending with the Tortured Souls series I in 2001.  I proudly displayed these toys for years on my shelves throughout my room, claiming that the child within me would never grow up and that I would never willingly seperate myself from them.  And then I got engaged.  One of the great perks of marrying my best friend is the fact that we finally get to shop for a house this coming fall.  We've never lived together (because we try to play by the rules/please our parents), so this is an exciting time for us.  As I've been looking for a job as a substitute teacher, I've had a lot of time to sort through a lot of my belongings and ultimately I felt that I didn't really need most of these things anymore.  So I listed about 90% of my toy collections on ebay, along with many of my old Playstation and Playstation 2 games that I don't play anymore, thus freeing up a myriad of space that I wouldn't have had in my first house anyways.  In a way, I was sad to let these things go because I felt like I was letting go of my youth.  I sold my entire WWF Jakks Wrestling figure collection for like $90.  Wrestling was such an important source of entertainment for me in my youth, and I didn't want to sell these at first.  When I realized that I hate where the WWE has gone these days, it was easier for me to list it on ebay.  I'm realizing now that marriage isn't about finding someone to put up with all of my stuff and finding a place to display it.  I'm looking forward to creating a home of our own with our own stuff: a place for us to exist.    But that doesn't mean that I'm giving up my Wacky Wobbler or Marvel Legends collections.  A guy can only get rid of so much when it comes to saying goodbye to his youth.    And the same goes for my Playstation 2, Gamecube, Dreamcast, Nintendo 64, Super Nintendo, Nintendo (THE TOP LOADER!), Playstation, and my Gameboy, as well as all of my games too.  Come to think of it... maybe I'm not saying goodbye, but upgrading in my tastes.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having graduated with a major in English Literature, I can guarantee that 99% of everything that I have ever read or a story that I have heard from birth until this very moment has centered around a hero of some sort.  Whether or not the hero is male, female, a group of people, good, evil, the notions remain the same:  there is a problem of some sort and it always threatens the well-being of one or more protagonists.  And this is where your hero is born.  This is where I get to come in, and I don't even know why I am here at all.  All I know for sure is that I saw a story on Fox News last week about Google going public, and that Google also owned Blogger.com, which prompted me to check out what's going on with this site since I have always wanted a blog of my own.  I don't even know whom this blog is being written for, since anybody can seem to access it, yet I never have been one to point out to others "Hey, check this out!  Look at what I have created!"  I suppose that this is here for me, and maybe even for those of you whom share in similar ideas or notions.  Currently, I am a recent college graduate and I'm looking for employment in the wonderful field of childhood education.  I am a large, hulking monseter (6'6" - 280 lbs.) with a degree in Elementary Education and English, and the job market here in Rochester, NY for teachers is more competitive than a litter of baby wolves vying for their mother's milk.  While I'm searching for this job of jobs (the one that I will be happy at for the rest of my life - wink, wink), I decided to also get engaged to my best friend and start looking for houses.  So, you're probably thinking "What's the point of this garbage?"  To me, it's simply a place to start.  As we have all started the first days of school with ice breakers and introductions, this is in a sense all I really know.  The best is yet to come.  Here is a place where I can finally post my opinions and whatever else I'd like to, and though you may not be able to tell, I am extremely happy that I found this place and not some stupid online forum.  Again, welcome to my new blog.  It'll be a fun ride, I swear.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a few days since writing my last blog (about 4, I believe).  I need to fix my lack of updates, and hopefully this "promise" to the many people who do not read my blog anyways will force me to adhere to it.  Anyways, my last post focused on the fact that I didn't get the job that I applied for, and mostly how I was disappointed with not being notified about this decision.  Anyways, in the days that transpired since writing that piece, I have come to realize that I am a full-fledged I-D-I-O-T.  Why?  I checked my cell phone voice mail this past Friday for the first time in a week, and what did I find?  I freaking 4 minute message that couldn't have been more professional from the assistant principal whom interviewed me.  Now I have NO idea how my cell phone came into his possession, but I felt approximately "this big" (makes half inch gap with finger and thumb).    Whether it was my never-ending persuit of quality or just my sense of guilt, I sent a thank-you letter that same day to the assistant principal, wishing him the best of luck for the upcoming school year.   This cell phone thing really perplexes me though.  I'll write more about this tomorrow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My job interview went well on Monday, and I know that I was one of four or five candidates for this position.  I knew everybody on the committee, and therefore I felt very comfortable during the interview.  What threw me off was when the Assistant Principal informed me that he would call with news by  no later than Wednesday morning.   So this morning came and went (in addition to a very long Tuesday).  I felt like a lawyer after making my final summation before the case is turned over to the jury.  There I was, trying to prove my innocence, my worth to a committee of seven people.  Six women and one man.  Five teachers, one consultant teacher, and one Assistant Principal.  Seven Caucasian people (at least I think they all were).  These people were charged with determining whether or not my argument, my case, was either fact or fiction.  Did I mention how the wait was torture?  It's common knowledge that the longer the jury takes to deliberate, the more likely a defendant is found "not guilty".  If you are looking for a conviction, you want a jury to be quick and relentless to come to their decision, so that there is no time to actually think things over and discuss them.  You want your evidence to be so overwhelming that the jury is convinced beyond a reasonable doubt that you are good enough to work with them.  The longer the wait, the greater the chance that you won't get the conviction that you are looking for.   These thoughts rang true tonight...   At about 7 PM, a good friend phoned my fiance with news that one of the jury members was introduced to the new long-term sub today (the job that I applied for).  Needless to say, it was not me whom met this woman.  What really made this sting for me is that somebody took the time to phone this candidate and inform her of her success, took the time to introduce her as the newest edition to this team of teachers,  and yet not one ounce of effort was made to inform me via the telephone of my position with the team.  Nobody took the time to actually keep their promise of letting me know where I stood with these teachers, with this school by the Wednesday morning deadline.   That stung.  A lot.    It's not that I don't approve of their selection.  She's a great person and obviously the "jury" felt that they were doing what was best for the school.  She has more experience than I, and since I know her, I believe that her selection was the right way to go.  I don't harbor any ill-will towards the committee either, as many of them were a pleasure to work with as a sub, and two of them even knew me from when I was in kindergarten!  These are great teachers and it is obvious to me that they know what they are doing.  I support their decision as much as I support them.  What I don't support is the fact that I had to find out about my fate from a third-party.  A source that heard on a whim about this situation during a chance meeting at a picnic.  If she hadn't heard about this then, would I still be waiting for a phone call, wondering about my fate tomorrow or the next day?  Would a phone call ever come?  A letter?  Anything?  At least I was fortunate enough to receive the verdict.  Now I can wash my hands of this situation and move on with the rest of my Summer.  Something will work out.  I know it will.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that my Summer vacation is officially here, I have no idea what to do with my time.  I have too much free time for the next two weeks, as my summer job doesn't start until after July 4th.  Today will be a day spent with videogames, reading (Alice Sebold's  The Lovely Bones  which is awesome), and perhaps a viewing of Kill Bill again on DVD.  See?  My days are as long as they are boring.  This is actually the butt of many jokes with my best friend.  Early on in the year (January-ish), he would call from work, asking me what I did that day.  I would reply that I watched some movie from my DVD collection that he didn't even know existed like  Dark Blue, Holes, Who Framed Roger Rabbit , or some other title that came out of nowhere.  There is hilariousness to be found in these situations.  Sometimes I have to laugh at how much I don't really do on days like this, but I'm learning to appreciate any opportunities that I get to enjoy them.  Sometimes I worry about many of my friends and family at the abundance of work that they do.    Nobody gets any breaks anymore and the work hours get longer and longer.     I know that there are all sorts of people who feel that Americans have too many days off of work as it is, but that's not really my point here.  My point is that we aren't doing enough to actually  relax .  We need more down time.  We need to unwind more often.    Then again, this may just be another naive opinion from a guy whom is unemployed at this point in time.  But I have a feeling that I'll be able to put my money where my mouth is once I do get a job.  Sometimes I just turn work-mode off in order to refuel, and other times I just sit back and watch in awe at the people I know that never stop with their work.  Maybe work is their passion, or maybe it's all that they know.    What I do know right now is that it's 8:53 and I need to play my Xbox while I wait for my phone call regarding my job interview yesterday.     Written on 6/22/04 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Potential Employer:  ...we'd like for you to come in on Monday, June 21st at 11am for an interview for the sixth grade position.   And that's when I creamed my pants...  FINALLY!  Now that school is ending on Friday, it only makes sense that the first day of my summer vacation is spent preparing on how I would be a good addition at this particular school district.    This is the school where teachers tell me that they would like to see me wind up here.  This is the school that may be interested in me because of my extensive 6th grade teaching experience (albeit was student teaching and 90% of my substitute jobs).  This could be my money shot, but I won't get my hopes up.  I can't take myself out of the moment by having any expectations, and just take everything in as it comes.    ANNNNNDD... my Xbox is taking up a great deal of my time right now.  I regret giving it the cold shoulder when it first came out.  Everything on here is beautiful, forcing me to sell more of my Playstation 2 games in order to buy them for the prettier console.  Now I understand why people say the PS2 sucks in comparison to the Xbox (graphics make a lot of difference when one is crisp always and the other is always fuzzy like mold).  Anybody else think that this post was utterly pointless?
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I bought an Xbox this past Friday.  I picked up the limited edition Halo green one, the LAST one at my local Electronics Boutique.  It's beatiful, and I am very happy with it.  Oh, and I wrote the letter to avoid getting yelled at by my fiance, as I bought this while she was out with a friend and she then came home to find the system sitting on my lap.  Her response?  She laughed as she read the letter and gave me a kiss on the lips.  I'm the luckiest man alive.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I swear that for most corporate executives, greed is as necessary an emotion as love.   Executives love money, and they do what they can to generate more of it.  Whether it's for a company's success which ultimately affects them with kickbacks or more stock options, or if it's solely for their own benefit, it's starting to piss me off.  I'm not all "anti-corporation".  If a company or individual comes up with a way to get really rich, they're entitled to that money.  However, when they start messing with stuff that affects me, that's when I get upset.  What upsets me today is the future of my DVD collection.  At stake is the heir apparent to DVD.  On one side we have Sony's Blu-Ray disc format.  The opposition to that format is Panasonic's HD-DVD.  Both formats are apparently aiming for a 2006-2007 launch date, and while there are rumors that evey company involved would like to work this all out, they are only rumors.  From what I can tell (and I keep up-to-date at www.thedigitalbits.com), every movie company that puts out a movie on DVD pays the owner of the patent rights to DVD technology (some japanese company that has slipped my mind at this moment).  That's the reason for the pending format war right now, as there are all of these companies that want a bigger slice of the DVD profits.  I mean, it's official that DVD is THE accepted format right now, and VHS is officially dead.    So the genius writers at The Digital Bits painted a very grim picture if Blu-Ray and HD-DVD come out against each other.  As sony owns various movie companies (like the companies responsible for Spider-man and whatnot), they may ONLY release their future movie releases for Blu-Ray format discs (and these are discs that are encased in a plastic case - thus negating my current DVDs from working on Blu-Ray players).  Panasonic (I think this is the company behind HD-DVD (Hi-Definition DVD)) is responsible for Warner movies like Harry Potter.  To have to buy two different players to enjoy the movies that I love for their two completely different formats is absolutely insane, and it would make me pray for a movie-market crash.  I own over 250 DVDs, which amounts to thousands of dollars that I have put into this great collection.  My biggest concern is backwards compatibility, meaning I want to be able to watch my current DVDs on future DVD players.  I don't like the idea of all of these DVDs going the way of the VHS tape or even Beta.  I don't want to buy Back to the Future on the next format in two or three years.   When I step back and actually think about VHS, it was introduced in the mid-80's wasn't it?  And DVD started to take off in 1999 (techno-uber-geeks ate it up for a a few years before that), so can I at least have a few more years before the next format?  I don't want to put thousands of dollars into a new type of movie device that replaces DVD, because my fiance (whom would be my wife by then) will freaking kill me.  Honestly, why can't industry just be happy with the commercial success of DVD right now? 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    So here we have the most beautiful little girl in the world.  This is my best friend's daughter, whom shall remain nameless at this time as I'm not entirely comfortable putting out personal information about other people.  I snapped this on June 5th after working with her on the whole "Say cheese" thing.  It's times like these that I wish I had one or two of my own, so I could stop doting on other people's kids.  Maybe I'll just wait until she turns 13.&nbsp; urlLink      What I meant by waiting until she's 13 is that every 13 year-old girl becomes significantly more unbearable than they were when they were 12.  It's a scientific fact that exists amongst all women.  From the ages of 13-20, all women go through temporary periods of insanity. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow is Wednesday, June 9th.  It is the first day in about a month that I haven't had to teach while school is in session.  I guess that must speak volumes about the job that I'm doing as a sub, but I used to have like one or two days off a week back in March and April.  I never figured that I would be this busy towards the end of the school year.  So, as I kick back on my laptop while watching what looks to be a promising Lakers-Pistons NBA Finals series (GO DEE-TROIT!), I can't help but ponder what sorts of fun things I am going to do tomorrow.  When I finished with college this past Christmas, I had many days off.  I didn't have a job as a substitute or anything else, and I treated my days off as an extended Christmas break.  Well, once all of my post-college friends went back to work after New Year's Day, the whole days off thing got old very fast.   It's one thing when you're on break, but it's completely different when you're unemployed.   Breaks are good for everybody.  I don't think that most people in our country take enough breaks for themselves.  But I don't need weeks of doing nothing.  A few months ago, these days off would involve me being really bored after waking up at 9am and watching some movie on DVD or playing some stupid videogame.  After doing this morning ritual, I'd feel the need to go and spend money on more DVD's, videogames, or some toys that I collect.  That was all then.  Now, within the past two months, any time that I've had off from teaching has been devoted to getting stuff done.  I'm talking about haircuts, bank trips, getting resumes out in the mail, shopping for stuff that I actually need.  It's nice how things seem to have more meaning now.  It's nice to see my crazy spending habits are calming down a bit.    So, even though I may be years behind the curve of the rest of humanity, I am slowly starting to understand that while breaks and days off are important, it's also important to realize that you don't have to waste any extra time that you find yourself with.  Smile and say "cheese".
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My best friend in the world is the newest assistant principal at a prominent middle school here in the Monroe County area in Upstate NY.  He told me the great news on Saturday evening, before we (as we were accompanied by our significant others) traveled to  Rochester's greatest secret - The Alexander Street Festival .  As we were at this great block party (which is essentially what ASF is), I came across a few friends from high school and found out what they were all up to.  While I listened to their stories, I continually thought about my best friend's new opportunities and realized at several points throughout the night how proud I was of the people that I have known and come to know.    At the festival, I spoke with several old high school friends that could have been classified as the stoners of our class.  These kids were all about smoking weed and partying (I think most of them did this through college too).  Seeing them at this festival only reaffirmed to me that some things may never change, but instead of talking about what were aspiring to become or what parties we've been to, we instead were talking about what we  were doing .  Here I was, talking about what I do for a living and hearing about what other high school friends themselves were doing to pay the bills.  To me, it was amazing.  Listening to the people working for well-respected companies tell their stories of office life and the benefits of insurance sales made me wish that I could hurry up and find a job of my own, just so I could feel like my side of the "Where I'm working now" conversation had some weight to it.    As for my best friend's new position, nobody could be more proud of him than I am right now.  This is a guy whom is almost 7 years my senior and used to spend thousands of dollars on videogames every year.  From 1999 until 2001, we reviewed videogames on an internet radio show called "Gamingnoise".  We were nerds, but this was a guy that I thought would be young forever.  During these years, while his wife was pregnant with their first child, I'll never forget how my best friend said that "Nothing is going to change."  I laughed as soon as he uttered those words, and I still laugh when I think about them today.  Sometimes I just feel overwhelmed with a pleasant feeling when I see how much progress people have made over time.  Sure, we still have certain people whom will always remain a real jerk, or the people whom fail to realize their potential, but that's always the easiest stuff to point out.  When I think about myself 4 years ago, I realize that I was a lot different back then.  Then I look at people like my best friend, my fiance, and old friends from high school, and I just feel proud to be associated with them.  Rock on.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This card came along with my real letter from Stephen King.  Apparently, true horror buffs are afraid of these skeleton keychains.  I don't know which is scarier:  The fact that people will join this club for the free key chain, or that some will actually join for the chance to win a VHS collection of Stephen King movies.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Look at me with awe and wonder you puny nerds! I recieved a REAL letter from the greatest author of the past 30 years, Stephen King himself! Apparently, even Mr. King realizes that I am the new God of Cool, and that's why he's asking only me to join his club. The best part? The two books he mentions (Carrie and the Stand) are the last two books I need to complete my Stephen King collection! I must be the luckiest man alive! Sometimes you just have to wonder how stupid these companies think people are.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I write what I like.   Have you been paying attention to the national news lately?&nbsp; I used to go to foxnews.com every day like it was a religion, but lately I've been feeling that Fox is a little  too right-wing  for my tastes.&nbsp; I went through this stint where I was a total hardcore Republican (like my father and his side of the family), but the more I learned about where Republicans stand, the more I try to distance myself from their moral viewpoints.&nbsp; I hate the fact that MTV glorifies teenage sex just as much as the next person, but sometimes I feel that Foxnews does nothing but complain about everything that doesn't support the elephant (aka - the symbol of the GOP).   Anyways, I obviously paid the price for my lack of desire to surf the likes of Fox News or CNN, as I had no idea what was going on with this woman (Lori Hacking) from Salt Lake City whom disappeared after she went jogging one morning.&nbsp; Apparently her husband lied about graduating from college, lied about being accepted to medical school (located in North Carolina, where they were to move very soon), and was found the night of her disappearance running around a hotel area completely naked (which led him to being institutionalized).&nbsp; He has now retained a lawyer.   So basically, things aren't looking very good for Lori Hacking.&nbsp; I mean, she's been missing for about a week and any time there is blood found on any sharp objects, it never seems to bode well.&nbsp; I can't shake this feeling that this husband is NOT telling the truth when he says he has no idea where his wife is.&nbsp;   Why do so many husbands resort to killing their wives?&nbsp; Maybe I'm just reacting to this news on top of the whole Scott Peterson case, but it just seems to me that the "in" thing for sicko husbands to do right now is murder their wives.&nbsp; On the flip-side of things, I guess sicko wives are more into killing their kids.   I'm not trying to downplay these tragedies, but when this Hacking guy is charged (and he will be) with his wife's murder, I can already feel some sort of insanity defense building, and personally I file that crap under the same excuse that Andrea Yates used to kill her kids (her defense team claimed that she had some sort of depression after giving birth to her kids - but I can't remember the name!).&nbsp; I just don't buy these defenses at all.&nbsp; Mr. Hacking got caught in a lie by his wife (maybe many lies) and felt that he had to kill her.&nbsp; It will most likely be more complex than that, but there will be a lot more evidence that indicates his role in this.   I think that a majority of these husband/wife crimes reveal that couples have a huge problem on their hands in our society today:&nbsp;  we don't know how to communicate with each other .&nbsp; Communicating does not rely solely on being able to say how you feel, but instead it's being able to convey your feelings while listening to what the other person has to say.&nbsp; We work too hard, we bury our true feelings because it's easier to sweep them under a rug then it is to actually deal with them.&nbsp; Why did Hacking lie to everybody he knew about being a college grad and a med school student?&nbsp; Why couldn't he come clean with whom is supposedly the most important person in his life?&nbsp; Look at what these lies may have forced him to do.&nbsp; Or take a look at Scott Peterson.&nbsp; Regardless of his guilt or innocence, the man cheated on his wife a lot.&nbsp; He made no attempts to save his marriage (at least they haven't been revealed - unless you count getting his wife pregnant).&nbsp; If you're unhappy, you need to talk about it with your spouse and either get counseling (a third party is as unbiased as they come) or you try to work it out together (it can be done when it's done right).&nbsp;   It's the tragedies like these that make me realize how lucky I am that I can communicate with my fiance (and that we're going to have a happy marriage).&nbsp; There are things that we have a tough time dealing with (i.e. - finances and spirituality), but we are learning how to deal with them in a way that doesn't involve slamming doors, hitting each other, or destroying each other with hurtful words.&nbsp; It's a tough process, and we get into fights where we want to just go nuts on each other, but we're trying very hard for our own happiness&nbsp;and survival.&nbsp; I love my fiance very much (even when she is possessed by evil demons and I want to kill her :) ), and even though I lose my cool more often than not, I am trying to be a better listener and convey my feelings in an effective manner.   For what it's worth - I do hope that this Hacking guy is not responsible for this crime against his wife.&nbsp; It would make me feel a little&nbsp;better about the husbands here in the US and how they treat their wives.   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I write what I like.    Steven Biko would begin his essays with that line as he wrote in anti-apartheid newsletters back in the 1970's.&nbsp; It's a line that I should use more as I write here in this little nook of the online universe.   Today was one of the busiest days of the summer.&nbsp; My camp had to go to Six Flags Darien Lake today, which means that over 100 kids come out for this trip that lasts from 9:30 until 5:30.&nbsp; Three and a half hours of this trip are spent going to and from the park, and another 30-60 minutes are required to round the kids up, make sure they are all accounted for, and load them on to and off of a bus.&nbsp; When you cut out the 4 to 4.5 hours of travel/organization time, that's 3.5 to 4 hours of actual ride time.&nbsp; We do these things called "buddy checks" several times throughout the day where kids come and check in with a specific counselor to let them know they're okay.&nbsp; These kids are all 12-14 years of age, and most of them don't need us holding their hands as they go through the park.&nbsp; Well, at the end of the day, one of my kids decided that eating ice cream was more important that checking in to go home.&nbsp; He delayed our departure by 25 minutes.&nbsp; The saddest part?&nbsp; His body could have done without the ice cream, if you get my drift.&nbsp; Harsh for me to say, as my body is far from perfect, but I would never put my stomach over 120 campers and counselors, even at that age.   Once we got home, Jamie and I had a quick bite to eat at Applebee's for about an hour before heading over to our second round of premarital counseling.&nbsp; I love our mentoring couple, but tonight we were preparing for one of the most uncomfortable moments of our lives:&nbsp; the&nbsp;talk about "it".   Now I won't go into the details of the talk, as I greatly cherish the privacy of our sessions and especially my fiance.&nbsp; However, some things were a little harder for us to swallow than others.&nbsp; Jamie is a Christian, but I can tell that there are some things in this religion that she does not necessarily agree with (but I do not attempt to speak any of these feelings for her).&nbsp; I consider myself to be more agnostic than anything else.&nbsp; I know there's something, but I don't think we can understand what it is most of the time.&nbsp; I like all religions, plain and simple.&nbsp; Some more than others, but I like to diversify as much as I can.&nbsp; This is a touchy subject for many people, so I will end this discussion before things get too upsetting for some of you (and even myself).   I end my rambling tonight with a little anecdote from this evenings counseling session.&nbsp; Jamie and I had to come up with a budget for our lives after marriage.&nbsp; We sat down with Jamie's mother after dinner on Sunday to do this activity, and it was very eye opening.&nbsp; I think that Jamie and I were not as prepared as we thought we were for the life of paying bills all the time and living in a house, and therefore we became very stressed out.&nbsp; While we agreed that this was a great activity to get to understand ourselves and our finances better, we also shared great pleasure in discovering that we were both very much afraid of the question: "How can we possibly afford these things?"   As we shared this story with our mentors tonight, I came up with a great quote that I will market to the editors of quotebooks that are sold in bookstores throughout the country:     "We left at each other's throats, and returned in each other's arms."     How cool am I?&nbsp; Go on and admit it:&nbsp; That's a good one!   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Now for the latest installment of "Album of the Moment". On deck this week is one of my favorite albums of the last few months. The bad news is that it took me forever to find this band for myself. I don't watch MTV anymore (what's the point?). I don't really pay attention to music publications of any kind. The only way that I get to discover new music is when I buy songs for 99 cents on iTunes. About a month or two ago, I saw something about the Yeah Yeah Yeahs and checked out two songs: Maps and Y Control. These two songs are not only awesome as far as the voice of Karen O and the perfect fusion of guitars and drums, but they're the best songs on the album. Apparently, this band has been around for at least a few years and has a rather large following. I'm just counting my blessings for finding them when I did.&nbsp; urlLink    &nbsp; Aside from having a huge following, the Yeah Yeah Yeahs have been compared to an unquestionably more popular band known as  The White Stripes  (another band that I seriously love&nbsp;since I "discovered" them last summer).&nbsp; I could see the legitimacy in comparing the two bands in the sense that they're both garage rock and both YYY and the White Stripes have exceptionally talented singers.&nbsp; Anyways, let me break down some of the tracks for you: &nbsp;   Tracks worth listening to:&nbsp; Rich, Date With the Night, Tick, Black Tongue, Pin, Cold Night, Maps, Y Control, and Modern Romance.  &nbsp; All of these are excellent at demonstrating how Karen O has a voice like Chrissy Hynde (a la Pretenders).&nbsp; I think these comparisons are as legit as they come, but I'm hoping for a longer album next time.&nbsp; 37 minutes doesn't really show me everything that this band can do  (or does it???) . &nbsp; The only track that I don't like is "Man".&nbsp; I feel like I've heard songs just like it many times before.&nbsp; It didn't really impress me.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Oh well, that's what I'm into for the time being. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Take a look at the crapfest that is the Summer 2004 movie  "Catwoman".  This is  THE  single biggest atrocity that I have ever seen in a movie since Nicholas Sparks' "A Walk to Remember". It's that bad folks.&nbsp; urlLink   Not only did they abandon almost every aspect of the original Catwoman as she has appeared in comic books, but once again we are forced to accept Hollywood's belief that tits and ass ( PLEASE PARDON THE LANGUAGE - BUT LET'S NOT KID OURSELVES HERE)  are the only two ways for a woman to fight crime.  &nbsp;  Here is how Catwoman abandoned the real Catwoman (and why the movie will suck cow manure):     Catwoman came to exist solely in Gotham City, primarily as a catburglar (meaning she committed crimes herself when she first started out).&nbsp; In this movie, it seems pretty obvious to me that she becomes Catwoman to fight crime and to get revenge on the thugs whom killed her.    Catwoman NEVER had any superhuman cat-powers.&nbsp; Everything she had in the comic books (i.e.- wall-climbing, fighting and stealth skills) were due to intense training,  NOT FRIGGIN' CAT SPIRITS BRINGING HER DEAD SELF BACK TO LIFE!       The least of the movie's offenses - Catwoman was white.&nbsp; Now I don't have a problem with Catwoman's race here.&nbsp; It worked with Billy Dee Williams playing Harvey Dent in the first two  Batman  films, and it worked with Michael Clarke Duncan playing the Kingpin in  Daredevil .&nbsp; If the character were more accurate, I would think that Halle Berry would have done a great job.    Uh...Catwoman lives in Gotham City.&nbsp; Who else lives in Gotham City that fights criminals like the original Catwoman?&nbsp; Hmm...I don't know....?&nbsp;   MAYBE BATMAN?!?!?!  &nbsp; Where the heck is he in all of this?&nbsp; The rights to Batman and Catwoman are BOTH owned by Warner Brothers.&nbsp; Why would they allow for this to happen to Catwoman?&nbsp; One word:&nbsp;  Crack Cocaine.     I've saved the greatest offense of  Catwoman  for last, and that has to do with the absurdity of her outfit.&nbsp; How much T&amp;A does Berry need to show in order to stop bad guys?&nbsp; If I were a thug with an Uzi, you know I'm shooting her in her stomach, breasts, and arms because all I see there is skin.&nbsp; Oh, and if I miss all of those parts, I would shoot her in her  OPEN-TOED CAT SHOES!!! &nbsp; What is the meaning of this?&nbsp; Why does Catwoman have to look like a prostitute on Halloween?&nbsp; Why did they have to ruin a great comic book character in order to make this movie?&nbsp; The sad part is that Berry apparently loved the character that she plays here.&nbsp; Too bad she has no idea whom Catwoman really is.   Catwoman is a catburglar/vigilante whom happens to love Batman (and he loves her), but they always wind up on opposite sides of the law.&nbsp; Maybe love is too strong a term here.&nbsp; They at least like each other enough to flirt while fighting.&nbsp; None of this is presented here except for Berry flirting with Benjamin Bratt's detective character.&nbsp; The whole thing stinks like dead fish if you ask me.&nbsp; If this movie makes over $100 million, then I will truly believe that the world has gone mad because truth no longer has meaning to anybody.  Then again, this is coming from the guy that loved Angelina Jolie in  Tomb Raider.    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My interview went to Hell yesterday.&nbsp; I feel that it went okay, but I didn't get the phone call that I was told would come to the "winner" of the third grade teaching position.&nbsp; So I went to work right after the interview, proceeding to change from my suit into my camp counselor shirt and cargo shorts as I drove.&nbsp; I was actually driving down Ridge Road in my undershirt and boxers at one point, and a truck driver was the only person who saw me. &nbsp; My 6-8th grade Fun Camp was traveling to Sea Breeze amusement park yesterday, so as I paced around the park, making sure that my campers stayed out of trouble, I was glued to my cell phone just in case it should ring with some good news about my job scenario.&nbsp; Unfortunately, that call never came.&nbsp; It wasn't waiting for me on my answering machine when I came home, and it didn't wake me up this morning.&nbsp; It never came, and now I can't help but feel&nbsp;a little deflated after all of this.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I tried to escape this stress last night with my little brother by taking him to see Spiderman 2 (my 2nd time and his 1st).&nbsp; I liked it even more this time, but I realized that I would never make a good teacher, as there wasn't one child besides my brother that I could visualize leaving  unharmed  after experiencing strong desires to go on a homicidal rampage.&nbsp; Kids that sat behind me either kicked my seat as they would a soccer ball for the whole movie.&nbsp; Kids further behind me (and thus out of my reach) proceeded to have   shouting conversations with their parents.  &nbsp; And worst of all, the two stupid girls sitting in front of me could only seem to talk about how much the liked spiderman when he was swinging and complained about every other scene where he was out of costume.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Griffin really enjoyed the film, so ultimately I am very glad to have been able to bring him.&nbsp; We don't spend enough time together anymore.&nbsp; After the movie, we speculated about what might happen when Spiderman 3 comes out.&nbsp; Tonight we're watching  Brother Bear , which is a great movie about siblings.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Hmm...I guess that when I distract myself with loved ones, job interviews and employment mean squat to me.&nbsp;  However, I'd like to land something soon so that I can actually have a wedding and a house.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Best movie of the Summer?  Yup.  Am I seeing it again tomorrow?  You betcha.  Without a doubt, the biggest reason why Spiderman does so well is the storytelling that occurs in the film.  Here you have a hero whom is struggling with his two identities and how Peter Parker just wishes that he could STOP being Spiderman.  There are a lot of themes presented here than many other kinds of movies which ultimately resonate with viewers.  It's easy to see the conflicts between characters and even conflicts within themselves as being more entertaining than the action.  If people wanted straight-up action with their superheroes, look no further than Van Helsing.  If you want a good story, then this is your movie.  It's interesting how both movies deal with heroes and villains, yet both are presented in completely different ways.  Just my two cents.  Oh, and the reasoning behind the title?  Doc Ock was played brialliantly by Alfred Molina.  This is Michael Clarke-Duncan as Kingpin good, or Ian McKellan as Magneto good.  Not Jack Nicholson as the Joker good.  But infinitely better than Schwarzenegger as Mr. Freeze.  And the reason why I have testicles?  Because apparently I'm on my best friend's "poop" list because I saw this without him.  Hey fool, thanks for going to see Napoleon Dynamite without me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's a little tidbit that I'd like to share with you about my little brother.  He's the coolest kid in the universe.  I was browsing through my picture inventory tonight and came across this little gem from our last trip to Florida. In this shot, I was trying to get him to pose for a picture, and with my family consisting of a high level of dorkiness, we either make stupid faces or we just leave.  In this case, it's easy to see that my brother chose the latter option, and this is the only shot that I was able to get of him that night as he ran through the house.  He's 10 right now, almost 11, and I often stop to think about how in another year or two, he's going to not want to hang out with his big brother anymore.  Then again, I don't think I was much of a good brother to begin with, but I'm sure that some of you can understand how it's easy to idolize your big brother and/or sister even when they aren't perfect.  I just hope that I've done a good enough job with him in order to have a good relationship with him during what will most likely be the worst years of his life.  I hated adolescence more than any other time in my life.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I just got back from a great 24+ hours at my cottage, located up in the ever-beautiful Port Bay, NY.  I spent yesterday afternoon and evening there with my fiance, and it was nice to just be there without the normal chaos of my family.    As I write this now, I am kicking myself for not taking any pictures to post from this beautiful weekend.  Seriously, the weather could NOT have been any better out there on the waters of Lake Ontario.  I was in charge for dinner that evening, and so I got out to the cottage at about 1pm to start my prep so I didn't have to do a lot later.  Once Jamie arrived at about 3pm, we got into our suits and jumped on the boat to go swimming at Chimney Bluffs.  Well I guess I should say that I was the only one whom went swimming, as my beloved is really a large cold-blooded lizard that only lives for laying in the sun to warm her.    I actually managed to read over 200 pages of my book (and wound up finishing it) in a 24 hour period.  The book that I read was  The Lovely Bones , by Alice Sebold, and it was a fantastic read.  It's about a girl whom is raped and murdered by a neighbor and how she observes the lives of her family, friends, and killer as she lives in Heaven.  Look at it as a story about how people cope with the tragic loss of a young person and how lives are virtually ruined and rebuilt.  It's more a story of forgiveness and redemption than anything else, which makes it as powerful as it is original.  This is a book that could have easily gone in the direction of vengeance and justice, a Law & Order show in print if you will, but I'm grateful that Sebold took advantage of her talent and took the reader in a greater direction.  Anyways, it was a very low-stress weekend.  I love the time when Jamie and I get to just exist together.  There isn't anything better than that.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing is going on.  I have no important news to report, other than the glaring fact that I have not yet seen Spider-Man 2 yet, because my best friend wants me to wait two more weeks until his birthday.  WHY CAN'T WE JUST GO SEE ANCHORMAN INSTEAD SO I DON'T HAVE TO WAIT!?!?!?!  I have a huge interview coming up next Wednesday for a third grade position at a school that I really want to work in.  It's a two hour interview, which means that I will have 120 minutes worth of opportunities to ruin my job prospects there.  I know that I put up this mantra about not having expectations because they ruin the present moment, but if I could do really well at this interview and have the job offered to me, I'd be very happy.    Summer Camp has officially started this past Tuesday, and it was a blast.  I am in a new group this summer and I'm literally in heaven.  I used to work with an inclusion camp (kids with special needs), and while that was a lot of fun (including the fact that I was working with my fiance), I felt it was time to move on to something with less stress (you wouldn't believe how much worrying I used to do while on the job).  Now, I'm working at a 6th-8th grade Fun Camp, which only goes on field trips.  The staff is excellent this summer, and the kids are all very good.  I think that's everything that's been going on for the last couple of weeks.  Oh, and my Xbox and I are the best of friends right now.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From what I understand, it's been almost two weeks since blogging.  What happened, you ask?  NOT A FREAKING THING!   I have no job acquisition to report of, no broken bones, no earth-shattering story to tell about how I almost died while saving the lives of strangers, and no pictures to post!    It was actually an uneventful 14 days that went by since my last blog.   I had a decent interview with Victor Cental Schools last week, but I won't find out about that until the end of this week.  Other than looking for jobs, I have been working my tail off for a paycheck that might as well read "$0.00" on it.  I love my job, but I can't understand how I lose more from a six week job in taxes then I do when I sub during the school year.  It's very frustrating.   The only highlite worth reporting is my very fun day with my best friend Chip two fridays ago.  He took the day off so we could hang out for the day, which allowed us to see  The Village  (which I thought was awesome - but I stand head and shoulders above everybody else when it comes to opinions on movies :) ).  We also started playing this nerd-game called  Pirates of the Spanish Main  which actually allows us to create fleets of ships for naval combat (16th century style!).  That was a fun day.   I also have one story of interest.  It involves a phone call with a man named   George Lucas.    I'll post that tomorrow. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>