<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a blog that will be developed in the near future.  My other blog is  urlLink here .   
     
    
</post>


<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, the cable guy is coming to take away our cable tv and internet access today, so I won't be able to post until we get to Iowa.  Moving tomorrow!  Wish us luck -- see you in a few days!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday, the conferences and events group I've worked with at Deutsche Bank for the last nine months had a little going-away lunch for me.  It was so nice.  Amanda came along and finally got to meet almost everyone from work.  As usual, the conversation was fast and furious, the topic changed every five seconds, and everyone was laughing like crazy, which was perfect because it was entirely representative of the general dispositon of the group.  They're so much fun.  I've only been away from work for a couple days and I already miss it.  Yes, I'm excited to move and start new things, but it was a great job and you honestly could not ask for a better bunch of people to work with.    Also, went to No Idea? bar last night (just down the street from us) with some friends.  It was "Jason" night, meaning that anyone with the name Jason got free drinks from 5-11 pm.  Wait a second...I COULD HAVE GOTTEN FREE DRINKS!!!  Anyway, our wonderful friends Nicola, Martha, Steve, and Katie came by and we had a great time.  I guess it was sort of an unofficial going-away party.  I have a peculiar way of dealing with leaving people and places.  I try to maintain an exceptionally positive attitude at all times and it usually works.  It's not denial, exactly, because I'm not really denying or ignoring any realities or feelings.  Rather, I just concentrate on the fact that we're planning to move back to New York in three years - and with modern technology (LIKE THIS BLOG!) there are all sorts of ways to keep in touch with people - and whenever you move somewhere new, it's kind of like you're starting all over with endless possibilities ahead of you.  I don't mean to act or sound like a motivational speaker, that's just how I deal.    Okay, I should totally be packing boxes and cleaning our apartment.    (If you are interested in booking me as a motivational speaker, please e-mail me at jasonvbnyc@hotmail.com)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'll redo some of the stuff I had blogged earlier, such as a quick update on life right now.  Here's where it's at:  Amanda and I live in New York City, where she just graduated from NYU with her MA in Performance Studies and I worked a "temp" job at  urlLink Deutsche Bank   on Wall Street.  We're moving to Iowa in TWO DAYS, where we'll hang out with family and friends for part of the summer.  In early August, we're moving to Orange County, California.  I'll be studying for my MFA in Acting at  urlLink UC Irvine  for the next three years.  I'm rather excited to get started.    Previous to this, I had a livejournal.  If you'd like to check out old posts, go  urlLink here  .
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Something terrible happened to my old blog.  It just disappeared -- white screen -- nothing.  I imagine that it was somehow retrievable, but as there were only seven posts, I decided to start fresh.  Welcome to the new blog.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>