<Blog>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, the issues just keep piling up.  I can't watch, listen or read anything on current events without something making my blood boil in about five seconds.   Since this is my first posting, I am unsure how to kick it off.  I should just say a bit about what (if I actually keep posting that is), this blog will cover.  Well, my interests are many, but through my life thus far my ever enduring passions are politics and restaurants.  So, I will be posting, if only for myself, my thoughts on different dining experiences here in Minneapolis.  More importantly however, I will be ranting about the political and social issues of the day.  For the former, I think that with the number of times that I dine out, (breakfast, lunch, dinner), and the fact that I don't get paid for what I say, I have, at times more credibility that the "professionals".  For the latter, I am very conservative in my leaning, but not in a scary Pat Buchanan kind of way.  We are in a hard time as a country and I don't like where we are going as a nation or global society.  Ah! Wait.  You think me saying, I don't like where we are heading, means I am attacking G. W. Bush, don't you?  Wrong.  The president has and is continuing to make some perplexing decisions, but I am not attacking him.  Stay tuned, you'll get my drift in future postings. 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Following is a quick note I sent to Bill O'Reilly following him being embarrassed by Michael Moore.  &nbsp; Bill,   Just an observation, I watched Moore, do what he does best, eat your lunch.&nbsp; Surprisingly, he didn’t have a demand for chips and dip or chocolate covered doughnuts or something of like that to appear on your show.&nbsp; Never the less, I just watch him take you to school in your little debate.&nbsp; I was exercising at my athletic club during your interview and just took some notes afterward on where he got the best of you.&nbsp;   1)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; You think you would have taken the 40 seconds to look up the meaning of the word “lie”.&nbsp; Be the definition of the word, Bush isn’t guilty of what Moore accuses him of.&nbsp; Pretty simple to have missed that.  2)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; He said he would never have let Hitler come to power.&nbsp; So if President, he would have done something that he blasts Bush for doing.&nbsp; You mentioned it, but should have really pressed the matter.  3)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; He said Eastern Europe rose-up like we did in our Revolutionary War.&nbsp; Ours was a violent struggle; we took up arms to become free of our oppressive government.&nbsp; Eastern Europe didn’t rise up in at all the same way.&nbsp; You were correct to say that our military buildup bankrupted Communism, but why did you let him correlate our revolution to the fall of Communism in Eastern Europe?  4)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; You let him say that, “we went to war because Bush said Iraq was an immanent threat to our security”.&nbsp; That is, by definition, a lie.&nbsp; Moore knows that Bush said, “… before Iraq becomes and immanent threat”.&nbsp; You let that slip by without mention.&nbsp; I think for that along, Fox should restructure your contract… your getting paid to much to miss that.  5)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; You let him ask you if you would sacrifice your child to secure Fullujah.&nbsp; That isn’t even your call.&nbsp; We aren’t under a draft in this country; our soldiers join our armed forces by choice.&nbsp; And regardless, the correct response was, that you believe in the cause of liberating millions from a murderous regime; that by no means is defending the Iraqi people a death sentence and that you would be proud to have your child fight in the U.S. armed forces.  6)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; One more.&nbsp; You could have said that we went to war because for 12 years and 14 UN resolutions, Saddam lied to the world.&nbsp; He didn’t do anything he agreed to do, he didn’t stop shooting at us in the no-fly-zone, he didn’t give humanitarian aid to the people that needed it, he didn’t prove that he destroyed the WMD’s that the UN knew he had.&nbsp; He knew what the consequences were and he thought that Bush would continue down the same line as Clinton, by doing nothing.&nbsp; By threatening, but never following through.&nbsp;   You must have been bolted to your set last night, because he was spinning you like a top!  What say you, Bill? 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>