<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy again. Just started school, I think its gonna rain soon. Ah, the majestic feeling again.. I can't explain the beauty of the world, even to myself. Everything is so divine, everything. Just imagine... waterfalls in a dense rainforest, and mist forming at your feet..the clouds are dark and a light drizzle is falling... feel any tingle yet? How about gorgeous colourful flowers that border the lake that is the base of the waterfall you're standing in front of? A sparrow tells you its story as it perches on your shoulder and you feel so happy that you wanna cry. This feeling, you can only say what it is in French..yes, deja vu. I've been here, done this, and it feels heavenly. See how beautiful everything is? In this very way, the plants and creatures all around us are merging every single day to form a perfect harmony that we call nature.. And its all perfect because its a creation of God. Who says the world isn't as beautiful as it once was? It is, we just have to see the beauty in it. Yes, God. That's another thing I want to talk about. However, got a Management test next period and I need to go brush up on it. Ciao, beautiful people.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm feeling reeealll good today, dunno why..I kept smiling through every class and everything. This is weird. I would smile as I typed this in, but the guy beside me's gonna get freaked out fer sure. Wow, going to Mussoorie in 10 days...ohmigodd..TEN DAYS! ok, this is bad...shopping, packing...how am I gonna do it all? Forget it. I'll figure it out..got lotsa time. Lalalala...Going back to Poonamish Land now..
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I'm bored. Life's just a void these days. By the way, its raining life! Just kidding, its raining rain. I love the rain. Makes me feel really majestic..don't ask why...I have my eccentric ways. Moooving on, I think I need ear surgery. They just can't twitch. What's the use of having big dumbo ears if they can't twitch? Ok, just kidding again. Man...do all people fill in blogs with this kinda crap, or is it just me? That was a rhetorical question, by the way.     
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just starting out, feeling kinda blue. Kz, sometimes, we really don't have stuff to do here in school, and there's where this blog stuff comes in. Hey, it might actually be useful. I dunno. Dunno anything. Hmm.. I actually don't know what to say. Wow. Aaanyway, I'll come back later if my life happens to get more exciting. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks to the constant nagging(reminder's a politer word, but I'm not gonna use it) of my beloved friends, I decided to add another post! Yeah I know, woo-hoo. Anyway, it has been pretty long and I have yet to talk about my exhilating Mussoorie trip..sigh. Mussoorie, for all you non-Geographers, is a hill station in India, near the Indian Himalayan mountains. Moooving on, this was my second trip to these gorgeous mountains and I'm tellin ya, you just lose all you worries, tension, problems, whatever there! Until you come back, that is. I used to open the windows of my room every morning, and cool clouds would drift in...making the whole place misty, like in a dream. I went to Mussoorie to meet some very special people in my life, and taking walks along the dingy roads there with them was just bliss. One thing about mountains though- people don't like to walk cuz they're too..um.. physically challenged. Solution: they get horses. Many many horses. And you know what horse do? They poop. Damn right they do. Geez they must go like, 10 times a day or something. They don't even give warnings or anything! These things can do their business even while running...which would be pretty cool if it didn't scare the pjeebies outta me. yeesh. Gotta scram for now. India rocks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Will you believe it...I got a haircut.Again. After all that self-disciplining about how I'm gonna let it grow. That's me. Anyway, mid years just ended today so that was cool. Went for my hot yoga classes but no one there really bothers to share the joy of last day of exams, yeesh. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The green girl in the asthanga asana? That's me. Green's my fave colour.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>