<Blog>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can't wait till next week!!! This will be the first time I'll ever go to the East Coast besides the time I went to Florida when I was 11. But this is the first time I'll ever be anywhere far without my family(kind of a scary thought). I know this will be a memorable experience. And the girl I like is coming too. Maybe I'll make my move while on the trip. Yeah right, I'm way to shy, especially cause I haven't really liked anyone in a while. Hey you'll never know, It is a different backdrop, anything can happen.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally finished fixing my profile. I had too many characters in my music, 2x's too many in fact. It was so hard trying to decide what to take out. But I had to make some sacrifices.  People are watching "You Got Served" in the other room. Not really my cup of tea. Mix bad music, with bad acting, and a bad story line and that equals my worst nightmare. No offence to fans of the movie, though you might want to go see a psychiatrist for thinking that movie is good.  I need to read  Life of Pi  for English, I don't really mind since it's not that bad, but I just can't get myself to pick up the book.*sigh* And I still need to by a journal for it. I'm just too lazy for this stuff.  I feel stupid right now for writing this cause I doubt anybody would be reading this.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone, this is my first post. Finally decided to start one of these.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've noticed that I'm surrounded by inconciderate people. They try to be nice and stuff, but really they only do that cause they want something in return. Unsuspecting people are always being used by these people.   Some people will do about anything to get what they want and not even concider what they're doing to the people around them. They take advantage of other people's kindness and generocity, and if I say something about it, they just come back, "They wanted to do it! I'm getting it for free, I'm not spending money so it doesn't matter. You'd do it too!" The thing is if you really know me, I wouldn't. It's so selfish. I'm not saying that I'm the perfect person, I'm far from that, but at least I take other people's well being into concideration.  Another thing is most of the time, I don't think these people even know what they're doing when they do it. They're too stuck into themselves to even think about other people.  Just my little rant of the moment.   Brought to you by "Empathy," don't you wish everyone had it?
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This happened a few nights ago, but I just found out that the girl that I like so much is already talking to another guy. Why does this always happen to me? When it comes to girls, I never seem to get a break. Well atleast we talk sometimes, there's just so much I like about this girl, I've never felt so strongly about anything in my life. Some might find this crazy, but I remember almost every detail of the different times I've spent with her, though very limited. I'm happy being her friend n all, but it sucks when she's all that plagues my freakin mind. Even when I try to think of something else, I always seem to end up relating everything to her. Everything reminds me of her. I'm going fuckin crazy, and I have no idea what to do about it. It's like I'm going through withdrawl. I even went and told her that my thoughts were like diabeties, and she was my sugar(want me to explain more, ask me). I told her alot of how I feel, but it doesn't seem to do much. I'm torn in two. One side of me just wants to get over her because it just seems hopeless, but then there's this side of me that just,"Don't Give Up, If there's one thing you shouldn't give up is her." I hate this shit, that's why I always kept my heart small(reference to Saosin), so I wouldn't have to feel like this.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been home for a couple of days now, and I miss NY so much. I had such a great time.  I just told the girl I liked that I liked her last night. I just straight up called her on the phone and told her. I've wanted to tell her throughout our whole trip to NY, but I always chickened out. I knew if I waited any longer I wouldn't ever be able to do it, so I just did it. She told me she'd call me back, but still hasn't. Now I'm worried that I was a little too forward and I scared her away. I'll wait till she's ready though, she did seem very nervous after I told her. She told me she was blushing. She's so cute, If she could only see how nervous I was, I could barely get the words out of my mouth. It's probably pretty easy for some guys to say it, but if you knew me, I'm pretty shy.  It's kind of funny for a straight edge wallflower like me to like a party girl like her. I wonder how those things work out. Hey, if she ever needs me I'll hold her hair while she's vomitting on my shoes.  I'm still happy though, now that I finally got that of my chest.   Now that I think about it, she might've told me to call her. Damn I'm confused. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally got the new Atreyu album, The Curse. And I got the limited edition with an extra song, You Give Love a Bad Name; a cover song for Bon Jovi, produced by Beu Burcheall, guitarist of Saosin. Now all the cd's in my 3 cd changer have something produced by him; this one, the Saosin - Translating the Name EP, and The Bled - Pass the Flask album. It also came with the video for Right Side of the Bed, and a very nice black paper packaging with gold writing and their upside down star logo. There were also only 30,000 ever published. I personally like the cd  a lot. It really shows off the talents of each member. The guitar riffs and solos are so much better, and Alex's screaming has improved so much from Suicide Notes. The only dissappointment to me was that the lyrics didn't get any better, but they're really good, since Suicide Notes had really good lyrics anyways.     I can't wait to get the new TBS tomorrow. There was some worker chick in Hot Topic today talking about how she really liked it, and thought it was awsome even though John left and she loved him. She said it was different but good. I heard about half of it, and from what I've heard I 'd have to agree with her and felt the same way. You just have to get used to the new sound. I hope I could go to the live acoustic set too.     I'll try to get Underoath while I'm at it, I really want that one still.    And now about my weekend. I went on some "hiking expedition" with some cousins in PV last night. We went to this one park on top, and hopped this fence that led to stairs that went down to where a storm drain ended. Then we just kept going down, but decided to stop since it seemed like to end up nowhere and the only light we had was from the moon and the fog started coming in. We might come up there some other time and try to go down as much as we can to see what's down there.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's passed midnight and I'm bored as fuck so I'm just posting whatever.  First off I'd like to say that the new  Unearth  is fuckin amazing. It's probably my most listened to album for the past week. If you like bands like As I Lay Dying or Atreyu or metalcore in general, you'll love Unearth. It's suprising I still haven't gotten the new Atreyu or Underoath yet and those two were probably my most anticpated releases of the summer. They're only $9.99 @ Target, so I really hope I get them soon, and hope they got enough so they're not sold out.  Now I'd like to announce that I passed my AP Eng Lang Exam. Woo woo! It was only a 3, but hey passing is passing when it come to AP exams, right? It sucks I only had a 2 in Psych though, Damn Aquino! haha. It's cool though, atleast I passed one. Now maybe I could negotiate for a higher grade in the class. haha. I got a D in Eng, and getting that up to a C would be alot of help.  I watched an Afghan movie today called Osama(which was really good) for my summer assignment for AP Eng Lit. I just need to see a couple more movies and read a book I haven't even gotten yet. I hope to get it soon though. I know I could finish it pretty fast concidering I really have nothing better to do, but just in case.  For the past few months, I've really been concidering becoming atheist or agnostic or whatever, but concidering that my family has a pretty much very religious, Catholic&nbsp;background it's kind of scary to just do it. I already get criticized enough for not going to church and not participating in a lot of religious traditions and stuff. I might have to go in exhile or something. I'm probably the most unreligious person in my extended family from everyone I can think of. They want me to get involved and stuff, but I just don't see me doing it. Another thing that holds me back is that, I think I still believe in god sometimes.  And for the past couple of weeks, the vegetarian subject comes up again. Why did meat have to be so good?  I really have too many conflicts in my head recently. It's like a warzone in there, and there doesn't seem to be any end to it. Sometimes the only answer seems to&nbsp;be another Hiroshima and Nagasaki, but I've&nbsp;decided about a year ago that&nbsp;going kamikaze isn't gonna help anything and there's just too much I want to do before I can go. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided to google my name but couldn't find a link to anything, so I clicked on a link for some other search engine which found something my sister wrote in her blog about me which I found pretty funny.       quote of the frikken century!:   "my butt feels weird when i get scared. dogs cover their balls w/ their tails when they get scared. i think im trying to cover my balls, but i have no tail!" - ross baquir aka my brother  I actually remember saying that, but I have no idea why. Maybe it was just some random thing that I thought of. I don't know. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       One nation under the gun  Where forward thinking is shunned  A morbid tradition  Of archaic value systems  Where violence justified  Is just another pride  Under the surface lies  A holy plastic empire  With guarded golden fences  Where misfortune  Shelters decisions  A pain wrought from blood flowing green  The myth of protection  Is a sick fascination  A culture of violence is what you are feeding  Fear is an heirloom  And hate is contagious  A nation of sadists is what you are breeding  It's everywhere  It's everywhere that you see  But who decides  If you watch or turn the other cheek  And only in your mind  Is it your given right to be armed to the teeth  It's a common disease  The only immunity is to disarm  This holy plastic empire disease    Was just listening to it and thought it was a really good song, by a really good band.    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Michael Badnarik - 2004 Libertarian Party Presidential Candidate    I found some of his views pretty interesting. I know I would concider him if I were able to vote this Nov. (doesn't necessarily mean I would) This isn't here to promote him, but just to show someone besides Bush and Kerry. Remember, when you vote, don't go with what everyone else is going with, think for yourself, look things up, know what's up, &nbsp;don't just vote with ignorant eyes, try to see the ball through every possible side(note: balls have no real sides).      
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn I'm so confused right now. I really can't take all this emotional shit that I'm going through. I don't like it at all. It's driving me nuts. I could barely get to sleep. The only way I find my self going to sleep is if I just lay there doing nothing, not even thinking for about an hour, and it's really hard for me to do that. My hole life is probably just based on thinking, that's all I practically do. My social life is practically gone. If it wasn't for summer school, I'd have none. Which is only a measely 2 and a half hours of my day. The rest of the time I usually spend just listening to music, playing guitar, or video games. Well that's life for me.  Today I tried talking in a british accent the whole day. It was actually pretty fun. Only lasted a couple of hours, but it was interesting stuff. Bugged the hell out of my little brother. If I only knew a little more street talk it would've been even better. I love talking in accents. One of my very limited talents. Some people think I'm stupid for doing it, but their just jealous couse they can't do it, haha. Some people do stupid stuff to get atttention from others, I do it cause I love doing it. Some people think I say random things, but it's not really random when it's triggered by something you said first. I like to turn every situation into something funny, no matter what the subject is. I hate it when the mood gets sad, I hate saddness, and I hate seeing other people sad. When people around me are in a bad mood I tend to get in a bad mood. I could be the most misserable person in the world, but still be happy if everyone else was happy. But I know something like that could never happen, It's saddly impossible. And the world would probably be pretty boring. What makes life what it is and worth living is all these trivilizations that we go through. Yeah sometimes it feels like it's hopeless, but once you get through something you feel a whole lot better. Life can't just be about "good times", It needs "bad times" too or those "good times" will just any normal thing and you'd tire of it.  Ok, I'm just rambeling about about a bunch of shit n he-ha.  One thing I'm wondering is, is anybody reading this shit. I'd like to ask anybody that reads this to just comment on it. It doesn't matter if it's about anything. I'd just like to see if people actually read what I'm saying here.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I got scheduled for Summer School. I couldn't take gov't cause it was closed already, so I just got statistics. What's cool is that I don't have to wake up early cause I only have a second period. But I guess I'm gonna have to take gov't during the year, this sucks cause I'm probably gonna have to drop one of the classes I was hoping to take.   I woke up an hour early so could go early but I still had to wait for almost 3 hours to get scheduled. I had to stand with a bunch of incoming freshmen, I can't really stand all their gossiping and shit, talking about, "Ooh! *blah* is with *blah*. OMG!" I had to stand there with them since it was my cousin's gf's friends. They're pretty nice to me and shit, but if it wasn't for my cousin, they probably wouldn't even think of talking to me. Not that I would think of talking to them either, though. It's cool though I don't care to much, but every year, the new kids seem to get more and more irritating. God I'm gonna hate how school is gonna be. A bunch of little kids running around everywhere, thinking they're all that and a bag of potatoe chips.  Enough of that though. On happier news, it's my "friend"'s, b-day today, and she seems pretty happy recently. I just greeted her a few minutes ago on aim. I still haven't seen her in like 3 weeks, which sucks, and I haven't talked to her in about 2. It's nice to talk to her again.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      STUPID FUCKEN SCHOOL!!!  Well summer school starts today and I'm here at home typing this. Well I didn't get my schedule in the mail so I go there this morning to see what's up and I find out that they didn't even schedule my classes. One of them was pretty much a required class and I have to take it if I want to keep the classes I want for next year, which is gov't. The other one is Statistics, a class I need to take if I want be on the same page as everybody else for AP Calculus. I really can't afford to play catch-up right now. This is completely not my fault and is all staff error. I remember scheduling those classes with my councilor, I even wrote them down for her on a sheet of paper. Pretty much the only thing I could do right now is go again tomorrow, since that's the day people go to school to schedule summer school classes that weren't already scheduled.  To top it all off, I've been feeling really sick lately, I think it's a cold, but it's not like anything I've felt before. It's not really that bad, but I hate it, I also have a sore throat, that's even hindering my singing, I cough after every line.   The last 5 days have been hell for me, and I'm getting really easily irritated by everything. So to anybody that I've caused any greif to in the past week, I'm sorry.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First off I'd like to say, R.I.P. Marlon Brando.  Now about Warped Tour. It was fucken great. I saw Best Interest, New Found Glory, The Sounds, Saosin, Co & Ca, The Early November, Thursday, Story of the Year, Atmosphere, The Bled, Underoath, and Taking Back Sunday. The line-up could've been alot better, but I really have nothing to complain about since I did get to see Saosin and The Bled, which were the main reasons I came there. Some dude broke his fucken leg like a minute after Saosin started, which was fucken gay since it took the crew about 15 minutes to get him off the stage, everyone was pissed and some even left. I went hardcore dancing which was alot of fun, except I got socked in the face during The Bled and now my right eye is all swollen. It really wouldn't be a problem except I have senior pictures in a few days; I really hope it heals by then. The funny thing is I didn't even notice that my eye was hurting til I want to eat a couple hours later. I also have a bruised hip and thumb, but they're not that big of a deal. Another bad thing was during Saosin I was so dehydrated I couldn't sing along as hard as I could, I almost collapsed after they finished, luckily there was a frozen lemonade stand. Another thing was since I didn't have much to eat cause of lack of money I had this huge headache and after The Bled I almost collaped again, so my friend bought some water. But I really couldn't do anything for Underoath and TBS, so I just stood in the back somewhere and sang along. After that we went to Taco Bell and had some food; now that I could afford. After all that I still have no regrets from what happened, except I really wanted a Bled or Underoath shirt, which I couldn't afford. I really need a job. Oh and I think a highlight of the night was when Adam of TBS hung on the 20 ft. high ceiling during CUTE without the 'E' upside down, that was some crazy shit.  Oh and I saw this girl over there that looked so much like my "friend". That was sort of depressing to see. She didn't want to go anyways cause she didn't like the line-up that much either. God I miss her, I havent talked to her since "that night", and she hasn't been online lately. She's probably the last thing I think of right before I go to sleep every night. Atleast it seems I'm getting used to be "diabetic"(see a couple posts down if you don't know what's up).   On a completely different subject, I still haven't gotten my summer school classes yet which sucks. Now I have to go to school to pick it up. I really hope my councilor didn't fuck up and forgot to schedule my classes, cause I really need those classes or it'll fuck up my whole fall schedule.   urlLink    You bitches buy this shit, it's gonna be great.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                Advanced Big 30 Personality Test Results       Sociability   |||||||||   30%       Aggressiveness   ||||||||||||   34%       Assertiveness   ||||||||||||   38%       Activity Level   |||||||||   26%       Excitement-Seeking   |||||||||||||||   42%       Enthusiasm   |||||||||||||||   50%        Extroversion    ||||||||||||    36%        Trust   |||||||||||||||   46%       Morality   |||||||||||||||   42%       Altruism   |||||||||||||||   46%       Cooperation   |||||||||||||||   46%       Modesty   |||||||||||||||||||||   62%       Sympathy   ||||||||||||||||||   58%        Friendliness    |||||||||||||||    50%        Confidence   |||||||||||||||   46%       Neatness   |||||||||||||||   46%       Dutifulness   |||||||||||||||||||||   62%       Achievement   |||||||||||||||   42%       Self-Discipline   |||||||||   26%       Cautiousness   |||||||||||||||||||||   62%        Orderliness    |||||||||||||||    47%        Anxiety   |||||||||||||||   50%       Volatility   ||||||||||||||||||   58%       Depression   ||||||||||||||||||   54%       Self-Consciousness   ||||||||||||||||||   58%       Impulsiveness   ||||||||||||   38%       Vulnerability   ||||||||||||   38%        Emotional Stability    ||||||||||||||||||    51%        Imagination   |||||||||||||||||||||   70%       Artistic Interests   |||||||||||||||||||||   70%       Introspection   |||||||||||||||||||||   62%       Adventurousness   |||||||||||||||||||||   66%       Intellect   |||||||||||||||||||||   62%       Liberalism   ||||||||||||||||||||||||   78%        Openmindedness    |||||||||||||||||||||    68%       
</post>


</Blog>