<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some weeks make me wonder why I get out of bed.  This has been a month of those weeks and it has just been little things.  Or rather one big thing - the old guy.  Sometimes it really, truly sucks to have married a man with such a deep sense of integrity.  He had a great, stable job, excellent pay, full benefits, retirement, everything.  But the policy of said company was such as to allow the customers to abuse and berate the staff and reward lying with free food.  He couldn't live with himself for having to let people yell, scream, cuss and attack his crew people or having to give free food and refunds to people who were lying about their orders.  So he quit.  Unfortunately, in the two months since then, he's had three other jobs, counting he one he has now and none of them have given us enough of an income.  And, of course, you ask why my ass is sitting here blogging instead of working, well, I'll tell you.    (1)  I have two children, a toddler and a teenager.  And while I hear many say that a teenager can look after themselves, I'd like you to sit down and think about that.  In a world rampant with drugs, sex and lunatics, you want to turn someone vulnerable and impressionable loose in the world without adult supervision?  I don't think so.  The teenager needs more watching than the toddler.  This also hits on the double issue of daycare.  "You have a teenager, she can babysit."  Sure, for two or three hours while I do the grocery shopping, but not for 8 - 10 hours a day while I'm over an hour away.  She's not tempermentally suited for it, she's not responsible enough for it and there are no nearby adults that I'd trust to keep an eye on either or them.  (This isn't to say she's not repsonsible, but it takes lots of nagging and reminding just to get her to feed and water a dog.  I'd come home to find that the toddler hadn't eaten  or been changed since I did it at breakfast 10 hours ago.)  And would you believe that daycare has gone up to nearly $300 a week?!?!  Which brings us to...  (2) By the time you get a second vehicle, insurance, registration, gas for a two hour commute each way and daycare, I would bring home *zip*.  I'd have to make a minumum of $15/hour, which would be $600/wk BEFORE taxes.  I'm sorry, but that is not going to happen.  This isn't to say that I haven't been looking for something.  I've been doing regular weekly searches for online/telecommuting postions for things like data entry and transcription.  I could manage poppping into an office for a meeting or to pick up work, but I think it's important for me to be home, especially during the summer when the teenager is free and roaming loose in the world.  But it's not all bad.  We have food on the table and milk for the baby.  I've actually looked at Wic and food stamps, but I'm not certain I want the gov't in my business.  And, plus, Wic has a new requirement that the baby has to be malnourished to recieve aid.  WTF is up with that???  Your kid has to be starving before they'll help?  I thought Wic was supposed to prevent that?  In more happy news, Her Royal Majesty Queen Bess the Toddler (HRM), is finally beginning to attempt talking and, of course, she starts out by telling her older sister "no".  Which sent me into gales of laughter as the teen ranted. "She told me no!  I can't believe she told me no!"    Okay. A peeve just presented itself.  While I'm blogging, I'm watching the chat roll by in AOL's Pagan Circle.  For the last couple of days we've been enduring the idiocy of one "GeekGothShadow" who seems to think that he's being tormented by demon elves who are in love with him and that the King of the Underworld is trying to possess him.  Just a thought here - STOP SMOKING CRACK!  Learn to distinguish fantasy fiction from real life and *maybe* you might turn into a responsible, contributing member of society rather than some leech.  You're supposedly 21, so act like it!  It never ceases to amaze me how many people come in with these "demons are trying to possess me!" stories.  Just a tip -  You are not important or interesting enough for a demon to bother with.  You were probably drunk and/or stoned at the time and are now experience remorse, regret or guilt and wanting something else to blame for your own stupidity.  Well, sorry, pagans shouldn't play that game as paganism is *supposed* to be a path of personal responsibility.  We don't have a devil or demons to blame for our stupid actions.  We did it, we have to cop to it.  Period.  The End.  Deal with it or seek qualified mental help.  End of rant.    Now back to the topic I started. (Just a warning - I tend to ramble)  The whole work thing for the old guy is getting frustrating.  He's happy driving, no stress, no headaches, no screaming, cussing, violent customers, but he's not getting enough runs to make any money.  Partly because the local offices aren't turning in their runs to Denver in a timely manner and then Denver sits on them before giving them to the dispatcher in Arizona.  This system is completely screwy.  He's making some money from yesterday and today, though. He had a run to Raleigh, NC.  Hopefully he'll be home tonight.  It was nice having the bed to myself for one night, but I wouldn't much like doing it for two nights.  Well, I think that's about it for now, I'm sure there will always be more later.  There's ALWAYS something to set me off.  In the meantime, I feel the urge to write about The Many Adventures of Perfect Pete & Crazy Cahla.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Preface  I’ve spent a great deal of time trying to decide what to write and how to write pertaining to the Nine Virtues.  First and foremost, I had to be certain of my personal understanding of them.  Then I wanted to do something that actually expressed my understanding as opposed to a sterile essay based on syntax and definition.  I’ve also been following the current ADF-Dedicant’s thread regarding myths for our time, so my next thought was to write some sweeping, magnificent and astute parables for the ages.  Who doesn’t want to be a modern Aesop?  But, again, I sat down and thought about what I was doing, what it meant and what I wanted to come of it.  I came to the conclusion that these virtues aren’t only for me.  They are the very things I want to teach and pass on to my children.  That’s why instead of individual essays, I’ve simply composed a letter to my daughters.   Saturday, June 12, 2004  To my girls –  This is the first of a series of pieces that I have to write for my ADF Dedicant’s Program.  After much thought I decided that perhaps this format might be better than any other because these nine virtues are not only important to me, but they are the very things I’ve tried to show and teach to you.  These are not listed in any particular order.  It is my belief that they are all equally important.  I simply went down the list as given.  Modern ideas of wisdom are sketchy and vague at best and fraught with hedonistic over indulgence at worst.  “If it feels good, do it,” is one of the most popular and dangerous examples of modern wisdom that comes to mind as I write.  However, the very best wisdom is learned through experience.  I can lecture for years on moderation, good judgment and common sense, but the only way for you to really learn how to apply this is by doing.  Greater minds than mine have written volumes on the subject.  I will simply say this – wisdom is knowing in your soul what is right and what is wrong and truly understanding that there is a time for all things, including letting go of your children so they can live their own lives even if it isn’t the one you would choose for them.  Andye, you have asked me a very difficult question.  “Why do I have to believe in a god?  Why can’t I just believe in myself?”  To be honest I may never be able to answer that question.  No, that’s not true, I can answer it.  You don’t have to believe in any god.  No one does, but many of us choose to do so.  Why?  Because there are points in your life when no matter how strong you are or you think you are, you simply cannot cope with the things that are happening to you or around you.  Those times when you find yourself beaten, empty and grieving and you look up at the unconcerned sky and shout, “What the fuck?”  For some, this is a breaking point.  For others it can be an affirmation of their faith.   I think it comes to us all at one time or another – a stirring deep in your soul that as you look around it occurs to you that it takes more than random chance and a billion or so years for a single hydrogen atom to become a person.  That maybe, just maybe, someone or something put some thought into and crafted things to be just so, but without taking away the chaos or random chance.  And when you feel this, I hope you explore it rather than choosing to run screaming in the opposite direction.  Now, I’ve gone through all that to get to the next of the virtues – piety.  This isn’t really something you hear about very often, especially in (neo) pagan circles where so many either see all gods as aspects of one homogenous supra-intelligence or as a tool for magical gain.  Essentially, piety is giving our gods, either those we have chosen or those who have chosen us, the service, respect and devotion that is their due.  We do this by observing the holy days with the proper rituals and offerings, or by behaving in ways or taking actions that are in accordance with their Will.  These things bring us closer to them and them to us.  It is this connection that brings us that strength that is sometimes needed to get us through those hard times in life.  Sometime you should both talk to your Grammy.  I don’t know of many others who have that kind of strength and connection, but she does. Vision.  Hmmm.  To be able to see who and what we are is neither easy nor pleasant.  To go further and see beyond ourselves and to see where we belong in the ‘Big Picture” is that most rare of skills.  Some of our greatest leaders and other people who have shaped our world for good or ill were able to see the world for what it was, see it for what it could be and travel the road that leads from one to the other because they believed that it was their duty as a human being to make the possibility a reality.  This is probably the most difficult thing you will ever have to do.  Very few people ever find their real place in the Big Picture and they settle for getting lost in the rat race.  This naturally brings us to courage.  Some say that courage is the ability to act appropriately in the face of danger.  Courage can be as simple as looking into the mirror and accepting what you see or standing up in defense of another’s rights.  Both are important.  Courage is what gives us the strength to stand up, square our shoulders and step out from the crowd and say “No!  That’s not right!”  It’s what gives a normal person the ability to run into a burning house in order to save another.  Even in the most ordinary circumstances courage separates those who can from those who cannot.  Another virtue that seems to have gotten lost in the modern world is this next one.  Integrity.  This covers a wide range of things:  honesty, fairness, respect and honor.  All of these things involve knowing what is right and what is wrong and acting on that knowledge.  Many people will tell you that there is no clearly defined right and wrong, that everything is shades of gray.  I do no believe this.  There is right and there is wrong, period.  White lies are still lies; killing is killing, even when you have no other choice.  It doesn’t make it better, it doesn’t make it right.  It only makes it necessary for survival.  I guess that’s the most important part of integrity, being honest about why you take the actions that you take.  Lies and secrets undermine and eat away at your sense of self and destroy not only your integrity but your sense of self.  This is true even if you never “get caught” by another person.  One person will always know what you have done and you have to face that person in the mirror on a daily basis.  Just look to your father as an example for this one.  I’ve never seen anyone with more integrity.  And when all else fails, just keep swimming, just keep swimming.  Perseverance is often confused with or even mistaken for obsession.  I see obsession as the ruthless pursuit of an idea not be good for you.  Perseverance is much more quite and subtle.  It’s that quiet voice that tells you that you can do it and then helps you keep going no matter what.  Just remember Dory who shows us perseverance in the face of not having a single clue as to what is going on. “Just keep swimming… Just keep swimming… Swimming, swimming…”  To be gracious, appreciative, generous and kind are also qualities lost in this modern rush as we hurry to get everything we can for ourselves.  To be hospitable or to show hospitality means that we are considerate, generous, entertaining hosts and polite, appreciative, attentive guests.  We don’t need special occasions to show hospitality.  It can be in a simple Monday night meatloaf or a cake for a neighbor who is feeling a bit low.  True hospitality is a generous spirit that does not give in a condescending matter, but gives freely in love and compassion.  Moderation.  I’m sure you’ve heard me preach on this many times and I’m just as sure that you’ll get to hear it many more times.  One of my favorite quotes is from Marcus Aurelius.  “There is a proper dignity and proportion to be observed in the performance of every act of life.”  Striving for balance in a world that caters to extremes is no easy feat.  This doesn’t mean, however, that you shouldn’t express yourself or what you feel.  Be passionate when you need to be and quiet when it is the right moment.  I want you to know boundless joy and deep sorrow in their proper turn, but I don’t want you to loose yourself in either.  Being secure and mindful of who you are, what you need and a proper perspective of the Big Picture will help you keep things in balance.  Go forth, be fruitful and multiply; well, maybe not quite yet.  There are so many more ways to have a fertile life.  Be endless in your creativity, curiosity and imagination.  Be a solid, productive member of society.  Appreciate and recognize all the wonderful and varied things in the world around you.  Share your gifts and talents with others and not only will you have enriched someone else’s life, but they in their turn may enrich yours by sharing their gifts.    These are just some of the things I hope I can manage to teach you.  It’s my belief that these things are important for society as a whole to function and for the individual to live a good life with few regrets.  All my love to you both –  M. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>