<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am whole-heartedly amazed at what is considered a sport.  Take for instance, football.  Summary: twenty-two guys on a field, trying to kill each other.  Run a definition of that sort by any guy and they will agree with you.  Into Thin Air is a re-counting of the 1996 Mount Everest Tragedy.  I don’t recall any headlines about it, but then I wasn’t much of a news watcher.  Still aren’t much of one.  But I digress.  The sport of “mountain climbing” has got to be one of the strangest – even stranger than football.  The physical suffering that these people go through in order climb to the top of something “because it is there” is extraordinary.  My mind reels to absorb the idea of walked up a wall of ice using crampons, two inch spikes that attach to the back of a climbers boot.  Crampons provide the necessary grip on a gripless surface.  The title is apt also.  They don’t use oxygen the whole time.  Instead their bodies are allowed to acclimate to the progressively thinner air.  If this is done too quickly they can develop HACE which is a nasty condition where the liquid is forced from the cells it is supposed to be in, causing bleeding internally, specifically the lungs. As I read, I hope to understand what drives the men and women who push themselves to such high altitudes, risking their lives for the sake of climbing “because it is there.” 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Interspersed in my stack of books to read are novels of a dubious sort.  The ubiquitous “romance” novel.  Anyone who reads the aforementioned genre knows that two classes exist – the good and the bad.  Jude Devearux is classified as “the good.”  Well-written, developed plots, intriguing characters and no heaving bosoms.  Her latest offering proves that she hasn’t lost her touch.  (Some selections in recent years have cast doubt on this proclamation.)  The main characters – Ford and Jackie – are stereotypes that everyone recognizes.  Ford is the overweight, food-loving, nice underneath everything guy, while Jackie is the slim, trim, healthy woman.  The extremes of where most of us either are or want to be.  The refreshing point was having the point of view switch between the two characters with each chapter.  Events were seen through both pairs of eyes, with enough details to show that everyone views the same events from their own perspective.  Accomplished with effect and no detraction from the story – how two terrible different people fall in love. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The tag line on the cover is "A story of Violent Faith."  I anticipated a David Koresh like religion; instead I got Mormonism.  According to the author, for every tax dollar paid, the residents of Colorado city receive $8 in service.  In comparison, a nearby Indian reservation receives $1 for every $2 paid.  Nice return on investment.  They hold no compunction about screwing the government and fellow tax payers.  It's all a means of screwing the beast that oppresses them.  To be fair and accurate, these are the Mormons that believe polygamy is a "God-ordained, God-pleasing" practice.  Not all Mormons are like this, but their religion does require some objective researching.   urlLink And plenty is available.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Clara, wife of Alejandro “Sandy” Stern, suffers from a disease that most wouldn’t even think of as one.  Every day she gets up and struggles to stay alive.  Only Sandy doesn’t find this out, until the end of the book.  Not because she spends each day working through the problem, but rather because the book begins with her suicide.  This novel had a variety of strings that seemed unrelated, but given the setting, the reader had to expect that all would tie together at the end.  And they did, neatly so.  I liked the story, liked the details and the plot development.  The main problem was the language – very stiff and formal.  It wasn’t a struggle to read, but rather a hindrance.  I have another of Scott Turow’s books that I picked up at a rummage sale.  I’ll try it and see if it is any better.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A sequel that doesn't require a read of its predessor always makes my list of good books.&nbsp; Amy Thomas -- the main character -- has a type A personality that has left everyone I've loaned it to laughing their heads off.   My favorite feature is the usage of footnotes to further illustrate and add to already humorous situations.&nbsp; If you've ever been pregnant, known someone who has, or thought about being pregnant, this is a must read. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A very twisted sort of book.  It starts one way, goes another, and ends with a bang.  I loved it.  Kevin developed the characters in a believable, accurate sense.  Even his female characters are good -- not the floozies and bimbos that are found in many of the murder mysteries.  Nor are the female characters static, the other extreme often found.  Highly recommended.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If you like the books without controversy -- this is Dan Brown's best.  If you like the discussion that controversy generally brings, than Angels & Demons or The DaVinci code is for you.  Either way, he is still a great author.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Green Mars is actually the next title in the series -- sorry.  And I am going to postpone reading it.  I just got a title from the library that I reserved in April -- the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Universe by Douglas Adams.  He is a British author; some of the humor is over my head.  But it is good so far.  The author worked with the Monty Python Troupe for a while, to give you an indication of what it is like.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've finished other books lately.  I just didn't feel like posting about them.  But I want to document that they were read anyway...   urlLink True Betrayals  by Nora Roberts  urlLink Birthright  by Nora Roberts  urlLink The DaVinci Code  by Dan Brown -- One note -- super good book.  Totally throws traditional Christian thinking on its ear.  I can see why a Potter like following has developed.  If I have time, I may become obsessed.  Prosperity and all.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I read this book several years ago when I was in college.  A high schooler that I worked with recommended it and loaned me a copy.  With the renewed promises of space exploration, I got to thinking of colonies on Mars.  Red Planet is the first of a trilogy that explores how colonization on Mars may go.  It's pretty deep in spots, and excellent throughout.  I just picked up the sequel, Blue Mars, at the local library.  (God bless them for feeding my reading addiction.)  I'm thrilled to start this next chapter of theoretical colonization of Mars.  I'll let you know how it goes.
     
    
</post>


<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was able to play piano for the first time in years last night.  I’m rusty, to be sure.  But muscle memory is an amazing thing.  Some of the passages needed specific fingerings and I was able to hit it dead on even though five or six years have passed.  I wasn’t ever a fantastic player, but adequate.  Now that I have kids, I want them to have music in the house.  The relationship to math is great.  Fractions always seemed easier once I understood whole notes vs half notes vs quarter notes.  Any advantage children can have will be needed in this world.  And I know enough to teach them basics, even if I could never teach them to be masters.  But if all they walk away with is a love of music, an understanding of the beauty, then truly, I’ve passed wonder onto the next generation.  

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Max is the dj on a local station that I regularly listen to.  He regularly contributes  urlLink the Scene , a local entertainment calendar with a few columns, features, etc.  The  urlLink article  for May concurs conclusively with my views on censorship.  “If things said or heard on a rock station offend you, here's an idea ... CHANGE THE FREAKING DIAL, MORON!  It’s a familiar mantra, but it still holds true. Stop trying to ruin everyone else’s fun. You’re like that tattle-tale hall monitor who never got over being stuffed in a garbage can on a weekly basis. You’re no better than the dumb-ass old lady who sued McD's because the damn coffee was too hot. IT'S COFFEE YOU IDIOT!”  In other words, take a stand, be responsible for your own actions and stop laying the blame on others.  

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   More days than not, my work is on a computer.  And more days than not, I sit and wait for it to process.  Usually I don’t mind.  I work on “personal” projects in the mean time, for instance, my writing.  But today, I’m trying to archive information from Microsoft Access.  I don’t know what is causing the slow running sequence, but it is pushing my limits of “what can I do while the computer works” creativity.  I’ve updated as much as I care to on my PDA, I’ve visited with co-workers as much as I care to, I’ve cleaned out the miscellaneous papers and notes that roost on my desk.  I’m really at a loss.  It’s only a matter of time before one of my co-workers notices that I’m not doing much and started writing nasty notes about me.  I really should try to be nicer to them.  

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I love to read.  If I could figure out how to get paid to read, I change careers in a heart beat.  To that ends, I'm starting another blog, specifically for the books I read.  While I don't read as much as I did prior to husband and kids, I still average 4-5 books a month.  (I don't watch much television or do as much house work as I should.)  The URL is http://book-club-at-434.blogspot.com/.  Give it a whirl and see if my tastes and views match yours.   

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another member from the Cast of the Co-Workers, this fellow is easily recognized by his slinking appearance, generally 10-15 minutes after the start of work.  He quickly rushes to his assigned seat, as everyone else is busy checking emails, voicemails, and the last crisis from yesterday.  Lunch is taken a few minutes early and lasts a few minutes too long.  Afterall who counts five or ten minutes here and there?  Time cards do little catch the Scam Artist; the honor system is still used and no one punches a card.  Special projects are carefully padded with extra time, so as to cushion their fall.  Appearances must be maintained.  Continuation of the great knowledge hoax perpetuates.  Unwilling to jeopardize their own foibles, no one brings the Boss's attention to the hours shaving from the 40 hour work week by the Scam Artist. 

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ahhh...the sun peaks over the edge of the umbrella, shining in gloriously, taunting its brilliance to those who hide from it.  The tree swaying in the gentle breeze, toying its leafy branches in its tantalizing way.  Cool drops from an icy drink drip onto bare skin as a straw connects with moist lips.  And as I stare at the paper filled wall, the vision is broken by the Whining Office Intern.  Haven't met this pleasant individual yet, eh?  Give it time.  Easily recognized, often suffering from last night's debauchery, revelry and shenanigans the Whining Office Intern is aghast to find out that, yet again, the world is plotting against her.  Not only did she find out that her apartment lease ends in the middle of finals week -- GASP! -- now she is homeless for three months.  And not only is this information shared with the landlord, Mom, Dad and fellow roommates, it is also shared with Mom (again), Dad (again), fellow roommates (again), sympathetic friends, meandering passers-by and everyone who dwells within the vicinity of the wondrous place I like to call "Cubeland."  Once visited, the nuances of Cubeland reveal themselves.  The smells from lunch.  Personal phones calls that really ought to have remained personal.  Bodily functions that are better performed in the bathroom.  Business calls that should have been subjected to a course in "Political Correctness:  Yes, you too can get what you want without yelling."  The various faces change, but the stereotypes remain.  Lingering among the living like the ghosts they should be.  Will they ever truly leave?  Or should I place the local diocese on speed dial?   

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   People who argue for censorship are befuddling.  They want to control what is printed, said, written, etc.  What they are really trying to do is push their point of view on to the reader.  Instead of censoring what should be printed, said, written, etc. the time should be taken to educate.  If people are educated, they will recognize for themselves what is good and worthy.  And censorship will occur for themselves.  Choose what they want to expose themselves to rather than having some other values doing it.  In truth we need not censorship, but rather values. As to what set of values, another debate-worth point is raised.  Perhaps at another time.  

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Mostly an experiment.  A check to see if I have anything to say that is interesting.  If I do, it will be found.  It's the "Field of Dreams" experiment.  And I'm curious to see how this all works.  I'm proficient in Excel.  Now I need a new challenge.  As if making it through to the end of the day wasn't quite enough.  

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am the biggest grinch when it comes to Christmas.  Just call me Scrooge, because I see little or no point in giving gifts to adults.  Take my husband, for example.  He is one of the worst people to shop for.  And my brother has the same problem.  They mention that they would like something.  Word gets around and eventually some one buys it for them.  Two weeks before Christmas, they’ve decided that the item cannot be lived without for one moment longer.  Immediately they rush to the nearest shopping compound and buy it for themselves.  Meantime’s, I look like an ass as I’m the one who suggested that it would be a great gift.  I usually start to cultivate a list during the summer – who do I need to buy for, ideas of what I could get them.  And then I watch for sales.  But this year, I’d really like to forgo it all together.  My kids are little; how many more toys do they really need?  If Hubby-dear wants something, he just buys it anyway.  And I can’t think of much that I would like except more time.  I know I didn’t always have this feeling of meanness that looms larger as the 25th grows closer.  I’m still going to start the list and make a “wish list” for my own family.  I just hope that it helps to alleviate the problem and not perpetuate it.  

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My company's official policy on internet and email usage is "work-related" only.  The moral dilemma is this -- if I spend five minutes to post to my blog, am I committing as horrendous a sin as my co-worker who spends anywhere from 30 to 45 minutes talking baseball or football or the level of intoxication reached last night?  I am of the opinion that a tracking device should be installed to check how long conversations of this sort last.  If they monitor what websites I go to, shouldn't conversations be tracked as well?  Productivity would go through the roof. 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A fascinating way to share books with other book lovers.  I went to the local Pick and Save, thinking it would be easy to find an out of place book, but after shopping and browsing for 45 minutes, I gave up.  Now, the hard part is deciding if has been found and not registered yet or if it still there.  I wish they would have given a hint of some sort. 

						
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Is it any wonder that I am overweight?  You can be pleasant and say stuff like "I'm still losing the baby fat," but get real.  The whole nation is fat.  Better bang for our buck at fast food places means that "super-sized" isn't an option, but part of the meal now.  If you aren't sure what I mean, check out Hardee's.  The ones in town have a small, medium and large combo options.  The small drink is a 24 oz cup.  It only gets worse from there.  Added to the conundrum of fast food places is the diet programs -- all backed by scientific evidence that completely contradicts one another.  Is eating red meat good or bad for you?  I couldn't even get a nurse to answer the question.  Her response was "I wouldn't ever recommend it as the best way to get iron."  If people had to go back to hunting and gathering, we'd starve.  That's the conclusion I've come to as Hubby-dear has come home from yet another fishing expedition sans fish.  And with the amount of rain has fallen upon us this year, the garden isn't so good either.  It's still in the starter cups, dying a slow death.  In the mean time, I'll keep running after my kids and eating the stuff I think is good for me while attempting to stay away from large boxes of chocolate.  I know what a big box of Godiva does by my ass, even if the scientists aren't quite sure. 

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am no fan of Wal-Mart for reasons like this article states.  I need to figure out how to follow this case.  I'm extremely curious.  Ah, yes...a whole website devoted to publicizing the crimes of Wal-Mart ---  urlLink Wal-Mart Watch.  

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Wired News: Heavy Betting on Election Domains  is a cool business to be in, depending on what side you are on.  The premise is that the Bush campaign was lazy and let a very searchable term slip by.  Now an anti-Bush support owns it.   urlLink The site  is a parody of what an election site may be like.  Whether I'm pro-Bush or pro-Kerry is quite irrelevant.  It is wrong to portray the site as legitimate.  It adds to the problem facing campaigns everywhere at every level.  It is one thing to disagree with politics and policy.  It is quite another to misquote and misprint views and promises.  Especially when the person is the leader of the country.  Regardless of what is thought of the man, respect the office. 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm tired of working at work.  I want to be one of those types that sits in their jammies all day and does fun things.  I want to close big deals and hold conferences while doing laundry.  I want to have a 19 inch LCD screen at my house, not at my job.  I wish I worked for someone who would allow telecommuting.  Hell, right now I'd even settle for a boss that talked to me on a somewhat regular basis.  He operates more on the "if you don't hear from me, everything is good" philosophy.  The best part about that, though, is I don't even work for him.  I'm "on loan" to another department and have been for the last six months.  My annual review is rapidly approaching.  Should make for an interesting time.  Especially when you consider that my supervisor reviews based on what he thinks should be done, rather than what is actually accomplished.  Ain't life grand? 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I recently moved to a new house with all my stuff, all of Hubby-dear's stuff and all of my mom's stuff.  (She lives with us as child care is outrageously priced.)  As  urlLink this article  states...   "As a society we're called 'consumers.' Last year the president told us to go shop as our patriotic duty. When we hear this, it's all about stuff -- not what you make, but what you do with it."   I just need to look in my garage, open my cupboards, or trip, again, over Thomas the Train to know my house is very guilty of too much stuff.  And we don't do as much with it as we should.  What really scares me is that my kids will learn from me...and my pack-rat husband...and my mother whose's mantra is "it was great-aunt So and So's."  They are doomed. 

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A day late anyway, is better than not at all.  We had a fantastic day in the Oshkosh Area.  I was able to wrangle the kids before they woke anybody up.  We walked to the nearest gas station for the all-important chocolate milk and the morning paper.  And once everyone was going, our day went to Green Bay to the  urlLink National Railroad Museum .  The kids were thrilled, but the best comment I heard was from the 4-year-old on the train ride.  The whistle blows, the passenger car lurches forward and he yells out, "Go Faster!"  He was feeling the need for speed.  After lunch at  urlLink Lambeau Field , Hubby-dear drove the sleepyheads home again.  Where dinner requests were fulfilled with cake.  What a wonderful way to spend the day! 

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink The MegaPenny Project  would be great for anyone with curious kids -- teacher, parent or childcare provider.  Great way to visualize some super huge numbers 

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I know, I know, with the  urlLink plethora  of games available, I should be able to find something more challeging that Minesweep.  But I just have to say...  I just scored 148 in the Intermediate level!  Thanks, I'm better now. 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When money is discovered inside the home, various rules apply.  These are our house rules.  1.  Any money found is fair game -- home team and vistors alike. 2.  Money found in the laundry is payment for services rendered -- regardless of denomination. 3.  Change is added to the piggy bank -- how else do the kids get to go to college? 4.  Change can be claimed after twelve hours. 5.  Paper can be claimed after twenty-four hours. 6.  Money in containers is considered "claimed." 7.  All rules are void when cleaning.  Any money found during cleaning process is considered fair game. 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The eleven month old was terrible last night.  Any time I was more than two feet away from him, he would cry and scream.  It was frightful, to say the least.  I know that when they start to walk, they become more clingy.  But shouldn't a person be able to pee when necessary? 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday's mail brought an invitation to a shower that I have no desire to go to.  It's for an old friend that through time and circumstances the friendship has waned.  I appreciate the gesture.  We are not to the point where it would be like asking for a gift.  We are still doing the "my life is so busy" bit.  But how do you break it off?  Should it be just allowed to die gracefully, through neglect?  Or should there be an aburpt ending, through a confrontation of sorts?  I'm at a loss, quite frankly.  I could go through the various points and reasons I have for not wanting to continue the relationship, but I fear that the individual would be recognized.  Not something that I want to do as we have mutual friends who might read this.  I do have bigger reasons than "my life is busy."  Screw that.  Everyone's life is busy.  Any advice out for the situation?  Have you gone through the graceful demise?  Or the confrontation?  What knowledge can I glean from your experiences? 

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Lurking on the countertop of the ladies restroom in my department are several bottles of lotion, hairspray and soap that never decrease in volume.  It is the old age home for unwanted toiletries.  I myself have contributed to the items -- a bottle of lotion -- that was donated as a gift for my baby shower.  The recipient of said lotion did not care for the scent.  And, I must admit, it leaves the user feeling the urge to use lotion.  Not a good recommendation.  I hate to throw it out.  And now that the baby is 11 months old and there it sits, waiting, content unchanged, I'm humored by its presence.  Not one person has dared to try it, yet no one throws it away.  I'm going to leave it there.  Perhaps in ten or twelve years, when I'm a vice president, I'll get a chuckle when I return to the department and there it sits, along with all of the other unwanted jars and bottles that seem to accumulate on countertops everywhere. 

						
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Being an overly obsessed HP fan, I bide my time before going to see the movies.  I'm not an opening night junky - although seeing kids compare it to the book, with the movie falling short always tickles my funny bone.  No, I'd rather wait until the house isn't going to be packed, so I am free to express whatever criticism come to mind with the poor person who was willing to go with me.  (I feel for them as I have one of those detail soaked brains that is capable of not only telling you that the dialogue isn't verbatium, but what it should have been.)  It makes for an interesting time at the show.  But last night as I waited for the events I knew were to occur, I thought of something.  J.K. is part of the process.  Some of the deviations were brilliantly appropriate.  If I change my prospective just a bit, rather than a travesty that ruins the movie, I could see it as a tickle for those individuals like myself.  How else can we be thrilled and amazed by plot twists when we know the very next word that will be said?  The visual of the movie merely serves to emphasis the points that the medium cannot.  Its limitations are such that developement must be faster -- 2 1/2 hours rathers than 433 pages.  The characters must manuever through their scenes in the extreme ends of their personalities.  Action packed though it is, the book still contains more that has been left out.  If taken simply for a movie, and not a knock-off of a book, it was well done, well developed and well, decent.  But the book was still better. 

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I belong to a group at Yahoo called  urlLink Freecycle . The idea is rather than take it to the curb, offer it to people who might have a good home for it.  The idea is fantastic.  I've felt the benefits of someone else's generousity.  The basketball hoop is great!  Thanks again, Becky.  But some people just don't get the concept.  The postings today included a request for X-box games.  Who is going to give away Xbox games?  Get real.  Or one guy was looking for a Palm.  In spirit the postings are supposed to be giving, not requesting.  It's okay to request, but of the 12 that resided in my folder, not one was an offer to give.  Each one was looking for something for nothing.  I'm not going to give up on it.  I love the idea.  As I go through the nooks and crannies of my house, I'm finding a few things to post.  And perhaps, when the "wanted" aren't getting the results they want, the group will be left with those who understand the concepts of generousity and giving. 

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Writer's Digest offers a month's worth of writing prompts for the uninspired.  I religiously save the list, intending to get to it every day.  After all, what's 5 or 6 minutes of my time for a creative writing exercise?  But it just never seems to happen.  As I think it over how I want to shape and grow my blog, I'm struck by the coincidence that the format provides.  Why not use the blog as a record of my creative genius?  It would be simple, really.  I'll think it over and let you know.  If I do use their prompts in this forum, I'll probably still have my own "originals."  The dilemma now lies in whether or not I mark them as such.  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is a struggle to keep my eyes open.  All I really want to do is lay on my floor and sleep.  The working environment really isn't keen on that sort of thing, nor is my floor clean enough for me to really consider it.  The baby is teething.  The sitter just called asking if it would be okay to give him some medicine.  It's going to be a long night of crabbiness at our household. 

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Online Books, Poems, Short Stories - Read Print   Want to read a book and only have access to the web?  Read Print gives web users the opportunity to read the classics on the web.  The catch -- the book must be public domain or printed before 1920.  Unless you like classics, the titles won't be of interest. 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If has happened again.  The office fridge is void of my icy cold soda.  The long anticipated carbonation won’t be enjoyed with my luncheon feast.  The affects of caffeine depravation are bound to kick in during the one o’clock meeting.  Who took my soda?!  What tormented soul would do such a thing?  Is it one of the interns?  The water bottle gossip?  The know-it-all next door?  Really, it’s a $0.50 can of pop.  It shouldn’t matter this much.  But it was right on top of my salad.  It was obviously somebody’s, even though it didn’t have a label.  Instead, I’m suffering through the lukewarm substitute that the reserve supply offered.  The caffeine benefits are the same, even though the enjoyment level plummeted.  Therefore, I urge you, respect your co-workers.  If isn’t yours, don’t take it.  

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My uncle Mel found out in April that he had cancer.  On Sunday, May 30, we were called and told to come to South Dakota for his last hours.  He passed away at 8:30 that night, a mere 6 hours after we got there.  I sat, with my myriad of relatives, remembering, talking and waiting.  I’ve never lived for such a long time.  The worst wasn’t knowing that he was going to die, it was waiting for it.  The type of cancer was harsh and unforgiving to a man who lived healthier than most I know.  And as I sat, waiting, I couldn’t help but think of how Mel had just retired, with his wife to do so also in two months.  The unfairness of it screamed its protests to all who listened.  All the savings, all the planning was for naught.  In a cruel trick, everything that they had waited for was gone.  But Mel left something large than himself.  Brothers and sisters were drawn together, for both laughter and tears.  Future plans are becoming present plans.  And what truly matters has been thrust forward with all that is petty behind it.  I’m going to miss Mel.  But I was able to say good-bye the way that I wanted to.  And I’m starting to get my priorities in order.  Life is much more than doing what you have to.  It’s about doing what you enjoy.  Every day, not just at the end. 

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Nascar is a boring sport.  Watching drivers go around the track 500 times, waiting for a crash is not my idea of entertainment.  I propose the following to improve its appeal and interest level.  1)  Cut the number of laps down.  I heard one driver on the local radio station say that it really comes down to the last 30 or so laps.  Why bother to have the first 470?  Cut the number of laps to 50.  Then we'll see who is really skilled.  2)  Take all of the ranking numbers.  Draw two of them from a bucket.  Make them switch places.  Let's see how well the third place driver does if he has to start at 47th.  3)  Base the starting line-up on the amount of money that sponsers give.  After all, more money equals a better car and a better driver, right?  4)  Base the starting line-up on a 500 list or one of the other company ranking lists that exists.  These are just a few of the changes I would make if I were in charge of Nascar.  I'm sure all think of more as I am forced to watch it on Sunday as it dominates all programming on that day. 

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A new blog for me to read.  I like his turn of phrase.  The Brits always have a little different perspective on things. 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is man is my new idol.  He only works part time and spends the rest of his day reviewing books.  I would lean towards fiction, if I could do this.  But the variety is amazing.  I'm going to have to read some.  Maybe I'll even find a few that I would be willing to check out. 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Need an answer?  Go  urlLink here .  Got an answer?  Let the world  urlLink know it . 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This site is fun, fully interactive and informative.  Words are ranked according to usage.  "The" is the most used word in the world.  "Stacie" isn't in the archive - by that spelling anyway.  "Penney" is; it comes in 42,964th.  One hundred is "got," while "milk" is 2,083rd.  I would think that the proliferation of the phrase "got milk" would have affected the placement of "milk."  Evidently not. 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't mind getting older; it's inevitable. I don't mind not being "cool" anymore either -- not that I was to start with. I don't mind the gray hair that I find either.  What I do mind that that the three gray hairs have decided to sprout along my part line. No matter how I style my hair, there they are, bright and shiny for the whole world to see.  I haven't been pulling them, but I gotta figure out a way to get them to hid under the others. A little bit, at least.  

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The whole concept of time travel fascinates me.  I'm linking to this site so I can look into it further.  I don't have time to right now, as I am, in theory, working. 

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You know how some sights require that you register in order to use them?  Check at Bugmenot.com and use a fake registration to avoid all of those nasty junk emails. 

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The worst thing about living in Oshkosh is the sevre lack of fantastic pizza.  On Friday I was determined to fix this and order a pizza from Boxcar Eddie's, as I was going to be in Fond du Lac and would be able to pick it up for supper.  Their Chicago style is 6.5 lbs of pizza, measuring 14 inches across.  With three toppings it was $18.47.  It fed my family for three meals -- now that's saying something!  I'm going to have to make this a once a month trip, regardless of whether or not I'm in FdL.  It's just too good to miss.  And nothing in Oshkosh even comes close. 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My husband and I went to a movie together for the first time in I don't know how long.  Considering it generally cost us $17.00 just to walk in the door, we rent instead of visiting the local theater.  I had to make an exception for Bourne Supremacy.  Matt Damon is a wonderful Jason Bourne.  The best part of this movie was that I had not read the book first.  Amazing, eh?  I started in when I was in high school, after finishing the Bourne Identity, but never completed it.  Probably needed to return it to the library.  Now that I have seen the movie, most likely I will read it.  The first book/movie were different without being annoying.  I'll probably find the same of the second set. 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   All I can say is, "About freakin' time."  If you are smart enough to be on the show then you should be able to rack up the money like this guy has. 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yep -- you read that right, folks.  The short and sweet of it is “the surgeons have to have someone to practice on.”  And this statement coming from an Army spokes WOMAN .  What a crock of bs.  I'll need to find and read the New Yorker article this is based on.  There simply has to be more to it than this is showing. 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I knew there was a difference.&nbsp; Afterall, I have broadband at work...but the network makes it slow...and as I don't do the same stuff here (aka home)&nbsp;that I do there (aka the hell hole) I'm noticing it more tonight with my new connection.  

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Now I just need my modem and life will be faster.&nbsp; If I don't get it by Friday, I'm going to have to call.&nbsp; Otherwise I'll need to renew my dial-up ISP for another month.   

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   J-Walk's blog always has interesting things to look at, especially when I should be doing work-related tasks.  What really makes the blog, though, is the comments and discussions through them.  If read regularly, individuals become as familar as J-Walk.  This discussion is quite similar to one recently had at my own home.  I love seeing how the views and opinions of those far from me relate to my own. 

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     As I am tired of everyone in my house complaining about my ISP being incredibly slow, I weighed the options of fast service vs. the cost of service.&nbsp; While I'm not upgrading to the 3 gig service provided by the location broadband, I did find  urlLink a nice DSL package  that was reasonable for the amount of time we spend on the Internet.    I made all necessary arrangements and submitted the application.&nbsp; On Friday the technician tests my line and says its fine; expect the modem in a few days.    My line may be fine for DSL, but it sucks for the telephone. Ever since he was there I have had no phone service. It makes everything a bit tricky as this is the time of the month that all the credit cards are due and I depend upon my internet connection to keep my buddies Discover and Mastercard happy.&nbsp; So, instead, we used cell phones all weekend and will continue to do so until further notice. If you tried to call over the weekend, sorry, we weren't intentionally ignoring you...maybe (tee-hee).    

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink This article  made me laugh so hard.  I have got to find a job with this company.  They answer the email requests from the scammer -- in this case the Nigerian Prince who just needs to borrow your bank account for a few days to get some money out of his country.  But the tables are turned when the responder agrees, only if the Nigerian Prince will join his church.  You've got to read it! 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I hate it when I am assigned a task that is menial and pointless.  It's even worse when I have another task that is meaningful and interesting but not for my boss.  My boss must think I have the brain of a betta fish and enjoy looking up archane information manually for thousands of parts. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The baby turns 1 tomorrow.  I'm not one of those nostalgic moms who can't believe that a whole year has passed.  He came out at 6lbs. 9oz.  He now weighs 27 or 28 lbs.  He eats everything in sight -- even if it isn't food.  He sleeps through the night, even if he is an early riser.  He walks with few falls and says two or three words -- depending on how you listen.  He has a head full of blond curls and loves to play in water -- any water, even the dog's dish.  Every day I can see that he is learning something new.  I don't need a calendar to tell me that a year has passed.  I just need to look at Jonathon. 

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Does any school system actually offer courses in shorthand?  I wonder, if taught early enough in schools, would it be beneficial in high school or college?  I know from experience that note taking during lectures requires an expertise that cannot be perfected until one has almost reached the end of the semster.  Each lecturer's style and test formats limit the ability to effectively take notes until then.  Maybe I'll experiment on my kids and see if it would make a difference.  Of course, my kids are under the age of five.  It's going to be a while before I get any results. 

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The above question was recently posed to me by my mother, upon her discovery that I have a website.  "Why?" said she.  "What's the purpose?"  A just question.  A fair question.  Perplexing to answer in simple terms.  True, it takes up time that probably could be better spent.  I always have housework to do afterall (two kids, a dog and husband.  Need I say more?)  True, I'm probably closer to polluting the electronic void than publishing worthwhile endevours, but I know that my posts are more enlightening that some of the other blogs that are out there.  At least I post regularly.  A quick search quickly reveals how many are started with fair to middlin' intentions that are never followed up on.  True, I have some personal writing goals that are being neglected even as we speak, er, type, er, read.  But all forms of writing are good, I argue.  And a writer should spend a portion of each day writing.  In theory, this is a small portion of my writing day.  Praytell, how did I answer said question?  With a shrug and a smile.  Afterall, what truly is the point of doing anything?  Love or money.  And I haven't received any checks in the mail lately... 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I sit at my desk, popping green grapes in my mouth, I notice that the skins don't seem to go down as smoothly as they should.  When I start to pay attention to the food I am consuming, realization awakens in my senses -- the skin is too thick.  While I'm not going to pull out my millimeter measuring devices and start a comparison study, I am going to go with my gut and say that this batch of grapes has extraordinarily thick skin. 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Thanks to everyone for leaving comments.  Getting in touch with some of my oldest -- meaning longest -- friends has been wonderful.  It reminds me of nights in the dorms, or at the apartment.  Trips to Mankato so we could get high on caffiene at the Klatch and share all of the weird thoughts, gripes and laughter.  I miss the people we were and love the ones we've become. 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Next month I'm having a birthday party for the Baby, who will be one year old.  A monumental moment for a child, especially when you factor what they learn in the first year.  The Baby has learned to walk.  He runs, really, with his arms straight in the air.  He can go from person to person and is starting to walk to inanimate objects as well.  And he has been doing this for about a month.  The problem is, who do you invite to a party for a one year old?  I want to invite people he knows, who make a point of knowing him, regardless of distance.  Unfortunately, we have some family members who simply assume that we are going to have something and that they will be invited.  Any other day they don't make the 60 minute drive to visit.  Really, what makes the birthday so special then?  It makes my heart tear just a little to be so calluous.  But if it isn't worth the time on an ordinary day, why make an annual visit?  They've missed watching him take the first tottering steps and subsequent falls.  His first word (depending on who you ask) was "Elle," the dog.  It continues to be his favorite as well.  He can eat as much ice cream as his four year old brother and devours ravoli at the same speed.  If someone is upstairs, he can climb them in the time it takes for me to blow my nose and throw the tissue away.  He loves lift the flap books and playing with Thomas the Train.  These are the things that are important, not watching him eat cake.  One day doesn't make a difference.  One day thirty times will. 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Last night, after discovering that we were out of the preferred cereal for this morning's breakfast, we headed to the nearest grocery store to get another box of "Shrek."  (Marshmallows, kids, it's all good.)  On this particular box, on this particular day, I happened to notice the expiration date -- January 2005.  After checking the calendar and confirming, yep, it is in fact the middle of summer, a cold fear settled over me.  What kind of perservatives are they putting in my cereal box that it can sit on a shelf for half a year and still be good?  Some kind of study should be done on this...by the way, Tiffany, how is the twinkie? 

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Quick explanation for the new link.  The Scene is a local monthly that has great writing while swinging widely to the left. Every issue has good points of view, good variety of content and the listing for all of the "cultural" events in the area. The online edition is the same as the paper copy which is available for free around the Valley.  I was disappointed that the online edition is still last month's copy. The cover article for August is a great story about Gannett newspapers and the monopoly they've established in NE Wisconsin. It slings as much mud and muck as any political rally, but with facts to back up each and every accusation. And both sides of the story are presented. Cheers to Tony Palmari for the excellent article!   

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just received notification that the network was down on Thursday and Friday.  As if I hadn't noticed as I was unable to access any of my files.  They had a big enough problem that files needed to be restored from a tape back-up.  Thank goodness I spent most of my time of Thursday working the phones and most of Friday waiting to see if I could get back on the network.  Rather productive couple of days, don't you think?  I was lucky compared to some in my department.  They now have to recreate whole spreadsheets that were the entire purpose of being here those two days.  It reminds me of being in college...and yes, we use the same network that they did. 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The baby is teething again.  Which wouldn't be bad, except this is the second battle that has resulted in no teeth.  And he is a true man.  Whiney, whimpery, clinging, and in general miserable.  I'm talking about me.  Or how I would be if I was to give up, admit defeat and act the way I feel.  The poor kid is miserable, I know.  He isn't eating (one of his favorite activities.)  Yesterday he had a few goldfish crackers and half of a Yumsters yogurt.  This from the child who normally eats a cup and a half of mac and cheese.  Obviously, he is ill.  My darling husband, seeing my level of frustration escalate through the day, suggested a sunset boat ride.  Really he was afraid I'd blow my temper on him.  However, I loved the idea and it worked.  The baby was sleeping, afterall.  My mom was able to finish the book she'd picked up at the Library.  And I got to enjoy the wind in my hair, the waves and my dog at my side.  And some good conversation with my husband.  We're at one of those crossroads where we need to decide what we are going to do regarding several aspects of our lives.  The open air is a great place to air the thoughts that had been rattling in both of our heads.  Perhaps I'll share some of the not-so-evil ones with you later... 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The increased number of links may need an explanation.  Rather than tying up my "favorites" folder with all sorts of links and try to figure out some filing system that makes sense, I'm using this as a vehicle for storing them.  Sorry for the lack of thoughts.  I'll try to include more of them in addition to the links.  My brain has been rather empty as of late.  Ta-ta.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I should be running around like mad, reporting logistic related data as it is the first week of the month. However, due to a network outage, I am instead doing my best to look busy. My main attempts at this are to find websites that I can use to "enhance my professional abilities."  Don't be surprised at some of the links I may record for prosperity.  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A good feature if you need a ready-made calendar or certificate.  Microsoft has several templates for most anything you can think of.  I use their fax and memo templates for stuff at work.  They have even thought of hard-working teachers and have included a section for them as well.  Not too shabby. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As if Nascar wasn't bad enough all ready. Can you imagine what would happen to the NFL if they followed the  urlLink same rules ?  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This site should be part of the child birth classes.  After a recent wave of "new babies," I have several names that would belong under the listing of "Let me spell that for you."  Let the child be different of their own accord, not because of the way his/her name is spelled. 

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Of course, this could be adapted to fit the other party, but I favored this version...  There was this new bar in town that everyone was talking about because it had a robot-bartender. A man walks in to see this for himself. He sits at the bar and sure enough, a robot was bartending.  The man orders a drink, and the robot asks him what his IQ is. The man replies that his IQ is 150.  So the robot begins discussing nuclear physics, hydrogen power cells, and the current state of the global atmosphere. The man is amazed. He has to see how good this robot really is. He leaves the bar and comes right back in and sits at the bar.  Again, the robot asks him for his IQ.  This time the man replies "100."  So the robot discusses football, basketball, and the proper way to grill a steak.  The man leaves and comes back in for a third time. This time he tells the robot that his IQ is 50.  The robot replies: "So, are you democrats really going to vote for Kerry?"   (Thanks, Tensie)   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Joke of the day...week...year.  A whole site devoted to the idea of "You might be _____ if..."  And yes, cheese heads have their own listing. 

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Every so often, I will search for myself in various engines, just to see who else is out there bearing the same nom de plume as me.  Addresses.com is fun to use as it also gives the option of using reverse look-ups for phone, email, etc.  I try it every so often on wrong number calls too.  It keeps life interesting. 

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Every time I try to get on the J-Walk website, I'm denied.  I wonder if work found out about it and is blocking access.  Or maybe he is having hosting problems.  Could someone check and let me know?  Thanks. 

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My husband turns 30 this year.  To properly celebrate, we are going to charter a fishing boat for some of his friends.  It all started because I was teasing him about having a "pirate-themed" party so they could do "piratey things."  It evolved into this.  He found  urlLink Dumper Dan's Sportfishing Charters of Sheboygan, WI , an uninformed participant to our diabolical minds.  The piratey things will entail beer drinking, eating, joking, ribbing and perhaps some fishing.  By the way, drop him a line and wish him happy birthday.  He'll thank me later, I know.  rpenney28 at yahoo.com 

						
</post>


</Blog>