<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow.. I don't know where to begin.. this weekend was awesome, camp fires, weenie roasting, marshmellows, live music, in a 3 day period, its great. Got to sleep in a tent too! It leaked on my side so I woked up drenched after it rained but that was no problem. Chilled with Tara most of the weekend, it was really fun!  Got an ace? ;) 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If you've ever wondered what I do, sitting up at 3AM, well, Im educating myself. Most of the time, its on history subjects, such as disease outbreaks and the such. This mornings topics I've been researching are:  - German Measles - Apollo 13 - Challenger Explosion - Chernobyl - Polio  Now, for you people out there thinking "this guy is a sick freak", I'm not. Im just interested in past events, and they don't teach us any of this stuff in school. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I ran across an interesting opinion article today, discussing Microsoft's upcoming Windows OS, "Longhorn", and Linux. Worth a read for all you tech geeks :)  "By the time Longhorn comes out I'm sure everyone will be sick of the subject "windows vs linux." Will longhorn finally destroy that pesky linux and mark another decade of Microsoft's monopoly, or will the underdog come out with a stunning upset and send a multi billion dollar company to it's grave?  Although both those views are pretty far from reality, at least in my opinion, that's what you'll hear a lot of. But this article isn't about that, it's about one side effect of longhorn which I don't think has been considered enough..."   urlLink Read the entire story at OSNews  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For the last ~12 years of my life, I've been an avid Windows user, from 3.1 up to "Longhorn", and over the course of those twelve years I've jumped in and out of the wading pool that is Linux, but I've never found a flavor of Linux that I could stand to use for more than a day or two, mostly because of the bloat and incompatibilites.  And then I found  Gentoo .  Gentoo is a whole different kind of Linux distro. You build your system from the ground up, with what YOU want. You compile the kernel yourself with optimizations for your machine, and using Portage, you can download and compile applications that are optimized for your machine, using your specified settings.  Installation was kind of tough, but once you do it a few times you get the hang of it; now I can recompile the kernel in about 30 minutes flat no problem, and every day I'm learning something new.  I believe if that the people over at Gentoo make an installer for their distro (there is already one available using Red Hat's anaconda system), this could very well surpass Windows, and put the next version of Windows, "Longhorn", to shame.  I'm using X11 as my desktop system, with Gnome as a Desktop Environment, and Metacity as my window manager. Using this combo allows me to make the system look like anything I want (right now I have my UI customized to mimic OS X almost down to a tee which is awesome).  This is awesome, I dont know if I want to switch back to Windows or not! 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>