<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was already half past eleven and Ramki was running late for a training session at office. Sensing that he did not have much of a chance in scoring brownie points with Janaki in this big crowd, Ramki said "Hey folks, its the last day of the week, loads of work at office - me's gotta go..Lets all meet up tomorrow morning at 9 here..Bye!" Janaki started to protest but aware that a pair of eyes were sharply observing her, checked herself in time. Damn Preeti!  "And my fellow country men, do you support this war against terrorism when millions of...." A roar comes from the television across the room (Senator Kerry is on another of his frenzied speeches)   As Venkatesh settled down on the sofa and Ramesh stared at the TV with renewed interest, Preeti ambled towards the kitchen "Hellooo..Is neone home?". Janaki who had wandered into her bedroom to change into her casuals shouted back "My roommate  Vaishnavi's gone shopping - if you want some grub help yourself - or have you still not learnt to cook?" Cursing Janaki under her breath, Preeti returned to the sitting room and flopped on the couch. Venkatesh, seeing how tired Preeti was, offered "You know I make excellent kaapi - can I do it for you? Please please"  Gattu was half asleep in the corner of the room when he heard a slight tap on the door. As the trainer droned on, Gattu managed to take a peek and saw that it was Ramki - late as usual. Quickly letting him in, Gattu enquired about Ramki's morning. Not wanting to let him know about where he had been, Ramki evasively answered "Nothing special yaar.. Overslept" Gattu gave him a long thoughtful stare and replied" Dont lie to me man..Someone called Varads called up at our extension and asked if everything had gone off fine at the airport..???" Ramki shrugged his shoulders and offered no explanation. Gattu stared long and hard at the ceiling.  Time and tide wait for no man...Swooosh.. Its now evening in the US..  Tring Tring  Ramesh lifted the phone off the hook "Hi Appa.. I am fine..studies... going on fine..will surely graduate next year... no appa.. I dont stay out late.. bars? Apdinna ? there are no women in my college..its all men....but... appa...ok..ok.. pls convey my respects to Velu mama..n my love to Annam..ok..Bye."   Venkatesh had no classes the whole of the week. He had interpreted it as divine approval for his mission when he realized that this coincided with Preeti's arrival in NYC. Whistling in happiness, he jumped into his Chevy and started the car "I'll take them to Vittorio's - Preeti loves Italian - and then buy her some flowers and when I get some privacy, bare my heart to her - tis a pity Janaki will be tagging along"   Ramesh had made grand plans of taking Janaki and more importantly, Preeti out to the movies that evening - he wanted to worm his way into Preeti's good books before that twerp Venkatesh made inroads - but the phone call had ruint his mood. Ruminating  over the misery that awaited him in India, Ramesh decided that he was in no mood for a trip to the movies. He wanted time to clear his thoughts. More importantly he wanted to thrash it out with Ramki about Preeti. He decided he would call him in an hour and meet him in person. And most importantly he needed a drink - a really stiff one.  Preeti had been sitting at the cafe overlooking Ramki's apartment for the last hour "Where has he gone that its taking him so much time..That jerk of his colleague told me he had left early for the day ? Should I confess to the past ? Will he accept me then - Ranjini, u were right n I was so wrong.. I am madly in love with him.. I cant live without him" Her thoughts were interrupted by the garcon who had asked her something. Preeti nodded and sunk deeper into depression.  Screeeeeech !! The Chevy spun and jerked to a stop.  He had been so engrossed in his dreams that he failed to realize he had arrived at Janaki's place. Venkatesh parked his car and rang the bell. No answer. He waited for 5 minutes and then realized there was no one at home. Since he had decided that this would be Judgment Day, he hurriedly scratched off a love note to Preeti - professing his undying love for her and also making a few snide remarks about Ramki. "Why do I feel there is something between them ?" - Dismissing the negative thoughts he slid the note in and was about to leave when he saw someone  walking towards the house.  "Hi, I'm Vaishnavi - since we've never met before I assume you aren't looking for Janaki - If its Preeti, then she's gone to see her friend Ramki". Venkatesh grimaced "That Ramki $*&^% "  Gattu had been lurking in the shadows patiently observing the café and Ramki’s apartment intermittently for the last two hours. Ever since he had received that phone call in the evening from "the Preeti", he knew for sure that things had boiled down towards the finale. It was pay back time..He would do it..Do it for his twin brother Anand - he would avenge the hurt. Gattu wept.. and wept like he had never done in the past.  Janaki had been at the library all evening unable to concentrate on her books - her life had just got complicated in the last 12 hours. While she cudnt kid herself that Ramki meant nothing to her, she was also aware that Ramesh had stuck through her thick and thin. Furious for letting herself get manipulated, she angrily picked up the phone and dialed Ramki's number "Hey Julia..Hullooo...Cmon speak up..Whozz this? Julia?" She hung up. She could not take it any more. She made up her mind. Packing her books she hailed a taxi and gave directions to Ramki's apartment.  Saturday morning 9 am: Ramesh was slumped on the sofa still suffering from the hangover of the night's drinking binge - Venkatesh was as usual, trying in vain to attract Preeti's attention who was flipping through Cosmopolitan - and Janaki was mopping the hall when the bell rang. "Who's that" shouted Janaki.   "Open up - we are the cops".   There was pin drop silence. The James Bond movie in the TV blared on. Venkatesh shuffled towards the door and opened it.  "Who's Janaki Chandrashekhar?"   "Why, thats me - wassup officer?"  The smart, 20 something officer of Indian origin flashed his id "The name's Mookherjee - Cowshik Mookherjee - Can I talk to you about your friend Mr Ramakrishnaswamy?"  The Bond movie title song rolled on in the background  "Why.. of course.. Whats with him ? Is he OK ?"  "He's DEAD - we found him murdered at his apartment - n u bet, I am gonna "FIND" the killer."      
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was already half past eleven and  Ramki  was running late for a training session at office. Sensing that he did not have much of a chance in scoring brownie points with  Janaki  in this big crowd, Ramki said  "Hey folks, its the last day of the week, loads of work at office - me's gotta go..Lets all meet up tomorrow morning at 9 here..Bye!"  Janaki started to protest but aware that a pair of eyes were sharply observing her, checked herself in time. Damn  Preeti !   "And my fellow country men, do you support this war against terrorism when millions of...."  A roar comes from the television across the room ( Senator Kerry  is on another of his frenzied speeches)   As  Venkatesh  settled down on the sofa and  Ramesh  stared at the TV with renewed interest, Preeti ambled towards the kitchen  "Hellooo..Is neone home?" . Janaki who had wandered into her bedroom to change into her casuals shouted back  "My roommate  Vaishnavi 's gone shopping - if you want some grub help yourself - or have you still not learnt to cook?"  Cursing Janaki under her breath, Preeti returned to the sitting room and flopped on the couch. Venkatesh, seeing how tired Preeti was, offered  "You know I make excellent kaapi - can I do it for you? Please please"    Gattu  was half asleep in the corner of the room when he heard a slight tap on the door. As the trainer droned on, Gattu managed to take a peek and saw that it was Ramki - late as usual. Quickly letting him in, Gattu enquired about Ramki's morning. Not wanting to let him know about where he had been, Ramki evasively answered  "Nothing special yaar.. Overslept"  Gattu gave him a long thoughtful stare and replied"  Dont lie to me man..Someone called Varads called up at our extension and asked if everything had gone off fine at the airport..??? " Ramki shrugged his shoulders and offered no explanation. Gattu stared long and hard at the ceiling.  Time and tide wait for no man...Swooosh.. Its now evening in the US..   Tring Tring   Ramesh lifted the phone off the hook  "Hi Appa.. I am fine..studies... going on fine..will surely graduate next year... no appa.. I dont stay out late.. bars? Apdinna ? there are no women in my college..its all men....but... appa...ok..ok.. pls convey my respects to Velu mama..n my love to Annam..ok..Bye."    Venkatesh had no classes the whole of the week. He had interpreted it as divine approval for his mission when he realized that this coincided with Preeti's arrival in NYC. Whistling in happiness, he jumped into his Chevy and started the car  "I'll take them to  Vittorio's  - Preeti loves Italian - and then buy her some flowers and when I get some privacy, bare my heart to her - tis a pity Janaki will be tagging along"    Ramesh had made grand plans of taking Janaki and more importantly, Preeti out to the movies that evening - he wanted to worm his way into Preeti's good books before that twerp Venkatesh made inroads - but the phone call had ruint his mood. Ruminating  over the misery that awaited him in India, Ramesh decided that he was in no mood for a trip to the movies. He wanted time to clear his thoughts. More importantly he wanted to thrash it out with Ramki about Preeti. He decided he would call him in an hour and meet him in person. And most importantly he needed a drink - a really stiff one.  Preeti had been sitting at the cafe overlooking Ramki's apartment for the last hour  "Where has he gone that its taking him so much time..That jerk of his colleague told me he had left early for the day ? Should I confess to the past ? Will he accept me then - Ranjini, u were right n I was so wrong.. I am madly in love with him.. I cant live without him"  Her thoughts were interrupted by the garcon who had asked her something. Preeti nodded and sunk deeper into depression.  Screeeeeech !! The Chevy spun and jerked to a stop.  He had been so engrossed in his dreams that he failed to realize he had arrived at Janaki's place. Venkatesh parked his car and rang the bell. No answer. He waited for 5 minutes and then realized there was no one at home. Since he had decided that this would be Judgment Day, he hurriedly scratched off a love note to Preeti - professing his undying love for her and also making a few snide remarks about Ramki.  "Why do I feel there is something between them ?"  - Dismissing the negative thoughts he slid the note in and was about to leave when he saw someone walking towards the house.   "Hi, I'm Vaishnavi - since we've never met before I assume you aren't looking for Janaki - If its Preeti, then she's gone to see her friend Ramki".  Venkatesh grimaced  "That Ramki $*&^% "   Gattu had been lurking in the shadows patiently observing the café and Ramki’s apartment intermittently for the last two hours. Ever since he had received that phone call in the evening from " the Preeti ", he knew for sure that things had boiled down towards the finale. It was pay back time..He would do it..Do it for his twin brother  Anand  - he would avenge the hurt. Gattu wept.. and wept like he had never done in the past.  Janaki had been at the library all evening unable to concentrate on her books - her life had just got complicated in the last 12 hours. While she cudnt kid herself that Ramki meant nothing to her, she was also aware that Ramesh had stuck through her thick and thin. Furious for letting herself get manipulated, she angrily picked up the phone and dialed Ramki's number  "Hey  Julia ..Hullooo...Cmon speak up..Whozz this? Julia?"  She hung up. She could not take it any more. She made up her mind. Packing her books she hailed a taxi and gave directions to Ramki's apartment.   Saturday morning 9 am:  Ramesh was slumped on the sofa still suffering from the hangover of the night's drinking binge - Venkatesh was as usual, trying in vain to attract Preeti's attention who was flipping through Cosmopolitan - and Janaki was mopping the hall when the bell rang.  "Who's that"  shouted Janaki.    "Open up - we are the cops".    There was pin drop silence. The James Bond movie in the TV blared on. Venkatesh shuffled towards the door and opened it.   "Who's Janaki Chandrashekhar?"   "Why, thats me - wassup officer?"   The smart, 20 something officer of Indian origin flashed his id  "The name's Mookherjee -  Cowshik Mookherjee  - Can I talk to you about your friend Mr Ramakrishnaswamy?"   The Bond movie title song rolled on in the background   "Why.. of course.. Whats with him ? Is he OK ?"    "He's DEAD - we found him murdered at his apartment - n u bet, I am gonna "FIND" the killer."       
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ramki always knew that once Preeti was in New York, life would again be fun. But the latest turn of events was something he totally wasn’t prepared for. He sat in the car and started the engine. But he was somewhere far away… lost…thinking.   How things had changed. How people seemed to have changed. How his perceptions about life, about relationships and most importantly about people had changed.   He couldn’t believe the fact that the dark and gawky girl of his college days could actually have transformed herself to this graceful dusky brunette sitting next to him. In those days, he had never bothered to give Janaki a second thought, let alone a second look… and now it was that same Janaki whom he could not get his eyes off.   Anyways, he put his Chevy out of the parking gear to reverse and slowly steered his way out of the parking lot. Once they reached the freeway, he could think of starting a conversation with her.   Janaki too hadn’t expected Ramki to behave the way he did. Under normal circumstances, she would have just ignored him. But something seemed to be pricking her deep inside. Could it be that she was feeling a bit guilty? Ever since she had set foot on American soil, she had always tried to shake off her forbidding image that had plagued her all through college. She had always been true to her relationship with Ramesh… she treated him as God… and now she couldn’t believe that she has cheating on him.  All along, she had also tried hard to overcome the thoughts of gaining Ramki’s attention, whom she had fancied once upon a time. She had actually come to realize that she had fancied Ramki all through college because she found him to be the only guy she could beat at anything they competed in… be it Acads, TT, Dumb Charades or even Quizzing… you just name it. She had always scored over him and may be this always boosted her ego and made her fancy the guy. But Ramki had never ever looked back at her and now he was almost leering at her… even whistling.   They slowly drove out of the parking lot… the attendant extracted his one dollar fee… and they joined the NY021 freeway for the 30 min drive back to Janaki and Ramesh’s apartment. “So how is your studies coming along”, Ramki suddenly said, breaking into Janaki’s reverie.   “Oh… I am doing ok… among the top 5 in the batch… will be finishing after the next fall session… you tell me… how’s work?”, another surprise for Ramki… Janaki had not gone on and on about her performance… had not bragged about her successes as she always used to.   Anyways, she had asked Ramki to talk about his favourite topic… his work… the first love of his life… he started… “My work is just too good… I am into Marketing now… no more coding and testing and stuff… You know, I am working for the semiconductor unit of this transnational organization… my primary KRA is preparing sales collaterals for their sales team worldwide… I am the single and only point contact for the entire business unit’s requirements… and believe me the profile I have got is one to die for… I am really enjoying my job…”  He suddenly felt very happy. He thought that it was again back to the old times and that he had scored a point over Janaki. He was just waiting for her retort. But it never came. She seemed not to be listening… again lost in thought.  He interrupted her again… “So what plans for marriage?”… Have you ultimately found your Mr Right?” He was trying to probe her… trying to find out who it was that she had called just before getting into the car.  She again shook out of her thoughts and said, “No daa… I am still not decided… Ramesh and me are living together for now… but there is still a long way to go”… saying this she quickly turned her face towards the window… She couldn’t believe what she had just said… Ramesh and she had been engaged last month… the wedding had to be put off till after next fall because she wanted to first get a H1B visa for herself… and now she was herself denying everything.  Anyways, she quickly collected herself and asked him… “What about you? Have you found your mate?”  “Naah… I am off women you see… no time for all that… now my career is my foremost aim in life”… He too was lying… keeping his options open.  “But I heard that you had proposed to Preeti… what happened”  “Aiyoo daa… all that was in the spur of the moment… but once I reached here, I got thinking about the whole episode… and then the thought of the price tag kept buzzing in my head… anyways… I’ll tell you everything in detail… what happened was…”, he turned to look at her. She was not listening. She seemed to have again dropped off into her own thoughts.   Ramki didn’t want to disturb her. In any case he was not able to think of any topic other than work and marriage that he could or wanted to discuss. He just turned to face the road and continued on the freeway.  ~*~  Meanwhile in the Honda, Venki was silently revelling in what he thought was a coup he had successfully managed to pull off. He had somehow managed to pack off Ramki with that vampish Janu (he practically detested her) and had made Preeti travel with him. This was his only chance to catch up with the woman he had yearned so much for … for the whole of one year. And more over, he just detested Ramki and was always suspicious that there was something on between Ramki and Preeti.  “Hey … Venkatesh !!! watch out …”, Preeti shouted out suddenly. Venki was so lost that he hadn’t seen the lady waiting with a parambulator at the gate of the parking lot. He was unknowingly staring at Preeti and had almost climbed onto the mother child pair. He somehow jammed the breaks and came to a halt.  “What are you doing Venkatesh?”, asked Preeti in an irritated tone. “Where are you looking? Do you always have to goof up like this when I am around? Are you really that dumb or do you purposely act like this to irritate me?”  Venki was taken aback. He had definitely not expected this outburst from the lady of his dreams. Here he was getting ready for a great time with her and she was just blasting him to no end. He felt hurt but said nothing. He thought, “Maybe it is the jet lag… she must be very tired traveling through the time zones… I’ll let this incident pass… After all, she has come here all the way so that she can be with ME… ”  “Ok ok… see now… everything is fine… I was just a bit distracted… You don’t worry… Relax…”, he said. “And by the way, my friends call me ‘Venki’ now… not Venkatesh any more… ok?”.   Venkateshwarulu Gejjalapati Sreerangapalli and Ramakrishnaswamy Pollipoti Iyengar were first introduced to each other when they reached REC (Kurukshetra) for their Bachelors in Engineering. Since they found very few Tams or Gults there, and found even fewer guys who spoke in anything other language than Hindi, they preferred to stick together.   Initially, almost everyone had a problem pronouncing their names and often made fun of them, and so to resolve these issues, they started being known as Venkatesh and Rama. Their parents, grand parents and relatives back home would have thrown a fit had they heard about this, but they realized that for small town guys to survive in the big bad world, they had to make certain compromises.   Inspite of all this, in the four years that they were at the college, they could easily count on their fingers the number of times they had spoken to any girl. Even Janaki and Ranjini – fellow Tams rarely gave them any bhaav. So, at the end of it all, they found that all through the four years at college, they made very few other friends and always stuck together. But, although they were always together, there was a latent sense on competition between the two and as a result, deep down, Rama and Venkatesh politely detested each other.  Ranjini had introduced Venkatesh to Preeti when they were both applying for MS courses at NYSU. He had instantly taken a liking for her and was hoping that both of them would stay at New York together. She also was responding well… atleast that’s what he thought… but he had never had the nerve to ask her. However, the evil quirk of fate struck and she was denied a visa by the consulate, while he got through. Even Janaki made it, but Preeti was returned empty handed. Venkatesh was almost devastated at the turn of events and was almost ready to give it all up. But she convinced him to take the offer and promised to join him as soon as she could.  Preeti took up a job in am embedded software design company and got busy with work. When he left for the US of A and she had barely spent 10 mts with him at the airport. She was very busy with some assignment and assisting her Marketing Executive with an important customer visit.  He gradually settled in his university and heard that Preeti was also doing well in her job. However, he was quite irked to learn that Rama was also working in the same company and was now known as ‘Ramki’ by his colleagues. He liked the ring in the name… ‘Ramki’… He also got to know that Ramki and Preeti were now friends. He did not approve of this at all. Anyways, what could he do? Preeti had said that she would join him at NY. So for the moment he decided to wait. He also decided that he too would change his name to ‘Venki’ so that it would sound better and more acceptable.  He smiled. Old memories always made him smile. He remembered what he had just told her and looked at her again. Preeti was looking very disturbed and tense. She didn’t seem to have registered his words.  “Hello Preeti darling… kahan kho gaye?”, he had picked up a little Hindi as well. “Did you hear what I just said? I am now known as ‘Venki’ among all my friends”.  Preeti looked back… still a sort of frown on her face. “Whatever…”.  “Kyun yaar… kya hua? Why do you look so disturbed? Is there something bothering you?”, Venki was now really getting concerned, but dint push hard. He just concentrated on the road ahead and followed the Chevy in front.  “Arre kuch nahi re”, Preeti started. “I just seem to have a head ache. Main thoda rest kar lun? Ghar pahunch ke baat karte hain”.  But Preeti was really very disturbed. Her last conversation with Ranjini was continuously playing on her mind. She wasn’t even able to get off it during the entire flight. Was she really playing up with peoples’ emotions? The list of guys she had flirted with and played with was indeed very long. Earlier she had never bothered about it. When she was dating Venkatesh more than a year ago, there was Pranav, Rajaram and Rohith as well. She was managing four fragile souls simultaneously and practically living four separate lives at the same time. But it never bothered or troubled her. It was always fun.  But ever since she met Ramki and spent so much time with him, she started feeling bad and guilty about her modus operandi. In face once Ramki left, she actually felt very sad and lonely. She desperately wanted him to still be around. At times she thought of confiding to Ranjini about her true feelings… but she was frightened… Ranjini would never believe her. She could not talk to any one else and this made her more lonely.   She now sat in the car lost in thought… thinking about the scene that took place at the airport a few minutes ago. The bear hug from Venkatesh, his constant blabbering, her cousin Janaki coming late, she anxiously waiting to meet Ramki, Ramki and Janaki hitting at each other, and now the division of couples in the cars. She was not liking any of it at all.  Preeti had never felt anything for Venkatesh… he had always been her muse… getting her flowers, doing everything that she wanted… everything. She had always bossed over him… she often did with all her muses. But now she wanted to put an end to it all. She was internally convinced that this should not go on any more, but how was she going to tell Venkatesh? He would be totally shattered.  Ramki’s arrival at the airport had made Preeti’s heart go aflutter. At that moment she realized that she was indeed in love with Ramki. She decided that she would definitely tell him this time. But the way Ramki and Janaki had looked at each other kept pricking her. Was it for real or was she imagining things? Something in the look that Ramki gave to Janaki, and the impromptu whistle seemed to suggest that something was amiss.   She quickly dismissed all these thoughts from her mind. Janaki was going steady with Ramesh, and there was nothing to fear. Ramki was all hers and she would not mess up the plot this time.  ~*~ The two cars moved along at 120MPH through the freeway. Both women silent nad lost in thoughts. Both a bit guilty at what they were going to do.  Both men silently driving along. Both lost in the excitement of what was coming up.  Janaki thought, “Ramesh would be off at the game now... Preeti and Venki seem to be going along well and Ramki… so my dear old Ramki is all mine... But what about my engagement? I don’t care… I can give up anything for Ramki… but I care deeply about Ramesh… He cant survive without me… I will go back to him eventually” She let out a wry smile at her predicament.   Ramki was thinking, “That bitch Preeti made me eat the price tag also… I will have nothing to do with her from now on… Janaki is looking awesome and seems to have the hots for me… I think I’ll pursue her seriously… especially since she and Ramesh are yet to decide…”  Preeti thought, “Enough is enough… I will set everything in order now… will clearly tell Venkatesh about my true feelings… Will apologise to Ramki about the price tag issue and then confess my love to him… No more playing around…”, she sighed.  Venki looked to his right, “There she is sighing… she must be really tired… ok then, I will not rush her into anything… I will let her relax and then she is mine anyways… What a time I will have with her…” The two cars came to a halt at the gate of Janaki’s house… The four weary headed travelers alighted and Janaki led the way up the porch… To her shock she found Ramesh at the door… He said, “Hey Janu, you are back so soon? I thought you would take much longer. That Yankees game got called off because of some stupid campaign riots… I tell you that John Kerry guy is gonna make lives miserable for us in case he comes to power.”  And then his eyes fell on Preeti. “My God”, he thought, “she is so damn gorgeous. Wonder why Janaki is not as hot as her cousins are. Anyways… no issues… she is gonna stay here now… I will surely get my chance”. He grinned thinking of all good times that lay ahead.  “Welcome, welcome all of you”… was all he said.  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thud ! Vroooommmmmm ! Fffff !!  The plane hit the tarmac hard, skidded on the runway and glided to a halt. 18 hours can be a long time especially if one cant wait to set foot on the shores of an alien land. With her heart thumping in excitement, Preeti skipped down the flight of steps - Her first impression 'O boy, where is all the dirt? Surely no place can be as clean as this'  Janaki has been waiting for an hour now - "Dammit.. why do I always let momma con me into these stupid chores? Surely Preeti is grown up and can get home safely..I just hope Ramesh doesn’t get cheesed off with me."  Venkatesh was in a big rush. After spending hours getting the "look" right - carefully ironing his purple shirt (actually her favorite color) and washing his smart Nike sneakers, he jumped into his snazzy Honda all set to meet the woman of his dreams..And to think he had not seen her in person for a year now since their last tearful separation at Mumbai airport when he had left to do his MS :-(  Preeti walked with her luggage and scanned the crowd for a known face "How on earth can this happen to me? Is that imbecile Venkatesh late as usual? N where's that silly cousin of mine - why isn’t Janu around? Holy Christ, I cant believe even Ramki  hasn’t turned up - What is this world coming to ?"  It had been two months since Preeti had added Ramki to her list of trophies in her collection and the hard fought victory had only spurred her to trap more unsuspecting sillies. "Pranav and Rohith had it coming but why Rajaram and definitely why poor  ol' Venkatesh ? The list has only been growing everyday, worse than  Hanuman's tail" mused Ranjini. It had all started off as fun but somewhere along the line she realized that things had taken a nasty turn."These were people's lives that Preeti is playing with and it seemed so unfair, especially Venkatesh..He's such a nice lad" pondered Ranjini. Dismissing her pangs of guilt, Ranjini stared back at her screen trying to collect her thoughts so that she could do away with this email before hitting the sack.  Varads, tinkering with the car in the garage, looked at Ramki who was checking mails in his laptop and simultaneously staring at some stunning model sashaying on the TV screen. "Dude, the bird touches down in 15 mts and nigger, u r as darn late as it kan be - move yer ass n git down before some vulture swoops on yer chick". Ramki turned around, smiled, glanced at his watch and settled down in an even cosier position on the couch.    "Aloha and welcome to the land of opportunity" echoed a ringing voice and lo! Preeti found herself tightly embraced by Venkatesh's bear hug. Struggling to shake free, Preeti threw all the luggage at him and opened her compact. Quickly checking herself in the mirror, she barked orders to Venkatesh to lug her stuff towards the duty shop where she would have to wait for her dimwit of a cousin."So hows ur MS coming along ?" asked Preeti in a disinterested tone. She was still scanning the crowds looking for Janu and did not even listen to Venkatesh's fumbling reply. Venkatesh, who had been waiting for this moment for ages, suddenly seemed  to be afflicted by a strange bout of paralysis in his tongue. Here was his goddess and at the most opportune moment, he hardly knew what to talk.  In another corner of the world, in an obscure village called Sundarapandiapuram, its midnight and in a small hut, Annalaksmi woke up with a scream “Appaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa" Worried as hell, VeluNaicker ran to his daughter and asked her "Enna ma aachu? Yaen da kozhandhai kathina? Edhavudhu ketta kanavu kandiya ?" (what happened child ? Why are you scared? Any bad dreams?) Annalaksmi, with a ghastly look on her face, exclaimed "Appa, maama'vukku... edho... aabathu ... Enakku... theriyum" (Mama..is in... some danger..i know..) Velu's face relaxed " Appove sonnen - Mani ratnam padam paakkadheyunnu….Maama , periya padippupadikka USA poirukkaar ma.. Avarukku onnum aagaadhu" (I told you not to watch those Mani Ratnam movies.. Mama is in the US for his higher studies.. Nothing will happen to him)  "Darling, I am held up here at the airport coz of that bitch of a cousin of mine. I jes cant seem to locate her. Hope you arent missing me much" explained Janaki on her cell phone.  "Huh, the Yankees game starts in 10 minutes and if you arent there I am not gonna wait for ya - would you dare keep GOD waiting in front of his temple" screamed Ramesh and cut the call in fury. Janaki swore yet again at Preeti.  Ramki unfastened his seat belt, checked the doors of the car to confirm they were locked and promising to himself not to get flustered or let the emotions seize him, casually ambled to meet Preeti. There she was - looking beautiful as ever but somehow Ramki did not feel good today. It was obvious to him from there that Preeti was clearly irritated - she was constantly fidgeting and ignoring the earnest attempts at conversation by the bloke standing near her. Things could not have been even better.   "There she is .. at last" - Recognizing Preeti standing behind a group of towering Afro Americans, Janaki waded her way across, desperate to end this miserable outing. Within a moment of each other, Ramki and Janaki both arrived at the book store. The usual round of introductions. Smiling politely and giving Preeti a quick Hello, Ramki turned his attention to the smart, tall woman nearby.. Appraising her from head to toe, he involuntarily whistled. "Hullooooo but what was that mister?" cooed Janaki. "Its a free world ma'am - a thing of beauty is a joy forever" retorted Ramki. "Some smarts you've got mister" said Janaki with a mischievous gleam. All this while Preeti has been angrily observing the exchanges - Now she couldn't take it any longer. "If you two will stop being kiddish, shall we move on?" As they trudged along, Venkatesh offered " Preeti,  lemme take your luggage - you can join me in my car and since Janu doesn’t have a car, she can pile on with Ramki. Wotsay ?" Before Preeti could object, Ramki had opened the door and Janaki slid in.   "Honey, I am getting held up here at the airport. Sorry I cant join u at the game - Lets sync up later" said Janaki on the phone. Turning around to Ramki, she winked and said " Wanna come home?"   
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The stork took away into the clouds. Fading away till the tail lights became another star in the vast expanse of space. Srinivasan tugged at his fathers shirt and said “Appa , see there’s a comet ,meteor there” he said. Thwack came the knock on the head , “Concentrate on the maths”, dad said “Its just the Lufthansa flight”.  Preeti walked out and crumpled the tissue in her hand. Ranjani rushed out from the shadows and ran towards her “What happened?“ She shouted from afar, “Has slob left” she giggled. Preeti threw up her hands in elation “He fell for it” she exclaimed, “the tear and jerk stuff worked again”. Ranjani doubled up in laughter. “I don’t believe it , I thought this is one guy who’s gonna get away from you”. “The cake bake routine was a sheer stroke of genius, I don’t believe he actually thought you baked that Cake , a 150 buck, Cakes and Bakes special. You know what, the clincher was when he actually swallowed the price tag. I had such a fright I thought he would notice and that’s when I gave him those fluttering eyelids, and he went gulp.  Ranjani was in splits “whats the count now “ she squealed in between peals of laughter , “24” said Preeti before jumping into the nearest auto.   There was a studied silence in the auto , Preeti wasn’t totally comfortable , but it was Ranjini who brought it up. “Hey what about your New York trip next month”, “Hmm that’s what I’m worried about too, cant lose slob anywhere in the office there” replied Preeti.  Ramki walked across the Tarmac briskly, or so he thought. Four paramedics rushed at him, and threw a huge rug around him, another minute and it would have been frostbite sneered a towering medic. Shucks this aint Chennai he reminded himself and stepped gingerly onto the centrally heated walkway that led to the interiors of the ‘JFK.  It wasn’t as he had expected it to be. Not at all. There were no cheerleaders with those teeny weeny skirts going “Gimme an R”, Gimme an A”…enough he reminded himself, he was a stranger in a paranoid land. A huge dark man bumped into him roughly, and he had the wind blown out of him. He immediately stood there and checked his wallet, passport, re-counted the number of bags he was carrying and totaled the cash, he was thirteen rupees short.  He walked on “Preeti paid for auto , I paid for coffee , then I paid for those gifts , then I paid for her new watch , did I pick up the change from the coffee shop ?” Lost in thought he reached the exit.   “Bye Preeti , sleep tight”. “No I’m worried about Mr. Overgrown”. “Why you really started liking him”, Ranjini winked. “Nope not that way , but….” Preeti walked out letting it trail. The auto purred away in the distance.  It was just over a month and he had already figured out the route to Rajalakshmi mami’s house where Rajesh and he teamed up for curd rice with mango pickles and the Sun TV soap on the net.   “What is up Varadarajan” ? gushed Mrs Rajalakshmi, as her neighbour walked in sort of unexpectedly, but as if he expected to walk in wherever he wanted too. . Ramki looked up expecting to see a full bodied Vaishnavite with all the accessories , what he got was a close cropped nerd with pierced ears. It aint “What is up lady”, “its sup” and it just aint Varadarajan or whatever u call me its Varads, u gotcha baby” he sneered in a tongue plucked out of the ghetto.  She nodded but Ramki was still popping his eye and gaped unabashedly at the alien being. “Watchya looking at dude” slurred Varad , “Chums lets grab a bud” , move it dudes” ordered Varads. They trooped off to a pandemonium of noise , knees and budweisers. “Kirby’s” remarked Varad’s “is where I ve been pubbin ever since I ve been pubbin” he said.” Doesn’t mean I avent been pubbin newhere else “ he joked.  It didn’t make too much sense, but women, all of them, every one of them. He had never seen anything like that before. Sinewy bodies, pampered to divinity, attired in the latest, designed to accentuate the curves they had worked so hard to attain. Proud bodies lusting for all the attention they deserved. He gave it all, round and round, in and out of those dance floors , till the 14 th beer pushed the floor hard on to his face.  “Preeti” he woke up , but his eyes were still closed . It had been a month, he hadn’t mailed or called, but today she was coming there. Preeti was going to be in New York and he wasn’t at the airport.  “Varad’s , I need a car mate” , he gurgled. ‘Sup dude”, he quipped. “My girlfriend ‘s coming to town”, “I have less than an hour left.” I haven’t mailed or spoken for a month now.” “Why did ya do that and why do you want to meet her now ?” asked Varad’s.  “Yesterday when we were in Kirby’s, I realized a great truth. It was probably all the beer, the noise and the alien land but I realized that love was something you gave into, not knowing what you get in return. Its what you give that matters in love and it doesn’t matter if the other person responds or not. All this time I had been evaluating Preeti and whether she really liked me, but last night I realized it didn’t matter what she thought, I really love her, and nobody else,” he said. “Then why dint ya keep in touch” he probed.  “Its because, I saw the price tag……….” Ramki said, eyes twinkling mysteriously…  
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was a lovely December morning in the hottest city in the world. All right, so that was a little unfair. Chennai is not the hottest city in the world. But it certainly is the city with the most uncomfortable weather among the cities that I have lived in. And I've been around. But I digress.  I was in the company bus on my way to work, as usual trying to catch up with my sleep. On this particular day, a girl got on the bus, came to my seat and sat down. "Good Morning," she said. I looked back at her through half closed eyes, replied "Good Night," and then proceeded to return to my half hour nap before the bus reached the office. Unfortunately, I was woken up by a punch in the arm.  "Wake u! p, bozo!" She was looking at me with a big smile on her face. "I'm not sitting next to you to listen to you snore."  Half-heartedly, I opened my eyes and turned to her. "What's up?" I asked. Preeti Mehra was tall, good-looking and slightly tomboyish. She was also my best buddy. "Come on," she said. "Don't look so disappointed. You'd rather sleep than talk to me?"  "I talk to you everyday, Preeti."  "You also sleep everyday."  "It's not enough."  "So you've had enough of talking to me, eh?"  You can't argue with a statement like that, so I had to give up. I grinned and said, "OK, sweetheart. What's on your mind?"  "I wanted to tell you what happened yesterday. Can you guess?"  "Anurag called you last night."  "How did you know?" She was stunned.  "Oh, he asked me for your number yesterday."  And you gave it to him?"  "What else could I do? And stop complaining. You've been drooling over him for weeks now. He must have thought he had a chance."  Preeti was the kind of girl who would openly ogle at every other guy she saw. And yet, she would not respond to any advances of a romantic nature. She'd happily join a group of boys to go to a cricket match, but if asked out to a movie, dinner, or even coffee, she'd never say yes. She defined 'Hard-To-Get'.  "You like putting me in these situations, don't you?" she said.  "No. That's not true. I love putting you in these situations!"  That invited another punch in the arm.  I had known Preeti for a year. We'd tell each other about our joys and our sorrows, our victories and our defeats. I'd tell her about all my crushes and she'd scold me f! or being silly. She'd drag me to classical music concerts and I'd add them to the list of things she 'owed me' for.  And though I never let it show, I must say that she punched pretty hard.  It was 12:00 am and my phone was ringing. "Hello," I said, as I picked it up.  "Happy Birthday!" It was she.  "You're supposed to throw me a surprise party, sweetheart. Not just call to say Happy Birthday."  "Well then open your door, dumbo!"  So I did and found her, cell-phone in hand, at my doorstep -- with what seemed like half the population of my company. My roommates were supposed to be working late that night. Now I knew why.  I blew a lot of candles (seemed like much more than 25), cut my cake, got kicked in the behind, and got painted with the cake's icing. If Preeti had had her way, she'd probably have pref! erred to use a paintbrush and a can of paint. But I bribed her with a copy of the book "Lord of the Rings". She'd borrowed it from me three times already. I thought it was about time I gave her a copy for herself.  We chatted for an hour after everyone had gone. "I think it's time I left," she said finally, trying to stifle a yawn. I nodded. I dropped her home in my roommate's car. As she was getting out of the car, I stopped her.  "Hey, Preeti."  "What?"  "Thanks."  "Hey, don't get senti on me now!" she smiled. "Are you trying to worm out of that gift you promised me?"  "You know, it's interesting how I'm getting you a gift on my birthday."  "That's just because you're stupid," she grinned. "And you better get me that book, or I won't return your copy."  "Hey, that copy was a gift to me from my dear f! riend Preeti Mehra. I can't let you keep that."  She wasn't falling for that. "Your dear friend? And what about me? Am I not dear to you?"  "Very smart. That won't work with me. I'm not one of your Love Crazy suitors. Why do you need the book anyway? You've read it umpteen times already."  "That is besides the point. You are getting me the book. We both know that." She smiled that wide confident smile of hers. "Good night." And she got out of the car.  I sat there for some time, just thinking. Our conversations were always like this - a little joking, a little teasing and a lot of demanding. But somehow, I felt that something had changed since the moment she had turned up at my door that night. I was still in my reverie when a paper ball landed on the windshield. I craned my neck out of the window and looked up. She was st! anding in her balcony.  "What are you still doing there?" she whispered loudly.  "Waiting for you to start a paper-ball fight," I whispered back.  "We can do that tomorrow. Go home now. It's way past your bedtime!"  "Ok, mommy," I grinned back. "I'm going home now!"  I'm an extravagant gift-giver, and it is definitely going to be my downfall some day. I made her wait for it, but finally bought her the book. That, and half-a-dozen other omnibus collections of various authors, including a copy each of `The Complete Works of Shakespeare' and `The Complete Short Stories of Charles Dickens'. All I got for it was an "I told you so."  I started spending a lot of time at her place after that. Mostly because I wanted to read all those books, and she wouldn't lend them to me."I'm not as stupid as you, ape-man. I'! m not falling into the same trap I laid for you. Plus, you dog-ear your books. You're not doing that to these masterpieces. So if you want to read them, you read them here. And if you want to mark your place, use a bookmark."  So that's what I did. She'd even make me wash my hands before I touched the books. It was as if they were sacred.  "Need I remind you that it was me that bought you the books in the first place? For my birthday!"  "So? They're mine now."  "Well, then. I've been meaning to ask you this for a long time. Where exactly is my birthday gift?"  "It was in your tummy at one point of time. It's probably been washed into the sea by now."  "Huh?"  "Remember the cake I baked you on your birthday?"  "You what? You can't bake cakes!" That was a mistake. She looked hurt. "You baked me a cake! ?" She didn't say a word. She just shrugged.  I was stunned. "But you never told me."  "You didn't ask." That was typical of her.  "It was fantastic! And you wasted most of the icing on me!"  "The cake was for you, dumbo."  "How long did it take you to make the whole thing?" It had been a two-layered vanilla-chocolate cake with three flavors of very creamy icing. She had done all that!  "Well, the chocolate cake took an hour and fifteen minutes, and so did the vanilla. Then cutting them up and putting them together took another 15 minutes. Each flavor of icing took 20 minutes for preparation, and then putting it on the cake took another half hour. Cleaning up the mess took an hour."  She seldom claimed the credit for anything, but once she started bragging, there was no stopping her. However, I wasn't thin! king about that right then.  "You spent over five hours on that cake?"  "A little over four hours preparing it, and an hour cleaning up. Yes."  I was speechless. I didn't know how to react. She hated cooking.  "I forgot to mention," she continued, "the hours I spent the week before that, practicing. Even the birds wouldn't touch the first three cakes!"  I couldn't help but ask. "Why?"  "Because the first one got burnt, the second one was only half cooked, and in the third one, I forgot to add sugar."  It was just like her, to try to divert the conversation. "I mean why did you spend so much time on baking me a cake?"  She looked at me like I'd asked her why the sun rises in the east. "For your birthday, stupid. Of course, I also wanted to beat every gift you've ever got me. Try beating this one." S! he was grinning like she'd won the world championship.  As far as I was concerned, she had. I'd never spent a week making her anything. I'd never even spent an hour making her anything. Getting her a gift normally involved me taking her to the store, letting her choose and use my credit card. Suddenly, I felt cheap. "Thanks," was the only thing I could say. "Thanks a lot."  "Hey. Are you getting senti on me again?"  I was.  I was still mulling over my feelings for Preeti the next day at work when my boss asked to speak to me.  I went over to his cabin and he started with the usual greetings, asking how work was going and whether I was comfortable. He then told me that the company wanted to send me to New York for a couple of years. Normally, this wouldn't have made much of a difference to me. I could work anywhere! and didn't have too much love for visiting places foreign. But right then, the first thought that came to me was that I'd be away from Preeti for two whole years. Twenty-four hours before, I'd have been disappointed to lose  her company. But right then, I was devastated. That was when I knew I was in love with her. I'd had crushes before. Lots of them. But this was different.  "Do you have any problem in going?" my boss asked, since I hadn't responded.  "Not really," I replied. What else could I say? That I was in love, and couldn't bear the separation?  "When do I have to leave?"  I had a month.  "Wow! New York! Great! I've heard it's a fantastic city! Did you know it snows there in winter?" Preeti was obviously very excited about my going. She didn't seem to share my disappointment on what I no! w saw as 'separation'.  I had not decided then if I was going to tell her how I felt. We'd known each other for a little over a year, and we were very close, but beyond some mild flirting, the relationship had never got even close to romantic. That was, of course, until I found out she had spent a week baking me a cake. It's funny how small things seem to make such a big difference.  "What happened?" she asked. "You don't seem very happy."  "Oh," I replied, "it's just that it's so sudden, that's all. And you know I was never all that interested in going to America."  "What an idiot. Go see the place. I've heard the women there are amazingly beautiful." She had a sly smile on her face. I wanted to tell her I didn't care if I laid my eyes on another woman again, if she wasn't with me. But I didn't.  I realized that I only had another month with her. She'd rejected every guy who'd asked her out ever since I'd known her. I didn't want the same to happen to me, and I didn't want to make it awkward between us. I didn't want to risk that month. I wanted it to be the best time I had ever spent with her. After I came back from the US, I might not even get to meet her again. Two years was a long time.  We ate out almost every night. We visited some of the best restaurants in the city. She also helped me shop for warm clothes, formalwear, shoes, toothpaste and a million things I'd never have thought of on my own.  "You need to buy a nail-cutter." My roommates and I shared one.  "I've prepared a list of must-have medicines that you should carry."  "Your iron won't work in the US. No point buying one here as you need one that works at a hundred and ten volts and has fl! at pins. You can buy one at a K-Mart or Wal-Mart as soon as you get there."  "You need at least two pairs of formal shoes and at least ten pairs of dark socks. The East Coast has a formal dress code. And you won't do your laundry more than once a week or two."  "How many ties do you have? And which trousers do your blazers go with?"  "Better get a haircut before you leave from here. Knowing you, you'll postpone the first haircut for too long."  She'd call me up at one in the morning to tell me to add 'one more item' to my list.  And with every passing day, I was falling more deeply in love with her.  The month swept by quickly. The day I was supposed to leave, I asked her to come with me to the airport. "Of course, dumbo. You think I'd let you go just like that, or what?"  After packing my bags for me and ch! ecking the lists for the hundredth time, she finally pronounced me "Good to go."  We reached the airport four hours early to beat the rush, because it was an international flight. She got a visitor's pass to sit in the waiting area while I went ahead and checked-in my bags. Preeti had got a spring balance from somewhere and so we knew my bags were well within the weight limit. I finished the formalities and came to sit with her. We had only a few hours before I had to go for my security-check. We decided to get something to eat at the food court. And all the time, the one thing that was going through my head was that, after this, I wouldn't see her for at least another two years.  "Hey, Champ. Why so glum?" She saved 'Champ' for special days. Normally, it was just 'dumbo', 'bozo', 'ape-man', 'matchstick man', 'weirdo', or if she was very irritated with me, 'nutcase'.  "I don't want to go," I said.  "I don't want you to go either."  "No, you don't understand." I couldn't hold it in any longer. "I can't stand the thought of living without you by my side."  She stared at me. There was a strange look in her eyes. I couldn't read it.  "I am madly in love with you, Preeti."  At this, a sound escaped her lips that sounded like a cross between a sob and a laugh. "Well, dumbo, you've picked an absolutely fabulous time to tell me about it!"  A tear escaped her eyes. It was all I could do to stop myself from wiping it off her cheeks.  "How long have you felt this way?" She seemed amused, though she was definitely crying. I didn't know what to make of it.  "From the day I found out you had baked me a cake."  She laughed. "That's ! all it took? Well, bozo, I guess a way to a man's heart is certainly through his stomach! Hold it. A month? You waited a month? You were the one who kept saying that if you really liked a girl you wouldn't waste a day in telling her!" She was smiling widely now. It looked funny, with her eyes all wet.  "Well, I was confused. How did I know how you'd react? In fact, I still don't understand your reaction. I thought it would change things between us. You've rejected every guy who ever proposed to you!"  "That's because I'm in love with you, you overgrown idiot!"  "What?" Somehow, I'd never expected her to say that. She was in love with me? "How long have you been in love with me?"  "Ever since the day you offered to carry my suitcase for me."  "But that was the first day I met you!"  "I guess I was always a sucker for chivalry."  "All this time you've been in love with me and you never said anything! Then you go and complain that I waited a month!"  "You guys are so bad at reading a girl's mind."  "You women are so good at keeping your thoughts a secret! Even Einstein couldn't figure you out."  "Einstein was a nerd. Casanova, on the other hand, understood us very well."  "I love you."  "I know."  That moment, my dear friends, was magic. I looked into her eyes and took her hands in mine. Physical contact for us had been limited, until then, to a punch in the arm, a slap on the back of the head, or giving each other a 'high five'.  "You realize, don't you," she said, "that this is our first date?" Leave it to her to notice the little things.  "I really don't want to go." I'd always maint! ained that love is a bucketful of emotions. I wasn't exactly delighted to be proved right.  "Don't worry. I'm coming there in a couple of months."  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Somewhere in the future…Year 2015…   The alarms went off left, right and center on Monday morning at  247, Pivot drive, NYC . They ended as abruptly as they began. A couple of minutes of silence and they went off again. The odd concoction of sounds rented the air again. The cacophonous medley of alarms were accompanied and more prominently followed by thuds of feet landing on the wood paneled floorboards. Feet shuffled about in various corners of the house, uncertainty filled every step indicating that those who had struggled to move after the alarms had rung were considering the next course of action given the realization of what lay ahead!    “Ammaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, Daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaadddddddddd”  the voice of an 8 year old rang out, the high decibel voice ricocheting off the walls of the house.  “Moooooooom, apppaaaaaaaaa”  cried out a second voice of a 10 year old. The pairs of feet rushed up the staircase - they burst into the room.  “You might be wondering what the commotion is all about on”,  said  Raghu  as he adjusted his horn rimmed glasses ala Harry Potter style,  “today happens to be Fourth of July”  cooed Shruti.  “It’s a Monday, and we have a Holiday,”  said  Shruthi .  “Now let’s hit the streets, the parade will be starting in a couple of hour’s time,”  she continued.  “Unlike every Fourth of July we don’t intend to sit around doing nothing, somehow you folks seem morose every Fourth of July!”  “And you promised us this year will be different, more so today is a Monday holiday, yippiee”.  With this Raghu did a cartwheel. However  Venkatesh  &  Janaki  who had been walking about the room when the kids burst in, shuddered inwardly. The fourth of July held a different meaning for them, especially the parade. 11 years since it had happened and they were still trying to get over it.   Way back in the Year 1975…   The sun rose over  Sundarapandiapuram  village in  Madurai  district, a well known city in South India. The people, their tongue, their Moustaches and their sickles had one thing in common. They were all sharp!!!    “Ele, paathu seeve le, oru varshathu velachal idhu! P** thinringala ille soor thinringala? Muttaa pasangala! Padiche pasanage thane? 74 le male nala kelu nasama pochu indhe varsham avadhu kasu pakonum”   VeluNayakar  yelled at the boys. (“Harvest the crop properly; it’s a year’s effort of hard work! Don’t you have brains you idiots! Educated aren’t you!? I lost my crop to the monsoons in 74, but this year I want to make money ”).  Gattu  and  Anand  didn’t need these filthy scoldings, but they needed the money that Velunayakar gave them for working as manual hands in his farm during summer. Gattu and Anand needed to complete their college studies; they had promised their mother  Karupayi  they would. This summer job would give them enough money to buy books and tattered second hand clothes at the weekly fair in  Marathahalli  at the northern most tip of the Madurai district. For Anand there was another reason to be at the farm house and Gattu knew that.   “APPAAAA, enge irrukihe? Mama vangi kuduthe kadh jimki sethee parungale, joor a irruku”  (Daaaad? Where are you? Look at this earring that Uncle bought me, it is wonderful)  AnnaLakshmi  cooed as she ran into the courtyard with  Ramesh  hand in tow. Anand was overcome by jealousy every time such things happened. Alas he was a poor boy and Ramesh was a rich Zamindars son related to Annalakshmi. He consoled himself with the fact that Annalakshmi had equally liked the paper boats & the kites he made, the ripe mangoes that Gattu and he bought for her. It was another matter that they were plucked, or should I say, stolen from Velunayakars farm! Ramesh had been observing these veiled advances by Anand, ably supported by Gattu. NO!!! he could not lose Annalakshmi and his Uncle's mindshare. He needed that till he could cream them off to go to USA for a life of riches! It was on one such day when Anand and Gattu were plucking mangoes that it happened. Ramesh sprung the trap on them….Anand Gattu’s dearest brother was the target he wanted neutralized. Anand, Gattu’s dearest Anand…”   PRESENT…    ““Gattu annaaaaaa, Annalakshmi pake pollammaaaa...gattu annaa… AAHHHHHHHHHHHHH”.  The sound of that voice turning from pleasure to pain shook Gattu from his reverie. The phone rang. Gattu flipped open his  Aqua3056  from Nokia. It was  Vaishnavi .    “You fool!”  She yelled.  “Venkatesh has been telling all of us what happened yesterday! What the hell is this! I though you told me you didn’t want to hurt anyone! Just a chance to settle old scores peacefully!”.     “I want revenge Vaishnavi”,  replied Gattu in a calm voice.    “But why Kaushik? And why a god damn gun!!???, I refuse to help you any further”  She retorted in rage.    “ Kaushik, who Kaushik? I thought that was Ramesh! He always had a habit of roaming around in various costumes back in Sundarapandiapuram, sometimes dressed like a lawyer, sometimes a doctor, sometimes a policeman and I assumed old habits die hard.  Obviously a case of mistaken identity. Relax Vaishnavi, anyway it was a fake gun. I intended to scare him, a sort of warning. Sorry”  he replied. Vaishnavi seemed mollified by his response.    “Do you want to meet up for dinner?”  Gattu asked.  “I will tell you what I have in mind”  he continued.   I have been waiting too long for this, though Gattu as he undressed to step into the shower.   Janaki  had been growing increasingly concerned at  Ramesh ’s behavior. Not withstanding her emotionally cheating on Ramesh, she felt Ramesh’s behavior was beginning to border on the bizarre. He had begun calling himself “God”, yelling at her for reasons unfathomable, positively letching at Preeti, being at home when he claimed he was out at Knicks game. What she held in her hand now,  was not new to her, but the content was. When cleaning Ramesh’s room she had seen similar chits, sometimes shredded, and sometimes burnt. This one however wasn’t, which is what caught her eye. On it was written in a neat type face    “RENDEVOUS @  Where mixed samoa Warrior number 191 waged with even planes, In a nearby avenue, middle men park their gains”    Janaki was confused as she sat on the sofa and read the Chit.    “The Central bank on park avenue”  intoned a voice from behind her. Surprised at the voice and the response, Janaki turned around to see Venkatesh smiling at her, an apple in one hand and a book titled the “DaVinci code” in another. Janaki was stunned. “What did you say?” she asked.  “You heard me…“The Central bank on park avenue”” he repeated.   “See Janaki, Mixed Samoa is an anagram for OSAMA who claims to be a warrior- the number there indicates the 911 attacks. Thus this place refers to WTC.”    “But there is nothing there now Venkatesh”  replied Janaki.    “Patience my child, look the second half of the clue. This place has to be in a near by AVENUE, and the word PARK literally refers to the avenue’s name. And this has to be someplace where one parks his gains. Where do we put our money? In a BANK silly! and middle can also be read as CENTRE.”  explained Venkatesh.   “The central Bank on Park Avenue near NYC of course”  blurted Janaki astonished at the intellectual powerhouse called Venkatesh who was sashaying out to the balcony now.  “BTW what is this crossie about? Is someone meeting you there?”  he asked as a parting shot.   “Some one is meeting Ramesh, and its not me”  Janaki muttered to her self. She had to find out who and what it was all about.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That twenty something officer turned out to be  twenty-nine . “ Cow , you *^&%^$”, screamed  Ramki  as he bound up the stairs, “What the ^%&^ are you doing here in that vague costume”, he screamed.  “Nothing yaar, didn’t get that software job I wanted so I have taken to acting to eke out my living.” “Wow buddy! Must be an awesome role - what did you land, the next  Bond  flick or some  Jerry Bruckheimer  monster.”  “Nothing so fantastic mate, I’m the 74th  cop in the next release of  Police academy . They are giving me a whole 3 seconds of screen time and it’s filled with emotion.” “Wow, what do you do?” “I am shot dead by a ravaging Al Qaeda agent and I cry help, thrice loudly before I die.”  Everyone in the room watched the entire conversation in horror. They were united in thought; “I hate this Moron” they all told themselves.  Janaki  decided that she would be more proactive than just mentally deride this uniformed mass of non-biodegradable Cow shit or whatever his name was.   “What the &^*% do you think your doing, just rushing into somebody’s house and playing such a stupid trick?”  Cow  shuffled back a few paces, he was amazed that some one of the opposite sex had actually addressed him in person and it was not long before he realized that it wasn’t exactly praises, that were being showered on him. “But..but..” he blurted out , “it was  Ramki  who asked me to go inside and say this” stammered Cow.   Ramki  burst out laughing, “Fooled you guys, didn’t I”. “Haa...haa”, he went on. Nobody moved,  Venkatesh , sullenly walked towards  Ramesh  and said, “You know what - for a minute I thought it was true”. “Happiness never lasts long”, he cribbed.  Ramesh  nodded, “Me too”, he confessed, “I was thinking of the next pub to party in”.  As though on cue, all of them turned in and walked back to their chores.” Hey, what happened dudes, did I hurt you” pleaded Ramki. “Ya, by walking in alive “snapped  Janaki .   Ramesh  didn’t like the tone, but  Ramki  loved it. He knew this fish was in the kettle.  Cow  was feeling distinctly uncomfortable; it wasn’t exactly the best entry he had planned. He was also amazed that Ramki knew so many women, and he was even more thrilled to know that they knew him too, which wasn’t often the case with him.  “Er ..I’ve got to be going “  Cow  stammered. “Bye” they all screamed in unison.  The episode hadn’t turned out the way  Ramki  wanted it to. He had told Cow that he wanted to see if Janaki really loved him, the usual lemme test this kinda attitude. He told Cow to say his lines, and he wanted to walk in to find out if  Janaki  would rush in throw her arms around him and cry out her love.  It didn’t work out the way it was planned. “Poor  Cow ’s going to have a tough time getting back into this gang” he thought “but he’ll manage”.   Gattu  slipped the shades on. As a slim, tall guy he had no problem slipping into the crowds. He walked carefully behind Cow, who often stopped to stare at the beautiful behinds of most of the women who walked past him. Suddenly Cowshik broke into a run when an oversized  Negro  stopped to admire Cow’s behind, and even made a provocative nod at him.  Gattu ran with purposeful strides, and overtook Cowshik taking a clear look at his quarry. He pulled out his  Smith and Wesson  and aimed at Cow, point blank. Even a blind man couldn’t have missed, nor did Gattu. A fiendishly childish desire suddenly overtook him and he thrust his right leg between Cow’s oversized feet, tripped Cow, watching him fall flat on his face.   Venkatesh  had walked out of the house, with a lot more clarity in his life than he ever had. He had never felt so clear other than after his Hindi exam in the eighth standard. As he walked out of the hall he was certain, unlike never before. He wasn’t sure about  Schumi ’s next F1 win or  Warnie ’s flipper, but he was sure of one thing, that he would fail the test come what may. Such clarity he told himself was always useful whether it was for good or bad. Now he was clear that the last thing on Preeti’s mind was love for him. May be she even hated him.  He walked briskly, he needed a smoke it didn’t clear his mind but clouded it. In those clouds he would see his Preeti. As he stood at the edge of the street smoking, the clouds formed and there was somebody calling out, but it wasn’t  Preeti , it was an oversized policeman.  In practicing his role Cowshik had developed the uncanny knack of screaming a loud and clear Help. One that rent the air like a Train’s whistle and left no one in any uncertainty as to its origin.   Venkatesh  heard the cry and lunged out like the good outfielder that he was , two hands cupped he dived forward and clutched onto Cow’s face as it was about to hit the concrete. “Howzaat”, he screamed involuntarily.  “Not out” snorted  Gattu  as he sprinted away into the crowd.  “Thanks buddy” said  Cow  as he dusted himself. Venkatesh embraced him, it reminded him of cricket. He looked at the phoney police officer. He looked like a nice guy.  “Hey dude, I think we are going to be good buddies”, he confessed. “Me too” gushed Cow.  They shook hands and parted ways. Venkatesh was clear again. He ran home to Preeti. This time he was certain, he took her arm and pulled her brusquely. “Hey what the %&^%,” she screamed. “Shh, shut up”, he said softly.  With his arms firmly but politely on her shoulders, he spoke for the first time confidently into her eyes. “Hey  Preeti , I know you don’t love me. I am sorry I’ve been a pain, but I just realized that I have confused my crush with love. Wish you luck and I’ll be your friend whenever you want me to, bye for now”. He kissed her lightly on the cheeks and stormed away.   Vaishnavi , who had seen the entire scene walked in from the kitchen. “Who’s the dude “, she whistled and enquired with her eyes twinkling with more than a little admiration. Preeti, looked at Vaishnavi and winked, it was going to be another hot affair.   Cowshik  was baffled, he had suddenly been thrown into this room filled with people. He had been treated with contempt. He walks out and a vague character trips him, while somebody who had screamed at him saves him. Too much for the day, he decided. As he walked back home he told himself, I wouldn’t be surprised to see a nude girl in my bed. He unlocked his apartment door and…………   Gattu  closed his eyes , another day had passed and his thoughts drifted to a distant land , where there was laughter. A happy easy laughter, the one of his twin brother  Anand Dass ….! “Gattuuuuu anna…..”, he screamed  as he ran into his brothers lap. It was  Madurai , in the southern reaches of the state of Tamilnadu…..A green town with a lyrical dialect and razor sharp sickles………..   
     
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ..Wots ur choice?  The following piece is a compilation of some very candid confessions - secrets darker than what Gestapo has ever collected - of four of my closest friends. Most of it came verbatim from the proverbial horse's mouth (asides included). Acknowledgements to the   girlfriends-turned-spouses of two of my pals for their inputs too. Sorry guys, but I had to use this old piece since I ran out of stuff to write on my blog today - u know just like Uppma served at hotels :-)    12 new reasons to stay single unless you fancy...     Its early days:   * Going down on your knees persuading a common friend (to you and your gal) to get you a favorable intro and her phone number.  * Bribing this "obnoxious saheli" (yeah, by now she's not needed - more so since she wants to know everything thats happening ) to keep you posted on the other men in your gal's life.  * Getting turned down thrice (that’s the average..of course, law of averages don’t always work) and putting up with your gal's "play-hard-to-get" nakras for a normal Rs. 30 Capuccino date @ Barista. (Cheapskate I always was)  * Lying through your teeth that you spent hours in selecting the mushiest card at Archies for her Birthday. (Hey, they just hiked prices too :-()   The middle of the marathon:   * Sleeping through a movie of Brad Pitt / Ben Affleck or for that matter any handsome dude dimly aware that she's gushing on and on about the creep. (Thank God she atleast likes Rajini)  * Listening to her detailed arguments on how Butter popcorn has lesser calories than Caramel popcorn.(need to check on the veracity of her claims though)  * Replying to her mails of "Kya chal raha hai" once every 10 minutes, then professing your undying love once every hour and religiously forwarding every forward you get so that she does not miss a thing in your life. (I actually used to do that last part -  don’t laugh)  * Spending half an hour everyday on the phone discussing what the lunch menu at her office was and how she resisted eating all of the above since she was dieting. (Thankfully our future roti bill should balance our kapda bill)  * Walking in and out of a million clothes shops, asking your opinion on the colors / texture/looks / what-not for hours only to see her finally pick up the first tops she saw  at the first store.   The last mile:    * Nodding in agreement to her plans for a "simple wedding" which include an invitee list of only 1400 people, chef duties by Arusuvai Natarajan, reception concert by Mandolin Srinivas (she actually thinks he's cho chweet - Marriage counsellor, here we come!) and a honeymoon at Bali (Damn Hrithik and his KNPH)  * Getting into a discussion on the finest detail of everything from the size of the wash basin in "our" dream house to the color of the walls of the kennel of her favorite Lab, Roger - you haven't heard it all - all this hours before your engagement ceremony.  * Sacrificing your quality time in front of the TV watching "dumb", "manly" sports like Basketball and Formula One in favor of more refined choices like soaps on Sony and Zee.    Enough is enough :-)    I think, therefore I am... single.  (Due apologies to Rene Descartes) But i do realise that your perspective could be different - Mind letting me know :-)   
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am excited.. I can barely type..Yes, I know its a Sunday and I am sure many of you are wondering what on earth I am doing at office. But then I can barely contain myself. Good news is to be shared at once :-) Remember that engagement of my third cousin Sridhar (I  am told he is actually my second)  that I mentioned in passing in one of my previous posts - it was today - and boy, what an event it was..   First things first, I think I am getting old. Would you believe if I told you that I had mistaken the function for yesterday and had landed up at their home with a BIG bouquet? I must have sensed something was amiss when I did not see even a shamiana put up besides the lack of a crowd..But then I guess I was too caught up in my own world. Of course, I have always been smart (pat on my own back) and I managed to save the situation by cooking up some wonderfully believable (or so I think) stories about how I might be busy the next day and so had to drop in and wish him on the momentous occasion. Save this small gaffe, Saturday went off well.   Sunday:  I have never really relished these social gatherings and the prospects of being the only representative for my family at the function only added to my apprehensions. The muhurth was between 10:30 and 12 noon and with an idea of skipping early, I reached  their house sharply at 10 am. To my horror, I realized that everyone had turned up an hour before me. And before I could say Bingo, I was accosted by all and sundry and asked to explain my mother's absence. Mumbling ridiculous excuses, I vaguely scanned the  crowd in search of a known face when I finally saw my savior in the form of my  Chinna Thatha  (Grandpa's bro) Now, I have  to say a few words about this man..   C.S.Ramachandran:  A 75 year young gentleman - he's one of the smartest people I have ever seen - a man capable of matching wits with ten of my generation and still coming out trumps. A well read man with a penchant for unnerving young kids in the family with difficult puzzles and quizzes,  Mani pa  (as we call him fondly) is simply put, delightful company.  Settling down into a seat besides him, we started our sparring session. It had been a few years since we had met and he was actually amazed that today I was giving as much as I was getting. Clearly pleased at the progress I had made, he started firing Qs on the  current political scenario, the latest book I had read and how I was doing my Hindu crossword and whether I was taking my Table Tennis seriously. Without claiming to be modest, I must admit that I was in  "full form"  and literally charmed him with my replies.  This was then followed by the expected tortures - I was introduced to all the obese maamis, the old gossipping pattis, my beautiful cousins (;-) and anyone and everyone I "HAD" to know. And once the engagement ceremony was over ( Sridhar  n  Priya  looked really nice together - mebbe marriages are made in heaven), the women folk got down to their favorite pastime...Making plans for the next bakra..A few of my aunts gathered around  Jayanthi's payyan  (that's me - as u can see I had no identity of my own) and asked him   "When are you getting married?"  Usually I get flustered by this rubbish and lose my cool. But today I was in full form and I ended up saying  "Maami, if only you were 25 years younger, I would have had no hesitation marrying you - Lucky uncle :-)"  And this I saw, made them really happy and they bugged me no more.  Watching me handle all this with aplomb, my  Chinna Thatha  crowned me  "The most intelligent person in my generation"  and this for me was the  "piece d'resistance".  On second thoughts, this might be a crown of thorns considering I will now have to live up to his gargantuan expectations but then.. I shall enjoy this till it lasts.. which could be the next engagament or wedding in our family :-)   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Italy    Location:  A tiny peninsula in Southern Europe   Population:  around 60 million  Famous for:  Handsome men, Renaissance art, crime and mafia gangs, soccer  My first love affair with Italy started in Std 6 - I still remember vividly how my class teacher who had visited Venice once used to spin stories about how beautiful the country was - She would rattle on and on about the famous gondolas rides and how she was "this" close to the Pope at the Vatican. Impressionable age that it was, I decided that one of my first holiday destinations when I became rich and famous would be Italy. Needless to say, the last time i saw Italy was when my 8 year old nephew opened the atlas last week.  It was during one of my first quizzes in school that I also heard of that great all rounder of the 16th century (am I right?)  urlLink Leonardo Da Vinci . Artist, inventor, architect, mathematician - a genius if ever there was one. Did you know that he used corpses stolen  from the gallows to perform his medical experiments - of course u did - but did u also know that he wrote in his own style of  "mirror writing"  - starting at the right side of the page and moving to the left. It was only when he was writing something intended for other people that he wrote in the normal direction. Comprendre?  Then came movies and  Marlon Brando  as  Don Corleone  changed everything I had imagined about this wonderful land. However since I had grown up by then, blood and gore and power and politics also appealed tremendously. I wanted to be  urlLink "mafioso"  - I dreamt of honor and pride and imagined myself to be of pure Sicilian blood. I saw all gangster movies and basically went mad.   The last few years (and I use "few" very loosely) my only Italian connection has been with footer. Every Amar, Akbar and  Anthony knows that I am a big fan of the  Azzuri  and it infuriates me whenever these self proclaimed pundits rubbish the Italian style of playing as "boring". Hey, do I need to remind that defending is as much an art as scoring goals ? Besides the sublime  Gianfranco Zola  and that towering giant  Christian Vieri , aren’t we forgetting that awesome footballer  Francesco Totti  for providing us moments of sheer bliss with his wonderful .... urlLink foot-in-the mouth quotes  :-) Love live the Azzuri !  As I keep saying, there's something about this nation that will always fascinate me.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink        urlLink Madh Island     Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .     You could love her, you could hate her (not so sure abt this though) but you could never ignore her. You could be forgiven for having first impressions of her as hot headed and impetuous  -  but I, for one, knew her much better than that. She was honest and loyal - always spoke her mind - enthusiastic and committed in everything she undertook.  Jaya, When I look back today - those detailed mails about ur temple tours before u reached SP, those long walks in Juhu beach singing old Ilayaraja classics, that heart-to-heart talk we had while waiting for our Rural Marketing Prof to land at Mumbai airport, our last fun trip to Madh Island .. These are memories that I shall treasure forever.   "U r a wonderful pal - simply one of a kind"  Happy Birthday Amma!  ps: Keep smiling as you r in this snap. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I cant take it nemore. The pressure is too much. I have been told in no uncertain terms to stop the crappy stuff i blog and to "write ssomething sensible". So pls find below transcripts of one of the most stimulating evenings i have had in the last few months.   Venue:              Yet another pub in Bangalore  Time:               Sometime in Feb 2004  Principal players:  Four long lost bosom buddies - lets call them Alpha, Beti (she was the lone female), Gama and Jupieee    The occasion:       Reunion -  a year after/(post) graduation    Topic 1:     Beti:     How is work yaar?  Alpha:    *%^&*( , lets not talk about it ( gushes down a mug full of beer in one shot)   Gama:     My designation says i am a consultant - i have to handle 20 critical requests over email every day, slog 50 hrs a             week and i get paid a measly 8 lpa. Why doesnt anyone realise the value of us MBAs ?  Alpha:    Oh, u've shifted from Infy to Accenture huh??  Beti:     I have a great team, my boss is chilled out, the timings are flexible but i still have to travel far, yaar..Gama,              isnt Accenture on Cunningham road.. Any openings?   Gama:     Yeah, but your profile wont fit  (sneers)   Alpha:    Jupieee, u *(&^%, hows u doin' ?  Jupieee:  So-So  (grunts )   (Jupieee is a man of few words)    Topic 2:    Gama:    So when are YOU guys shifting jobs?  (in a tone that suggests that neone who hasnt shifted by now is a dunce)   Beti:    Netime newhere as long as i get a 40% hike. Cmon dude, the market is booming. Neone has a list of headhunters?  Alpha:   @*&^%$...These morons have promised me an on-site opportunity in Germany next month - praying that it materialises.  Gama:    I assume they are flying you by Lufthansa and not some cheap airline. And u Jupieee?  Jupieee   (mutters):  Am undecided. Lets see!    (Jupieee looks a worried man)    Topic 3:    Beti:     So any marriage on the cards? Cmon guys, spill the beans!  Alpha:    Women..They are so much like domain names: the best ones are already taken..Life is so friggin' unfair man.   Gama:     I dont have the time to look out yaar - new job, more pressure - However i have told my folks to look out for a well educated gal preferably from the IIMs - She should be from a respectable family and should be working, preferably in      a software firm - so that she can relocate with me, u see. Of course since i am tall, ideally she should be atleast 5'8"  Beti:     Whoa !! Thats gonna be tuff !!  Alpha:    yaya..What about you Beti ?  Beti:     Me, there is a Mr X in my office - he's a CA rank holder - tall, dashing and his father is a steel magnate - he has asked me to marry him twice but i am confused. He's not very funny and gets serious too easily.  Gama:     Jupieee, u still going around with that Plane Jane or are you on another of your endless searches for Ms Perfect?  Jupieee:  Who - what ? No mate, i am off women !  ...n that precisely was when all talk ceased and people got down to the more serious business of eating and drinking.   Ladies and Gentlemen, presenting to you the four typical products of B school - the  cynics (Alphas), the  mercenaries (Betis), the  snobs (Gamas) and the  confused ones (Jupieees).    
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       	 		 		 We came, we saw, we conquered (hearts)   Btw, we also got dream jobs !! 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Class of 2003 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink Jupieee .			 		 	  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Winking at grandpas and ruffling childrens' tresses Dancing in electric trains and driving bike triples Sketching on borrowed books and playing drums on vessels These are a few of my favourite quirks    Trin trin       trin trin       trin trin       trin trin    Sleep-acting in training and karaoke when shaving Sending blank SMSs and buzzing in messenger fights Playing soccer in the slush and watching movies full of mush These are a few of my favourite quirks  When the power supply fails When the mail server conks When i feel bored I simply indulge in my favorite quirks And then i dont feel so ... bored.    (Repeat all verses)    I take a bow     ps:  Anyone needs a songwriter pronto jes contact me - i have more of these "free verses"  pps:  Beware -  urlLink plagiarised versions  are also available
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ahem!! Doesn’t the sound of this word have a magical ring to it ? Now now, don’t you even think on the lines of rubbishing this.. Coz all I have to say then for ye non believers is  "Sod off"  !!  Its been a good four years since I quit my first company but I still have fond remembrances of Pune. Last Friday evening I was stuck in one of these nostalgic moods thanks to a phone call from an old colleague of mine. I was due to go for a movie later that night but somehow just didn’t feel like it. Since it was supposed to be a family outing, I could not ditch 'em.. Surprise of all surprises, who would you think was sitting in the row ahead of me at the hall? My best friend from those days :-) Oh boy, was I thrilled !! We ended up gossiping for an hour - catching up on our lives - The poor guy has lost it all - He's married :-)   Cut to March 2001  and I think there was this  Lawrence and Mayo  free eye camp at my workplace in Chennai..Never one to be even remotely interested in such sessions, I  remember being literally dragged down to the basement and forcefully subjected to a test by a pesky colleague of mine...He kept telling me that for all that I knew I might fall for the cute optometrist :-)  Que sera sera ...It was there, that day, that I met my first serious crush (pardon the oxymoron) and would you believe it if I said that it was the optometrist's assistant :-)   Cut to the present:  If there is any complaint that I have about Bangalore then it has to be that I have lots of "distant" relatives who live here. It becomes a real pain considering each and everyone of them want you to drop in at their place once in while (without even the promise of a dinner or a lunch invite) I have been having this eerie feeling for the last two days that something big n bad was gonna happen.. And lo, it happened today morning. My mom informed me that there was this third cousin of mine, Sridhar, who was getting engaged this Saturday and that I was supposed to represent the family. N to think I had grand plans for myself in Chennai :-(   Have you ever felt cornered by fate? Do lemme know - would be a real comfort to know that I aint the only person suffering! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       22:12 pm 20/5/2004   Pffft !!   Just as Wendy is getting cosy with Chandler on my favorite sitcom Friends, suddenly i find myself staring at a blank screen..Unable to understand whats happening i fiddle around hopelessly with the remote - without any success - i peep outta my window to check if alls fine with my neighbour's television - it is - she's as usual watching some soap on Sony. Unable to take it nemore, i holler to The Good Lord up above  "It just aint fair - why me? Why me?"    Flash!! A brilliant streak of lightning!!   A booming voice thunders  "Kya hua? Why the heck are you cribbing, you nasty earthling? Its a tough job i got here and once in a while i do screw up - cant you just ignore it as an aberration?"   I retort  "Not this time - i've had too much for this week"   The Voice is annoyed and threatens  "I dont get it - u better explain or else..."   Not to be cowed down i sneer  "After enduring days of shameless drama i discover that my country has a reluctant and almost reclusive Prime Minister - I realise that my bosses earn "obscene pots of gold" while i am expected to slave on for "pride" - and to add insult to serious injury, you screw up all my weekend plans with a silly wedding (assuming marriages are still made in heaven) - If this isnt reason enough to crib, what is ?"   The Voice ponders  "I guess you have a point - how can i compensate ? I grant you three wishes - Name them fast.. Your time starts now..10..9...8.."    "Hold on Hold on - Not so fast - Can i phone a friend?"    "5,4,3...."  "You *@&^%$, ok, here i go...First of all, i want.."    "Sorry, your time's up but since you started your first wish i will let that count - Finish it" "Want to.. want to.. see Aayitha Ezhuthu (Yuva in Hindi)tomorrow night - can you arrange for 2 tickets please"    "Thathasthu"  is the last i hear and lo, i find myself with two passes to Nataraj.   08:07 am 21/5/2004   My friend screams  "You crazy git - Havent u seen BRUCE ALMIGHTY? Couldnt you have asked for something bigger?"   (Hanging my head in shame)  "Like what?"    "Dunno... but atleast balcony tickets yaar not stall" 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Queen's English, they say, is the purest and noblest of all forms - we've inherited this as a legacy of the British Raj and this is one standout example of how everything that is videshi aint bad after all :-) Though i must admit that we have done a good job of mastering it - the BPO industry is proof enough - there are still occasions when i am not so sure...The Texan drawl, the Australian twang - they are all manageable but these Mellus :-)    Me:  Dinesh, if Maino comes to power i gotta leave the country mate.  U know anyone abroad who can get me a job?  Dinesh:  My ungle ees in the Gelff - zimbly eemeil heem n esk no  Me:  ???   Me:  Boss, i have no clue whos got the doc  Boss:  Penguj dold me he hed it..jeg vith heem..    Me:  Hey macha, lets go for this Roger Waters thingy man  Arun:  Remgi, I like wonly pope muzik..No da..No da..please da..  If my pal whos jes back from Kolkatta is to be belived, then things are even funnier there.. Guess v shud all kombile a list of the Inglish we hear.. Would you like to contribute ?   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its a new start! Here i am ..  Been thinking of penning my own blog for long but never got down to actually doing it.. Many a slip between the cup and lip.. But to be perfectly honest, i kinda suspected it would become compulsive and eat up too much of my time - considering i got better things to do like..hmmm...doing nothin' :-) But then u never know till u try..   Its a new day.. Its a new plan.....So here i am..
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ESPN-Star  is still down. I have threatened my cable operator that I will disconnect but it seems to have fallen on deaf ears. After all, how does Rs. 200 lesser every month matter to someone who is reportedly serving 800 households. Monopolistic trade practices be damned. I've tried praying also but it doesn't seem to be working. So in the absence of  Wimbledon , the next most exciting thing I do is watching movies in my CD player. Monday night, dunno why, I revisited that ageless classic   urlLink Casablanca  ... Ahem...The enigmatic  Rick Blaine  helping the divine  Ilsa  and her husband  Victor Laszlo  to escape and then walking into the sunset with the unimaginable ally  Louis Renault  is one of the most memorable cinematic sequences I have ever seen. After watching it for the umpteenth time, I sat back and thought. (Danger ahead)  It’s been 60 years since then but why hasn't anyone ever bothered to find out what might have happened in the lives of these characters. Positive that there must have been something that happened, I googled and was not at all surprised when it threw up some of the following results.  1. A horrendously stupid movie sequel idea unfortunately called   urlLink Brazzaville   that has to be the product of some retarded bloke.   2.  Micheal Walsh's  book "  urlLink As Time Goes By  " released by  Warner  in  1998 , sort of a  prequel and sequel to  Casablanca . It answers a lot of hypothetical questions like    Do Victor and Ilsa make it to America?  Do Rick and Louis join the Free French garrison in Brazzaville?  Why can't Rick return to New York? Will Rick and Ilsa ever see each other again?    I, for one, have never been bothered to seek out answers for all these questions. However one thought that's always haunted me is "  Can Ilsa ever be happy with Victor?"    My good friend  Girish  and I have had a million discussions on this one and other similar situations. While he feels that it’s more important to be loved and contends that Ilsa's memories of Rick will soon fade away, I am of the firm opinion that even it doesn't last long, it’s important to get the person you want - Ilsa would have been much better off with Rick.  Wot's your take on this? 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn  Sreenidhi Cables . To hell with  ESPN-Star . Yes, it’s my infamous foul temper at work. My cable operator has blacked out  ESPN-Star  since Saturday evening and I have missed the best part of the last four days of action at  Wimbledon  and  Euro2004 .   Even though the punks are out thanks to Portugal, England continues to be the flavor of the month for me. These Brits are never short of real entertainment. Take Tim for example. Come June and the whole of this nation gets into a frenzy hoping to see their local boy crowned champion atleast this time around at Wimbledon. When was it the last time around?  Fred Perry  in  1936 ? I never support Brits but this time my heart goes out to  Henman . He has struggled through the early rounds but surprisingly beat the  Scud  yesterday. Next up is  Ancic  and then it’s the usual semifinal date. Never matters who the opponent is - this one will be Tim's mental match. If he can cross this, it will be his year.   Sunday evening had another British treat in store for me as I finally saw   urlLink Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  . I have always had crazy tastes and just to give you an idea, my favorite character in the books is without a shadow of doubt,  Severus Snape . But then he hardly gets any screen time in the movies which narrows down my choice to  Hermoine Granger . (Pronounced: Her-Moy-Nee: I insist on everyone getting their pronunciation right) Wanna know why ? Read on..  Intelligence is a rare commodity to find amongst women and when this is coupled with oodles of loyalty and loads of attitude, the combination can be truly deadly. Born to Muggles, Hermoine is the smartest of her lot at  urlLink  Hogwarts  . She's studied wizardry since childhood and has answers to all the questions. Backgrounds of creatures, histories of characters - If it’s ever been in a book, Hermoine knows it. And just like all other brilliant people (pat on my back), Hermoine can't tolerate stupidity and rubbish. Check out her disgust for  Cybil Trelawney  and  Divination , watch out as she ticks off Ron over and over again :-) Sigh !! Hermoine is one heckuva intellectual turn-on :-)    urlLink Emma Watson  .. Hmm.. Don't get ideas folks but I would be failing in my duty if I did not compliment this wonderful lady for her glowing performance in HP3. Be it the scene when she ticks off Harry for trying to reach out for the magic pendant or when she punches Malfoy, Ms. Watson is a sheer delight. She more than compensates for the drab and boring  Daniel Radcliffe  and is a wonderful foil for the adorable  Rupert Grint . IMHO, this is clearly the best of the three movies and full credit to  urlLink  Alfonso Cuaron   for extracting such wonderful performances and also deviating from the book to add his own magical touches. Couldn’t agree more with this  urlLink  wonderful review  .   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It’s been a week now and things have slightly become better. But as  Frost  said  “There are miles to go before I sleep" . It's in these difficult circumstances that I remember that wonderful movie I had seen a few weeks back. Got to give the devil it's due.   Starring  Jim Carrey  and  Kate Winslet ,  urlLink  Eternal Confessions of the Spotless Mind   written by the redoubtable  urlLink  Charlie Kauffman   is the story of two people who have been in love just sometime back till they suddenly realize there is no fire in their relationship. Deciding to undergo a procedure to erase each other from their memories, it is only through the process of loss that they discover what they had to begin with.  Now let's come to my  Aaha experience . Imagine the implications of a memory erasure - just think how it would feel waking up one morning to find out that a certain part of your past has been completely wiped out. The first situations I can think offhand where this would really help me are:  ###   I wouldn't need to buy people a lot of presents. The second half of the calendar year traditionally has me GIVING more than GETTING - If only I could forget that I had ever received :-)  ###   I would not need to be reminded of the various times I goofed up. For starters, How about the last time I loved a perfume so much that I presented it to my aunt failing to notice it was one for gents. Or how about wiping off going out on my first date to a Hindi picture without realizing she doesn't know the language and whose original I'd already seen in Tamil?  I am sure there are million other practical applications for this magical memory erasure but hey, I don't think it ever should be used to wipe away recollections of a happy-once-sour-now kind of relationship. After all, u win some u lose some - Life should go on.  Leaving you with some wonderful lines from the movie. These lines are part of  Alexander Pope 's stirring poem " urlLink  Eloisa to Abelard  "   How happy is the blameless Vestal's lot! The world forgetting, by the world forgot. Eternal sunshine of the spotless mind!  Each pray'r accepted, and each wish resign'd.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink        urlLink Portugal go     Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .     England have crashed out of Euro 2004. And rightfully so.  After going ahead through (surprise of all surprises) a freak goal by Michael Owen in the 3rd minute, England played disgusting football for the rest of the 87 mts of normal time. Their attackers seldom moved forward, their creative midfielders lacked imagination, the combative midifielders just didn't win enough balls and the defence barely managed to shut out the rampaging Portuguese.   Big Phil has always proved himself to be a very shrewd reader of the game and the introduction of Simao in the second half was a stroke of sheer genius. What impressed me most was the confidence with which he pulled out Luis Figo, a move sure to have cost him his job if Portugal had lost. But Simao and the other two subs, Rui Costa and Helder Postiga repaid the faith reposed on them by their coach with two wonderful goals. To their credit, England did play brave football in extra time but the tired legs showed. Besides, the passionate crowd and the intense desire to win was the difference between the two teams. An exhilarating match that produced breath-taking football - the rest of the tournament now has to match up to some really high standards.   England's hero for the day : Ashley Cole  Portugal's hero for the day:  Christiano Ronaldo  England's Villain for the day:   urlLink David Beckham   Portugal's Villain for the day:  Costinha  Magical Moment of the match:  Helder Postiga's outrageously taken penalty.  Controversial moment of the match:  Sol Campbell's disallowed goal  For more   urlLink match stats   For complete photo gallery, click on the link at the bottom of  urlLink  this page  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "The journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step"   - and quite often its a faltering one. Heavily panned by the critics, here's my first amateurish attempt at short-story writing. After all history needs to have a record of my humble beginnings.  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------    Friday, February 13, 2004 11:54 pm     …I do it for …. You.”  The lilting music came to a slow stop and the audience instantaneously broke into raptures. The handsome crooner took turns bowing to various sections of the audience, lapping up the well-deserved applause. Sitting at the far end,  Preeti  watched as all the people jostled towards the centre of the  dance floor where the huge 10 feet cake had been laid. It was almost midnight and  Preeti  glanced at her watch yet again. There were a lot of things that bugged her in life but men coming late for a date was one thing she had never been able to tolerate.  "How could people mess up on what is probably the most important occasion of their lives?"  she pondered aloud for the umpteenth time, staring at the three empty chairs in front of her.  And just as she was resigning herself to making a quiet exit, she saw them coming. Surprise.  "They have all made it finally - but hey, am I seeing it right ? Are they actually coming in together ?”  Viewing them suspiciously as only a woman can do, Preeti's instincts told her that something crazy was about to happen.     Friday, February 13, 2004 10:57 pm    Checking her appearance one last time in the mirror,  Preeti  walked back to the table she had reserved for the evening and steeled herself for the most important hour of her life. In a few minutes, they would all be here. It was time for her to carefully weigh the merits of each case and decide on her future. The last conversation with her best friend  Divya  and those final words of advice rang loud and clear.   “So you told him yesterday that you would give your answer tonight?”  “Yes, I hinted at that.”  “Are you really sure today is the day ?”  “Yes,  Divya  !  I have waited too many years looking for Mr. Perfect that I have given up. Surely he is not going to fall down from heaven on my lap. I got to decide with what I’ve got – Besides there is no point in postponing this.”  “But Preeti, you barely know this guy. How could you even be thinking about him seriously ? C’mon, you met him during one of your training sessions and then went on-site with him. Granted he is intelligent, going places with his career but don’t you think he suffers from a big “I-am-the-biggest-gift-to-womankind” attitude ?”   “We vibe well,  Divya . I think his attitude rocks. If he’s got it, I see no reason why he shouldn’t flaunt it.”  “So does that mean Mr. “Funny n Romantic” is out ?”  “Hmmm.. I have actually called him too. Yes, we did have some wonderful times together. Those coffee dates, those movie outings, those delightful mail exchanges – I don’t deny that he is special but then we have drifted apart these last 6 months. I always got the feeling he wasn’t serious about this whole thing – he kidded around too much for my liking.”  “Oh my god ! You are just imagining things. Why don’t you just ask him ?”  “Maybe today I shall”  “Is that all or has anyone else also invited to this Swayamvar ?”  “Don’t kid me  Divya . Of course, you-know-who is also coming. I just mailed him today morning and he said he would join me.”  “What ??? Don’t tell me. Has the puppy still not stopped following the lady? Its been a year, Preeti. What more proof do you want? Can't you see he is madly in love with you."  “Hmmm”  “So how are you going to choose between them ?”  “God knows. Shucks, gotta rush coz I don’t want to be late. Maybe I will just choose on a  first-come-first-served basis considering you know how finicky I am about being on time.”  “You are so impossible. Whatever happens, darling, just remember to go with the flow. Follow your heart.”     Friday, February 13, 2004 10:46 pm     "F&^%, crazy son of a gun"  shouted  Harsha  from the side.   Screeeeeeeeeeeech!!!    "Hey, what’s the matter with you, mister ? Your girlfriend dumped you or something and you decided to end your life in front of my car. Would have happily run you down except that I’m just not in the mood for it - You better explain"   said  Priyanshu  as he rolled down the glass and shook a fist at the visibly shaken guy standing in front of his car.   "S-s-sorry folks. I was just lost in my memories. I should not have strayed onto the road. I am sorry. I am kinda late for a date and I could not find a taxi"  mumbled the lanky jeans clad guy  "Btw, the name's  Girish "  and proffered his hand.   "No time for all this. We're bloody late. I am heading downtown - so if you want a ride, jump in"  said  Priyanshu .   "That would be really useful"  said  Girish , climbing into the rear and settling down after moving aside a big bouquet of flowers.  Watching him closely in the mirrors,  Harsha  asked  "So. Where exactly are you headed?”   Fingering an exquisitely etched wooden casket,  Girish  exclaimed  "Valentine Day party at TDS - There was so much work at office that I could not pick up my date for the evening - had to call her and fix up to meet straight at TDS. I just hope she is a good mood. Especially since I plan to ask her to marry me tonight."    Shifting gears and maneuvering the sleek Ikon ahead of a slow moving bus,  Priyanshu  remarked  "Good luck mate".   Harsha  turned back and smiled. Returning the smile,  Girish  leant on the soft cushion, closed his eyes and tried to recall the strange phone conversation he had had with  Preeti  yesterday evening.    "Hi  Girish . Guess who this is"  "Hmmm.. sounds familiar but please, I am no good at these guessing games. Can you please spare me this suspense?"  "Hey, its me -  Preeti . Long time nuh..How are you doing ?"  ""What a pleasant surprise. Hi  Preeti . I am doing fine. Where were you these last six months ? I had called you up at office and even left behind numerous messages. You never called me back after that Barista date where I serenaded in front of everyone. Was I so awful that day ? We were supposed to see  Koi Mil Gaya  together, remember. What happened ?”  "Sorry yaar. But I shifted jobs and had to leave for the US on a short term assignment for my new company. You know how these things happen right ? I just came back on Wednesday and you are the first friend I am calling here."  "Great to hear that. So..Hmmmm...Whatcha doing for Friday nite ?"  "Nothin' really...You've got any plans ?"  "Why don’t we hook up for that party at  TDS ?”  "Deal. But hey, I have to meet an old friend of mine so I will join you there directly. Shall we meet there at, say, eleven p.m."   "That sounds real cool. Ciao. Will catch ya then"      Friday, February 13, 2004 10:22 pm     Harsha  sprinted down the stairs, taking them two at a time. Reaching the bottom of the last flight, he turned and ran towards the door.  Govind , the night-watchman wished him Good Night.  Half-acknowledging the greeting,  Harsha  eyes searched in vain for a taxi. One look at the deserted streets and it dawned on him that today was the taxi union’s strike. Damn. Silently cursing his bad luck,  Harsha  tried calling up his room mate Shiv to summon help. Damn. The mobile was not reachable.  Murphy’s law  had always worked against him  and today seemed to be no exception.  “I’ve got to hitch a ride.   Preeti  said 11 and I am already running late. Maybe I should buy her some flowers”   Walking purposefully towards the florist at the nearest chowk,  Harsha  saw a nice, sleek  Ikon  a few metres ahead at the intersection. It appeared as if the driver seemed to be stuck in an argument with a traffic cop. Sensing his opportunity,  Harsha   moved in and said  “Any problem?”    “Hey mate, I have no clue why this guy pulled me over but now he refuses to let me go and I can’t seem to figure out what he is saying.”  “Let me handle this”    Harsha  settled the issue by bribing the cop to ignore the “minor offence” of speeding,   “Thanks a tonne, mate. I am terribly late but I really owe you one so maybe you want me to drop you off somewhere ?”  “That would be wonderful. Any chance are you heading towards  TDS  ?”  “Touchwood – pile on”  “Wow. Thanks. So who’s the lucky chic ?”   “Am just meeting a friend of mine – what about you, Mr. Flowers-In-Hand Romeo ?”   Harsha  grinned but did not reply back. It had been three months since he had first met  Preeti  in a training session and as usual, he had started off flirting shamelessly with her. Working together in the same team for a client, Harsha had realized that he shared so much in common with Preeti as far as career goals and ambitions were concerned. So it didn’t surprise him too much when he actually found himself increasingly thinking seriously about the relationship. He had casually brought up this topic with her on a few occasions but had seen no green lights. Maybe something nice would happen today – his instinct told him there was a happy ending in store.    Friday, February 13, 2004 08:00 pm     "Chadthi Jawani..."  blared the stereo. The gongs struck 8 in  Priyanshu ’s sub-conscious mind. He had never needed an alarm to wake up for dinner -  Anand  always took care of that. No sooner would  Anand  enter home after work, than he would switch on the damn radio. Snuggling deeper into the sheets,  Priyanshu  tried to ignore the music which had now risen to intolerable volumes.    “Don’t you want to shave, take a shower, and grab a bite and leave? You don’t have much time, dude and Preeti despises late-comers, remember”  piped  Anand  from the shower.  Getting  up from his bed,  Priyanshu  grabbed the towel and ambled on towards the other bathroom. Looking into the mirror, he reflected silently on the events of the afternoon. He had just returned from the night shift and checking mail for the last time before his siesta, he had been surprised to see a mail from  Preeti . All it said was   “Dear Pumpkin, Its Val Day tomorrow – in case you didn’t realize.  Wanna meet you @ 11 @ TDS.  Love, Plum”   Aware that the evening might not transpire into anything remotely romantic, he had very reluctantly agreed to join her. Now, on second thoughts, he wasn’t so sure it had been a great idea. For one, he knew he still didn’t have it in him to bare his heart to her and more importantly he has this strange fear that something awful was going to happen that day.   “ Hey Anand, I don’t think I should go.”  “You moron, this could be your last chance to tell her. You have been Preeti’s friend, philosopher and guide for a year now. Need I remind that it was precisely this date that you broke off with Divya last year. You’ve waited long buddy. Just go get her.”   Tidily decked in an ironed, pink shirt (Preeti’s favorite color) and reeking of expensive CK perfume,  Priyanshu  pulled his car out of his garage and set off to see  Chameli . An hour and a half into the movie,  Priyanshu  changed his mind and decided to go to  TDS  after all.    Friday, February 13, 2004 11:58 pm     Girish  was first. Nervous that he clearly was, fiddling with his hands in his pockets, he ventured “Hi  Preeti . Sorry I am late.” And just as he was done with the sentence,  Harsha , who had a big bouquet of  Preeti ’s favourite orchids, rushed in. Seeing  Girish  around, he quizzically turned towards Preeti seeking an explanation and had barely started a question when  Priyanshu  trooped in. Seeing the other two, he was totally puzzled.     And then it happened.    The green-eyed, handsome crooner who had been wading through the crowd of admirers joined the group and introduced himself. “Hi, I am  Jupiter .”     Ten... Nine... Eight....     Turning his eyes to Preeti, he said  “ I’ve been observing you all evening. You’ve been waiting for someone for the last few hours. Some people spend their entire life times waiting to find their soul mates. I have found mine today. When I saw you from that corner , I realized you were my future. I realized my existence would be meaningless without you. Will you marry me ?”     Three...Two...One...      Saturday, February 14, 2004 00:01 am     “Yes, I will.”   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear Reader,  Confusion reigns. I am all hazy. Came across this wonderful (??) poem some time back but after giving it three reads I am still none the wiser as to what this profound poet has to say. Would someone please care to elaborate ? For starters I do understand that this is a verse where the poet has bared his heart out to his muse but beyond that I would really welcome if someone explained the passion in more simple English.   Expecting your inputs.  A very anxious Jupe     Thy, the heavenly blossom of mine, Why, this quest in u'r eyes so benign.  You aer the one, my life's bubbles spring up from thee, Deep blue horizon, where my sky chooses to die The breeze that glows up the fire in my soul You are my breath, the anchor that wont let me fall  The very life of me, oozing from the pores of my heart.  My heart ceases to beat, fading ur song in my ears, I stand in a dream, with trembling lips for the feel of ur cheek.  My only friend,  my foe, u make up for both. The gloriest rose an, the thorn laying beneath. Sparkling drop of rain an, the cloud's fiery breath, My eternal soul, an its brittlest sheath.  My birth an my death, here I lay in ur lap.  The heavenly blossom of mine,  Never want to see those blue eyes in a pain.  My joyous company, an dreary loneliness, The fire of my script, an the words I misspell, You light up my nights, still my sorrow of darkness, You r my sky, my wings that fell by  My dearest, you own me , all seen an unseen.  Thy , the heavenly blossom of mine, Dew drop in my desolate terrain.  The breeze that glows up the fire in my soul You r my breath, the anchor that wont let me fall    Note:  Spellings and words have been reproduced verbatim - didn't wanna be sued for misrepresentation. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There are just two kinds of people in this world - people who have a Gmail account and those who don't. For people who fall under the second category, all I can say is  "Get a life"  - You folks aren't even worth talking about - insignificant, worthless elements who have no reason for their existence :-) For all the junta who fall under the first category, all I can say is  "Join the gang".    In case all ye laymen and laywomen (perverts, don’t get ideas) out here reading this fantastic blog are wondering what this brouhaha is all about,  Gmail  is an internet email service from  Google  and is currently available  urlLink  here  . Now hold your horses. There's a catch to it. Right now it is still in the Beta testing phase hence the registrations are restricted. You can join only if you get an invite from an existing Gmail user. The existing Gmail users do not have the luxury of inviting unlimited users to Gmail. Hence getting a Gmail account is actually very difficult  (So do I see expensive gifts coming by courier?)   What’s so great about Gmail? First things first - it makes for amazing party time conversation. While having a Gmail account  might  help you score brownie points with the more intelligent amongst the opposite sex (chest swells with pride), not having one is a sure sign of a loser.   Let’s now get technical. It offers  1000 MB  of space (ok, rediff also does but..) and their simple text based interface loads up really fast.  Messages never to be deleted (after all space is not a constraint), they can be flagged, archived but also retrieved easily since Google's searching technology is extended to Gmail too. The address book on Gmail is also on auto-prompt mode - when you type the first few letters, it displays all possible matches from your address book. I am a mouse guy but for all the keyboard junkies, the keyboard shortcuts are really cool. There are so many more features but I am yet to discover most of them.  urlLink  For more details    Signing off, Jupe17(at the rate of)gmail(dot)com
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The weekend is done. I know it’s been done almost 36 hrs back but as usual, it was so eventful that it’s still worth revisiting it so late.  Friday @ work was godawful - I could hardly wait to get back home and chill out - Saw  urlLink  When Harry Met Sally   for the fourth time.  urlLink  Funny, witty, clever and definitely romantic  , this is what one would call a timeless classic - which brings us again back to the fundamental question  "Can women and men just be good friends?"   Harry Burns , much as I think u rock, its such a pity that you simply cannot understand the comfort levels in such platonic relationships. The movie was over by 11 and I still had over an hour to wait till  Euro 2004  came up on telly. Was really down, more so after seeing the movie, that I was quite tempted to down a few bottles of beer. But then a promise is a promise :-(  The best thing about friends, and I mean the really close ones, is that they know  how, when and what exactly to do to lift one's flagging spirits. Considering Lakshya was so hyped it was no wonder that all big halls were displaying House Full boards for the whole weekend. However the big depression (not in the seas but within me) had still not tided over by Saturday noon so two of my bosom buddies realized that the only way to "help" me was to take me out for a flick. So we ended up at Tribhuvan watching Lakshya 4 to 7 pm - I personally enjoyed the movie and now realize  urlLink  Farhan Akhtar   might not be a one film wonder after all. We then hung around in a few pubs and as much as Satan tried all his tricks, didn’t down a single mug. (Pat on my own back - proud of ya nigger)  Sunday was simply the highlight ! Good, nay excellent, Veg Pulav at my cousins for lunch was just the start of what turned out to be a delightful day out. I had planned to catch up with my good friend cum Sunday movie date,  urlLink  Mansur   (single and available -  he's joining IIMA too) and we had made plans to see HP3. Reaching Symphony at around 5 pm, we found that balcony tickets were sold out. Snobs that we were, we refused to sit in stall and so decided to buy front row tickets (no sniggering pls). Since such cheap tickets are usually sold only after the costlier ones are filled up, we decided to while away time at Planet M and hang around MG and Brigade doing boys stuff :-) Surprise of all surprises, when we came back at 6, it was HOUSEFULL. Faced with the prospect of a full 3 hrs at our disposal we didn't know wot to do. After an hour of book shopping @ Crosswords and an hour @ Barista bullshitting under the guise of advising about life at B-school, we had an early dinner. No sooner had the plates been cleared when Mansur opened up and gave me gyaan on how to succeed in my social life. My, my, I have never heard anything funnier than this before. Here was one of the biggest MCP's and an engineer too (hehe) teaching me how to score with women. And listening to those pearly words of wisdom I couldn't but help observe that they seemed to reflect experience. Did I miss something these last 3 years da ?   You know I get around 32 readers every day - hopefully 50% are female of which 50% are single of which 50% are looking - That should give you 4 to choose from..Inky Pinky Ponky Wonky..Lemme know if u score :-)  Ciao folks ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tamil film music has seen a lot of new talents emerging the last decade thanks to the incomparable  AR Rahman . One such person who's impressed me tremendously since her arrival in the music scene has been  Anuradha Sriram .   Born into a family with deep roots in music, Anu despite doing very well in acads in Padma Seshadri Chennai and wanting to become a Doctor, was persuaded by her father to take to music seriously. She trained under many respected Gurus such as  Padmasri Tanjavur Sri. S.Kalyanaraman, Sangeetha Kalanidhi Smt. T. Brinda  and  Dr. T.Viswanathan  in the Carnatic style and under  Pandit Manikbua Thakurdas  in the Hindustani style. She was a Gold medalist in both B.A., and M.A., in music from the  Madras University . She was given a fellowship to do her Masters in World Music from  Wesleyan University , Connecticut, U.S.A. While in the U.S.A., she learnt Western Classical Opera and Jazz. Besides this, she performed in Indonesian and West African music concerts. The  President of India Gold Medal  in 1987 for Carnatic and Light Classical Music and the  Central Government Senior Fellowship  in 1989 add to her list of many achievements.   Diversifying into films, her first big break came when she was  part of the chorus (supporting vocals as ARR likes to say) in  Bombay . She however gained fame only with one of her early solo numbers under ARR, the haunting  Anbendra Mazhaiyile  in  Minsara Kanavu . From there till today (she has even turned MD with  Five Star  along with her husband  Parasuram Sriram ), it’s been a wonderful journey and it would be an understatement to say that she has been a sheer delight to her millions of fans. Be it folk tunes, classic melodies or outright dappanguthu numbers, Anu's versatility is to be heard to be believed. And this is one artiste who can sing better in live programmes if ever that is possible. I personally feel she is the female equivalent of SPB in Tamil and would not be surprised if she acted in movies and did extremely well. To be honest, I even have a superb role for her in my script - if only someone would lend me the dough :-)  Here are some of her  urlLink  best hits  . Long live Anuradha Sriram.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Aldous Huxley  once said  "After silence that which comes nearest to expressing the inexpressible is music."  Music is a very integral part of my daily routine - No day starts without me switching on my music system after the early morning jog, I can't imagine how I could endure those torturous last hours at work from 4 pm if it weren't for my Winamp play list and then the bed-time .  While I listen to just about anything from boy bands to balle balle and trance to tapori numbers, my season's flavor changes as much as my moods do. Since the audience for my blog spans language barriers, let me mention 3 of my current favorites  1. Rom-com movies always hold tremendous appeal to me and when their sound track has some fun numbers, I always fall for them big-time.  Purrfekt example:   Ladki Kyuun  from  HUM TUM  with that extremely witty ad-man  Prasoon Joshi  penning the lyrics.   Trivia:  It seems Prasoon wrote the lyrics of 'Hum Tum' on the pot in Malaysia and text messaged line after line to Aditya Chopra and Kunal Kohli in Mumbai! Thankfully, we won't say that they're potty lyrics! Sample these...   Pyaar Usse Bhi Hai Magar Shuruaat Tumhi Se Chahe Khudh Mein Ulji Ulji Hai Par Bhaalo Ko Suljaayein I Mean You're All The Same Yaar Hum Achche Dost Hai Par Uss Nazar Se Tumko Dekha Nahin Woh Sab To Teek Hai Par Uss Barein Mein Maine Socha Nahin Sab Se Alag Hai Tum Yeh Keh Ke Paas Tumhaare Aaye Aur Kuch Din Mein Tum Mein Alag Sa Kuch Bhi Na Usko Paiye Uff Yeh Kaisi Shirt Pehnthe Ho Yeh Kaise Bhaal Khatathe Ho Ghaadi Tehz Chalathe Ho Tum Jaldi Mein Kyo Khaathe Ho Gimme A Break     urlLink For full lyrics     2. For all you Tamil music lovers, wake up..There's life beyond  AR Rahman .  Yuvan Shankar Raja  simply rocks in   urlLink 7G Rainbow colony   and how !! The album with sensitively penned lyrics by  N. Muthukumar  has a wonderful mix of fast paced numbers, lovely instrumental music (Raja's genes after all) and of course my favorite slow, sad melodies. Here's a taste of YSR magic.   Ninaithu Niniaithu   (Male version by  KK )   Pallavi:   Ninaithu Ninaithu Paarthaen Nerugi Vilagi Nadanthaen Unnaal Dhaane Naane Vaazhgiraen... Unnil Indru Ennai Paarkiraen Eduthu Padithu Mudikkum Munnae Eriyum Kadithum Edharku Pennae ? Unnaal Dhaane Naane Vaazhgiraen... Unnil Indru Ennai Paarkiraen...   Saranam 1   Amarndhu Pesum Marangalin Nizhalum Unnai Kaetkum Eppadi Solvaen Udhirndhu Pona Malarin Mounama... Thoodhu Pesum Golusin Oliyai Araigal Kaetkum Eppadi Solvaen ? Udaindhu Pona Valayal Pesuma...? Ullankaiyil Vetpum serkkum Viralgal Ingu Engey...? Tholil Saayndhu Kadhaigal Pesa Mugamum Illai Ingey Mudhal Kanavu Mudindhidum Munnae Thookum Kalaindhadhey...!   Saranam 2   Pesi Pona Vaarthaigal Ellam Kalanthorum Kaadhinil Kaetkum Saambhal Karaiyum Vaarthai Karaiyuma...? Paathu Pona Paarvaigal Ellam Pagalum Iravum Kelvigal Kaetkum Uyirum Pogum Uruvam Poguma...? Thodarndhu Vandha Nizhalum Ingey Theeyil Serndhu Pogum... Thiruttu POna Thadayam Paarthum Nambavillai Naanum Oru Tharunam Edhirinil Thondruvaay Endre Vaazhgiraen....!   3. English music .. ahem.. I know there are scores and scores of mad rocks fans here who would love me to quote from some of those cult classics of the 70s. But pray forgive me, considering the way the last month has turned up, one song which had me all ears has been  Daniel Bedingfield's   If you're not the one . I know, I was always a sucker for mush, but still... this is one heckuva song, check out these lines that start the song..   If you re not the one then why does my soul feel glad today? If you re not the one then why does my hand fit yours this way? If you are not mine then why does your heart return my call If you are not mine would I have the strength to stand at all I never know what the future brings But I know you are here with me now We ll make it through And I hope you are the one I share my life with    urlLink  for full lyrics     Any comments ?  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One question that keeps popping up often when I meet folks who cant understand what a  "Senior Marketing Executive"  does is how does a typical work day of mine shape up. So lemme just give you the more significant events.  Kaalai ezhunda udan kaapi (Coffee as soon as I wake up in the morning) - Hindu crossword in the bus - check blog and write some crap - Idli n Vada for breakfast -  mails (Yippeeee) - Good Mornings over MSN - official phone calls - more mails - hot pantry coffee - a little casual flirting over YM - a little bit of work - mails again.    LUNCH   More phone calls - a few official mails - strong coffee - a meeting here - personal mails - a presentation there -  music in Winamp - closing mails - sleep in the bus - dinner at home - Friends on Zee English - 11pm HBO - hit the sack.  The real high point however is at 2 pm - jes after lunch when I get my daily dose of  Calvin and Hobbes . Am sure everyone worth his/her salt knows about this strip but for the nerds out there, C&H was created by  Bill Waterson  in 1985. It features principally  Calvin , a hyper active six year old kid with a monstrous imagination and his best friend  Hobbes  who is in reality a stuffed tiger.(or is he not?) Then there are the fringe characters like  Susie , the gal Calvin loves to hate (or is this jes a mask for hidden affections?)  - Calvin's teacher  Mrs. Wormwood  who gets harassed no end - Calvin's  Mom and Dad  who have to perennially endure his whims -  Rosalyn  the baby-sitter, who is the only person with some control over Calvin.  Different people like C&H for different reasons. I love the inherent contradiction in the "real" Calvin exhibiting eccentricity bordering on lunacy and the "imaginary" Hobbes firmly rooted to reality. I love the rebel in Calvin, I think his brattish attitude rocks but I also freak on Hobbes and his common sense. You need to experience them to understand how I feel. Just to give you a sample, here's some delightful  Calvin-speak  for you:   "If ignorance is bliss, this lesson would appear to be a deliberate attempt on your part to deprive me of happiness, the pursuit of which is my unalienable right according to the Declaration of Independence"  "Childhood is for spoiling adulthood"  "There's never enough time to do all the nothing you want"  "The problem with the future is that it keeps turning into the present"  "If I 'm not going to be eternally rewarded for my behavior, I’d sure like to know now"  "Weekends don’t count unless you spend them doing something completely pointless."  "I'm only civil because I don’t know any swear words"  "I thought I knew everything when I was three. Now, a lifetime of experience has left me bitter and cynical."   And the last line of the last strip that WATERSON drew  continues to be one of the most endearing ones ever..C&H are zipping off on their sled and Calvin says   "Its a magical world, Hobbes ol' buddy...Lets go exploring."    Doff my hat to BW ! Long live C&H !    Other useful links:    urlLink All about C&H   - one of my favorite haunts !    urlLink  C&H quizzes      urlLink  C&H trivia  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Keep It Short n Simple  is one of the biggest lessons I learnt at B-school. If you cannot sum up a 1 hr project meeting in 5 mts (I am just back from one such long drawn affair..Twas all Aramaic and Hebrew) or a 3 hr movie in 8000 words, you are simply put - inadequate. The  urlLink  elevator test  , which I presume most of u have heard of, is the oft quoted reference in this context. Now, I am sure u are asking me how is all this relevant to today's blog. Simple answer is that I don’t have  much time to write anything earth shattering so will simply  KISS .  Before I forget, let me try and fill you in on whatever happened last weekend. After a meticulous search  which included downloading specs from multiple websites, taking down quotes from atleast 6 vendors, I finally zeroed down on a   urlLink Nokia 3100   for my new mobile. I can hear the groans - yes, it’s an old model but then the joy I had on discovering it is akin to that of a palaentologist who discovers fossils of a dinosaur in his backyard. So please welcome  Bob , the latest addition to my family. No prizes for guessing wot color he is.. Blue rules.. Pete , though is still with me - have turned it over to my parents.   So where did I finally buy it from ? There is a  Sangeethas shoppe  at the  Forum in Koramangla  and they sell mobiles at prices which are considerably cheaper than anywhere else in the market.(Thanks Priya for the tip) And lo, who did I see when I went there on Saturday evening ? Guess.. Guess.. Clue:  Some of the Indian cricketers are attending a camp in Bangalore..Okie, times up. I saw   cho-chweet Irfan Pathan   (SS, this guy is tall, handsome and has a winsome smile..He's an Adonis..n he has talent too - Neday better than that bloke Yuvraj - sudhar jao) and   butter-fingers Parthiv Patel   at the Reebok store presumably trying out shoes..An hour later they were still there at the shop and twas then that I realised it was a publicity gimmick.. People were going crazy with their camera phones. Neway it was a good evening out at Forum.  Shucks. This post has exceeded its planned length. Havta go. Byeeeee.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saw Denmark dominate Italy yesterday @ Euro2004 and am now not so sure that we will go all the way after all. This opinion has only been reinforced seeing Sweden's dominant display later last night. So what should  urlLink  Traps   do? Remove  Del Piero  and bring in  Pirlo  for sure, after all AC won the Scudetto thanks to this wonderful playmaker.  Gattuso  has to start - we need this combative midfielder to win us more balls. But most importantly I believe that with the hyped  urlLink 4-2-3-1  formation, quite a few people do not really know where they fit in and what they are expected to do.  Zanetti  looked lost,  Totti  looked bored and  Cassano  after coming in as a sub hardly created a ripple. I still prefer the old fashioned 4-4-2 with  Vieri  and  Totti  up front. Wonder what the Italian papers said this morning.  Another thing that struck me as I watched Italy play yesterday was that these guys could actually do well in  Rugby  too - beats me how they never do well in the  urlLink 6 nations cup . Their fullbacks,  Nesta  and  Cannavaro  in particular, tug at shirts and bring down opponents so effortlessly they cud easily make the switch to the back row or scrum halves. Ever observed how these Italian midfielders move forward - its always a 5m pass backwards who then moves forward 3m and then passes it back again.. Getting it ? Aint it summat similar to rugby ?  Enough of footer. Got this joke over e-mail yesterday - found it quite amusing.  (Dedication: P, Lage raho)   Enjoy !   Boys are like apples on trees. The best ones are at the top of the tree. The girls don't want to reach for the good ones because they're afraid of falling and getting hurt. Instead they just get the rotten apples that are on the ground, that aren't as good, but easy. So the apples at the top think that there is something wrong with them, when in reality, they are amazing. That is why we just have to be a little patient and the right girl, the one who takes a chance to find the good, right apple, will come someday...    Ps:  Today’s episode of  urlLink  “The Original Love Story”   will not come out due to the scriptwriter suffering from verbal constipation. The inconvenience caused is regretted. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Came in late 2 office today since folks have moved in finally..Have so much to say about the weekend but then theres loads of work to do :-( So will fill up space with something i wrote some time back..Needless to say, its "utter crap"..Ensoii the toture !    Good friends   are like four leaf clovers: hard to find and lucky to have . Thankfully, my friends have been fortunate to have known me.  Acknowledging the fact that many of my buddies have had defining influences on me, this leads to a more fundamental question: What does it take to sustain such friendships ? Easy enough question but the answer is not so simple.  Quite often I’ve realized that all it takes is to say a few simple words like  “I care”  or  “I’ll be there for you”  rather than leave it to be implicit. And what better way to say these than with gifts/presents/treats/simple acts! However if you are a pathetic poet like me, then forget all those filmi herogiri where you can break into a song at once    :-(  Here’s what I usually do…  •	The easiest way to a man’s heart is thru  food . So all you gals, just find out his favorite restaurant, book a table in advance for a crowded Saturday evening - preferably somewhere in the centre (shady corners are only for lovelorn couples), order his favorite dishes (men hate ordering) and then let him ogle at all the women who come in. If possible, sweetly bitch about a few and engage in casual banter about the women in his life. Believe me, he feels on top of the world. He feels he is significant and people care about him!!  •	For all you guys listening, nothing turns on women like  new clothes .. So take your friend along asking her to help you pick clothes for your sister/cousin. While she helps you out, no woman can resist trying out some for herself.  Just observe what she freaks out on and without her knowledge, gift her same stuff she tried out.   Note:  The above two acts are better done on just any other day rather than a special occasion like a Birthday.   •	Girls love  lipstick  and  makeup . Read about it, find out the latest “happening brands” and then take them to a big shopping mall where they can try out a million shades before choosing the one they saw first.. Stand besides and offer ’’educated opinions’’ (women really appreciate that). Try n sense their pulse, reassure them about their selection - Generally be very supportive even if you don’t agree with their choices!  •	An ordinary friend knows all about your favorite movies and your crushes on the stars. A great friend takes you out to all those movies even though he/she cant stand them - I know its tuff for gals to like Govinda but have u ever seen the joy in his face (read mine) when you sit with him and ensoii the mindless antics ? Be with him and watch him go ga-ga over  Bipasha Basu  and i promise, he wont forget that evening for a lifetime!! And yes guys, we all care a damn for  Hrithik Roshan  or  Brad Pitt  but its just 3 hrs - Surely its worth it , for friendships sake !  •	For an erudite friend, nothing is more appropriate than a thoughtful book. It always works! While  Bach  is recommended,  Ayn Rand  is not! Heavy philosophy, murder mysteries are a no-no. Light comedies, classics have done best for me!  •	 Music  is divine! Nothing can work better than a CD recorded with all the songs that he/she has enjoyed since his/her youth. And if you are a childhood pal, it helps if you know who his /her heartthrob was during school and college days and recording all those hits songs.  •	Another simple yet sentimental idea would be to gift your best friend a framed  photograph  of u and him/her together.   •	On second thoughts, all the above are useful but in my list, this last one tops it all. I’ve never claimed to be a great poet but for my dearest of dearest friends, I always gift ‘em a  Tee with a personalized poem  inscribed on it.    Hasta manana till I get my gift! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      and all I have are questions.    Why is it that we never realize the value of something that's been with us all along till we know we've lost it forever ?  Why is it that after so much preparation for the most defining moment of our lives, we still miss it and realize only after its too late ?  Why does it happen that in the search for perfection, we miss the simple joys of being flawed ?   Why do we so insist on dwelling on dreams that we forget to live ?    Contemplative mood this surely is.. And what’s more frightening is the fact that most of these questions are today throwing up answers that seem to be diametrically opposite to what I have believed all along..  Thanks to all those who commented on the previous blog :-) I wud love to comment that " Emotional blackmail works " but I guess I shud know better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its been a very rough week @ work what with bushfires all around, the fire brigade on leave and anyone and everyone who knows how to handle a water hose asked to pitch in..Neway its all a thing of the past n I shant spoil my Friday by having yet another flashback considering there's so much to look forward to this weekend.  For starters, F1 moves to the American continent and I have this gut feeling that  Montreal  is gonna throw in a real shock result. The folks at  Maranello  aren’t gonna be popping their champagne bottles come Sunday - am tipping  BAR  to put in a strong performance. After all its gotta happen sometime this season -  Button  and  Sato  have been simply too good. And of course there's Euro 2004 at Portugal - it doesn’t get more intriguing than an  England vs. Franc e match, can't wait to see  Henry  and  Pires  run riot.. And then there is my Fatherland trying to salvage its reputation against  Netherlands .   N then there's  Bebo  to drool at in  Dev ..n  Cybil Trelawney  to catch up with... Loads of B'day shopping to complete..Must also look out for  Bob  since I’ve decided to offload  Pete  to Mom n Dad..So much to do, so little time !   Interesting times are back again  !   ps:  I need to crib - its compulsive. I know there are a million people reading my blog everyday (or so I wud like to believe - sitemeter though maintains its only  31 ) but why on earth can't they jes leave behind a nice li'l comment. I understand its a pain to register but atleast as  ANON , yaar. I demand it..Else I will stop blogging..Okie, I didn’t mean that..But u better or else !! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      He he he :-) That actually rhymed.. which means I am making progress in my poetic endeavors. (My heart swells with pride - but why am I almost blushing like a new bride - Shucks, yet again I digress - but then maybe its due to the stress - There's loads to do n its already bloody late- Ranting at this odd hour seems to be my fate ) Holy Cow !! That also rhymed ?? Mebbe I am India's answer to Wordsworth ;-) Its now 2:04 am.. That brilliant verse took me jes four minutes..Wow !!   Neway, wots it with two o clock n me..When I look back(that’s the third flashback for this week) I remember a lot of crazy things that have happened at this unearthly hour..The most recent thing I can recollect is meeting Ramkumar, a long lost school mate of mine after 9 years at a roadside motel last week. Both of us had been returning from our hometowns to Bangalore and had alighted from our respective buses half woozy suffering from the intolerable movie being played in our buses. Literally bumping into each other at the Johnny, we had exchanged visiting cards, cell phone nos, gossiped a little about life and then gone our ways.  And then…The 11 pm late night HBO movie ends at around 1:15am and after eating my Maggi from the night canteen, I still clearly recollect the endless hours of Table Tennis that I’ve played at SP. Thrashing the living daylights outta Ashish " Bond" Jain at those odd hours gave me a terrific kick. It was as if  I was taking revenge on behalf of all the engineers against the CAs - the buggers used to screw us in acads :-)  And anyone whos ever watched Asianet (shant tell u which day) will also tell u that 2 am is a great time to have an honest man-to-man talk.... Distinctly remember how Murali, one of my good friends from under grad days, called me up one night in December 2000 (it was the week when our cable wala disconnected our line citing our refusal to settle his back wages), woke me up from my deep slumber and gave me a blow-by-blow account of what had transpired you-know-where :-)  There are lots more..The drunken walk from Enigma to SPCE after Tusku's job treat.... I could go on.. but I shall rest here..yawn... Zzzzzzzzz 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We are all quirky..Every single Joe (and his mother too) but some of us are quirkier than the rest.. And then there are people who are downright nuts. No prizes for guessing which category I fall under. It isn’t entirely co-incidental that I was called " normal " at college. Tracing the origins of the way i am today.... Zzzzzzzzz...Transport to the not-so-distant past...  The movie was  Roja ..Posters were put up in very few corners of  Trichy .. There was hardly any publicity.. Sensing a chance to watch a  Mani  movie FDFS, I remember rushing to  Ramba cinema hall  at around 9 am to catch the 11 am première. I was eighth in the Queue..The counters opened at half past ten and after selling precisely seven tickets, they downed the shutters. Imagine missing it by just that proverbial whisker.. Undaunted, I stayed back determined to catch the matinee..After all, I was now first in the line. But believe it or not, they did not even sell any tickets at the counter at 2pm. It was all out in the black market. I returned home dejected and swore not to see the movie at that hall.. And it ran there for 75 odd days before they shifted it to another hall - whilst poor me was torn between wanting to see it desperately and maintaining my resolve.  Then of course, I also need to mention about my cricketing experiences. I think the year was  1994  and I was in Std 11. I was representing my district at the under-16 level and we were playing Pondicherry in the quarterfinals away from home. The whole of the first day had been rained off and winning the toss, we put them in on the final day. Pretty soon things had taken a horrible turn for us and we'd dropped around 8 catches in the first hour. Edges were flying to the slips and gully and all the butter fingers in our team had been taking turns in letting them through.  Since I had a strong arm and was one of the safest pair of hands in the team, I had as usual landed up in the outfield. (If not, I'd have settled for nothing but Point) But at the drinks break, my coach ordered me to get into the slip cordon. Reluctant to join the circus, I stood at second slip and watched my captain  Navin  drop a sitter at first slip. We switched places but the ball followed him to second. He dropped another. And in the middle of all this, our wicket keeper  Lawrence  muffed a sitter of a run out. There was too much action around me and it was on that chaotic day, I solemnly pledged never to get into the slips again. Needless to say, my pledge remains unbroken. And ya, we won that match - wanna know how - by spin of the coin since both teams could not complete even a single innings.. So ironic !!  There are numerous other incidents that I can recount but the latest cranky decision of mine is to never see the movie  HUM TUM . Lemme explain. There is this person I asked out for this movie (and I don’t ask every  Jane, Sally and Susie  out..so u can stop smirking) and she actually had the gall to turn me down :-) Wots this world coming to ? People are out to ruin my statistics. Killjoys. Sadists. Considering my plight, I decided to fall back on the standard rules that are religiously followed by "losers".    Rule 1  - If u don’t get what u want, erase all evidence that u even tried. But since I am honest  (did I score any brownie points with this confession)  I cannot obviously follow this.  Rule 2  - If you cant erase the evidence, rubbish it away. But again this is not gonna work coz I have told all n sundry that  HUM TUM  was a movie I strongly believed to be MISS NOT.  Rule 3  - Last resort- damage control: Create an impression that it does not really matter :-p  I think I will settle down to saying " When Harry met Sally is an absolute classic and I am not gonna let a cheesy, Bollywood remake ruin my fond memories ". Wotsay ?? :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Unforgettable moments on the silver screen can sometimes be relived through their sound tracks. After all, who can ever forget  Nino Rota  and  Carmine Coppola 's haunting score in the  Godfather  trilogy (remember the mournful solo trumpet in the Godfather Waltz) or  Francis Lai 's catchy piano notes for  Love story .  However being the sentimental silly that i am, one sound track that has always had me rivetted to my ear phones is  urlLink  Notting Hill  . With a super script penned by  Richard Curtis , ably directed by  Roger Michell  and starring the exteremely likeable  Julia Roberts  and the incomparable  Hugh Grant ,  Notting Hill  remains one of my all time favorite movies. A fairy tale romance between a famous movie actress and a loser of a bookstore owner, Notting Hill is absolute feel good fare. And the music in this movie contributes so much to the magic that even the sound track was a mega hit. It has something in it for everyone - from boybands ( 98 degress, Boyzone ) tp country singers ( Shania Twain ) to classic soulsters ( Al green, Bill Withers ).  Everyone's surely heard the hugely popular " When you say nothing at all " by  Ronan Keating  but the album also boasts of two enchanting instrumental pieces composed by   urlLink Trevor Jones   on his guitar. However my personal favorites in the album are the heartfelt  "Ain't no sunshine"  by  Bill Withers  and the surreal but nice  "She"  by  Elvis Costello .  And before i sign off, here are some lines from  Al Green 's  "How Can You Mend A Broken Heart?"   And how can you mend a broken heart?  How can you stop the rain from falling down?  How can you stop the sun from shining?  What makes the world go round?  How can you mend this broken man?  How can a loser ever win?  Please help me mend my broken heart and let me live again     Track listing:   urlLink  No Matter What   - Boyzone  urlLink  You've Got A Way   - Shania Twain (Notting Hill remix)  urlLink  I Do (Cherish You)   - 98 Degrees   urlLink  She   - Elvis Costello  urlLink  Ain't No Sunshine   - Bill Withers How Can You Mend A Broken Heart? - Al Green Gimme Some Lovin' - Spencer Davis Group  urlLink  When You Say Nothing At All   - Ronan Keating Ain't No Sunshine - Lighthouse Family (bonus track) From The Heart - Another Level (bonus track) Everything About You - Steve Poltz (remix, bonus track) Will And Anna - Trevor Jones (Score) Notting Hill - Trevor Jones (Score)   Highly recommended ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to the most romantic fortnight in every calendar year                     'If you can meet with triumph and disaster                  And treat those two impostors just the same.'    Welcome to the annual pilgrimage to the Mecca of tennis – Welcome to the Theatre of Dreams - Welcome to Centre Court, Wimbledon.   The usual suspects:  Strawberries and umbrellas – “Play is suspended” and  urlLink Alan Mills  -  urlLink Smartly dressed ball girls in dark green and purple  –  urlLink The courtesy for the royalty  – Sir Cliff Richards and Mick Jagger – Sue Barker and the pilgrimage to Henman Hill……..   Down memory lane:   urlLink Borg’s fifth in 1980  -  urlLink John “You can’t be serious” McEnroe in 1981  –  urlLink Boom Boom Becker in 1985  –  urlLink Tearful Novotna in 1993  -  urlLink The first streaker in 1996  –  urlLink The People’s final in 2001   I could go on and on but I will leave you to reminisce on your own fond memories of the hallowed turf. But before you folks leave, please also check out this  urlLink virtual tour of Centre Court  and the rest of Wimbledon and don’t forget to visit the  urlLink new art gallery  in the museum.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       40000 feet  below sea level...That was how low I had felt yesterday.. There have been days when i've been cross with everything and everyone around me for no rhyme or reason.. God help all those who interacted with me on one of those days..But yesterday was different. I knew exactly why I was feeling run down but could do nothing about it..It all boiled down to one person   35 42 24 54 11   .. I know that's cryptic -  Maybe its my predilection with puzzles or my new found obsession with The  Da Vinci Code  but do have a shot at it just for kicks -  Hint:  Don’t assume its a name with five alphabets ;-) The bell has rung and I am on my last lap as far as the novel is concerned and much as its been predictable these last hundred pages, I could barely put down the book as my shuttle reached office this morning. Am leaving for home today evening - might be my last visit to  Trichy , so nostalgic - and hope to finish it in the bus.  And yes, the much awaited hike happened today and u know how I feel :-)))))))))))))))   Ciao and have a nice weekend folks !  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Continuing from Page 164, yesterday was a stark contrast to Day one. The chapters have become increasingly shorter, the encounters more and more predictable and the whole novel seems veering towards an end I think I already know. I guess only time will tell..After yesterday's read, my inadequacies in history and religion have been thoroughly exposed. I am totally intrigued by the fact that there seems to have existed a  urlLink "radical"  school of thought which actually believed that the Bible was a totally fabricated book compiled by people with vested interests with the sole idea of promoting the divinity of the  human  Jesus Christ  and using his influence to further their own power base. Besides this, it is also believed that the  urlLink Holy Grail  is not simply a cup but actually refers to a woman who is a direct descendant of Jesus.(So Jesus Christ did have a girlfriend) Remarkable, isn’t it ? And yes, one of the scenes also mentions in passing about a  urlLink Bois de Bologne  or "Garden of Earthly Delights" situated very close to the famous Roland Garros courts. Gotta check it out whenever I go to Paris :-)  And talking of Roland Garros, its the second week at the French Open and believe it or not, some things never change. The  Spanish Armada , a regular in the last 4 for the past decade, might have been replaced by three Argentinians (??) -  Korea (Coria),  Nalla pandian (Nalbandian) and  Gow Deo  (Gaudio) but its still those long, overdrawn rallies, still the same rowdy crowd and still the dark red, slow clay.. How boring ! I cant wait for Wimbledon to start ! However on the flip side, those two siblings (yuckkk) are out and what we have now are some mysteriously romantic names from the erstwhile USSR -   urlLink Anastasia Myskina   and  Elena Dementieva . Three cheers to women's tennis !    "The old order changeth, yielding place to new..."    What’s cooking on the office front ? Nothing much. My sweetheart of a boss finally broke the news to me about the impending "salary correction" - the pessimist in me noted the usage of "correction" rather than "hike" and started worrying, my optimist of an ex-roomie Anand explained that maybe my boss felt I was grossly underpaid (wishful thinking) and hence used the word "correction" instead of "hike" to boost my ego. Wotever it is, I just hope it happens - and if it does - Anand, u get an extra special "mmwaaaahhhhhhhh" - on MSN, of course ! :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can't believe I am in office today - started  Dan Brown's The Da Vinci Code  yesterday evening and must confess that it's been gripping so far - never read anything as compelling as this since  Forsyth . (Gee, thanks Mansur!) Besides the fact that I am a crossy aficionado and the anagrams were delightful, what’s impressed me so far is the way  Brown  has mixed fast paced fiction with loads of details about art.   And of course, there was this incredible thing about   urlLink PHI  ..Lemme explain.. PHI  (pronounced like in fie), as the more mathematically inclined amongst us would know, is the numeric constant  1.618 . However 1.618/1 which is also called the  Divine Proportion  is a very important number, almost ubiquitous in nature. Would you believe if I told you that  #  the quotients of adjacent terms in the  urlLink Fibonacci series  has the astonishing property of approaching PHI  # you divide the number of female bees by the number of male bees in any beehive, the result is PHI  # sunflower seeds, which grow in opposing spirals, have the ratio of each rotations diameter to the next as PHI  # the next time you are in a shower, measure yourself from the tip of your head to the floor and then divide it by the distance from your belly button to the floor and the result is PHI  # the ratio of distance from your shoulder to fingertips / elbows to fingertips = PHI    PHI  is present everywhere - in the architectural  dimensions of the Greek Parthenon, the Egyptian Pyramids, the United Nations Building in New York, in the organizational structures of  Mozart's sonatas,  urlLink Beethoven's Fifth Symphony  and was even used by  urlLink Stradivarius  to calculate the exact placement of the f-holes in the construction of his famous violins (think Sherlock Holmes)  Exhilarating, isn’t it ?   164  pages done and  320  odd more to go, I called it quits at 2:40 today morning.. If only I didn’t have my appraisal due for discussion today, I would have been on my way to  Chennai  to attend  Ramakrishnan's engagement  (my roomie at SP), reading The Da Vinci code in train ! (sigh) Alas - things don’t always fall in place.. Wouldn't it be so nice if we could have  urlLink Book leave  to add to Casual, Sick leave etc..Wotsay old hag ?  The lappie is still not working - My office PC is still shutting down for every 15+ mts of inactivity and I don’t have the time to reformat it..Life sucks !! And the first mail I check after logging in is one from the big boss with a "big wish list" as to what he needs of me pronto. Fair enough but when most of it is work like calling up people to get the latest business projections and then sieving through loads and loads of data in XL, you can imagine how I feel..Neway havta rush now..Will keep you all posted on The Da Vinci Code..Till then, ciao !!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ego trips have often taken me on unforgettable journeys of self-discovery. A lot of us must have often indulged in Googling about ourselves to measure up where we stood on the popularity scale.  "Self-Googling is not simply narcissism, though that's certainly part of it,"  explains  Alexander Halavais , who teaches at the  University at Buffalo .   Unable to decide on a topic to blog today, I set off yet again trying to determine how much the world knew of this wonderful superhuman Jupie - with considerable help from a few  urlLink passer-bys , I finally landed up at  urlLink Googlism . Trying out Jupie, I drew a blank and my ego was shattered. Settling down for the more common-place Jupe, here's what came up...N my my, was I surprised..My comments on the results in italics.    Jupe is thinking of how to make a perfect crime   (Not again :-( How does everyone find out whenever I plan to smoke in the loo to set the fire alarm off?)    Jupe is a lovable 2 year old shepherd mix who loves to play with other dogz as well as kongs and jollyballs   (Talk about a dog's life - spot on)    Jupe is adept at using big words and frequently uses them to his advantage   (I hold an opposing viewpoint - I think that’s preposterous propoganda - unpardonable sacrilege.....)    Jupe is jann's husband's ex   (Its all relative, u see!)    Jupe is missing   (Advertise in LOST and NOT TO BE FOUND pls)    Jupe is a skirt   (Errr..Its okie..You shud complete that.. add  chaser )    Jupe is a slow learner   (Whoever said that the slow and steady win the race wasnt lyin', I hope ?)    Jupe is a business studies graduate with over 15 years experience in the marketing services industry   (This is scary..this thing knows me..The real me..)    Jupe is one of the best artists I know   (Knew it all along - Vincent and Leo' ve been singing my praises since ages)     Jupe is the best thing i've had in bed   (Aint this the heights of self-gratification? Yuckkkk)    Jupe is more human than oliver   (Is this the Twist in the tale?)    Jupe is the only character who gives us a sense of hope in hard times   (N this, ladies and gentlemen, is why I blog)    Jupe is still doing its job as the solar system's vacuum cleaner   (Eureka! Finally my dream job..)    Jupe is redeemed humanity   (This is THE TRUTH and nothing but THE ABSOLUTE TRUTH)    Jupe is disqualified from being a director from 1st august 2000 to 10th july 2006   (And to think that I had barely yelled my first ACTION and CUT..tch tch)    Jupe is one of the most interesting yet laid back people I know   (Come to my arms, ye enlightened soul)    Jupe is the brains   (Arent we forgetting the CAPS and   bold  )   I sure enjoyed this.. Dont hold back..Just go ahead and try it :-p 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Hey old hag,      You did it once in the past when u shifted jobs - i didn't take offence coz i kinda understood. But u r doing it again now - u think i don't know, dont u ? Okie, i know all about January 2005. So will u be honest and tell me or do i need to be kept waiting. Don't u know happiness is the only thing that doubles when shared. We r pals, right ?      Cheerio,     J    **********************************************************************************   Hello Mr.Curious,      Thanks for that compliment that i seem to be managing my time well. Many of the posts are typed on the spur of the moment (I try my best though to "collect my thoughts", "get organised" and "run a spell check" always), quite a few have been ideas at the back of my head for a long time&nbsp; but nowadays with my lappie back in action (yippeeee), i do type some of these posts at odd hours. For example, the  H20 post  was done at around 3 am when i couldn't get to sleep :-) Did that answer your question ? Good. Next fanmail pls.  Cheers,     Me     &nbsp; **********************************************************************************   Dear u-no-hu,      I..errr..wanted to know if...(Tongue-tied) Chuck de (Shud i - shud i not) Not now atleast. (how much longer Jupie)        &nbsp;   Have a super day :-)     R    **********************************************************************************   Respected  Premji-san ,       "Sorgame endraalum adhu namma Wipro pola varuma"  Sorry, got carried away. I just meant to say "I love your company and adore you" :-) You were so nice during the  MSI , now be a good ol' man and give me a whopping  PPR  and i will serve you loyally. In case you are a little confused about the %, maybe i can send you my timesheets for the last 2 weeks to help you make up your mind. Or easier still, repeat after me -  Jupie deserves a 50% hike  :-))))  Kind regards,     Emp no: 93135    **********************************************************************************   Dei PB,      I know you don't read this blog but i will get someone to fwd u this post coz i am way too nice to ask u all this F2F :-)&nbsp; Here's my wish list        1. Wireless headfones       2. Twelve O' Clock High VCD       3. Loads of chocos       Doesn't it look familiar? Yeah. Its precisely what i asked you last time around when u claimed u had no time to shop ;-) Take care and go to Vegas this time without fail.        &nbsp;   R       &nbsp; **********************************************************************************   My dear dear blog,      I've been hearing from people that u were cribbing about how i rarely give you an off. How would you like a weeks break? Did i hear u say " Good riddance " :-)        &nbsp;   See ya. Ciao     Me     &nbsp; **********************************************************************************  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've realised that sometimes when we don't really want to talk directly to people but still want to get some messages across, there are ways to do this tactfully. For example, we could drop some (not-so) subtle hints in letters that weren't supposed to have been read by the intended recipients but somehow got to them. I am NOT saying the following are something like that but... :-)     Dear girlfriend,   First things first. U shud have never married Boyfriend till the deadline was over :-( I know thats not how it is in  My Best Friend's Wedding  but still... :-(   Secondly a) Having done it, u shud quit trying to keep in touch with "whats happening" here. Its so annoying. OK? :-(  Secondly b) I have still not seen  HUM TUM  so stop asking me again n again n again. Grrrrr.   Thirdly, I am sure you have read those stupid  Erica Jong  books (i remember seeing  FEAR OF FLYING  in ur Chennai pigsty) - that woman spoke some sense too - here's her take on  ADVICE  " Advice is what we ask for when we already know the answer but wish we didn't."  So from now on, please advice accordingly :-)   Fourthly, I'm still waiting for those tickets to  Singapore  or have i been compromised in your latest austerity drive ?   Fifthly, summing up, u r such a pain - why don't they send you on a mission to  Mars  or  Venus,  whichever is further, for 6 years with the option of an extension :-))   Love  The-Jilted-One     ************************************************************************    Dear Boyfriend,   Firstly a) Please get urself a job in a timezone where i do not have to endure 2 hrs of YM chat with ur better half on a day to day basis.  Firstly b) If you can't shift, i am game - get me a job faaaaar faar away, even  Reykjavik  will do.   Secondly, i don't like that name one bit. Its unisexual. Please, please dont let her take  ALL  the decisions.   Thirdly, thanks a million for saying more that night by not saying and jes listening. U r the best (but i am the bestest)   Love  R   ps:  NSU  is not that great da - ask your cousin to call me up.      ************************************************************************   Dear Anon,   I know i said a lot of stuff that day but after a long nights sleep, i am wiser. You have been the catalyst yet again :-p I have kinda made up  MY  mind but I am  NOT  gonna tell  YOU  exactly what you should be doing - coz i have now realised i am not the most competent person to do that. After all i do seem to be " flippant " and " frivolous " so just follow your heart - it will never fail you. Take care and remember i am just a call away.   Forever  R      ************************************************************************  Dear Ram,   The dear was put there purely coz my mom wouldn't approve otherwise. I know u r a real bozo and will probably never read this post but if u ever do, its time you returned my 4k back.   Asshole   ! (Mom, you didn't see or hear that)   Love (purely outta respect for my mom again)  B***u    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We were 16 of us in the Admissions Committee. We were the envy of most of our batch mates. We were the " chosen ones " - the ones who decided the future of SP. We had our parties - We had our fights - We went through all of it together - we were  FAMILY .  Before our farewell,  Aparna  had this idea of designing a Tee shirt with a caricature of each of us in our characteristic poses. When she was through with it, we loved it so much that we decided we will take a snap along the same lines. Needless to say, lot of the poses weren't very flattering but we were all sports and today this is one snap that brings back a flood of memories.  Attagal !! Here it is...   urlLink       urlLink Adcom group snap   Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .      Sitting/squatting from left to right    Thiruvalli Rangachari Anand aka TRAsh  - Sharp brain hiding behind that lazy allure captured in the pose of Lord Ranganathan himself.   Nandakishore aka Nandu Re  - The dancer/musician/artiste of the gang   Jayashri aka Amma  - caught in the act - if it was the Kavach kundala for Karna, then its the cell phone for this lady :-)   Pranav Dhar aka Peelu  and  Neelam Singh aka Neelu  - Thick as thieves, pals forever   Narayan Subramanian aka Nari  - The sincere, serious, hard working swamiji who had to be persuaded to smile for this photograph   Aparna Sivakumar aka Appu  - The creative brains behind ADCOM including this photo/caricature    Standing from Left to Right    Rahul Sarin aka Casanova  - Young, dashing knight-in-shining-armor who doubled as Shweta's guardian angel   Shweta Jhanji aka JhaanGE  - the "Behn of all Behns" tying the "Rakhi of the day"   Ramakrishnan aka Ki Bro  - the smiling (due to relief) "Bhai of the day"   Rajesh Kumar aka Dada  - ADCOMs home-bred Kumar Sanu   Ritesh Arya aka Aaloo  - " Hic Hic Hurray " was his motto in life   Raghunandan aka Rags  - " Show me the beer " was the mantra for this man   Sachin Anand aka Andy  - Our Captain with his "usual luggage"   Amrit Pal Singh aka Paaji  - " Wots my next funny line " reads the look on his face, always   Kiran Kumar Das aka KKD  - Forever lurking behind, doing nothin'  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just back from a  2 hr 32 mts 41 sec  conference call. Of course i had a  7 mt break  in between when i came back n did some important things..Hold on.. Like commenting on friends' blogs, replying to personal mails..Nothing official about it.. But these conf-calls can be sucha pain u know. Uffffffffff. How many more years am i gonna speak about this  1B$ ,  3O2OO  employees,  30  offices,  91%  schedule adherance, blah.. blah.. blah.. Oops. we just hired  6  more ppl so make it  30206 . Neway need to unwind hence this post. Don't swear coz nobody is forcing you to read it.    Movie mania:   Generally speaking, i seem to have a healthy dislike for sci-fi movies. To quote die hard fans of&nbsp;this genre, I have always lacked the "imagination or class" to appreciate such multilayered efforts. But one movie which beat the trend was  Steven Spielberg's   MINORITY REPORT . Saw it for the second time again on Star last Saturday and enjoyed it much more this time around. An ingenious concept, brilliant narrative, deft technique, sublime performances..The movie had it all.   I was always a sucker for mush (ok ok some ppl call it chick flicks) and when i heard my CD wala sing praises of this "latest"  Pierce Brosnan  movie being a "super hit", i fell for it. It takes a lot for me to rubbish a rom-com but  LAWS OF ATTRACTION  is very mildly put, absolute trash.&nbsp; Imagine a romantic movie where there is no screen chemistry between the lead pair and comedy sequences are not even half as funny as  Johnny Lever's  (yikkkessss) - add to this insipid dialogues and a sleep-walking performance by the starcast and what do you have - A perfect recipe for a horrible Sunday evening.  Avoid LAWS OF ATTRACTION like the beubonic plague.     Musical ramblings:   I have still not got over the  Phir Milenge  hangover. My mom calls its the official  Suprabhatham  of 257/1 :-)  Prasoon Joshi  is the best thing to have happened to Bollywood in the last few years.. No, maybe  Mallika Sherawat  is..Or is it  Katrina Kaif ..Chuck de ;-)  Check out  Jeene Ke Ishaare  - Gulzar would be proud of lyrics like these...  Kuch Khushbuyen Yaadon Ke Jungal Se Beh Chali  Kuch Khidkiyan Lamhon Ke Dastak Pe Khul Gayi Kuch Geeth Purane Rakhe The Sirhaane Kuch Sur Kahin Khoye The Bandish Mil Gaye  Jeene Ke Ishare Mil Gaye  Bichde The Kinare Mil Gaye  Meri Zindagi Main Teri Baarish Kya Hui  Mere Raste Darya Bane Behne Lage Meri Karvaton Ko Tune Aake Kya Chhua Kahin Khwab Neendon Ki Gali Rehne Lage  for  urlLink  full lyrics       Book corner:   Remember, you heard it first at my blog.&nbsp; Its official now.   urlLink THE RULE OF FOUR  ,&nbsp;the book i reco'd looong time back, is selling like hot cakes at all of India's book stores. Stars and celebrities ranging from  Naseeruddin Shah  to  Sachin Pilot ,  Amisha Patel  to  Jupe  are all planning to read it. Yes. Its out in hard-bound and it costs a whopping Rs. 510 (nobody gets me expensive gifts) *sob* *sob*    Miscellaneous:    Joke of the week:  My friend Mansur whoz joined IIMA this year won an election on Thursday. He successfully contested against 4 other "gentle"men to become the first year rep.    Funny:  When i asked him what were the responsibilities of this exalted post, to quote him verbatim this is what he had to say  "It means they the pgp office kicks my ass if they're not happy with the batch and the batch kicks my ass if they're not happy with the office"   Funnier:  When quizzed on what made him stand for this  "It's a big post for the 1st year -&nbsp; not to mention the fact that i get to meet all the girls in the 1st year"   Funniest:  When i asked him how he managed to win, he said  "I stood on the planks of honesty, fairness and commitment"     Some things never change, do they ;-)   High point of yesterday:   People call me funny but compared to my bro, i am rank pedestrian.   urlLink Venki  's stories were legendary at  SP  and he's now joned  MindTree  here in B'lore. The  Ki Bros  r back though he refuses to meet me till i promise to share "my women" with him :-p&nbsp; See, isn't he funny ?  Yesterday he had me in splits with stories of his interaction with  Jiju Jolly  (now eemajin yeh Mellu sey that), his boss and  Ruku Jolly , his boss's sister. Wot's it gonna be today bro - If not for these Mellus, who wud provide us such free entertainment :-) As i say Lage Raho !!  Now will someone pls share with me a nice Mellu joke&nbsp; :D 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Jetting against the waters on a fast speedboat with the waves splashing on your face.    River rafting down the Ganges.    Sounds exciting? I agree but please count me out of all this - I'd rather sit back and listen to my friends yapping away on how adventurous it was. Its not that I don't like the thrill but I’d rather rock climb or go on a jungle trek.  Yes. The truth is "  I am scared of water  "   Born and brought up in a town which was pretty much away from the sea, my annual excursions to the beach in  Pondicherry  and  Chennai  (yucckkk) during my childhood had been very pleasurable except that I’d rarely ventured beyond 20 meters from the safest spots. Of course, I loved the waves drenching me wet, the shells getting stuck on my feet, the sands making me itchy for a nice hot bath but nothing on earth ever made me step beyond 20 meters - despite seeing kids half my height and age swimming in gay abandon in the middle of the sea (okie, that's another 20 meters further inside)  Looking back, I now remember how jittery I was during that short 5 minute motorboat drive from  Juhu  to  Madh Island  -&nbsp; clinging onto the railing for dear life whilst a fisherwoman, who'd probably gone up and down that stretch all her life, balanced a huge basket on her head and still stood near the edge caring a damn for her safety. Brave woman she was.  Just to illustrate how much I fear water, let me recollect a nice incident from the not-so-distant past. My friends and I were seeing  Titanic &nbsp;at  Devi  (or was it  Sathyam ) and when that famous scene where  Leo  and  Kate  stand at the edge and spread their arms out and enjoy the breeze and the beautiful blue sea around them, whilst my friends were rediscovering their romantic self, my inner voice kept shouting at me " He's gonna fall and the damn fool doesn't even have a life boat. "  Talking of life boats, here's another humorous incident. A few months back, one of my oldest friends at&nbsp;work wanted to go swimming at our Corporate HQ. We have a lovely pool out there but more on it later. After a very persuasive lecture on how swimming helped one stay fit, the next five minutes were spent in him drilling into my head all the theory that went into the art of swimming - everything from hand-leg co-ordination to breathing and what not. Finally I was asked to change into trunks and just when we were about to dive into (not exactly, but again I will explain this later) the pool, I asked this million dollar question " Where is my life boat? ". My friend tells me that amongst the on-lookers, some eyes popped and some jaws dropped. But I don’t remember any such thing. He exaggerates, as usual. I thought I was perfectly justified in being cautious. Didn't they teach these people at school that "Its better safe than sorry". Okie, now for that twist in the tale. The pool's depth was only  4 feet . You heard it right.  4 feet . But still, I was justified, wasn't I....No prizes for guessing that i didn't get into the pool that day. Went and played TT for an hour and beat the living daylights out of all and sundry. There's got to be a law or something which bans life-endangering sports like swimming and promotes healthy games like TT :-)  So many more stories but I am sure you folks have funnier stuff to narrate. So will leave it here... 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A ferocious pull by  Brian Charles Lara  at the Lords - a masterful diving volley at the net by  Boris Becker  in Centre Court at Wimbledon - A chip over the bunker by  Tiger Woods  at the 16th at Augusta - a dizzying spell of potting by  Ronnie O' Sullivan  at the Crucible - a masterfully taken penalty by  Helder Postiga  to kick England out of Euro2004.   If there is no ball involved, it ain't sport.   Sports does not get more exciting than this.    Or so I thought till it happened. You could pardon me for believing so for I had still not seen the greatest spectacle of them all. Yes, I am talking of the   urlLink TOUR DE FRANCE  . The 2004 edition started off on a sleepy Saturday evening,  July 3rd , from Liege and 23 grueling days and 3400 kms later, the event had a champion and I had a new hero.   urlLink LANCE ARMSTRONG  . I've seen  Sampras  dominate tennis,  Schumi  rule F1 and the  Aussies  demolish opponents in cricket but believe me, (this is no understatement)  Lance Armstrong  was much, much better than all of them put together.   Spread over 20 stages, the  Tour De France  covers 11 flat stages, 6 mountain stages and then the cyclists compete in 2 individual time-trial stages and 1 team time-trial stage. Its a true test of man's skill, strength and stamina. With just two rest days and 7 stop-over towns in between, the  Tour De France  is one of the most rigorous events in the sporting calendar. For every evening from that Saturday, I have been glued to Ten Sports watching as the race wound its way from  Liege  to  Charleroi  and then to  Waterloo , through  Chartres  and  Saint-Léonard-de-Noblat  and then the mountain climbs from  Limoges  and  Castelsarassin  before touching  Valréas , entering  Annemasse  before culminating in the beautiful  Champs-Élysées  in Paris. Breath-taking mountains, hidden valleys, rocky climbs, the serene Seine...The last 23 days have simply been magical as I toured France with that amazing man Armstrong.   For the entire photo gallery, please check   urlLink here  . 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What do i wish someone who already has name, fame and pots of gold :-) Being mentally challenged has its limitations, so i will shy away from original poetry like the " Aaj ka Shelleys " and google for a nice B'day poem for you.    urlLink       urlLink BuddyGal   Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .    Got it.      Happy birthday to a special friend!  Although I haven't known you many years,  Perhaps because you've dried so many tears,  Pleasure reigns as I these greetings send.  Your happiness should last till all things end!  Because you've been so sweet and understanding  In tough times you've made me laugh and smile  Rejoice in your own specialness awhile:  This I'm not requesting but demanding!       PS:  Hmmm.. I might have failed with my greeting card (i know it doesn't match upto my usual high stds) but i am sure the gift compensated. Wotsay? :-)))    PPS:  Rgds to  Uncle  n  Aunty  and woof woof to  Oshi .    PPPS:  Sorry for that photo - Ur recent ones would invite undue attention, besides this one is my favorite - chimply cho chweeet.   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A signature line on a mail says a lot about one's personality. In the last 5 years of my active mailing, everytime i think i have seen them all, i have been proved wrong by yet another fascinating signature.  My first job in a software company opened my eyes to the geeks and the nerds. One of the first signatures that caught my fancy there was a simple    "Code so clean you could eat off it"    attached to every mail from  Ryan , my client contact in the UK. Then there was this  Doug Linder quote  which was also popular those days - It ran something like    "A good programmer is someone who looks both ways before crossing a one-way street."    So true :-)  Then there is what i would call the motivational stuff -  Boris Becker's     "I love the winning, I can take the losing, but most of all I love to play"    being one of my favorites.&nbsp; I believe there is also a category of signatures which can be classified as " wise sayings of great men " - I petly call them " celebrity crap ".  TRA , my ready-reckoner at SP, use(d/s) them unfailingly but some of his selections are good - in particular&nbsp; Benjamin Franklin 's    "Be civil to all; sociable to many; familiar with few; friend to one; enemy to none".    Besides, not all celebrities are a bore, i do admire the wit and wisdom of a select few. Just check these out     "I always pass on good advice. It is the only thing to do with it. It is never of any use to oneself"    -  Oscar Wilde      "A classic is something that everybody wants to have read and nobody wants to read"    -  Mark Twain      "I often quote myself, it adds spice to a conversation"    -  GB Shaw   How about folks who think " rude is coo l" - I must admit i have enjoyed quite a few of their signatures too.  Johnson , my pal at Infy used to have one that went something like    "The more people i meet, the more i love my dog"    Another line that grabbed my attention was    "If it weren't for people like you, nobody else would have an above average IQ."     Then there are people who are imaginative enough to change their signature based on wots in the news now. The best one i've seen is one from my pal,  Krish  which says    "When there's a will... I want to be in it!"    :-)   Finally, though my own signature lines keep changing based on my mood, the more regular ones are    "Intelligent women are like domain names: the best ones are always taken"         "I don't suffer from insanity; I enjoy every minute of it!"  "Too many freaks, not enough circus's!"   "All generalizations are false"           What's in for me now is    "Are part-time band leaders semi-conductors?"    Tis a pity my boss hasn't caught the drift ? Did you ?  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Good morning darlings :-)     Two days i am away and people don't miss a chance to run a man down. With f(r)iends like the ones i have, no wonder i've never needed enemies.   Okie, to quote   William Thacker   (Hugh Grant) from my my all time favorite movie   Notting Hill  ,&nbsp;  "I wish to make it clear I've turned a corner and henceforward intend to be impressively happy."  So its bad news for you all. Before i forget,  Ekta , that was very, very rude - You've never laughed at any of my posts before ?? :-( And  G  boy, " Revenge is a dish best served cold ". Just wait n watch.   So wassup folks? Nothing very interesting from my end. The last few days have been a little rough at work but yes, once in a while its a welcome break from having to click on one's  SEND/RECEIVE  button in  OUTLOOK  once in 6 seconds :-) On the domestic front, its been very nice going back to a home where the fridge is stacked with  Toblerone  and  CDM  and the dining table is always full of yummy food. No wonder i weigh  81kg  now - havta lose some weight :-)   Oh yeah, before i forget, let me remind you all that i will be inaccessible to external forces on  August 1st . Yeps, its   FRIENDSHIP DAY   and before you start trashing it, let me state upfront i also DO NOT believe in such crap. After all, one doesn't celebrate a wonderful thing like friendship on a single day. Ditto that for   FATHER'S DAY   and   MOTHER'S DAY  . (Note: I am not even talking of that stupid   VAL DAY  ) Down with American consumerism. I see that i have digressed yet again. On   FRIENDSHIP DAY   this year,  Zee English  is devoting 12 continuous hours from 10 am to 10 pm for Season 9 of my favorite sit-com   FRIENDS  . Sounds too good to be true, right? But yes, i swear its true. Did i hear some " Oh my gawd "s? Good, you've already gotten into the spirit :-)   The weekend is almost here - 8 more hours to go. Fingers crossed. Have a great time folks.  Spiderman , here i come. (And this refers to both  Tobey  and  SJ Suryah )  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Reproduced below r de high points of a conversation between 3 gentlemen:  G, Venu  and  Jupie  @ around  10:45 pm  IST on  Wed, 21st Jul . Dis comic show lasted all of  35  mts - De phone call costs vere as usual picked up by  TCS  (Venu here works for de world's best company)    Venu:  So macha, are u still on one of ur BACH kinda journeys ?  Jupie:  Hmmm  Venu:  Wotz de latest count ?  Jupie:  No comments  Venu:  Wotz de latest count ?  Jupie:  I said No comments  Venu:  Wotz de latest count ?  Jupie:  U friggin' deaf or wot. Neway itz less than urs.  Venu:  Of course, i am sure itz less than 14 but i'd still like to know the exact figure.  Jupie:  5  Venu:  It includes that 1 who was born for you (smirk)  Jupie:  Hmm  Venu:  Wow, a loser like u also has a market as big as 4. How many have u seen ?  Jupie:  Are u nuts, u moron. Child marriage is prohibited by law.  Venu:  Someone just told me he is phsically 26 and  mentally 62.     Venu:  Just spoke with 1 more, Mridula i think, last weekend macha. And i had to say NO.  Jupie:  How can neone ever say NO - Have u thot abt how she feels.  Venu:  Foto all nice da macha. Good family but all she kept talking was opportuntities/openings fer software in the US, H1B visa&nbsp;  Jupie:  Ha ha ha.. This sounds so much like Hyderabad Blues and dat Swathy Aunty's daughter character.  Venu:  And then she loves Junior NTR da macha.. I cant stand that bugger. Even in email she wrote abt this last film Samba  Jupie:  I am loving this. You like Ramba and she likes Samba.   Venu:  Macha, its my life da. I cant compromise. I will wait for Ms PERFECT.  Jupie:  Wot if urs got lost because she took a wrong turn and is too stubborn to ask for directions.  G:  Ha Ha Ha.. Awesome man.     (By now Jupie has considerably cheered up at Venu's expense)   &nbsp;  Venu:  So when are u getting married?  Jupie:  Ask Kirsten Dunst. She just broke up yesterday. She has to decide.  Venu: &nbsp; Get serious da. Are u going to Chennai for that thing only?  Jupie:  Gimme a break asshole. Can't ya Gults think of anything but marraige ?  G:  Chuck it da Venu. Neway our man is going to SUNDARAPANDYAPURAM to get his girl.  Venu: &nbsp; I didnt get that.  G:  Thats the village Arvind Swamy goes to get a gal in Roja  Venu:  Oh that way huh. Who is it gonna be - the bold Roja or her demure elder sister?  Jupie:  Fuk you guys, why cant i get that HOT Rukmani even in my dreams.  G:  He he he he he he he he  Venu:  U r ulti macha.  Jupie:  Yaya, considering i've used that line thrice today :-(    Jupie , some people's existence is only to bring happiness and cheer into other people's lives.They were born to entertain. Now stop this silly sulking and get back to being "normal". If this aint convincin' enuf, look at ydy's site numbers - they are faaaaaaaalling. Come back sonny.   Sorry 2 for writing this but i guess i can take that liberty, canti ? 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pardon the intrusion, dear blog. I know i'd sworn to stay away from you till i had got myself sorted out. But then read this wonderful piece on  urlLink  Megha's blog   and found it simply mind-blowing. Just wish i had read it 24 hrs back, before i had made my decision but then, there's no looking back now. Here it is...     The way we women describe the intimacy we want is remarkably consistent: It's that sense of oneness between two people that flows from an open, meaningful exchange of thoughts, feelings and affection. It's about each one entering the other's private world, not merely for a short visit, but to unpack and take up residence.   urlLink   read full post      ps:   GB , Good job on  GWH . Lage raho till i get back..    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Jupie  is in a terrible mood. Requsted me to fill in for the whole of dis week. Since i'm just back from a holiday in the North-East, thot i'd share my travelog. But  Jupie  insists i write on only stuff i know somethin' about. Which he presumes is movies - this beggar actually wants to be a chooser :)   Nyways,  GOOD WILL HUNTING  is 1 of our all-times faves. Tis got something for all kindsa ppl. The romantics, the sentimentalists, the losers, the philosphers, the entire lot. So will showcase it for the whole of dis week.   For details of basic plot, cast and characters, plz check   urlLink here  .     GWH for the romantics     Will  sits with  Morgan  at the bar watching with some amusement as  Chuckie  and  Billy  play bar basketball game where the players shoot miniature balls at a small basket. In the B.G.Occasionally we hear Chuckie shouting " Larry !" When he scores.   Skylar  emerges from the crowd and approaches  Will .    SKYLAR   You suck.    WILL   What?    SKYLAR   I've been sitting over there for forty-  five minutes waiting for you to come  talk to me. But I'm just tired now  and I have to go home and I wasn't  going to keep sitting there waiting  for you.    WILL   I'm Will.    SKYLAR   Skylar. And by the way.  That guy over there is a real dick and  I just wanted you to know he didn't  come with us.    WILL   I kind of got that impression.    SKYLAR   Well, look, I have to go. Gotta' get  up early and waste some more money on  my overpriced education.    WILL   I didn't mean you. Listen, maybe...    SKYLAR   Here's my number.   Skylar produces a folded piece of paper and offers it to Will.    SKYLAR (cont'd)   Maybe we could go out for coffee  sometime?    WILL   Great, or maybe we could go somewhere  and just eat a bunch of caramels.    SKYLAR   What?    WILL   When you think about it, it's just as  arbitrary as drinking coffee.    SKYLAR   (laughs)  Okay, sounds good.   She turns.    WILL   Five minutes.    SKYLAR   What?    WILL   I was trying to be smooth.  (indicates clock)  But at twelve-fifteen I was gonna come  over there and talk to you.    SKYLAR   See, it's my life story.  Five more minutes and I would have got  to hear your best pick-up line.    WILL   The caramel thing is my pick-up line.   A beat.    SKYLAR   Glad I came over.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a start to the day. Just had a "normal" telephonic discussion over VoIP ( decibel levels must have been at 80 ) with one of the  Technical Managers  here. I always thought i was cocky and arrogant but this " gentle "man makes me feel like an amateur. We got into a healthy debate on the pros/cons of a particular marketing approach ( shan't bore you all with trivial details ) but luckily for me, it was one of those occasions when i knew what i was talking about. It did help that i had done a lot of home-work on this particular topic ( 5 hrs on Saturday ) and was prepared for all his counter-arguments. I am usually a gracious winner and never believe in hurting a man who is already down-and-out. Dunno what got into me today but despite the fact that my opponent was beating a retreat mid-way into our conversation, i did not let go. I dragged him deeper and deeper and refused to let go till he finally accepted that he had been wrong. Felt good  :-)    Big boss  is in Europe -  Small boss no: 1  is in Pune -  Small boss no: 2  is at the customer's premises. I was also due to go to Chennai but lest there be a leadership vacuum here, i graciously offered to stay back and rule. Did i say rule? Technically, as  Aravind  loves putting it, i am head of the BU for the whole of today. Will someone please bring me some papers to sign? Will someone please call me up and request for approvals - attendance record, leave records - kuch bhi chalega.  I AM THE BOSS TODAY :-)   Break for coffee. (Slurppp) I make good coffee (shabaash)   Back at my seat. No fires to douse, no more arguments to pick up - have only our  Six Sigma  project to do. Maybe i should listen to some music. Hmmm..  Phir Milenge ? Yes. After the critically acclaimed  urlLink  Mitr  , this is Revathy's second venture and stars  Sallu ,  Abi baby  and  Shilpa "hot legs" Shetty . With music by my favorite  SEL  and lyrics by that funny man  Prasoon Joshi ,  urlLink  Phir Milenge   does not disappoint. Here's a taste of my favorite song in the album   Betaab dil hai dhadkanon ki kasam Naa reh sakenge ab judaa hoke hum Waada karo tum, Jaane se pehle  Waada karo tum, Jaane se pehle  Phir Milenge sanam    And no prizes for guessing who sings this number -  Sonu . Yesssssssssssss.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saw   urlLink Troy   yesterday. Before I start my dissection (do I hear groans?) let me confess upfront I loved the movie inspite of its obvious flaws. The hype and hoopla was worth it. Here's my take on the movie   Helen:    "Baby, this old buggers no good - I wanna have good sex every day. Puhleeez"    Paris:   "Oh boy - coool - but I got nice new Kurl-Ons at home in Troy - wanna move in with me ?"   Helen:   "Sounds good - lets go baby"   And so  Paris  abducted  Helen  and  Melenaus  waged war and  Hector  died defending and  Troy  burned and  Achilles  became immortal ...(in background,  Bryan Adams  croons " And its all for SEX... All for SEX.. ")  On a more serious note,   Thumbs up to the  Brilliant cinematography, haunting background score,  spell-binding art direction and excellent performances by  Eric Bana  (have just penciled you in for my first Hollywood movie) as Hector and  Peter O Toole  as Priam.   Thumbs down to the  Lack of depth in the characterisation of Hector/Helen/Menelaus, Absence of genuinely stirring emotional moments.   A few questions to  Mr. Wolfgang Petersen , the director    * If Helen was supposed to be "the face that launched a thousand ships", then why Diane Kruger? Why not Catherine Zeta Jones or Keira Knightley or even Kareena Kapoor?  * Was Paris such a wimp even in Homer's   urlLink Illiad   ? (Gotta check out this book now)  * Eye-popping visuals apart, did you need a 180m$ budget to reinforce the Tenth Commandment "Thou shalt not covet thy neighbour's wife" Someone give me this kinda money to make "1984" - Please. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Did you know that there are 13 million homeless children in India? Did you know that 3% of India's children are mentally/physically challenged? Did you know that of every 100 Indian children born 1 dies before birth?   There are many more alarming statistics about the aged, the destitute and other under privileged that I can pull out to prove my point but this post is not for dramatic effect. On the contrary, I am sure we are all aware of the situation around us. Whilst we are all proud that INDIA is indeed SHINING on the economic front, I am sure we are also in agreement that there is lots more that needs to be done.    Social revolutions  do not need special people - all it takes is for each of us to realize our responsibilities towards the society we live in. "The journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step" But why is it that we are all so pre-occupied with our own lives that we think we have done our bit by simply sending in that odd check towards our favorite charity. I am not, in any way, demeaning our efforts but isn't it time we realized we needed to do more than that. Finances are scarce and yes, the monetary angle is definitely one that needs attention. But when was the last time we took a Sunday afternoon off to meet these abandoned old citizens and spend quality time with them. Do we remember our last outing to an orphanage when we set aside half a day to see life through their eyes?   When I say "we", I do not take the moral high ground and exclude myself. I am as guilty as you are. I still remember the delight in the eyes of all those wonderful, old people at  Annai Ashram  when we visited them to gift them the clothes we had collected at RECT. I still have fond memories of that trip to the orphanage in East Tambaram when I was working in Infy. Why, even that half a day trip to the home for abandoned children near  Churchgate  during first year at SP remains fresh in my mind. Why is it that I have never been able to do it more regularly? Isn't it time we all woke up to the fact that we are so much better off than some of our other brethren? Isn't it time for us to do something about it? Think about it.  Leaving you with a link to one of the people I tremendously admire in my life. I am sure you must have heard about  Vidyakar  of  urlLink Udavum Karangal   Anyone who has ever visited his facility at  Tiruverkadu  will be a reborn person. However if you are weak at heart, I would advice that you stay away since one is sure to be emotionally gutted.  I guess I have made my point.  At this point I would like to acknowledge the efforts of a few people.   My friend  Jayashri  in Chennai who for all her crankiness unfailingly devotes time teaching under privileged children every weekend.   BP  for your unselfish and tireless work for the  Infy foundation   All my fellow Rotaractors, particularly  Mansur, Partha and BK  who believed in what we did (however small it may have been) those days  And lastly,  KS , for being my conscience keeper and reminding me that my writing this post could actually make a difference. I am proud to have known ya and I gotta thank Infy for it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       17-7-2004 Pisces   Things may not be perfect but judging by the current planetary setup, they are probably good. Still if there is any element of an arrangement or close relationship that you would like to improve, its vital that you express your views. Be forthright with those involved about where you stand.....blah blah blah    That was my astro prediction for the day based on TOI. When I saw it today morning, my eyes lit up. Ever heard of favorite weekend tantrums ? Mine usually involves ranting and raving about how the world does not accept rebels like me. Screaming and shouting about how I wanna give up this monotonous job and do something that really excites me is not very uncommon. So after reading the day's prediction for me, I thought I should say the thing that used to scare my folks most  "I wanna get into the movies - If Nagesh Kukunoor and Cindy Crawford can give up Chemical Engineering and Mani Ratnam can give up an MBA, so can I."  Please note: I use the phrase "used to" - So you can guess what happened - Yes, they did not react to it. I am beginning to believe they've seen through me :-( But, why is it that no one thinks I can make it big at K/B/Hollywood ? Hey, you doubting Thomases, check out my past - I was always one of the best in school plays. Check out the emotions.   urlLink       urlLink Schoolplay1   Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .      From left to right   1 - Solomon Gerard: now all of 6'6", coding at CTS 2 - Johnny Prabhu: God-Knows-where 3 - Naveed Ibrahim: MBA from Australia, now plying his trade in Chennai 4 - Prabhu Missier: slogging his butt off at Honeywell 5 - (Can't name since paparazzi will swoop on this snap): Entertaining 32 ppl every day   Hey, maybe I got it all wrong. Maybe that astro-prediction was not for my career. Coz this is what my daily email prediction has to say  Here is your horoscope for  Saturday, July 17 :  You have never been luckier romance-wise. It's like you've won a lottery that you never knew you entered, and you're completely baffled as to how to spend the money. Be creative.    (Acknowledgements to whoever gave my email id for this daily subscription - I was so tempted to unsubscribe but the last 3 days it's been saying nice things and I didn't have the heart to)  So what should I say/do now ?  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am referring to my   MITR   here. For those of you who don't work here,   MITR   is an internal counseling program that's being actively promoted within my company. As the publicity posters/mails clearly specify, the counselor does not give advice&nbsp; to the problem. He/She is there to help you to see the problem objectively and enable you to take the decision you think right.     Minal  , whos volunteered to be a   MITR   and describes herself in 5 words as    Positive, Emotional, Intelligent AND Effervescent    ( Avinash , don't you dare laugh) seems to be jes the right antidote to my "problems". I think she will make my best   MITR   considering people often call me    Negative, Indifferent, Dumb AND Passive    :-)   And hey, I am proud of the fact that I was one of the first to see that spark/halo around her.  Kaushik  and  Avinash , damn you guys. In case you are hooting with laughter on reading this, you can go to hell.   Have a nice weekend folks but pls don’t forget to visit my blog tomorrow too. There's loads to do so I am working. For regular readers, plans are afoot to revive our Mega Serial  urlLink  "Love Story...revisited"   - The   WunderKids   cud be back in action soon. Keep your fingers crossed.    PS:  This post was primarily to check the new formatting thingy which allows me to use colors. Yippeee....  PPS:  Iske saath hat-trick of two posts per day ho gaya - Now I can RIP :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some guys are plain kill-joys.  And *&^% (he doesn't even deserve a mention) is the biggest of them all amongst my buddies. I had mailed him on how i had given up my seat in the company bus Tuesday evening for a sweet lady (i believe she is married and 30+ so don't even dare to suspect my motives) and what does he do.. He sends me a questionnaire yesterday. Am reproducing it here with my answers.   Do you usually open doors for women (cars, hotels)? Yes, almost always do  Do you usually offer women your seat in a crowded bus ? Ahem..Sometimes  Do you usually let women get into the elevator first? Yes. Always  Do you usually pull chairs for women in restaurants? Hmm.. Most of the times  Do you usually offer to hold hands and help women negotiate a busy road / rainy puddle? Yes, i do  Do you usually offer to help them with their coats? Haven't had an occasion to but i guess i would..   Proud that i seemed to have fared reasonably well in the test, i was eagerly awaiting his mail in return till he sent me this  urlLink disgusting piece .  Now i am not so sure :-( 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Second consecutive day when I am troubling my readers with a double bill. But kya karoon, can't help it. This afternoon's incidents were too hilarious to not report.   Murphy's law  rocks. And how...  Had this customer from the  Netherlands  dropping in on us at EC. As it usually happens, when less important people in my company get stuck in deep shit, they pull in the more important ones too so that the pain can be shared. So at 2:15 today afternoon, just when I had returned back from a hearty lunch I got my summons from boss to attend this customer meeting. Half asleep, I trudged towards the other half of the campus only to find that I was running late and had to climb five flights of stairs to reach this place called OAK. No sooner had I entered the room than the usual introductions happened. These guys insisted on exchanging business cards and it was only then that I realized that I had none in my wallet. My boss gave me a stare which roughly translated as "  ()**&^%$^($ , How on earth did this scum bag get into Marketing  ?"   10 minutes into the meeting, my eyes drooped and I fell asleep only to be rudely awakened by what seemed to be a question directed towards me. Mumbling something incomprehensible under the guise of an answer, I resolved not to make a fool of myself anymore. Since the tea and coffee had not yet come in, I thought I would keep myself awake with some Pepsi. And yes, it happened again. The damn can would not open and when I gave my last almighty tug, it fizzed out making as much noise as a hundred hissing serpents. Needless to say everyone stared at me. Anxious to make amends, I stared solemnly at the screen and nodded at everything that was said. Soon there was a change of presenters and the projector connections had to tinkered with. Eager to redeem myself, I offered to do it but predictably, the customer's laptop conked off no sooner had I touched it. That was it. That was the last straw in the camel's back. Taking it as sign from God, divine intervention to stop this lousy sequence of events, I gracefully (??) withdrew from the rest of the evenings proceedings.   Now as I sit back n think, has it been one of "those days" ? If so, just like that funda  Samuel L Jackson  gives in  Unbreakable , "Is there an exact opposite for this kind of a day ?" Just imagine - I wake up as late as I possibly can, the geyser heat is just about right, board the bus and get my favorite seat,  Sunaina  plays all my favorite songs on  Josh 91 , open my inbox to see 76 mails incl: that one looooong one from u-no-hoo, then my blog gets 20 hits in 10 minutes, boss calls up n gives me credit for something I did not do, have a good lunj - aloo paratha and juice with Kau giving us his wonderful stories, return back to surf the net, do some work, play TT and then leave at 7:30, watch some tennis on telly and then round off the day with  FRIENDS  on  Zee English .    If wishes were horses..!  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have often been accused of forming strong opinions about people based on their proficiency with the  English language . No kidding. On serious introspection, i do admit that this might have been the case on more than a few occasions but i can't help it. Dats me! Coming to think of it, its no coincidence that some of my people i really respect are ones who can weave magic with their writings -   urlLink Onion ,  urlLink Copygurrl ,  urlLink Milind9x ,  urlLink Sidin   to name a few.  Looking back, i think it all started with my studying 14 years in  Campion  in Trichy. At school, we were always under the vigilant eyes of our teachers who would never tolerate if the students spoke in anything but English. (save the Language classes) We also had those  L&D classes  on Thursdays or Fridays which we all used to really look forward to. My interest in the language was also sparked by my Std 8 English Teacher  Mr. Vernum  , a gentleman who could speak impeccable Queen's English (In Trichy, twas a rarity) and whose vocabulary and diction remains till today one of the best i've ever heard.  Today when i write letters (i still do once in a while) or mails, i find myself enjoying the language, toying with it to suit the occasion. So when people call me garrulous and remind me that "A silent man is a wise one" i retort saying "A man without words is a man without thoughts" :-)  A few weeks back, when i was at some sort of crossroads, one of my pals adviced me saying that its "Better safe than sorry" - Quick to the return, i quipped "Nothing ventured, nothing gained" - It was only later that i realised that the language itself had given me a solution to my predicament.  I do use a lot of other contradicting adages to my advantage, some of them being   Two's company; three's a crowd  The more, the merrier  What will be, will be     Life is what you make it  Birds of the same feather flock together Opposites attract  Lets cross bridges when we come to them.     Forewarned is forearmed  The bigger, the better     The best things come in small packages   In case you know any more let me know.  Knowledge is power  :-)  (Hint: Hint:) 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have never felt so good for months. Yippeeeeeeee ! Remember I mentioned in some post ages back that I’d seen  HP3 . Okie, here's a nice story.   My friends and I had gone to  Rex  to catch the evening show but as usual someone had goofed up and we were one ticket short. And being a Sunday it was  HOUSEFULL  too. Since I had already seen it once, I’d offered to go back home when we chanced to find a family who had an extra ticket. The only problem was that the seats were not in the same row so I thought I might as well not take it. But when this chweeet, adorable 11 year old walked upto me and said  "Uncle, we have an extra ticket and you should see this movie, HP movies are so cool"  I was floored (the Uncle part hurt though)   The next two hours were simply amazing.  Sirisha  (dats her name) without any exaggeration on my part was a raving, mad fan of  JKR  and the  HP series . She was literally sitting at the edge of her seat and chatting with me incessantly, giving me every single detail about the scene. When I was groping for the name for that bus which helps Harry when he escapes from home, she rebuked me for forgetting such "simple things" and educated me on the  "Knight bus and its conductor Stan" . However I did get my revenge later in the second half when she forgot the name of the  "Whomping Willow"  :-) When the  Marauding Map  first made its appearance in the movie she almost shrieked in delight. I was really sorry when the movie ended coz I have never had such intelligent company for a movie date. As we descended down, her father exchanged pleasantries and chatted up with me. We also exchanged cards (I’ve lost his)  And then it happened today afternoon. Am reproducing the mail here   Hi Ram uncle,  Remember me. Wasn't Azkabun cool? Nowdays i see Spiderman trrailors in TV. Heard its coming August. School's there but I will see it. U must too. Tobi is so cute.  (((((( Ram uncle ))))))  Bye Sirisha   I've always hated emoticons but when I checked wot this meant, I was moved. I always knew kids were the bestestest things God created but this one takes the cake.  Sirisha , u r my bestest friend. Can I join u, uncle and aunty for Spidey? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some people hate  Calculus . Some others  Algebra . I don’t fall under both these categories. My pet hate in school was  Trigonometry . If one goes by  Greek word origins , I think u will see that  tri  means  three  and  gonia  means  angle  and  metron  basically means  measure . So roughly  trigonometry  translates to measurement of three angles or simply put,  measurement of triangles . Careful post-mortems have linked a lot of my miseries today to the fundamental problem this subject seems to have with me.   (Flash back to end-of-school days)   Tall and lanky that I was, I had always dreamt of being a tear-away pace bowler a la  Joel Garner . It was only when I tried living my dreams in the 22 yards that I realized that the ball never landed within the nets. Throwing aside sheer pace, I used to try and concentrate on line and length a la  Glen McGrath  but then my pace was so pedestrian that the keeper had to come in front of the stumps, collect the ball and try and effect a stumping during those rare occasions when the batsman had not smashed me out of the park. While I labored on, my coach  Mr.Rex  never had the heart to ask me to take a walk. He would always encourage me during the trials subtly suggesting that I should return to take up my off spin since I could use my height and get my beautiful arc/loop going. However in those days, spin was for sissies and I would have none of it. Finally, on D-Day when it would be time for announcing the list of selected people, I would invariably hear   "There is someone else.."   Those dreaded 4 words. Yeah, I was still selected for my off spin but then there was this unknown third entity who always got wot I wanted, the third variable in the equation that I always failed to factor in, the much hated third angle to the problem that I had not measured.  Trigonometry at work.   Ever since, I have had more than my fair share of spats with Trigonometry. The one I can recollect immediately is how I was allotted to my  TOYS R US  project at  Infy . Since I had expressed a desire to get into  Telecom , I had been half expecting to get allotted to the  Alcatel  account but then I had forgotten about this mysterious third angle that always seems to spring from nowhere to ridicule me. There was another lateral,  Karthik Narayan(an)  from  TCS , who had been dilly-dallying on his joining date since the monsoons in  Mumbai  had led to all the trains being cancelled for a few days on the route.(July 2000 monsoons were awful in Maharashtra) This guy who had conveyed to HR that he would be delayed by a week suddenly landed up on the same day as I did. So as usual it was   "There is someone else..."   and I had to settle for second best. I was forced into  Retail  whereas  Mr. Third-Angle  was given  Alcatel  on a platter.  Today after so many years, when I think I have finally made peace with trigonometry, there it is raising its ugly specter again. Just when I have fallen in love. Or atleast I think so. Please don't smirk, OK - Please - Its not  books, Govinda, Wimbledon  or even my new  Gmail account . Its a  she  - a real she - not the  Kareena  or  Maria Sharapova  or  whoever . But why do I get that intuition that there is this third angle lurking behind in the shadows. In fact, I am dreading the day when I'm gonna hear those words   "There is someone else.."     Brave men die once - Cowards and people who hate trigonometry die a million deaths.  Will keep you all posted, for better or for worse :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think today's post is gonna be one of my favorites. Got the idea from a fellow blogger's entry.   COMMUNICATION:  The activity of process of giving information to other people.     Down memory lane:   At  school  (not the business one) the only forms of communication I had ever heard were the written and the oral form. The former I loved - essays, critiques and letters. The latter I abhorred - speeches and debates. I still have horrid memories of my first public speech. Till my std: 10, I had participated and won most of the events based on written English in my district, be it  Spelling Bees  for 5 years or creative writing contests (okie, mebbe it shows how abysmally low the competition levels were but I’d like to believe otherwise) My quizmate and bosom buddy  Shakir  had always been the one who had stolen the show whenever it came to stages and speeches. It all took a turn for the worse in Std 11. I recollect how my  English teacher cum Vice Principal   Brother Thiruthuvam  forcibly entered my name for an oratorical competition. It was all scheduled for a Monday afternoon and the topic had been   "Should begging be banned?”   I was sure I’d make a fool of myself in front of an audience of around 400 (all students from std 8 to Std 12 are usually invited for this) and so secretly planned to take the afternoon off by sneaking out post-lunch feigning illness. But smart man that he was, our VP had warned the  Principal  that certain students might be inclined to take this route and so I was denied leave. And then when lots were drawn, I was first up. I will fast forward the next 6 minutes of what happened but just to give you an idea of what happened, I think my dear friend  Sridhar  later told me that if I had been measured for my performance on the  Richter scale , I would have clocked a 10 :-(  My next public performance was at REC in Trime 1 for the appropriately titled   "Communication for Beginners" . Thanks to  Ms Banumathi , we were atleast allowed to choose our own topics. Those were the days when I used to be a last bencher, hang around with the " enfant terribles " and generally rebel for no rhyme or reason. Two amongst the numerous rules for membership to this exclusive, elitist gang was a total refusal to speak English and to completely ignore women. (the founding members of this club were obviously from  Mech  and  Chem ) I had decided I would make a one time exception and flout rule: 1 and had carefully prepared a speech on  "Chances of India winning WC '96"  - However Man proposes, God disposes. The lady who spoke before me,  Anusha  an  NRI  returned from  Dubai , gave one of the most stirring speeches I have ever heard on  Indian culture  - and btw, she was dressed in a western outfit that left nothing to imagination :-) That one really got my goat and I changed speeches and launched into a furious diatribe on such pseudo people. Needless to say, I scored high on that assignment but the Prof. never ever ventured to allow us to pick our own topics after that. And better late than never,  Anusha , sorry - it was never personal :-p  The advantage of working in a more than a few companies is that u get to while away a lot time under the guise of induction/training every time u shift jobs. My first job at  MBT , needless to say, had a communication module as part of its initiation program. The only difference was that we were all video graphed. This time there was additional pressure since my colleagues were MBA grads  from SIBM  or undergrads from  IIT-Kanpur . But my my, wot a ball we had. I have seen weirdos and whackos but  Sarvesh  at MBT has to be the best. His speech was loosely based on " Women and how to pataofy them " - half way through he was stopped and asked to change topics. He then chose "Y oga and music at 5 am (and how it helps to win women) " Needless to say I have never laffed harder than that in my whole life. My speech, relatively speaking was a tad boring on " Life in hostels ". Two days later, after the course was over, we were video graphed again to see whether we had improved and I think I did fairly better. These courses actually help, you know.  Then came  Infy  where I was hired as a lateral so no training programs for me :-( But then there was  Toastmasters . Since it had been almost 4 months since I’d challenged myself to talk in front of a crowd of strangers, I signed in. It went off well except that people seemed to have a trance like look after I had finished my speech. I had chosen to speak on  MPD  and how  Sidney Sheldon  has made a mess of it in " Tell Me Your Dreams " :-)  Hmm.. Cut to B-school  - Third week@SP - The course: Communication. The procedure: same old videography method except that this was to be a presentation in PowerPoint. (pssst: When I had joined SP, my only lofty ambition had been to go to  Lonavla-Khandala  as one and come back as two. That didn’t happen :-) This was my second chance to floor everyone) I had zeroed down on two topics that would both make me comfortable and also appeal to the "intellectual women" in my batch - " Humor in English Literature " and " Why I was born to be an SPJIMRite " - But all my plans went awry when we were all allotted topics - and mine was supposed to be a business presentation to corporates on " SPJIMR for you ".  Result:  a B on that assignment.  After that there have been numerous other instances of presentations in Mktg classes but all that for another rainy day. Maybe I should start working now :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No, I am not toking of yet another  Schumi  win - which incidentally is getting more and more boring. I am specifically referring to how thrilling life can be during weekends. Whilst one of my friends was on a safari tour in  South Africa , yet another embarked on a trip to  Bangkok  for a song-n-dance routine - A third pal of mine was gallivanting in  Sikkim  fresh from the success of selling " our " first movie script ( Girish , I will never ever forgive u for this) whilst the fourth seemed to be holidaying in a beach in  Kerala  days after joining the 'rigorous' IIMs. With so much excitement happening around the world, can I be far behind ? Guess Guess.  Okie, I was reeling from an experience which had more excitement that what I had Bargained for even in my wildest dreams. I was busy controlling a flood. Okie, as usual I exaggerate but Sunday evening was the time the Rain Gods chose to bless  Bangalore  with all the water that was due for the last two years - all the water that cost  SM Krishna  his re-election. And Sunday evening was also the time, the underground water pipe in  Koramangla First Block  decided it was time to go phhhhtttt. The result was that at 7:08 pm, water entered our house.  My folks, having witnessed a messy flood in  1977 , were naturally aghast but innocent me was reveling in the joys of seeing a new spectacle. It wasn’t until the water level in our hall rose to around 4 inches that some sense prevailed on me. I have never understood how on earth my MBA helps in my present role as an SME but it sure seems to have taught me composure and presence of mind. With the calm approach of a practiced hand, I was soon shifting my new TV, old washing machine and our really old dining table to the first floor. Next thing I understood was that water is always very difficult to contain - so the easiest way to get rid of it is to help it find its flow. So I managed to find a small outlet to the earth near our garden and helped divert some water there. Lastly, the biggest learning was that when there are problems like this never visit the Johnny - coz the damn thing never flushes. It comes back.. Yeeeeeeeeeeeeek.  The scene yesterday night at around 12 was that all the water had drained but the place was a big mess full of leaves, twigs and wot-not. Needless to say I had a sleepless night. I was in no mood to come to office today but as usual, a person's true worth is known only when they are not around (sob sob..Kisiki yaad aa gayi) - so many fone calls asking me " Jupe, yeh kaise karna hai" "Jupe, aaj custy visit hai.. aa jao plssss.. Wipro needs you" - So I had to come here. The meeting just got over. N I  HAD  to blog - hence am here. But believe me folks, I think I will settle for something less excitable next weekend.  I have made plans too. Am gonna hire a sports bicycle, wear 2/3rd trousers, spike up my hair (yaaaaaaaaaaaaa), wear orange shades and ride up and down  Brigade  and  MG . Wotsay ?   PS:  The high point of y'day evening was when I wanted to take a snap of our house at around 8 pm. Needless to say, u can imagine how my folks reacted. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Dear Mama,     Some things never change, do they? Starting from my early childhood when you used to force me to earn my B'day presents by setting me difficult quizzes to the present day when you don't hesitate to point out every slip I make (wasn't  Circa  the last?), I got to hand it to you for being the most influential person in my life. And believe me, that’s as big a compliment as I can ever give. Cutting to the chase, why this letter today? It’s because of this  "Hypnerotomachia Poliphili"  thing you mentioned in one of your mails a month back.   ( For the uninitiated, "Hypnerotomachia Poliphili"   as a book defies categorization - is it an autobiography, a book on architecture, erotica, or does it champion women's rights. Is it a puzzle book or is it plain gibberish? For more details, here is a very  urlLink  interesting link   )  At that time I had dismissed it as yet another attempt by you to show me how much more catching up I had to do (how about a handicap system like in polo or golf) but I just managed to read an article in ET a few days back on those two wonder kids and their book  urlLink  "Rule of Four".   And yes, mildly put, it was very intriguing indeed.  It seems  Ian Caldwell  and  Dustin Thomason , two 28-year-old Ivy League super-achievers have drawn upon an authentic  1499 Renaissance  text to create a thriller about two Princeton undergraduates who try to unravel the mysteries in " Hypnerotomachia Poliphili ". It’s rumored that  Caldwell  and  Thomason , who grew up across the street from each other in  Northern Virginia , put in almost 6 years of research effort into this book. The book has been released in the US in  May  and has been declared an instant hit. Critics have compared it more than favorably with my other favorite  Dan Brown 's  urlLink  Da Vinci Code   (which you must surely read)  I am not so sure  "Rule of Four"  is out in India but you can be rest assured that I shall buy it, read it and send it to you as soon as i am done. After all, so many people read this blog of mine and I am sure someone must be thinking of it as a nice present for me :-)    Forever Me     ps:  Love to  Abhi  and  Nandhini 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have no ideas for a post today. I see sitemeter telling me my blog has reached  1000 hits . Yesterday's site stats says i had  47 visitors  - It's got to be malfunctioning or has the world FINALLY discovered me? (and about time too) Wowwww !! I am as proud as  Hugh Hefner . (gloating) Ok, let me explain ;-)    Playboy 's first edition never had a date stamp coz Hefner never believed there would be a second edition. The rest as they say is 'his'tory. Now u see the connexion.(Atleast I don’t) Neway, what do I generally do when I am at a loss for topics?  I think of a word that catches my fancy, go to Google Images and then get my material for the daily ritual. Today's word is  MUD-WRESTLING .   After sieving through some "interesting" and some "not-so-interesting" photographs, I’ve finally found this one which was kinda cute.    urlLink        urlLink mud-wrestling     Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .      Now who do I imagine as the two women in the red and blue corner? How about "subse best Rly Minister ki patni"  Rabri Devi  and rabble-rousing  Maneka Gandhi ?  Or wouldn't it be interesting if it were Rebecca Loos and Posh...If this were the 70s, then  Rekha  and  Jaya Bachchan  would have been a good match-up too. Or how about  Amelie Mauresmo  and  Jennifer Capriati . So many possibilities.... Any suggestions? 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I took the  urlLink Blogging Personality Quiz  at  urlLink About Web logs  and I am...   The Writer    Words captivate me. And, I like to capture words. Blogging enables me to write often. It also provides a place for me to share what I write with a reading public. I can be funny, inspiring, intelligent, cynical, or morbid. It doesn't matter what I write about in my blog. It only matters that I write.     I liked most of those adjectives though morbid wasn't exactly complimentary. But I guess all these tests have a certain margin for error and I will excuse them, this one time, for getting that bit wrong.   And hey, not every day do I blog (to be read as: crap) just for the sake of blogging. Maybe just to reinforce this point of mine, I shall write a detailed analysis of  Chidambaram 's budget in a few days. Or maybe why  John Kerry  has chosen  Senator Edwards  as his running mate. Or should it be a commentary on the history behind the feuding Iraqi tribes. You getting the point nuh? I can basically write on anything under the sun, erudite I really am. (  If you've got it, FLAUNT it  ) It’s only that I choose to blog (to be read again as: crap) this way.   Before I sign off, I got this funny thingy a few days back in e-mail. See if you can crack it.   Schwartzenegger has a big one Michael J. Fox has a small one Madonna doesn't have one The Pope has one but doesn't use his Clinton uses his all the time Mickey Mouse has an unusual one Liberace never used his on women Jerry Seinfeld is very, very proud of his. Cher claims that she took on 3 We never saw Lucy use Desi's   What is it? 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now that I have dispensed with the usual suspects, let me concentrate on the silent and often unacknowledged  behind-the-scene players  who have contributed so much to making my 2 year stay at SP a memorable one.   Thanks a tonne to...    Everyone@TheBistro  especially young  Sharad  - u guys were almost family - feeding me those endless coffees, pastries and soft drinks.   Valsan, Ajay  and  Prashant  at CC for helping me get my comp back running no sooner had it crashed (which was once too often for my liking)   Preeti  for sending us those long dreadful mails about classes and test schedules that no one cared to read :-)   Bankim  and  Vincent  at admin without whom I would have never realized the powers of bureaucracy   Suhaas  and  Prahlad  at admin without whom I would not have learnt how to get around bureaucracy :-p   Mukesh  for your loads and loads of patience in putting up with Adcom   Khidkiwaali Sunita  for making me wait to pick up the books over the counter - believe me, those hours seemed like just minutes coz of u :-)    Nishi  for being our silent partner in scheduling classes such that we had maximum time off ;-)   Varsha ma'am  without whom my education at SP would have been so incomplete  All the  Professors  and  Lecturers  for trying ur damnedest to get me to learn - special mention to  AKD sir  n his sense of humor,  Noorul Islam  for those wonderful Ad videos,  Ravi  for your "balls" lectures and  Jayesh Talpade  for his  Art of Living  (to be read as:  Sales and Distribution Channels ) lectures  All the  staff of Vrindavan  for those wonderful lunches and dinners at discounted prices   Shiva  for his unique qawali entertainment and quaint paan shop   Guptaji  for his incomparable cutting chai and vada paav (Saakshi, u never know wot u missed, ask Richa)  The  STD booth wala  who always complained that I never made looooong fone calls :-p   Harish  at the music store in Planet M, Andheri who was brave enough to try my management funda (shelf space optimisation) in reality   Prithvi, Fame Adlabs, Juhu beach, Crosswords, Mahalaksmi, Ram Naik, Lokhandwala, Madh Island, Navrang  and a  million other places  where I have left my indelible footprint - Thanks you all !   Whew !    (Clap Clap Clap)   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If Oscar winners are allowed to make speeches, then why aren't we allowed the same privileges at graduation ceremonies. After all, this is as big an event as it gets in every Joe's life. Considering I never got a chance to make one, here I go attempting one.   (Since I don’t have our yearbook with me now and all I have is the B'day calendar staring at me, the acknowledgements are in the order of ppl's B'day)   It’s been a great pleasure knowing all 132 of you. Each one, in ur own way, have left an indelible mark on me and as I find myself running the last 10 mtrs of my student life, I would like to place on record my humble thanks to    Inspector Shukla  for teaching me that money borrowed during Markops and Markstrat is probably the only time in life when it does not need to be repaid   Chinu  for showing me that a 2 year all expenses paid holiday is still possible staying at B-school - Ur poor father !   Tusku  for all those magical moments of sheer madness on IP at 1 am in the morning   Sumit  for all those proxies in Market Research without which my Wednesday evenings would have been lifeless   Saakshi  for discovering the romantic in me (Saathiya...Saathiya) and proving that kids will always be kids   Dada  for entertaining all the D-wingers by being more KKD than KKD himself   Onkar  for teaching me that one could LOVE-ALL   Aunindo  for enlightening me on the merits of leading a clean life   Ramesh  for giving me definite proof that GOD exists and for those 8 weeks of sheer delight called DOCC. Oh Podu !   Rads  for reminding me that women can sometimes be smarter than men :-p   Addy  for reinforcing my belief that nerds could be extremely fun-loving too. You rox !   Jaya  for our great times in Adcom and for our long and ever-lasting friendship    Break ke baad     Venki  - my bro, my soul-mate, my partner-in-crime, my man-for-all-seasons from TT to Television    Neelam  for all the treats, movies, walks and hours spent doing boring Adcom work   Kerry  for showing me how to live life serving others :-)   Promod  for shocking me with ur wild ways and infuriating me with ur affection :-p   TRA  for being my ready-reckoner for anything remotely associated with Marketing and academics   Pankaj  for teaching me "priorities" in life   Nararyan  for reminding me of what I could have become (and what I thankfully didn’t turn out to be)   Amina  for putting up with all the nonsense from D-16 and still being nice to us :-)   Aparna/Aarthi  for all the Val day dates and our Tam gang get-togethers - precious memories those !   Sachin  for your undying enthusiasm working for Adcom   Pranav  for redefining 'COOL' for me, staying "off" my women and a million other things - actually for every minute spent together at D-16   Suchi  for filling in that gap of being the sister I never had and the one person whose notes I could always xerox :-p   Trooni  for teaching me some of life's most invaluable lessons and for laying the foundations for the mad Jupe I am today   Ashish  for trying to match me in decibels in the hostel and intensity in B'day bumps - u havta admit though that u always were second best !   Paresh Nagar , our desi Shekhar Suman meets Udham Singh equivalent, who provided us BH-168 and other cheap thrills :-)   Amit  for all those googled case studies and heart-to-heart talks   Sagun  for being my only love in college  and finally  Dhruv,  for sparing the world from  Rads  :-p 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink        urlLink Hotchick     Originally uploaded by  urlLink Jupieee .    ....then not all promises are meant to he kept. Neway much as I tried my best to round up a snap of " the hottest one " and scan if for ye all, I could not manage to get my hands on her..ooops...snap, i mean. So went to  Google images  to try my luck and gawd, " Hot Chick " does throw up some interesting results - Trust me :-p   The one that caught my fancy most is shown here(I swear)   ps: Can anyone whoz seen  Hyd Blues2  give me a detailed review? How many stars did it pick up in  TOI ? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okie, the title for my post is a dedication to the  Right Honorable Professor. Arul  who taught me  OB  at   urlLink SP  . His classes were a welcome break from most of the usual management crap taught at B-school. Honestly speaking, in more than a few ways, his was the course that helped me discover new dimensions about myself :-) So what is the parallel between this and my weekend?  I can hear the groans and almost predict that you must be saying "What could he have possibly learnt from  Greece  beating  Portugal  or  Schumi  winning yet another F1 race or even  Federer  slaying  Roddick ?" Good. For once I am not gonna ramble on about sports.  I had gone home this weekend to attend one of my closest and longest pal  Satish 's wedding at  urlLink  Mayavaram  . For people whose favorite subject at school wasn't Geography, Mayavaram is also called  Mayiladuthurai  and is represented in the Lok Sabha by the verbose  Mani Shankar Aiyar . It is situated 140 odd kilometres South East of   urlLink Trichy  , the world's greatest city. A rustic town whose only claim to fame are the wealthy Chettiars, the first thing that strikes one on arriving at Mayavaram is its heat. Man, is it hot! And I am in no way referring to the presence of people like me :-)  (Pls spare me this liberty)   We (my parents and I) checked in at the exquisitely named  Hotel Silambu  at around 5 pm on Saturday evening. Since the reception was scheduled for around 7 pm, I quickly washed up, dressed down (after all I wasn't getting married) and switched on telly to watch   urlLink Maria Sharapova   (droooool) dismantle Serena effortlessly. And before I forget, let me thank Maria for her mention of me in her victory speech.  urlLink  Mmmwaaaah Maria dahlings  . I digress. Okie, it was 7 pm when we finally left for the marriage hall. We were cordially invited, escorted to the dining hall (Rule no: 1 - whatever time you go to a South Indian wedding, there's always some yummy food to grab) where I gorged on some "light" snacks. The groom and the bride were soon escorted to the centre stage and showcased to the entire townsfolk. (Literally every damn person worth his salt in that town had turned up) 2 hrs and a music concert later, dinner was served. Needless to say, I indulged myself heavily. It was at around 10pm that we returned back to the hotel.  I hate waking up early on Sundays but this was probably one of those rare exceptions when I was the first to be up and ready. I had been told that there were a lot of "cute womenfolk" expected and I could "turn on the charm" if I so wished :-) A few hours later I was at the receiving end of one of the harshest reality checks on earth. "Cute" apparently is very relative and Mayavaram's opinions do not seem to match mine. Let’s just leave this at this. The wedding was as expected, a gala affair - heavy turnout of friends and relatives, a ceremony short on dramatics but high on traditions and most importantly, cooking was by  urlLink  Arusuvai Natarajan's   group. (Tamil Nadu's greatest cook)   Which brings us to the learnings...I have always believed in simple weddings - maybe a short ceremony at the registration office and a small reception hosted for the really near-and-dear ones with a  NO GIFTS  rule strictly enforced. I have also maintained that "grand" in a wedding context always meant "ostentatious" and I was of the firm opinion that these functions are a damn waste of money. But after this wedding, I am not so sure. There seems to be an alternate school of thought that these weddings are a small industry by themselves. They provide livelihoods for the pundits who conduct the ceremonies, the hundreds of cooks whose only working days are at such functions, the hundreds of servants of the mandap who get good food only these 2 days, the pandal and flower decorators who earn money only during Muhurth days, the musicians who play only at weddings, the videographer who doesn't get to work on half the other days...I could go on but an entire group of people seem to flourish during weddings. So maybe the money spent doesn't go down the drain after all. It’s a thought worth considering? Is someone listening? Please.  I've ranted for too long. Will upload select photos of the wedding in a later post as soon as I have scanned them. Till then... Ciao. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did it. I won my first serious battle at home. Nopes - am in no way referring to the usual "Why don't you cut down on your sleep and start exercising ?" or "When do you plan to settle down ?" arguments. My folks are chill. I am talking of this  BIG FIGHT  between me and the cockroaches. These pests have been bugging me for over a month now and much as I’ve tried to keep my house clean, they keep popping up from nowhere. Taking my mom's advice, I tried that magic chalk powder but the ones in Bangalore seem to be wiser than the average Joe.  HIT  and other repellants had also failed. So  cometh the hour, cometh the man .  Tuesday night , broom in hand, I attacked them. Guerilla warfare. I hid behind doors (assuming they can see me) and surprised them. My, my, did they retaliate. They ran like crazy. What happened next..   Commercial break ke baad    Trivia 1 for the day:   Cockroaches are among the fastest running insects, capable of 50 body lengths per second, which is equivalent to a human running  the 100 yard dash in 1 second.   Shah Rukh Khan , with a silly grin on his face and a sporty Nike shoe in hand, hams "Haaaaan..If you wanna run faster than these cockroaches, use  NIKE . Just do it."   (Commercial break over)   Silly ol' me had forgotten to close the doors. Needless to say they started escaping to other rooms and I had great trouble restricting their movement. Hurrying behind them and taking pot-shots once in a while, I soon claimed 3 victims. But there were atleast 5-6 left. Next weapon to be used was the bucket. Standing a good 2 feet away from them, I threw a bucket on a couple of 'em the intention being to closet them within that and suffocate them by cutting off their oxygen supply after 3 minutes. 3 minutes ke baad, when I opened the bucket, Lo....what happened next   Last commercial break ke baad    Trivia 2 for the day:   Cockroaches can survive even nuclear attacks.    Amitabh Bachchan , with his deep baritone voice, says " Wanna eradicate cockroaches. Send them to watch  Kabhi Khushi Kabhi Ghum . Bol diya tho bol diya"   (Commercial break over)   The damn things almost flew at me. Okie, maybe I am exaggerating but they sure took off towards me. Screaming and stomping my foot on them at the same time, I managed to get two more. Bravo Jupe ! Now all that was left was the final assault. Summoning up all my courage, having a small flash back about the numerous instances in the past when they had embarrassed me in front of visitors with their pesky presence, I had one last hugeeee swipe at them. N yessssss, I got them all. Mission accomplished.   As I look back now at those 15 minutes of irrefutable valor, my chest swells with pride. I've finally discovered that lion within me.    PS:  This piece is dedicated to someone special as she starts what is probably the most crucial phase of her life today. So here's truckloads of best wishes and prayers for her success. (A peck in the cheek..SLAP....Ooops..sorry)   PPS:  I was kinda considering writing a piece on the hottest chick I’ve met but I have postponed that for Monday :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some people think I am journo material - so insulting :-(  Others think I am made of Booker stuff - so boring  :-(  I hate you all - In fact I hate lots of things in life. Hey,isn't that a great idea for a post. So here i go. I can't stand..   @ Guys who visit Archies gallery not to buy cards but to secretly write down those lovely wordings. These dumbos actually believe that their women will be fooled that it was their own creativity at work.  @ War movies that need to have a brave Muslim soldier die to prove his loyalty to his motherland.  @ Rap songs that need to have the mandatory F word atleast 5 times to become a chart buster.  @ Products that come strongly advertised as User-friendly though in reality they aren't - in some cases even their user manuals are written in Hebrew.    @ Women who make statements with weird Birthday gifts to their men - what on earth is a nail cutter, a travel bag or a book on  Ancient Greek Mythology  supposed to mean?   %$*&^   @ (And toking of weird) people who can't spell that damn word right -  weird , I mean ! My statistics tell me 87% of folks get it wrong more than 50% of the time. Now go check your blogs :-)   The list is endless. But the rest of my compilation will have to wait.    ps:   ESPN-Star  is back. But  Henman  lost and  Serena  won. I hate life..Blah blah blah.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What is it that makes every growing adolescent guy (and even his grown up father) wish that the woman-of-his-dreams is someone like the chirpy, fun-loving  Geetanjali  (Girija) in  Idayathai Thirudathe  or the bubbly and adorable  Preity  (Preity Zinta) in  Uyire . Who would not want to have an understanding soul-mate like  Chithu aka Chitra  (Revathy) in  Anjali  or  Indira  (Simran) in  Kannathil Muthamittal . Hey forget all this, who doesn't like the brave  Roja  (Madhoo) in  Roja , the strong-willed  Shakti  (Shalini) in  Alaipaayuthe  or the stunning  Meera  (Kareena) in  Yuva  :-) Ok, pardon me just that last inclusion. So what is it about  Mani Ratnam  and the magic he weaves around his heroines ?  While jealous peers and obsessed critics fault his supposed fixation with style, they forget that at the heart of all of Mani's masterpieces is a wonderfully etched, multi-layered female protagonist. I need not look beyond  Mouna Ragam , one of Mani's timeless classics and a movie I have seen  15  times fully (no exaggeration this) to prove my point. The heroine  Divya  (played by Revathy) is one of Mani's most interesting character sketches till date - here is a gal who is the apple of her family's eye, used to getting her way in everything, raised almost like a guy - boldness et al. But again all it takes for her to be swept off her feet is a dashing local thug (Cmon,  Manohar  played by Karthik is not like a glorified Robin Hood et al) and some hopeless romantic stunts. Falling for him like a tonne of bricks, Divya tries to make a proper citizen of the man but fails and loses him forever. To make matters worse, she is then forced into a marriage with a total stranger  Chandrakumar  (played by Mohan) and has to move to Delhi. Seeing her near-perfect world come crashing down within a few weeks, she is now forced to be someone she has never ever imagined possible. How she copes with a reality that is stranger than her worst dreams and how she rediscovers life is brilliantly depicted in true Mani style. Some scenes which stand out in my memory are  # When her husband asks her what she would like for a wedding present, Divya asks for a divorce  # When Divya leaves the wedding party at home in a huff and then repents for her hasty actions  # When Divya explains to her visiting parents how things are all fine between her husband and her  # When Divya wears the anklet and tries to grab her husband's attention  # When Divya finally sheds her ego and confesses her love for her husband  Where are these real life  Divyas ? Please don't tell me they are like  Santa Claus  :-( 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         10  of my all-time favorite romantic Tamil film numbers (whew.. that’s a lot of adjectives) Here they are in no particular order      Kadhal Rojave (Roja)  - USP: Awesome SPB, sublime lyrics, the electronic flute      Anjali Anjali (Duet)  - USP: Sax and sentimental lyrics      Kaadhalin Deepam (Thambikku Endha Ooru)  - USP: Rajini, Madhavi and er.. Madhavi      Andhi Mazhai (Rajapaarvai)  - USP: The violins, a song to be heard on a rainy afternoon      Enna Satham (Punnagai Mannan)  - USP: SPB, the pauses and silences in between      Valai Osai (Sathya)  - USP: Amalaaaaaaaaa...drooooool      Om Namaha (Idayathai Thirudathe)  - USP: Janaki and hehe..the picturisation !      Pani Vizhum (Ninaivellam Nithya)  - USP: Rich lyrics, listen to it as u jog in the morning      Pottu vaitha (Idayam)  - USP: I have no clue but I love this number :-)      Sundari Kannaal (Thalapathi)  - USP: SPB agai        9  women I'd love to date. Again in no particular order      Catherine Zeta Jones  - a classical beauty if ever there was one      Priyanka Gandhi  - there's something about this lassie - deserves much better than that bloke Wadhera.      Perizaad Zorabian  - or is it the character she plays in Joggers Park. Whoever :-)      Benazir Bhutto  - a woman of substance      Courtney Cox Arquette  - Greek Goddess and I am specifically talking of her... chuck de ;-)      Kareena Kapoor  - she's got some spunk and chutzpah and I love that in women      Meg Ryan  - America's sweetheart and mine too. Hey Meg, you've got mail (from me)      Carrie Anne Moss  - she's hotttttttttttttttttt ! Need i say more?      Sushmita Sen  - one of the very few cases where brains and beauty overlap      Dare to dream, Jupie :-)      8  " Never-do-it-with-Jupie " things on YM  1.  Buzz  when in the middle of a conversation - If u don’t see anything from my side, it means I am thinking.  2.  Use emoticons  for no rhyme or reason - I jes don’t get most of 'em :-(  3.  Reply with monosyllables  like K, Aye, Na esp when I am in TOK mode.  4.  Not say anything  when I am in LISTEN mode. Silence sucks.  5.  Reply to SUP  with "the ceiling" - that’s my patented line :-)  6. Set  status messages  in alien languages  7. Say " You are soooo funny " or " Whoever is gonna marry you is a very lucky person " - more so if you happen to be a friend of the opposite sex (Why is it every gal except "the actual one" feels this way)  8.  Change the Environment  I have loaded to somethin' else - hurts my ego!!  Supplementary to 8 - 8a. Play chess and beat me at it.    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I won my first open quiz  for all school students when I was in my Std: 6. From then till now, quizzing has been one of my biggest passions. If it was  Balls by Picasso  at  RECT , then it was the daily afty quiz at  Infy-Chennai . Though we tried a lot to make  Quizzine  at  SP  a regular feature, the results were far from satisfactory. The quizzing circle at Wipro is pathetic to say the least and so these days I stay content watching  THE CHALLENGE  in  CNBC  on Saturday nights (where the SP team incidentally is screwing the corporate world - WTG Dipanjan) and reruns of  MASTERMIND INDIA  on Sundays in  BBC . Which brings us to the reason for this post.  For those of you unaware of the  MASTERMIND  series, please look t up   urlLink here  . I am a big, big fan of the Mastermind series and gave it a shot in 2001 in Pune where I missed the prelims cut off by 1.5 points. Believe me it was bloody difficult and thank heavens I didn’t make it through since I would have surely been severely exposed. Since then I have watched as many episodes of Mastermind as was possible. I have been fortunate to see some wonderful quizzers be it Mohit P or Amalesh M from Infy and even that wonderful lady,  urlLink  Priyamvada   who won   urlLink Mastermind India 2000  . But after seeing a repeat of   urlLink Ramanand  's winning Mastermind India 2003 finals performance today morning, I am beginning to feel very very inadequate. After scoring a massive 25 in his chosen subject of  Stories of Tommy and Tuppence  by  Agatha Christie , he blew the opposition away with a stand-out performance in the GK round to score a cumulative 42 which fell short of Priyamvada's all time high of 43 by just one. I suspect he actually took it easy towards the end but that still does not take away absolutely anything from this masterful performance. And I am not yet done.. On googling for this guy, I came across   urlLink his blog   and my, he writes brilliantly. I had always considered myself unique in my own way - maybe Jack of a million trades - but after seeing Ramanand, I havta to be the joker of the pack. This guy is simply awesome. Check out his pet   urlLink JaDe project  . Btw, he is a Tam :-))  I think I have been in self deprecation mode for too long now. Ain't I de best ? Bye sweetoos ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink  Jonathan Livingston Seagull (JLS)    was a masterpiece. I savoured every minute of reading it and was so impressed that strangely, for a long time i resisted reading more of  Bach . I didnt want to lose "the feel good" factor. Illusions was strongly recommended but i resisted the temptation. But when i chanced upon  THE BRIDGE ACROSS FOREVER  while roaming the Sunday roadside market of Pondicherry with my uncle, i cudn't hold back any longer. Ok, the fact that my uncle recommended it was good enough but what clinched it was the fact that it was priced at Rs 10 :-)  300 odd pages later, i understood why this book evokes such extreme reactions and reviews - With good reason too. To cut a long story short,  TBAF 's about  Bach 's seemingly endless quest to find his soulmate. Every person who's ever been in love or who's looking for love can relate to this.  Bach  explores varied emotions like love,insecurity, fear, despair, success, betrayal and handles them with such aplomb - transporting the reader effortlessly into his own world so much so that soon we begin to go through his emotional rollercoaster.The book's "literally" laced with striking metaphors,liberally dosed with flowery prose and  takes the reader on alluring trips up and down time. On the downside,   Bach  does tend to go overbo(red)ard with allegorical references.The stories of flying do not strike a chord with all and the book becomes a drag once  Bach  and  Leslie  start on their sermonising tours. Towards the end, one also gets the feeling that the book could have been a good 50 pages shorter.Still, for those people who are on the lookout for their soulmate, this book offers solace and is a real eye opener - it asks to open our hearts, look within and not to give up hope as there is someone yearning for us as hard as we're pining for them :-) How corny !!  A few lines from the book to help you make up your mind:     She reached out and touched my face..."Did you ever feel," she said. "that you were missing someone you had never met?"        "The only thing that shatters dreams is compromise."   "Look in a mirror and one thing's sure: what we see is not who we are."   "We're the bridge across forever, arching above the sea, adventuring for our pleasure, living mysteries for the fun of it, choosing disasters triumphs challenges impossible odds, testing ourselves over and again, learning love and love and LOVE!"       
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "America's leadership must be guided by the lights of learning and reason or else those who confuse rhetoric with reality and the plausible with the possible will gain the popular ascendancy with their seemingly swift and simple solutions to every world problem."   These are notes from the speech that was to be made at the Trade Mart in Dallas on November 22, 1963. Just that they were never delivered. Barely anyone recognizes these lines today. However, " The president is dead "  are immortal words entrenched in the memory of people who went through the trauma of seeing one of the world's most popular statesman shot dead by a “mad” sniper.   The murder of John F Kennedy.   My interest in this whole affair was sparked off by Oliver Stone's award winning but highly controversial movie JFK. Gripping plot, convincing performances, excellent direction - the movie had it all. I was so taken up by the whole saga that I must confess I spent a good part of two months in my second year at SP reading a helluva lot of material on the JFK murder. Starting from the  urlLink  Warren commission report   to the  urlLink  Clay Shaw case   transcripts to the   urlLink single bullet theory  , I suppose I must have read loads and loads of documents but what is fascinating is that even today whilst it is known that Lee Harvey Oswald was the one who pulled the trigger, no one still knows whether he did it all by himself or there were people behind it. Was it the  KGB  or  J.Edgar Hoover and his FBI ? Or maybe it was the handiwork of the  Texas Oil Barons  or  Castro  or the  Cosa Nostra ? There is no dearth of evidence but it's been virtually impossible piecing it all together and coming to one firm conclusion. 41 years later, the  JFK murder  continues to be one the most confounding whodunits in the history of crime.  I am very passionate about the subject and this post might have made absolutely no sense to people who are not aware of this case. However if you are someone who loves a mystery and has time to spare, just ping me and I shall share all the wonderful links I have assiduously collected over the last two years. Trust me, there is so much literature on this case in the net that I wished I was in the business of coding and “in bench” :-)    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Thursday, August 5th, 2004 11:02  Perfect. Just about perfect. That would sum up today. Maybe the only glitch was that i had to be awake at half past six in the morning since it was gonna be a big day but then once i was up, everthing went on like clock-work. Switching on my CD player to start the day with the sweet strings of  Pt. Ravishankar  on the sitar, went through the daily ritual - brushing my teeth, coffee with  Good Day  biscuits, shining my shoes and checking the previous day's answers to the  Hindu crossword . By this time water was at just the right temperature for my bath :-) After the bath, switching on telly to catch the day's headlines and finally having to rush through the dressing up and catching EC-9A. My usual seat was taken but got another one by the window and had the mandatory nap :-) It was chilly when the bus finally reached EC, checked the welcome board near  Gate 6  and then had the usual  idli-vada  at EC1 canteen for breakfast. The chutney tasted nice and the sambhar was piping hot. So far so good :-)  I had hardly reached my seat and checked mails when i got the call from Gate 6 that the customers were already in. Never one to be disturbed when mails are concerned, read each one of them before rushing over to escort them to  Nagarhole . After flaunting my newly printed business cards, started with the presentation at around half past 9 and went on till quarter past 10 without a hitch in between - not a stutter not a single loong pause to cook up a story nor a question where i wasn't confident of an answer. Then there were some technical discussions which were plainly boring (Greek n Latin are easier) so got a pal of mine to call me up and using that as an excuse skipped out. Came back to my seat to see a scorching fire - had to work really hard and quick to turn around a presentation for a meeting at a customer's premise at 1 pm. Dit it successfully and returned back to the customer meeting at hand just in time for lunch at 1:15 pm. Usually i try and dodge these since the food is awful but i had hand-picked the menu this time so gorged down some delicious paneer, rotis, pulav and rosagullas :-) Even the  Pepsi can  opened without troubling me :-)  Post lunch, we took them on a tour of the campus and i was totally in my elements spinning stories about our amazing training initiatives and security practices. Suitably impressed, we finally packed off our customers at around half past 3.  In no mood to start new work, i sent out a few official mails, updated the BDM on the happenings of the day, cleared some pending Six Sigma work and then visited my usual daily sites -  Rediff, Salon, Indiafm, BBC, ESPN-Star, Yahoogroups ...Bored and with still a few hours to kill before the 6 pm shuttle, I turned my attention to  Yahoo Messenger..  And by  Toutatius , chanced to make a new friend  D  - was nice chatting up with her and finding out that life in B-schools in Inida hadn't changed much. Hey, here's wishing you all the best for your placements in a few months..Till then   FUN   A   LOT   FIKAR   NOT   :-) And then it happened...(how i love dramatising it like this)  Just as i was about to pack my bags at around 5:30 pm, got embroiled in a nasty fight with one of my close friends on YM. Almost 3 hours and a lot of  Grrrrs  and : -( s later, our friendship strengthened ten-fold. ( Di , if you are reading this, you r de best!!) Took the  8:30 pm shuttle  but was denied a nap thanks to my seat-mate who insisted on chatting all the way along about how small towns like  Bhopal  and  Trichy  were much better places to settle down than  Bangalore . Thank God the driver drove really fast :-) Reached home, had a quick dinner, flipped thru ET and watched  Friends . Twas the episode where each of them reminisce about their 30th B'days - laughed my guts off though Dad cudn't see anything funny in it - He's getting old :-) At half past 10, switched channels to see a  20-20  match between  Lancashire  and  Yorkshire  -  War of the Roses  -  Ian Harvey  was in awesome form. Its now 11:20 pm and as i type this away, i am listening to the  OST  of  Passion of the Christ . Should go to bed in another 15. If only every day could be like this......   ps:   Dinesh Kaarthik  is in the Indian team. Yessssssssss. This merits a separate post. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ever asked a B school grad who are the most important people in his/her life for those 2 years? Professors, placement reps, room-mates, (girl/boy) friend....?? Na..  Professors can be booted out by giving bad feedback and you can choose competent people to be your placement reps. Girl/boy friends are available  dime-a-dozen  and if you have a bad apple as your room-mate, you can still work around it by kicking him/her out or swapping rooms so that you get to stay with like-minded people. But if there is one thing which is not "technically" in your control, then it is the selection of your acad group mates. Most B-schools today lay strong emphasis on group work - and more often than not, to form these groups names are drawn randomly from a hat. Trust me, for all practical purposes, these acad groups could make or break your life - these are the people with whom you need to spend a minimum of 12 hours of group work every week besides the tonnes of assignments and presentations and submissions.  I must admit that i was very fortunate in my first year to be part of some really wonderful acad groups.  My  Trime 1 acad group , as providence would have it, was full of  Tams.  We were  5  of us, of which there were  2 pucca Tams ,  me  n my bro  Venki  and then there was  GOD,  a   Tallu  ( half Tam half Mallu ) and then there were these  two Palghat people  settled in Mumbai,  Suchi and Narayan ,  who claimed the language they spoke was Tamil :-p   You can imagine the kind of riotous fun we had in our meetings and group studies. We used to sit in the Bistro, sing Rajini songs, chat and gossip and do everything but work. Finally when push came to shove, we would fight over who would do the assignment and usually boiled down to either Suchi or Narayan saving our skin. My fondest memory of this group has to be the  group OM viva- voce  we had with  Chacku . Or was it  Sesha Iyer  and  QM  ? Oh god, we were asked some really stupid Qs (read: Qs for which we didnt know the answers)  and since it was a group viva, i recollect each of us  muttering in Tamil to the other and helping out with the answers. The best part was when I forced  Suchi  to change her correct answer to my incorrect one and ended up getting her the least marks. Was she furious ?? Ha Ha Ha !!  At  SP , we also had a system by which every student was  Course Coordinator (CoCo)  for a particular subject in a Trime. There were a few Professors who did not believe in random allocation and allowed students the liberty of forming their own groups with the help of the  CoCo s.  Marketing ,  which ran across all 3 Trimes in first year, was one such course where we had a separate acad group. As luck would have it, i was one of the  CoCo s for this subject in Trime 1 and could not believe my luck when i was told to form the groups that would work across trimes and assignments for the whole of first year. Suffice to say that i was one of my the most wanted guys in campus those few days since every  Tom, Dick, Harry  and  Jane  wanted favors.  Realizing the gravity of the situation and the seriousness of the decisions ahead of me (:-P), I ran an in-depth profile analysis to select my own group first. With all honesty, i wanted some real diversity so that the learning process would be beneficial to all the members. After some serious soul searching, i chose a  Bong ,  Anirban  (O-neer-bon) from the software industry (someone i cud relate to coz i was under the misconception that all Bongs were profound intellectuals), a hard-working n enthu  Narayan  (it also helped that he was a Mumbaikar and we expected to be invited to his house for food),  an intelligent and down-to-earth  Mangesh  from the manufacturing sector and a freaky, fun-loving fresher  Tushar  with a commerce degree from  St.Xaviers . It all then boiled down to the choice of the female. I had known a few of my batch mates through e-mail interactions before joining SP and i naturally wanted to bond with them closer. But since i had to accommodate some of my friends' requests, I finally zeroed down on a smart lady,  Taruni  with a Japanese Honors from  JNU . My My, what fun we had in our group.  At the start of the year, we had to select a company/sector which the group would track and apply all Marketing fundae in presentations. As self-appointed leader of the group, i scheduled a meeting when  Taruni  wasn't around and we "unanimously" agreed to select  WIPRO  and the IT sector :-) Needless to say,  Taruni  who knew nothing about even computers (at that time) leave alone software industry, was furious. Till today, she accuses me of sabotaging her grand plans to learn some Marketing in B-school. We had great fun the whole year - We fought like crazies, we gave ourselves nicknames ( Raunchy, Nari, Mangy, Tusku, Fishfood and Hitler ) and we partied hard.  What would SP have been without these acad groups !! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You can keep a man away from his blog but you cannot keep blogging away from him. So if  As You Like It  doesn't want me, i am sure there are loads of people who would give an arm and a leg for a guest post from me. Neway, this is just for the  21  of you darlings who seem to have visited my site despite knowing there would be no activity here. I happen to be writing this week at    urlLink OKs    where i am a joint contributor (shameless self-publicity) - so u know where to go now :-)    Bye bye sweetoos!!   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>