<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent the night at Marie's last night. We were totally going to go see Soul Plane but it was rated R. Ugh... why are there even ratings on movies anyway? kids see just as much sex and stuff in real life and even more. i think it's just stupid. Me and Marie played with my play-doh collection last night and it was sooooo fun! i have the coolest collection. i have a George Foreman play-doh grill and a play-doh fun factory and SOOO many cans of play-doh. last night i bought scented play-doh at the mall. it smells like crap on a stick. When i go to see The Day After Tomorrow with Stan tomorrow then i'm gonna buy some more play-doh stuff like a buzz cut kit. :D YAY! Me and Marie are going to Folk Life in Seattle with Erin on Monday and i'm so excited! i've never been there before. In Spencer's at the mall there is a blow up penis hanging from the ceiling and little stuffed toy ones. it's so sick. i wish i had a York mint patty right about now....  "Got worms? Let us find out!" (From a vet's office billboard in Burlington)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well all is alright except for me having a cyst on my ovary. OUCH! I am in a bit of uncomfortable pain, but only when I move. Looks like I'll be a couch potato for awhile. At the emergency room they did a cat scan on me, an ultrasound, and put an IV in me for like 4 hours. sooo boring. i was there for 7 hours all together. and the worst part is that i can only eat liquids til tomorrow and i haven't had a thing to eat all day. Bleck... Looks like i'm going to have a radical time this weekend camping with Marie though. hope i'm better. for now Stan has subsided to calling me Miss Ovary. great....oh shit i missed the STD slide!  To all the Marmalade Boys (that one's for you Marie)
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stayed home from school and i'm going to the emergency room....great. and to think i have a concert tonight. but who cares it's just mrs. weaver. i hope it's nothing serious. i'm scared cuz i've never had anything wrong with me before. ooops my ride is here to wisk me away to nothingness.... wish me pleasant dreams  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am soooo bored. i just got home from ye olde Stan's. I wish i was watching THe Price Is Right. Bob Barker is like my dad...Everything is boring. even ALADDIN! isn't that scary? well yah. OMG i found these really cool clothes on ebay. yah, look....   http://cgi.ebay.com/ws/eBayISAPI.dll?ViewItem&category=11479&item=4152644358&rd=1  http://cgi.ebay.com/ws/eBayISAPI.dll?ViewItem&category=3064&item=3481710276&rd=1  AND  http://cgi.ebay.com/ws/eBayISAPI.dll?ViewItem&category=63864&item=4152811416&rd=1  yah they're cool. mooshka....  Yes and No
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well i've been sucked in. I swore it wouldn't effect me but it did. The world of video games has opened its doors and i have walked in with a smile on my face. I don't especially care for new games though. i stick to sega and nintendo. Stan gave me his old sega and i've been playing it non stop. i'm looking into getting a nintendo but haven't found a good deal. i'll stick to playing it on the computer for now. Yesterday me and Marie fixed up this old floating dock we found in the crick and now we take it out into the lake and jump off it. it's a hoot if i do say so myself. Friday is Stan's birthday and i'm taking him out to dinner, buying him a video game, and paying for tickets to see the movie Dodgeball. Me and Marie are going to go to the cabin the week after the 4th of July. I can't wait to catch some more turtles there :D The fireworks on the lake are coming up too. Also there's band camp...fun... Piam is being soooo piamish!   "You say Rolls, I say Royce. You say God, GIVE ME A CHOICE! You say Lord, I say CHRIST! I don't believe in Pizza Fan, Frankenstein, or Superman. All i want to do is...BICYCLE!" -Queen, "Bicycle Race"
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well tomorrow i'm leaving for a week to go to band camp. hooray hoorah. it'll be fun because i get to spend the whole week with Erik. YAY! but it won't be fun because we have to play music ALL DAY. except for a few hours that we get to have breaks and swim and stuff. yes i'll get to see Snack Time Matt. he was this really weird guy that worked at the snack place last year at camp and was all pervish to my friend Davida. today me and marie went to the Highland Games and watched the Parade of the Clans, the strong man competition, sheep dog trials, and lots of other stuff. it was awesome possom. last week i went on vacation to Long Beach with some of the Simmons Clan. i went with my granny, my aunt Jeanie, my cousin Steven, and his girlfriend Trina. it was fun and me and Trina went to thrift stores and bought stuff. oh yah me and Marie stuck a pad on the side of the co-op downtown. it was sooooo funny. i'd better go pack.  Jake the Alligator Man Says "Hi!"  (i witnessed this marvel at Marsh's Free Museum in Long Beach, Wa) 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was the 3rd of July. (the 4th for Big Lake-ians) the day was started off with my family (the whole Simmons clan) shooting off bottle rockets and such next door. i all of a sudden found out that the Sheriff was in our driveway talking to them. turns out that bottle rockets, and a few other items that they were posessing, were illegal to shoot off. the advice that the sheriff gave to them was to wait til it was dark to light them off so nobody could tell who it was. then later me and my mom went into sedro woolley to pick up Stan. we came home with him and shot off some more fireworks over at my granny's. our new and favorite toy were some dry ice bombs that Steven and Ryan, my cousins, were shooting off. then came the big fireworks onthe lake at like 10:30 and we all "ooo'd" and "awwwwed" at them. tomorrow Marie FINALLY gets home from her dad's. i got these really cool shoes on ebay just recently.  urlLink   they're the best. i might go see Farenheit 9/11 today. seeya  "It's a little bit funny, this feeling inside..."  -The Duke in Moulin Rouge
     

    
</post>


</Blog>