<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hihi. ermx i think my dreamx has come true le worx. so de happi sia.. u noe wad is it ma... my dreams is goin to tung san basketball team and training at there.... den realli come ture le worxx......got one of my friend ask mi go to tung san training worx so happi...... i will treasure this chance de.....:P but he haven confirm yet with his coach yet worx.. hope can go in to this team la......... 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haix... i am jus a useless guy in this world. dunno how to make her happi but make her sad and angry...... haix.. maybe i am a fool and idiot bahx.... so sad..... crying now dunno wad to do realli think of killin miself now..... jesus wad shld i do.... haix... heart damn the fucking pain. y i must suffer from   love   y..... haix realli dun understand her and myself... maybe wadever she sae is rite de bahx...... sorry for making u sad and angry. i dun mind if u dun forgif mi anot.... all i jus want is u stay happi forever.... if u rem mi than sad i rather u forgot hu am i. tat all and tat wad i wish if u realli hate mi... :'( useless guy in this world called John Ng Wei Jie
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haix. dunno y this few week no mood and beri de sad... today so suay sia... go sch kana cut hair by mrs wong.... fuck man... last day den holiday le still cut.... curse her whole family die arx... den i spit saliver on her car... hu ask her cut mi hair and cut until so ugly... den quarrel with one of mi sch mate loh.... he sux man haix.... so sad today.. den in the klass keep thinking of her but also jealous too la...... so sad.... she realli like hack care mi le worx.... den i at klass today my eyes came out tears when i think of her and how she treat mi now... use mi friend de hp msg her also nv reply haix..... so sad.... heart damn damn the pain pain now..... dunno wad to do.. haix... i think i too BHB le bahx..... ppl no feeling for mi i still disturb so BHB. i so ugly, unkind,not caring and stupid... den like her.. she so cute, chio, kind and caring.. where will have feeling for mi..... but i realli realli   love   her alot alot. but she also dun care mi.... maybe i too guzi le bax... so jealous my frined now... haix dun sae le mi eyes tears cum out again and mi heart like gort ppl taking knife stabbing mi now..... :'(
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so sad. she like hack care mi le. tok to mi also sian sianx de.... sound like dislike mi le bahx.... haix.. maybe she realli love mi friend bahx.. but i still will treat her as mi good good gan mei mei de.... realli lurve her alot alot worx. heat pain pain
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haix... now i listening to jay chou de gui ji worx... this song is i and her de 1st met song leh.... keep thinking of her... miss her worx.. so sorry that cannot msg or reply ur msg cox mi fone kana confiscated by my mama..... haix.... i realli lub u alot alot worx... i nv bluff u de... and i am not a liar too..... call u also switch off hp..... but nvm cox u are the star rite through to my deepest heart.....and i will nv forget u de.... u are de most important person in my heart now.. i leave each day is becox of u loh..... realli.... although u like other guy now but i still will wait for u de... cox i realli lub u.,,,, muackx.... but i scare u dun like mi haix...... nvm.....
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haix. so sad man. yesterday go bball training den injure mi finger so  pain swallon worx...... pain pain..... den reach home le .... 1st thing step home is kana scold by mi bro.. WTF everytym scold mi and bully mi de.... den mi mum scold mi too cox mi bill over le..... haix den kana confiscate lohx..... no HP now liao la... sad... den yesterday i do finish all the house work den slp.... so tired man.... realli feel like killing miself...... haix... heng heng today got a gal gal from nchs de pei wo chat chat worx.. kekex.. so kind man:P.... buaix
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hAix. today i realli realli beri de sad.... and i nearly cry out infront of mi friend while i saw the msg that she sent mi...... so sad. but i nv blame her for anything i jus blame miself. i am such a useless guy in this world.... so ugly, bad, not kind n not caring. haix that wad i tot of myself..... my eyes came out tears when i look at the sky and keep on thinking and ask myself why why and why.. why i am so useless.... haix... but i told miself one important thing is tat... if i love her i must let her happi.. wad ever she sae if she feel happi jus support her..... haix... damn up sad now..... dunno wad to do... keep thinking of her and ask miself shld i let her go ma?...... i realli dunno de ans.... i feel that i realli suck leh...(WTF) haix. anyway i wont force her or wad de.... i will still treat her as mi good good gan mei.... she is a realli good gal loh. although she rejected mi but i nv blame her i jus blame miself... cox i realli sux to the core.. damn look like a idiot and a idot and a idiot x 100 idiot... haix... i jus look like a fool man... haix..... maybe ur will think tat i beri stupid la... but ur are rite. i'm realli a stupid freak and a useless guy in this world.... dunno how to make gal happi.. but always make them sad and angry.... haix heart damn de pain le and now mi eyes comin out tears again.... so i must stop here le...... buai... i am a stupid freaker so betta dun come near mi... later u will regret...... wHaT tHe fU*k am i doin. _|_ haix. maybe i am not important in her life bahx.... i think suld be 89% that i nt important in her life... sadx and cry le
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      tOday i am quite tried man...... bored too worx..... kekex.... at klass sleep de whole period sia.... so warm also.... den i jus came back from basketball loh.... i go pei mi friend play basketball at 120.... play until beri tired sia.. den injure my elbow. pain pain worx..... ermx..... hope that mi everyday can be happi sia.... haix... i go eat le. hungry liao.... heng mi papa cooked porridge sia. cox mi no $$$ to eat dinner kekex..... buaix
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yOx. kEkE. wAh!!! tOdAy dAmN tIrEd sIa.. aT 4 plus go gym at hougang.... after tat go ponggol cc play bball worx..... kekex.... i also gt pei wo de xiao bao bei... she is damn cuite siax..... love u so muchi. kekex.. u noe hu are u la..sO hAPPi kekex... ermx.. tml sian man still hab to go sch worx..... feel like nt goin leh.. :P... write till here la.... today no star sia.... hahax.... i go liao buaix.......
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yOx.. wah this morning rain beri heavy sia........ hahax. cannot go out worx.... so sad..... but nvm la... mi xiao bao bei gt pei wo chat worx. she is so cutie man!!! kekex... she is beri good to mi de worx!!! eh....... yesterday i nearly fight with sumone while playing bball but i controll miself..... kekex....... see i beri good de won't anyhow beat ppl de.. haix. later mi friend ask mi go pei him sia....... kekex... than his mum cook dinner for mi leh. so good sia..... kekex...... end mi speech here 1st la.. hahax..... :P
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      h| iS mI aGaIn wOrX.... tOdai i nearly gt taiji with other ppl sia.... de person wanna tio mi sia.. but i hack care him i walk away lohx.. is not i hUmJi la... is i jus dun wan to tio back him cox mi N'Level cumin liao.. wait i cannot take den die sia. kekex.. other den tat my day still ok la.. later goin to play bball at lor arsoo worx... haix... gtg liao bUaix.. kekex... to be countiue
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hIhI... eRmX mY nAmE iS jOhN lA... kEkEx.... sO sIaNx mAn... nTh tO wRiTe wOrX.. kEkE... nOw dAys wEatHeR bEri dE hOt lEhx lIkE sIaO sIaO oNe.. kEkEx.. mI nOw bUsY fInD gF lEhx bUt cAnNoT fInD sIa.. i tHiNk i aM tOo uGlY lE bAhx... hAix sAd SaD wOrX.. tOdAy aT sChOoL dAmN sIaNx mAn i aLmOsT sLp dE wHoLe mOrNiNg.. kEkEx bErI pIg hOhx..oK lA sO i eNd mI sPeEcH hErE fEr tOdAy k.. sO tIrEd wAnNa gO oRhx oRhX le...:p 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haix. so sad man.. u noe wad is de most sad and most angry thing in ur life ma? i noe le.... is ur beri beri close and best friend betrayed u and sae lots of lots of bad things behind u.... haix... this thing really happen it to mi le. so sad..... f*ck man... haix.. sad sad sad sad sad sad.......
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yox hahax. so long nv write le worx.... ermx today 3 on 3 basketball match we play 5 round win 5 round sia so happy... i hope we this year can get the champion leh... hahax.... eh... today is a beri tired day for mi worx...... tml still have to go to sch... than thursday still have to go to SMU there for the knock out game.... hahax.... but is fun la.. must play more more cox school reopen soon le worx... i must study hard hard.... now i no like anyone le.... yeah feel so freedom sia.....
     
    
</post>


</Blog>