<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My last day in this company. I'm feeling a mixture of excitement and sadness realizing that by tomorrow, I will no longer be sitting here. I have grown rather accustomed to my little cubicle. Though I haven't been working here for long, spending an average of 10-12 hours of my day here for the past 2 years somehow left a mark in my life. But Anne told me to cheer up. It's not the company I have a heavy heart of leaving, it's the people. And she's right.  *sigh   They have becomed more than colleagues, they are my frens. I hope I will meet equally nice and fun people in my new company.  I shall leave today's blog with pics of the happier times.    One of our many nights out.    Eric Meric.    Alcoholic Queens    The hitz.FM party at Batu Ferringhi    Tommy the King of Alcohol 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just got off the phone with  him .  Me, "Can you hear me?" Him, " Yes." Me, "Then why are you distracted?" Him, "What do you mean?" Me, "You are taking 5 seconds to answer me." Him, "That's coz I don't want to hear." Me, "Har.har.har. Very funny. Ok fine."  I guess he wasn't very receptive to my suggestion of offering to cut his hair for him since his favourite barber tutup kedai.  The 5 second man. Gentlemen, please don't do it to your ladies. We hate it. Just say no. *wink
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        "Those who have the courage to love, should have the courage to suffer."   (A. Trollope : The Bertrams)  Everybody rants about love. Today is my turn.  After reading  urlLink Datin's  entry yesterday, I couldn't stop thinking. Her entry said,  "We sat mostly in silence, contemplating our own universal concerns, watching the sky, admiring the new frangipanis in bloom.  I realised then that perhaps the center of my being is pretty happy after all. Not completely, but just enough. Enough to take me through the days and love this man next to me."   It reminds me of this guy I'm seeing right now. I have just met him earlier this year by occasion of work. We talked. We shared a few smoke breaks. We went home. It could have just ended there.  But  no , I sent a thank you note to him - for reasons of work as well. And from there, began a very lovely friendship. And sometimes, not unlike Datin...we also sit in the silence of each other's company, contemplating our own thoughts. Sometimes I am just dying to know what's going on in his mind...but I know better than to ask. Each of us need, at times, those moments of thoughts. Good thoughts. Bad thoughts. Silly thoughts. Nasty thoughts. But just the same - those thoughts we do not wish to explain.  He's older. Much older than me. Except for the moments when we sit in silence, I do not feel the age. He makes me feel safe. Someone who's been there & done that. He encourages me to grow, to do things, to live. This is what I especially like about him. Someone who gives me the space to grow. You don't get that going out with younger guys.  Younger men are still trying to 'make it' for themselves. They are engrossed in trying to make you fit in. They get too territorial and want to control  what  you do. They get insecure and want to control  who  you go out with. Like what gives?  *snort   Right on. I'm getting side tracked from my initial topic. So, what's all the big fuss about love?  If you asked  ME , I'd say it's distorted from all the bloody fairy tales and soppy movies you watched all your life. 'Girl gets into trouble, boy rescues girl, I love you and live happily everafter.' Or vice versa. (*just to be a little politically correct)  I grew up in an environment where there are more broken marriages than broken china. I have seen happy marriages, loving couples with great kids...and the next thing you know, the husband tries to hit on me. And mind you, he was sober. What the fcuk? What is then the meaning of love? What is love when your husband tells you I love you, pays all the bills in the household, comes home every night for dinner, plays with the kids, makes love to you at night, gets along with your mother and fcuks another woman occasionally. Is that ONE flaw big enough for you to leave him, or small enough to be contra off for all his other qualities?  Love, I believe is always conditional. Women who believe that love is unconditional are either lying to themselves, or being lied to by their partners.  There is only one unconditional love I have and that is for my immediate family. Everything else is conditional.  I think I have lost faith in love. But like what Ally (in Ally McBeal) said to her therapist in one of the episodes.....she doesn't believe in love anymore, but she can't help wanting desperately to be loved. Perhaps my fear is more of ending up with a bastard. I've seen too many of these slimeballs around. I don't need excess baggages in my life.  Like what I told Datin, we can only be happy for the moment. Everything else is beyond our control.  So for the moment, I am happy.  Not completely, but just enough.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This poem by Glen Allen reflects exactly who I have becomed throughout the years, moulded by what I have been through and what I have seen happening around me.   The Woman I Am   ~ Glen Allen  "The woman I am hides deep in me beneath the woman I seem to be.  She hides away from the stranger's eye -  she is not known to the passer-by. she goes her way, the woman I seem,  But the woman I am withdraws to dream! The woman I seem goes carelessly - when love goes by does not seem to see.  But the woman I am knows sudden fear... and hides more deeply when love draws near! For love might loook closely perhaps...and see her beneath the woman  I seem to be!"    ...the woman I seem...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had -at one point- a very happy family....of rabbits. The ideal family structure. Loving parents and three hoppy kids. All my pets were never caged. I don't believe that people should cage animals. My pets are free-roaming animals.  Which I think now was not such a good idea. The cats have struck all four of my bunnies and I'm left with the last one standing - Dustie. Dustie is my very first bunnie. Ironically, he is also the last one alive.    He loves daydreaming.    Hello people!  Dustie does not stay with me currently. Since I moved out to an apartment, he stays at my dad's house because he would then have a garden to stretch his legs on and also he will not have to be couped up all day in the empty apartment when I'm working.  But since the climax of the bunnie murders, Dustie has to be kept inside his wooden house at night now. I have decided to take him down with me to KL when I find a place of my own. He will have to bear the house arrest for a little while. If you ask me, after what he has witnessed, I'm sure he welcomes that.  So I guess I would really have to hurry up on looking for a place in KL.  *sigh  So many things to do, so little time.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I woke up yesterday to my mobile ringing. Fogged mind and sleepy eyed, I mumbled "Hello?". It was my dad.  Dad, "Hello. Are you still sleeping? Don't you have to work?" Me, "Uh..urm...dad? Uh, yeah sleeping. Working later. What is it?" Dad, "Peanut got attacked by a stray cat. It doesn't look good." Me, "WHAT??!!!" Dad, "Yeah. I just called your brother. I think he will take him to the vet." Me, "Uh. Ok. I will come along." Dad, "What??? Don't you have to work.  NO.  You go to work and let your brother handle it. There's nothing you can do anyway. Don't piss off your employers." Me, "But dad......I want to come." Dad, "No. You get your butt to the office." Me, "Yeah ok. I'll call brother now. Bye dad." Dad, "Yeah. Bye."  *click   Brother brought the bunnie to the vet. And I met them there. She really looked bad. Blood all over. She was limp and wheezing in pain. My heart broke. And the smell...oh god, the smell of blood was overwhelming. I controlled myself from throwing up.  The vet cleaned her up. 3 puncture wounds to the neck, just below the ears. Bad internal haemoraging in the thoraxic region. Peanut kept looking at me and my brother. Big eyed...not understanding what is happening. Trying to get out of the little basket we put her in, but she couldn't. She didn't have the strength to. Wheezing in pain all the while.  The vet said survival rate was very low. She was turning blue at the nose and lips. We could clean up the wounds and apply medication. At any rate, it would only be a matter of days before her body shuts down.  My brother and I looked at each other. We have discussed this before meeting at the clinic. This is   it  .  Me, "I think we should put her to sleep & end everything." Doc, "Yes, it is the best option." Me, "Yes, I don't want her in pain anymore." Bro, "Uh huh." Me, "Will it hurt her?" Bro, "How is it done?" Doc, "It will be quick. Depending on the individual. It shuts down the vital organs...the brain, the heart." Me, "Ok. Do it."  The injection was given to the veins in her ears. Before even half the solution was administered, her body gave a small jerk, her eyes rolled and her head tilted to the back. Within 5 seconds, the wheezing stopped.    Goodbye, Peanut. We will miss you. Heaven is definitely a better place to be in. You can eat all the carrots you want now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      3 words. "Too much alcohol."  4 days of downing alcohol of sorts is enough to last me for the next 2 months. Friends from KL up in Penang.  Drink up . My farewell clubbing night.  Drink up . Beach bbq.  Drink up . Friend from India in Penang.  Drink up . There seems to be a million and one reasons to grab a drink. But all in all, it was a good weekend for me.  *yam seng   We got ourselves a room in Parkroyal at Bt. Ferringhi beach. Did some swimming and fell asleep on the deckchair by the beach. Woke up in time to witness the setting sun in front me, nestled by clouds, the sea, the hills and sandy beach. Picturesque. I'm wondering why I never did this more often since I stay on an island. As with all regrets, it comes too late. I will be moving to the big city in less than 2 weeks and the closest beach I can get over there is Port Dickson. Which I heard isn't even a beach. Just sand and polluted pools of water. Well, looks like I'd just have to come home more often.  Yes, I must tell you about this onion ritual. We were worried that it would rain that Saturday night. So Kris mentioned this anti-rain ritual. If you put an onion outside, it will drive away the grey clouds. Her bf laughed. I pondered. I was in Langkawi Island earlier this month for a wedding. They performed the same ritual because it was raining for a week and that would really spoil the wedding plans. So they scattered onions on the beach....and prayed hard.  Waalaaaa!  NO rain.  So me and the girls requested for an onion from the hotel restaurant. The looks we got from the waitresses were one of sheer madness. We carried Mr. Onion, walked to the beach picked a spot for the BBQ and planted Mr. Onion firmly on a mound of sand. The beach boys were laughing at us. We didn't care. And it didn't rain.    Anne, me and Mr. Onion  We had a blast of a time. Lots of carbonised chicken wings, black peppered sausages, toasted marshmallows, satay, 5 litres of wine, 2 bottles of whisky, 1 bottle of tequila and way too much beer. Lethal combination for a small group of 18 and with only 10 drinkers. Bloody alcoholics we are! I stayed far, far away from the tequila. Hide the salt and lemon!!!    Raj, fire the coals! We are hungry!  Surprisingly, there were no casualties of alcohol puking. Unfortunately, Queen Anne got food poisoning and had to get 3 jabs to her butt to control the outflow of liquids.  Poor girl. Must have been the uncooked chicken wings, partnered with the insane mixing of spirits...like I said - lethal combination and she paid the price. I feel bad. She took the bus from KL to Penang just for the weekend, and she had to be the one to get sick. Nice people should not get food poisoning. They should just get drunk.    We should do this more often. I will miss these beautiful people when I'm away.  P/S : It was a cloudy day...I didn't get burnt! Hip hip hooray!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was in Langkawi a few weeks ago & went on my first sailing trip. It was great. Nothing but you, me and the big blue ocean, sun, sea and salty breeze. Sounds euphoric.  Reality check. After effects of the sun.  Whoa. The tan looked so good for a week BEFORE I started to peel. I look like a freak right now, flaking pieces of skin everywhere I go. I don't know why, but my shoulders peeled and revealed this streaky white lines which reminds me of elephant skin texture. For the life of me, can somebody please tell me what is happening? My colleagues tell me it's stretch marks. On my shoulders??? That can't be right. It was never there before...plus how can anybody ever have stretch marks on their shoulders? It's ridiculous. I'm going to ask my doctor about this.  I have freckles. I like it, they remind me of cabbage patch dolls. My mom hates it. Naturally, with the overdose of sun, my freckles decided to make their presence felt.   Ok, now let me tell you a little about mom. Since forever, mom has been very particular about our complexion. Mosquitoe bites - do not scratch. Scars - apply vitamin E. Complexion must be clear. Perfect. Porcelain.  As expected, when I got home from my trip - tan and all - my mom was horrified and kicked a big fuss about my over-exposure to the sun. But I  like   being tanned.  *sulk   Giving in to her persistent pestering, I agreed to undergo this skin regime. Since I was peeling anyway, I thought why not? There is this serum, toner, milk cleanser and special block of black soap which is supposedly packed with highly concentrated vitamin A of sorts.  I think the serum and toner have AHA in it. Technically, it's supposed to strip the first layer of skin off so that I will retain a healthier complexion. Out goes the sunburnt layer. But oh my lordy!, the process is ridiculously painful. The damn serum stings the skin.  I have heard of the wonders of AHA peel, however I am feeling nowhere near wonderful right now. I have no idea why women voluntarily go through this torture to achieve the 'lovelier, fairer' skin. I blame the mass advertisements advocating the fairer is better trend.  Alright, so I may sound like a cynic. But it's really difficult to sound cheerful when I have this constant smarting feeling on my face. This will be the last time I'm 2ft near anything with the alphabets A-H-A.  Tomorrow I'm going to the beach. My colleagues are celebrating my farewell. Oh nooOOOoooo. Beach. Sun. Pool. Sea. (* hands gripping seat, sweat dripping, knuckles turning white ) What am I going to do? I cannot resist....the...sun...and water....  Note to self. Remember to slap on 2 inches thick of sunscreen and pray I don't end up with a second sunburn.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Finally. My own blog. Amen.  For months now I've been reading other people's blog. Been meaning to register myself somewhere, but the sites I found were either paying sites, hideous templates or require one to have an existing personal site up and running. And today I stumbled upon blogger.com. Perfect. Pity they don't allow uploading of pics. Well beggers can't be choosers.  *stop complaining, moo   Who is Miss Stupid? This little madam from Germany is my  acting   supervisor at work. Let me tell you a little about her. She comes to Malaysia with the white man's burden on her shoulders and thinks she's God's gift to the company. I say, if you don't like it here - GO BACK TO YOUR COUNTRY! I could go on and on about her but I won't. I will be banned from this site with all the vulgarities which will come spewing out of my mouth.  So anyway, last week I tendered my resignation and I've been put in the coldroom eversince. No projects. No more phonecalls or emails coming in. "Wake up. Come to the office. Swipe my card. Switch on my PC. Surf the net. Cig break. Reply personal emails. Cig break. Surf the net. Lunch time. Surf the net. Cig break. Chat with friends. Swipe my card. Go home."  Wait a minute. What am I complaining about? This is bliss and I'm getting PAID for it. * smile   I'm going to enjoy every minute of the next 2 weeks before I start in my new company. Work will start pouring in. And life will be back to normal.  Which reminds me. I've got to start packing my clothes for KL.  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's been a while now. I have been in denial. It seems like I'm being really pathetic. Maybe it's  really  time to let go. It's 11:33pm &amp; I'm still at the office. Something is definitely not right.    "You ask me, how am I?  Well I'm still standing, aren't I?  That's something, that's one thing that's gone my way  It's so hard, to go out, like everything's ok now  When inside, I still cry for yesterday."   -"Unhappy Anniversary," Vitamin C       "The depth of darkness to which you can descend and still live is an exact measure of the height to which you can aspire to reach."   -Laurens Van du Post 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had free tickets to watch the premiere of Spiderman 2 last night with  urlLink Psycommotion . It was alright but I was disappointed that they focused and spent so much time on presenting poor Peter Parker as this lost, disoriented, clumsy mortal. And yes, the comparison of his agility and strength as Spidey compared to his mere human self was strongly portrayed.  *spoken icily, "I get the picture already now get on with it."   Since I headed to the cinema straight from work, I was a little tired by the time the movie started at 9:30pm. The first half of the movie was like this never-ending forlorn love triangle between Spidey, MJ & the NASA space boy, James. It felt like I was transported back in time to my teenage years where I read soppy story books about the 'geek meets superchick, falls in love and struggles to tell her truth, all the while making a complete fool of himself through his shyness and clumsiness.' But he's Spiderman for Pete's sake! I was really deciding whether I should catch a 15min shut eye and wake up in time for the action to start.    Spidey:  "Up yours, space boy. MJ is mine!!!"    Doc Orc: "I broke my spine & signed up for an experimental human powered multi-armed vacumm cleaner experiment."  I found this link online. A Spiderman spoof which was supposedly aired during the MTV Awards, last year I presume. My temporary desktop has no audio function, hence I cannot appreciate the full effect of this clip. You guys have a look and tell me how it is. I will view it again when my laptop arrives - if at all.  urlLink " target="_blank">Spiderman Parody  featuring Sarah Michelle Gellar and Jack Black from Tenacious D. Buckle your seats, boys & girls. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The weirdest thing happened this morning. The carpark attendant complimented that my handbag was nice. I said thank you in astonishment. Man, this guy's got taste! I've had compliments from female friends....but one from a carpark attendant is the first for me. It's a strange world out there.  I had a fabulous weekend of gastronomical and alcholic frenzy. A good friend working in India was in town on Friday night, so we met up for dinner at  urlLink Le Bouchon , French cuisine. Absolutely to be recommended.  La nourriture et l'ambiance étaient excellents!     The entrance to Le Bouchon in Changkat Bukit Bintang.     Accueil! Accueil!     Al fresco dining under the stars if it's not raining.    Another section of the al fresco dining area.    The cosy dining area inside.  On Saturday, I had this superb cod entreé at Bon Bon Brasserie with Hafiz. (My galfren had lunch here once and saw Dr.M himself lunching with his mates here. Hmmm. This joint should be quite good then.)     Bon Bon in Bangsar  And after dinner, we adjourned to  urlLink Telawi St. Bistro  to meet his friends. Guess who was there? It was Melissa, the Ponds' girl. I only saw the show once, but it's a short TV series sponsored by Ponds after their successful campaign with the cinema-holding-hands advertisement. (*I think. I'm not sure.) I'm a lousy TV viewer. As I grow older, it seems like staring at the idiot box really makes me feel like one. I'm selective about what I watch nowadays.  Ooh...uppity uppity little me.   Melissa is as cute as she looks on TV. And she's really nice as well in person, so that made a pleasant meet. After a few drinks, we headed off to Bar Flam a few doors away. One of the girls who was with us, her old high school friend was having a birthday bash there. So we all made our way there and said necessary formalities, hello, hi, happy birthday, hey, how are you, whatcha doin....yada yada. I didn't know a single soul there. Thank goodness for Melissa and Hafiz. We hung on to each other and our drinks like life jackets in a stormy sea.  15 litres of whisky. It didn't take us long to loosen up and soon everybody was chummy with everybody else.  Hahaha . The music wasn't something to shout about. They remix commercial hits and try to make them danceable. Sorry matey, not my thing. So it was a lot of drinking and "hello, how are yous?" goin on the whole night.  At one point, I felt a little dehydrated, so I walked over to the bar to ask for some water, and this guy from a table next to it talked to me. I graciously accepted the drink and chatted. For the life of me, I can't remember what we talked about, but it seems like there was lot of chatting going on. I only remember taking one drink, but my friends who were watching me swore I took at least 3-4 whiskys at the table. Did I? Did I? Fcuk. I don't remember.   I stood up, excused myself, thanked him for the drink and walked back to my friends' table. I thought I was still ok. I wasn't even tipsy or anything. Apprently I must be. Because 15mins later, I was puking my guts out in the toilet.  *maniacal laughter   And  that  was the end of an alcoholic frenzy night for me. Verdict? A good night out despite the anti-gravity gut wrenching process.    Do not under estimate the power of this little glass.  P/S: Maybe I should have gone easy on the double shots.  *wink 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Can somebody please tell me why my June posts are in italics? Aargh. They look fine in my preview....but why is it all screwed up in the actual webpage? Frustrating.  Did I tell you, I'll be getting my laptop next week? Woohoo. I can't wait. I'm so glad my company agreed to get me a laptop instead of a desktop. This means I don't have to fork out extra money to get a laptop...that saves me a whooping RM4k - minimum.  *skippity hop hop ala Mary Poppins style    *yawn  I'm so exhausted right now. I'm counting the minutes to 6:30pm, that's an hour away. I have to fetch my housemate on the way home at 7pm. I came back to the office last night at 12.30am (after spending half an hour getting lost in Bandar Tun Razak's confusing maze of a housing estate while making my way back to KL from Sunway), bought  maggi goreng  from the  mamak  opposite my office. Tipsy and hungry, I barged into the office to finish off and print out some documents for my morning meetings.  After that I went to Paddie's apartment to collect my Levis which I left there.  Cik Pelupa  forgot to pack her jeans while moving out. So anyway, Paddie was in a good mood last night. We chatted abit & I fell asleep while he was watching Germany vs. Czechoslovakia. Germany lost!  *wolf whistle - pheweet!  I'm sorry, I have not yet recovered from my emotional distressed inflicted by my previous company. I am scarred for life. Should I sue them? Hmmm.  Yeah, so sleepyhead me woke up at 6am and drove home to shower. Paddie said I could just continue sleeping and push off for work later in the morning. Yeah, don't I wish. But I had 2 morning meetings with company directors and I can't possibly walk into a meeting clad in a  Harley Davidson baby-T and black linen pants . Hello?!  So anyway...after the 2 meetings, my adrenalin rush sobered up & I'm all pooped. I've just finished the whole bloody pack of biscuits just to stay awake. * groan ....and I was  supposed  to stay off carbohydrates..... shite ......  Tomorrow....I  must  cut down on the bloody fat building steroids disguised as carbohydrates. Help, I cannot keep my eyes open much longer. This is crazy....the only reason I'm bloggin continuously is to stay awake. 5:22pm..... tick tock tick tock ....an hour more to kill....what shall I do.....?    The pussykat is sleepy....*yaaawn.....stretch.....
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last night I was in PJ to drop a colleague off to collect her car from the Proton Service Workshop because she was feeling sick and I didn't want her to take the taxi from the office all the way there. It was late afternoon and I thought I might as well hang out around there until the traffic jam clears up in KL, then I'd pop back into the office in the evening to finish off some work. So I called up my old friend,  urlLink Psycommotion  , and we met up in Sunway for a drink.  Well,  a  drink ended up to be 10 (*or was it 11, honestly I can't remember) bottles of Carlsberg & stretched to 11:30pm. One of the highlights of the night was his theory on 'The Alpha Male'. It all started when I was wailing about being stupid for sticking on to Mr. Paddlepop & although I appear  ganas  (*that's what everyone tells me) with the " fcuk off, don't mess with me because i'm in control " look, deep down, I secretly want to be controlled - to a certain degree - by the man of my choice.   urlLink Psycommotion  immediately responded with, " It's an Alpha Male syndrome. In every group, there is always the Alpha Male who is the baddest, loudest male & who would be the leader of the pack. And as much of a jerk he would be, it would be the Alpha Male who would also get all the chicks. The nice guys are passed over. "  You know what, he could be right. Ohmygod. So now the baffling revelation - why do nice girls like bad boys? Each one of us have our answers to this question. To each her own....but I guess we all like a little bit of the 'edge'. Most of the time, the 'edge' proves to be more damaging to our peace of minds than watching Tamil porn all day long.   "> Burp. Icecream is yum...  What flavour is the Alpha Male today? I'd say it's TomYam Paddlepop because he has flown into Bangkok this afternoon for a wedding party and won't be back until Monday. Talk about having fun. I hate him.  *rah rah rah 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Apartment viewing on Friday night went well. I liked the unit. RM750.00 for the whole place. New, clean, tiled with a  hob  & hood!!! Woohooo! The place is a dream already. It sits on a hill too and it's really lovely. Now comes the confusing part. Do I stay with the girls and save a little bit of money....or do I just stay on my own?  *fluttering eyelashes in confusing thoughts   So anyway, I moved out of IceKing's crib last Saturday. Had an emotional outburst, and I decided to pack up and leave...he got pissed off - naturally - and said I was making a drama out of the whole thing. Who? Me? Where?  I packed up and left with a Dear John letter left on his pillow. Ok, so it wasn't a Dear John letter, I just said thank you. Hey! Drama Queens can be polite too, aye. I figured this was ridiculous. I don't see him at all and we don't talk. The space invasion thing must be really getting to him. I think he really needed his space back, and I asked him. He confirmed my suspicions. I saw a problem and I solved it. Two words. "Move out."  And so I moved. Hey Ho. He was being Mr. Paddlepoppy aka. MoodyHead ( *you know how Paddlepop icecream has a million different colors all in one stick? it reminds me of IceKing, you'll never know what colour the next lick will bring you ) that day, and I was under this humongous emotional strain for the last 2 weeks. So I guess Saturday morning proved to be the ripe time for the debut of the Drama Queen. He wasn't even home when I got my butt out of his house. Which, thinking back, could probably be why he got even more cheese off from his already bad mood because he was working and couldn't talk some sense into me. I think.  So, now I'm staying with my girlfriend and we are trying to look for a place to move to. However, the search is getting very tiresome and exhausting. The prices of the places we want is just way beyond our budget. Compromises, compromises.....  Things improved on Sunday. Paddlepop & I met up and we sorted things out. He was a little more apologetic and understanding. I told him I'm cool with a very mellow arrangement. He's cool with that too. I don't know how this arrangement will develope and I guess only time will tell. He is emotionally dysfunctional and the only way this will ever work is that I practice lots and lots of patience. May God have mercy on me.  I don't know why, if it was any other guy - I would have asked him to fcuk off from my life. But somehow...I'm drawn to this little moody Paddlepop. We sealed the deal with a hug and a kiss. A good start & a hell of of patience. Pray hard.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday, I drove around the area to check out some places where I could potentially rent. Decent (*I'm not even saying they are nice),  decent  apartments without furnishing cost RM1k. Good lord. Would I have to work part-time in McDonalds to subsidize my accommodation?  *groan   I found a place, up in the hills surrounded by lush, green trees. These units were previously housing for rubbertappers or rubber estate engineers whatever. They look old, but they have the retro appeal. Talked to the security guards. They told me there are alot of empty units. The whole block of studio apartments (1 room) were empty. I was EXCITED. Took down the number of the marketing lady, called her only to find out that the reason those units were empty was that the ground floor had started cracking and they had to evacuate everybody out of the whole block. My heart sank to the bottom of the hill.  I would have been so elated if I could have a place here. I would work 2 shifts at McDonalds and Pizza Hut if I had to. Damn.  Today will be the beginning of my house hunting adventure. I will be viewing 2 units of apartments tonight. They will cost me quite abit to stay alone, but if I want to remain staying in this suburb, I have no choice. Going off now to see one of the units. I hope it's nice.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, after my meeting I decided to pop in my godfather's office for a surprise visit since it was lunch time. Coincidentally, his office is only 10 minutes away from my office. Ha.  It was good to see them. These are people who have known me since I was born. They are very good friends of my parents and they became my godparents when I was born in England and the four of them were working in the UK. When I was younger, godmom used to pamper me with girlie gifts. As I grew older, we saw less of each other. Perhaps now is the time to rekindle my relationship with them.  Godfather suggested that I stay in the apartments near his bungalow. It's kinda far. Probably an additional 15mins (without trafic jam) from the city and additional 30mins (with jam, if I'm lucky). However, the good thing is that I will be able to stay on my own (because rental is cheap there since it's considered the outskirts of the city) and simultaneously, I also have the comfort of knowing that my godparents are only a stone's throw away. And in the case of any emergency or if I get sick, they can just come over.  Of course....I wonder also whether I could use their washing machine, so I don't have to buy one myself.  Tee hee hee .  Oh, but Chloe is going to  kill  me. I have been so fickle minded about where I want to stay for the past 2 weeks. She will need to rearrange the requirements for the apartment we were planning to rent together. Chloe is my bestfriend, my second sister. But she will kill me all the same. How can I break the news to her in a nice way..... *hmmmmm   IceKing came home at 6:30am this morning and left for Singapore with his team of designers at 10am. He must be rushing for a job. Passed by his office on the way home last night at 2am. No, I did  NOT  purposely spy on him. His office is located on the main road which I use to go home. Saw all the lights switched on and figured they must be working through the night again. Jackpot!  Oh well. I''ll be sleeping alone tonite.  Stay away boogie man . And tomorrow, I will have to drive alone to another suburb for a meeting at 9:30am. I hope I will not get lost. Going to walk to Kinokuniya to buy the KL city map and pray real hard.  I'm off to meet a friend for dinner now. But first, buy a map.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have a club. It's called the Society for Magnets of Trouble. Membership is free, members can come and go as they wish and penalty charges are not applicable for members who quit the club. I am the President and this morning, I have recruited my first member. He insists that he doesn't want to be a member. But it seems like he fulfills all the requirements to be a member, so I told him he is a temporary member until he solves his troubles. Let's call him Nyamuk Aedes.  You see, people like him & me seem to endlessly attract trouble. Because he also has a bucket full of a complicated love life, he seems to understand whenever I needed a shoulder to cry on. He  almost  never judged me. He tries anyway. Good effort!  Last weekend, he just sat there listening to me rant on and on about IceKing. It was exactly what I needed I guess. A friend who listens and understands. I don't need somebody to tell me what to do. I KNOW what I have to do. I just need somebody to listen to me. I'm not sure whether I return the favour to him, because I although I try very hard to listen and shut up, I have a tendency to give him a piece of my mind whenever he tells me his problems.  I know you're reading this , "If I go overboard, just ask me to shut up ok?"  For all the times you have lent a listening ear to me, thank you. If you think you will be happy spending the rest of your life with your current gf, I really think you should give it one last chance. Afterall, there is nothing to lose at this point even if you don't win. At least you know you had given it your all should your plans fall apart - no regrets!  I hope to lose you as a member soon. As for me, I think it's a genetic curse. I don't go looking for trouble, they come looking for me. I can't help it. Sometimes, I feel as if I have this permanent stamp on my forehead which says "Free parking for troubles."  But I guess I'm just a whiner. Despite the certain lows in my life, I am grateful for everything which I have, the friends & family I love whom have helped me and everything nice which have happened to me.   Amen.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It had been a lovely past couple of days. First, IceKing made a feeble attempt to redeem himself and second, I went back to Penang for the weekend. Yay!  Last week, he actually came home early the day after the volcanic sms (* surprise, surprise ). And on Friday, I went back to see my sister who was back home from Singapore and disappeared from the city for the weekend. It felt so good to be home. I missed my mom and my own bed (*and shower room) so much!  Found out that some old high school friends who are working in KL have decided to go back to Penang every month, so all of us could car pool together. This is good. I never really enjoyed bus rides anyway. So I guess I will be home rather regularly. Aptly put by Bill, technically speaking, if we go back every month, we only see our parents 12 times in a year...and statistically, it's the  least  I could do for my lonely mommie.  Of course, later on in the car ride, I also found out that Bill recently got himself a Penang gf...which explains the regular trips back to the little island. Which also makes me wonder whether the filial child explanation holds true.  *cynical laugh   Mom, sis and I spent girly escapades picking out accessories for sister's Nov wedding and finalising the wedding dinner arrangements with the hotel. We decided it wasn't necessary to wear gold, so sis & I settled for chokers. Sis was a white choker with silk flowers and Swaroski crystals, mine was a blue butterfly diamante choker on a baby blue ribbon. Mom would look funny with a choker at 57. So she got herself a conventional necklace and earring set. Lovely, nothing like a shopping spree to cure all emotional problems. How bimbo can I get? I cease to surprise myself sometimes.  *smirk   Arrived in KL last night and was greeted by a big hug and a peck. Nothing to shout about, but an improvement nevertheless. I guess my weekend disappearance proved to be a good thing. I wonder whether he missed my presence over the weekend. I hope it will be a good week ahead. Everyday turns a new page in my life....sometimes it's a horror flick, but this week, please let it be an Enid Blyton story. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "To love means to commit oneself without guarantee, to give oneself completely in the hope that our love will produce love in the loved person. Love is an act of faith, and whoever is of little faith is also of little love." -Erich Fromm  I'm reading Paulo Coelho's Eleven Minutes at the moment. It's about this Brazilian girl who goes off to Switzerland in search of adventure, but ended up a prostitute and how she copes with this and her struggles with the concept of love. She gets very idealistic on the ability to create a distance between loving a person and not wanting to own the person. (*see excerpt below) Easier said than done, if you ask me.  *tsk tsk   Love fails you when you want something out of it. Theoretically,  I think it's true, the best kind of love is to love without expectations or anything in return. But  HONESTLY , whoever can do THAT? Who...who can?     Excerpt from Eleven Minutes.  "All my life, I thought of love as some kind of voluntary enslavement. Well, that’s a lie: freedom only exists when love is present. The person who gives him or herself wholly, the person who feels freest, is the person who loves most wholeheartedly.  And the person who loves wholeheartedly feels free.  That is why, regardless of what I might experience, do or learn, nothing makes sense. I hope this time passes quickly, so that I can resume my search for myself – in the form of a man who understands me and does not make me suffer.  But what am I saying? In love, no one can harm anyone else; we are each of us responsible for our own feelings and cannot blame someone else for what we feel.  It hurt when I lost each of the various men I fell in love with. Now, though, I am convinced that no one loses anyone, because no one owns anyone.  That is the true experience of freedom: having the most important thing in the world without owning it."   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "To care about someone is to give them the power to hurt you." -Matt Margolis  By accident, I saw  his  creditcard bill laying on the table. Picked it up and saw that he was in Penang. I didn't know that. He gave no indication that he was coming up to Penang the weekend just before I drove down to KL. A room checked in for 2 guests.  I went berserk. What do you mean 2 guests? My emotions catapulted from being angry to sad to upset. And then I cried. Alone. What should I do now? I can't just ask him about it because I wasn't supposed to rummage through other people's mail -  even if the envelope was  not  sealed . And I normally don't do this at all. My parents brought me up to respect other people's privacy...but the envelope with the Penang hotel address was too tempting to resist. And I can't even ask him who it was because we only agreed to see each other regularly, not exclusively. So I guess, the territorial pussycat has to keep her mouth shut.  Couldn't take it anymore, sent IceKing a message yesterday. Told him I like him, but I'm not one to be begging for affection. I haven't had a decent conversation with him since I arrived. He goes out with his friends and I go out with my own friends. We see each other only in the wee hours of the morning in the grogginess of slumber and when I'm off to work, he's still sleeping. When he comes home, I'm in bed already.   He didn't reply my message. But when he climbed into bed last night, I think he tried to redeem himself. He appeared concerned over my emotional state of mind and concluded that I was just stressed out. I was cheesed off and mumbled some mono-reply. What does he expect? It was 5 in the fcuking morning. Even if I had some disastrous emotional malfunction, that question came a tad too late.  Anger!   Stressed out.  Stressed out?  Of course I'm stressed out.  *jeez 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I started work in my new company. I was told to report in at 8am. So I arrived at 8am, only to find bolted doors and a very confused me staring at the big, fat lock in astonishment. "Did I get the right building? Did I get the right floor? Did I get the right unit?" Check check & check. Affirmative. I'm definitely at the right place.  Called my colleague-to-be. Office opens at 9am. Can anybody feel any   stupier  ? The girl who informed me must have made a mistake. So I went downstairs, bought The Star and a bottle of water. Sat by the water fountain and killed an hour, accompanied by the nation's latest news, a few cigarettes and the sound of water. For the first time in yonks, I was reading the papers early in the morning. Not too bad a start.  Obediently went upstairs at 9am. This is a temporary office, shared by 2 sister companies...my colleagues are not here. I sit and I wait some more. They strolled in at 9:30am. [* mental note to self : No.1 Flexi hours & No.2 No swiping of bloody employee tags. Yay! ]  There are some problems moving into the new office, so it looks like I'll be stuck in the temporary office for at least a month...but we're looking at two - realistically. Hmmm. And I don't have my own PC yet. Boohoohoo. They are in the midst of ordering it. I'm borrowing somebody else's PC to check my mails now. She's not in the office. What happens when she comes back? I refuse to do my work in hardcopy, only to transfer it to the PC later. I refuse! I rebel!  *sigh   There are alot of girls in this office. So far, pretty friendly. Good. But where  are  the boys? Tee hee hee.  I drove in last Friday. Moved into IceKing's place. Spent the whole weekend hanging out with my bestfriend, Chloe. Couldn't resist and bought some shoes. Wearing my new shoes to work and they cut my feet.  *pout  We watched The Day After Tomorrow. I thought it was pretty good an attempt for an American film to be satirical of itself. I was hoping to watch more ppl freeze in 3 seconds when the eye of the storm moves above you. That was cool. So is IceKing. Temperature check -20 degrees C. No change.  I'm surrounded by friends and colleagues, but I feel lonely. I miss my mom.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      At this age...I really don't want to keep on playing this game. I don't want guess what the other person is feeling or thinking. And it's frustrating. I'm not 18 anymore. I don't have the energy for that kind of sulking-guessing-one liner situation.  Ok the truth is...I think I fancy  him . I think he likes me too. But how much, I don't know. And that's what makes me want to bang my head on the wall.  *thud thud  And he doesn't make it easy for me to interpret his actions...We used to have at least one short conversation a day. It reduced to text messaging. That's fine too.  Sometimes the IceKing melts a little and I get all excited. But I don't want an IceKing. It's so fcukin tiring....it's exhausting.  Yesterday, a friend of mine asked me. "If you had ONE wish. What would you want?" I thought about it for a minute and answered, "I want to always be happy." I wanted to type I want a digital camera (*been eyeing one for a long time now, just can't decide which one to get), I want a Baby Jaguar, I want a laptop.   The thing is - I have everything I  need  but I want a million other things. How many out of these millions do I have to fulfill to be happy? I figured, more important than getting what I want....is to be happy.  There are many ways to be happy. I pray that I will find solace in the simplest one. Until then, I must find a way to melt the IceKing.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dustie is not eating. What am I going to do?  I'm at my dad's house. The maid tells me the rabbit is refusing food. This not good news.  I think he is depressed. I pick him up. Cuddle him. He falls asleep in my arms. But he won't eat.  Somebody tell me what to do....please....
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I'm so sleepy and so friggin' tired...and I can't even go home yet because I have to attend this  exclusive  screening of 'Bloom', a film based on Jame Joyce's  Ulysses  at the Australian High Comm. organised by the Irish Embassy. Under normal circumstances, I would have been more than happy to go...however today I woke up from a nightmare, crying. I was so traumatised by the dream that I could not bring myself to fall back to slumber and continued sobbing in bed until my nose got blocked.     &nbsp;   So I got up and had a ciggarette. Looked at my mobile, it was 6:30am. Decided to take a hot shower and get ready for work.     &nbsp;   7:00am. I'm all dressed....now   what  ? Sherene has to go to court today. She was supposed to leave the apartment by 7:30am. She's still sleeping. Woke her up.     &nbsp;   7:30am. I don't have the keys to the KLCC office. No fcukin' point going to work early because nobody works early there. Maybe I will have breakfast first. Grabbed car keys. Chloe asked me where I was going. To have breakfast. Where? I don't know yet. Why don't you just eat at home? By the time you cook and eat, it'll be just nice to get to work. Hmmm...good idea.     &nbsp;   7:40am. Took out some pseudo crabsticks and a packet of maggi mi. Made breakfast.     &nbsp;   7:50am. Ate breakfast out in the balcony over looking KL's skyline.     &nbsp;   8:05am. Chloe called. The road is jammed. Take the Bangsar route to town. Ok.     &nbsp;   8:40am. Put on my new shoes. Buckled up. Walked around.  Nah ! Decided a closed toe slingback would look more decent in a&nbsp;high comm.&nbsp;than a 3" stiletto. Changed shoes. Nobody takes a bimbo seriously. Wrong image to project in such a group of people.     &nbsp;   8:50am. Decided to use the Federal Highway. Shouldn't be jammed by now. I was right. Smooth flow. Good.     &nbsp;   9:30am. Walked into the office.     &nbsp;   10:00am. Fatigue started to hit me...so tired. So sleepy. Meetings will start soon. And I have 2 today.  Dang !     &nbsp;   6:40pm. There! Just sent off my business proposal to my boss who's in Langkawi. Decided I'd update my blog.     &nbsp;   6:48pm. Feeling a little peckish. Should I walk down to the mall and grab some food? What if they serve finger food later? Hmmm....think I'll just make my favourite Milo&nbsp;Nestum drink. Mmmm. Yum...this is so good.     &nbsp;   7:00pm. It's been 12 and a half hours since I've been awake. Most of my colleagues are leaving. There's a couch right behind me....hmmmmmm, should I or  should I ? Muwahaha. I hope the event won't end too late tonight....rather, I hope I don't accidentally fall asleep in the cool, dark room...AND start snoring. That would be the pits man! Another hour before I start to make my way to the event. Thank god it's just across the road...but I'll drive there anyway and park inside the high comm. With all the funny murders happening around town, a girl out alone can't be too safe nowadays. But the truth is...I'm just too  lazy  to walk back to my car at the end of the night.     &nbsp;   7:05pm *yawn....time can't get any slower than this.     
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Little stars on a field trip.    &nbsp;  It turned to be a better Sunday and a splendid Monday. Woke up a little more grounded after the lousy Saturday night, cleaned Chloe's fish tank and my car. I haven't washed it since I arrived in KL and I'm getting embarrassed driving it around with all the dust and rain marks all over my car. Had dinner at Paddlepop's house and woke up feeling happy on a Monday morning.    &nbsp;  A little foolish and simple, but to each his own. As long as one is happy, I guess sometimes it doesn't matter how happiness is achieved. Anybody who tells me otherwise can fcuk off.  *grrr     &nbsp;  It couldn't get better. The giant French-Australian joint venture&nbsp;company called me up after 3 bloody months and asked me whether I'm still interested to join them. I say, make me an offer and we'll take it from there.    &nbsp;  Talk about an ego boosting trip. So today, I just want to immerse myself in the self- satisfaction that my career market value still means something to corporate giants and the simple fact that I had a great evening last night.    &nbsp;   *smile ...it's been a while since I have felt this way...and it feels damn good.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I guess one of the best things about having a laptop is that I can write my blogs at home during instances such as now…on a Saturday night - too exhausted to go out, too restless to sleep. In actual fact this splitting headache has been bothering me since dinner at Chili’s…and I thought maybe after I eat, I would feel better. Wrong. The Monterey Chicken was too big a portion and I was too greedy to stop before it was way too much. Chloe & gang went to watch i-Robot, I gave it a miss.   So I went off on my own, wanting to go home…and I needed to pee. KLCC’s toilet renovation is taking a ridiculously long time. What are they construction? Niagara Falls toilet bowls?  Jeez. *rolling eyes    I must remember to not be adventurous on foreign lands when I’m tired and when it’s bloody midnight. Can’t believe I took the wrong turning at NPE and ended up paying a freakin’ RM3.20 toll just to make a bloody U-turn. Stupid stupid.   Came home, too lazy to shower…but I decided I should. I’m so sticky and a shower should help with the headache. Wrong again. Here I am in my jammies and I still have a headache.  *groan    YEL was telling us a story over dinner the other night at Opus. She has a male friend who has some problems with his girlfriend. When asked why he doesn’t address the problems, his stand was to just let it be and hope it will go away. Apparently males have a tendency to do this…   This triggered a fearful realization. Perhaps I am a problem he hopes will go away if he just ignores it.    Sigh . Get over it, girl.  But I can’t…or I won’t. I don’t know.  I fear…this is one major emotional screw up which will scar me for a long time to come. It haunts my conscious thoughts &amp; it entwines itself in my dreams…my nightmares. I can’t run away from it…I can’t even hide. I feel like a star nebulous bursting with light but trapped in a jar with its lid screwed on too tight. The ray of light shines through the glass but the lid is there, ever reminding…ever watchful…ever tormenting…   Maybe they are right. Maybe I should just shut the fcuk up and get over it. I know I should. Maybe they are right. Perhaps there are nice guys out there & I’m not giving them a chance….because just maybe, I screwed myself in that little fcuking jar and screw the lid tighter every time the little star&nbsp;drops a ray of light&nbsp;   Where is he just when I need him the most? To take away the lid. To stop the haunting. To not wake up from a dream, wishing I had never slept. The little star continues to sulk in her own solace on a Saturday night, and nobody will ever know because her ray shines through the glass.        Feather brained star.   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I'm finally going to get my camera. Wooweee...  A very good Samaritan have generously donated half the cost of my new toy so that I can buy it. God bless him & may he find a wife soon.  Nyuk nyuk .  I've confused myself so many times trying to decide which model I should get because I love squarish designs...and the Casio Exilim Z40 is gorgeous. Sony T1 is like a bimbo, looks good but mutton brains. Pity, coz I would have snapped it up in a second! Oh well...my little red riding shoot makes up for the design dripping in metallic red on steel. That's good enough a compensation. I'm easily pleased.  I will be receiving my baby in 3 weeks time. Muwahaha. Let the world be warned...Miss MiniMoo will be equiped with a camera. *flash *flash    Delirious...  Gosh, I didn't realize that I haven't updated my blog for ages! I guess after my personal promise not to whine anymore...I have also stopped writing that much. That didn't quite turn out right...but...rainbows & sunshine!!! I'm BACK.  Work has been picking up and my time & thoughts are being taken up for more productive and sensible things to do. I also finally got my laptop from the company. That stupid Technical Director was so fcukin mean. I was supposed to get the new laptop, but the bugger decided to take mine and passed me his old IBM. Stupid prick.  Nevermind. Whatever. I'm not going to sweat over the small things in life.  Ohm...ohm...   On a better note...Paddlepop made a recommendation for me to meet the MD of this healthcare company. She needs somebody to help her out. The discussions have been rather positive so far and I have a swarm of butterflies in my stomach being so anxious, excited and nervous at the same time.   I shall not divulge any details...maybe I'm superstitious, but I find that if I tell people my plans, they never work out. So today - I'm keeping my mouth shut. I hope it would be good news.  So the Technical Director can take my new Mimos craptop and stuff it up his arse when I resign. The Purchase Order was approved for a new laptop and it falls under MY budget...hellooOOOOoo!!! How could he bully me and let me use his old one. Meanie.  Ok, I'm off to KLCC to meet Chloe. The sales have started and I just cannot resist walking over from the office. After all, it's a Saturday and I worked until 5:30am last night...I deserve to do some bimbo activity. Cheerio sweetie pies!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last night I went to KL's longest  pasar malam  in Cheras. Interesting...it's like bringing Sungei Wang to the streets. Hahaha. I can't believe the CDs are RM10 for 3. Crazeeee....so much cheaper than Penang and I thought Penang has the cheapest pirated stuff. I'm not ashamed to admit that I'm a strong supporter of piracy! God bless....long live piracy!  Last weekend was spent helping my good friend, Niki, do some filming for her wedding video. It was good...except that I gorged myself silly as well. I ate enough in over the weekend to last me for a week! But I couldn't resist, she kept bringing me to the famous spots...how could I  NOT  eat? HOw? How?  The last one week has been pretty good. A lot of things to do. Alot of things to eat. And of kilos being piled on....  Work is starting to pick up. Which is good because I'm sick of being bored out of my brains in the office. Tonight I'm going for the opening of  urlLink Footsteps  in the  urlLink National Art Gallery . I'm going to meet Alfred - a friend of a friend of mine in Penang.  *I wonder how he looks like.  Anyway, this friend,  urlLink i-Ming , is an artist...so since I'm working in an art gallery I thought it's high time I wet my feet in artshow openings. And  urlLink i-Ming , is nice enough to introduce some of his mates to me. So, anyway Alfred's friend, Ivan Lam is one of the featured artist for  urlLink Footsteps  so hey! why not. I could catch the other exhibition,  urlLink Malaysia Art NOW  as well.   Oh! it's going to be an interesting night...I hope I'll meet nice people there...not those snobby and snotty arty farty divas. Muwahaha. Oooh...I'm excited!     Bus in my soup  by Yusof Majid (Footsteps)     Installations  by Tengku Sabri (Malaysia Art NOW)          Pillar mural series  for Christmas by  urlLink i-Ming 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Farah's getting experimental in Melbourne. I really  have  to get my digital camera soon. It's not fair, I wanna play too.   The Sony Cybershot DSC T1 is gorgeous. I'm in lurrrve.....Can't wait for the next camera fair.   Something is wrong. Why are all the pictures tinted in red? *grrrrrrrr        Woozy.    *yawn...    Dun mess with me today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink      Dissolved Girl  -  urlLink Massive Attack    Shame, such a shame I think I kind of lost myself again Day, yesterday Really should be leaving but I stay  Say, say my name I need a little love to ease the pain I need a little love to ease the pain It's easy to remember when it came  'Cause it feels like I've been I've been here before You are not my savior But I still don't go  Feels like something That I've done before I could fake it But I still want more  Fade, made to fade Passion's overrated anyway Say, say my name I need a little love to ease the pain I need a little love to ease the pain It's easy to remember when it came  'Cause it feels like I've been I've been here before You are not my savior But I still don't go, oh  I feel live something That I've done before I could fake it But I still want more, oh.   urlLink    Massive Attack: Melbourne 2003 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Coming back to KL on a Monday after spending the weekend back home is a torture. When we parked the car at the apartment, this short clip of our conversation captures the essence of my feelings.  Chloe: " Aah! We're home. " Me: " No.  YOU  are home, Chloe.  I  am back in KL. " Chloe:  *laughs  Me:  *silence...no doubt also silently sulking at the same time   I have been eating Maggi mi for dinner quite often lately. Whoever invented the condiments for Indomie's Mi Goreng is a genius, it's my all time favourite flavour. However, I must admit that having 5 packets in 10days is pushing the taste buds a little too far. But this is the consequences of not wanting to go through the hassle of cooking dinner for one person & not wanting to drive another 10km just to buy dinner.  Maggi mi...no matter what brand, is almost like the noodle of the masses. Go anywhere, you can find maggi in all kinds of flavour and style of cooking across all races. Maggi goreng kosong, Maggi goreng & telur kerbau, Maggi in chicken soup, Maggi in prawn soup (Penang hokkien mi), Maggi in  'wan tan mee'  soup. Name it, you can find maggi as subsitute for anything you fancy.    The humble maggi, they even named a hair perm after it.  I remember, when I was in Australia, I actually   craved   for Maggi. I'm such a sick girl. I mean,...like who on earth actually  craves  for Maggi? But I did. I went to Woolsworth, headed straight to the Chinese section and grabbed a couple packets of Maggi...they didn't have Indomie (* darn! ) but did I care? NO. Hahaha. Just give me my Maggi...they had another brand of Mi Goreng and  that  to me then was good enough.  "My maggi & me." (* ring a bell? *wink )  P/S: This is  unbelievable . I stumbled across this website where people actually discuss how to cook Indomie Mi Goreng. I suspect these are staff of the Science Faculty in NUS (National University of Singapore). Check it out. It's rather baffling - really.   urlLink Indomie Mi Goreng Discussion  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Letting go is easier said than done...     The walls we build around us to keep out the sadness also keep out the joy.  - Jim Rohn 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm back on the island!  Woo weee...!  The elation of driving through the Penang bridge, seeing the familiar lights and buildings, crossing the sea illuminated by the moonlight at 12:30am......is something which I cannot describe. The click of my heart that sends this super-neuron to my brain saying - Amy, you are home.  I don't want to go back to KL. Call me a country pumpkin or whatchamacallit  'kampung ah-nya' ...I don't care. I hate the muddy KL water, the polluted air and the terrible mamak food. I'm going to go AWOL from work on Monday.   urlLink Psycommotion  retorted that I should not run home with my tail tucked between my legs. Sounds like a   man   now, doesn't it? Muwahahaha!  Anyway, I told him....but what is there to prove? And WHY do I need to prove anything to anybody? It's plain and simple. I hate it in the big fcukin city. It's true that it's bigger...but how much  better  is it? And honestly, I can't answer that. There's just more of everything there - more restaurants, more pubs, more clubs, more cars, more buildings, more cars, more theaters, more this and more that......  But to me....these are merely superficial  'mores' . It's doesn't make an ounce of an improvement to my lifestyle. In fact, the amount of time I waste sitting on my arse in the jam is enough to quirk me of leaving the office on time for decent dinner hours. And what good is life when I leave the house to work, and come home to sleep....too tired to do anything else?  I have everything I need AND want here. I haven't had a good night's sleep for a few weeks now. I have almost forgotten how that feels like. I am paying for a house which I realize now I am not even able to appreciate.  I am asking myself....why the fcuk did I move down?  *cynical laugh   Looks like I'm going to have to reactivate my resume. Wish me luck....I'm going to come home...by hook or by crook. Fcuk the big city. I'm happy being an Amoi Kampung.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       The stars are shining on me the last few days. I have finally moved into my own room on Monday and I love it. It's cosy, it's me. Sharing a room with Chloe was beginning to stress me out because I miss my privacy and it feels as if I have lost my identity in the place I now call home. Everything around the apartment does not belong to me and totally does not reflect my personality. However this is going to change! HAhah.      My room has been revamped. I even changed the white drape curtains to this transparent gold weaved Indian textile. Now, when I lie on my bed at night in the dark, I can see the sleepy skyline and lights of Old Klang through my NEW curtains because the windows are glass all the way down to the floor. I finally understand why ppl like to have full glass windows.      I brought my hi-fi down from Penang and I can now play any CD I like all night long. I can't sleep without having the music on. And none of my housemates share the same taste for music as me, so it had been quite a distressing month for me to listen to pop music all the time. I can play my Chemical Brothers, or my Underworld, or my Norah Jones whenever I want.  Bliss .      My next project is to revamp the whole apartment. * snigger       It must have been my lucky day yesterday. Two companies have verbally offered me a job as a Brand Manager.  Wow . I'm flabbergasted.      One a French-Australian construction joint venture. The other a Swedish healthcare company. Sometimes I wonder why anybody would trust   me   to handle their branding. I feel so young at times, but I'm probably in denial of my age...perhaps I have aged subconsiously....you think?  Hmmm ....      Of all the people out there who have more experience than me, who have been in the branding line of work for ages...they picked me. It's so unbelievable. I just can't get over it. I'm just so happy that I am actually worth something in the market...for a position nobody my age would ever imagine possible. I am just so grateful. I really am.      It's 7:15pm. Time to scoot off from the office. I'm going to meet Anne for afterwork drinks at Waikiki.      P/S -   Self prayer: Dear God. Please let the offers be real. Please don't play a trick on me and have the companies change their minds before giving me the offer letter. Please. I will not be able to take it. Thank you.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>