<Blog>


<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Marriage  - Should I fear it?  No beating around the bush, lets get straight in!  My Mom thinks I should get married, I say "NO". My relatives think that since I am in the US and still saying "No" to marriage, I must have an American girlfriend! Its almost as if, "Now you have a job, there is nothing more you can do, so get married!" Hmm, if you have someone in your life then its fine, else, not a very nice situation.  I really cant warm up to the whole concept of an "arranged" marriage. I know and understand that in the past, everyone, well, ALMOST everyone did that and they have been pretty successful. The truth is, I am too much of a romantic guy - I want to find the girl of my dreams, fall in love, propose and then marry her.  One of my friends said this about arranged marriages: "specially arranged ones end up as some kind of mechanically comfortable arrangement so you have someone as a spouse - there is usually very little or no passion/love involved". I do not agree completely with this statement - love and passion will develop in time if all goes well but the first part really feels bad: "A mechanically comfortable arrangement"???? Is that really what it is? Am I so desperately lonely that I HAVE to get married, one way or the other? I agree that I do feel lonely at times, I live alone, and once I go out of office I am alone till next morning. But is an arranged marriage the ONLY solution? To marry someone because they come from a good family? I'd rather love and marry someone who has nobody in the world at all and is yearning for some love in her life! My heart just FLATLY refuses to believe that I will not find anyone. I am not a Shahrukh or a Hrithik, but I would like to think that I have my virtues - surely someone is out there??? But when will I find that someone?   Lets examine an arranged marriage situation: boy and girl meet knowing FULL WELL that the ultimate aim of the exercise is to get married. They do not know each other at all. Will they not be at their best behavior and try to hide any vice they might have? I do not have a LOT of experience but I have found people whom I thought were very nice indeed at first seem quite revolting after I got to know them. Is it not too high a risk to take with your life? On the other hand, if you meet by chance, and fall in love after sometime, is it not a better thing because you know the person better?  But as a bitter rival to this statement comes the fact that the divorce rate in the US (Where almost everyone has a love marriage) is much higher than it is at home. People often use this as a supporting statement to advocate arranged marriages. I beg to differ - I feel that it is higher here ONLY because people are more independent - they will NOT accept anything they don’t like. But in India, people adjust a lot, which is a good thing, especially if there are kids. Still, that does not solve my problem. I do not wish to get married out of 'desperation', for want of a better word.   So...I keep saying No and I wait and I wait for her to come...She will! She has to! But When? God only knows! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does anything matter?  We all live our lives doing all kinds of stuff - But what if we didnt? Would it matter? Why do we run after all things material? How would one define "material"?  Our money, our houses, our cars, things we buy in shops, are they all the material things? Is love a "material" thing? The love that one has for one's parents, brothers, sisters, wives and husbands - Is it 'material'?   	Maybe I am wrong, but does "material" refer to anything that is said or done or obtained with a condition on it or with a view of getting something out of it? If thats the case, then I would struggle to find something that is not "material". For even when we love, we expect something out of it, right? Don't we atleast expect the person to return the love? The purists would argue night and day about the concept of "unconditional love" - For a while I thought it existed - I thought there indeed was something called "unconditional love". Maybe I am too much of a materialistic person who looks only at his own gains - But I try my best to keep my love from reducing even when I am disappointed. I do not wish to delve into the personal details, but - there is no decrease in the amount of love that I have for the person/persons, but doesnt the very fact that I get disappointed make me a materialistic person? Am I not disappointed ONLY because I do not get what I expected to get? I am ashamed at my disappointment - ashamed, because I feel that it does not match up to the level of purity that I thought my love had.   	Then we come to the question of what indeed IS eternal - If everything we know and touch and feel is just temporary, why do we all pay so much attention to them? Shouldn't we be spending all the time we have to attain something that is eternal, everlasting - something that will remain constant and untouched through the annals of time?  	We all go about doing our daily chores, laying down our careers, trying to become great people, rich people - but ultimately, does it really matter? I think about what use the world has for me and I realize that the world would be no different without me - So I try my best to help people, I try my best to make a difference, to touch the lives of other people, to do community service - I sign up for every community service event; Its not to prove anything to anyone, but its just to make me feel a little less guilty at having done nothing to improve the state of man. Its just to make me do something which I feel is atleast in part "non-materialistic". I KNOW for a fact that when I help people in the community, people whom I have never seen and whom I will probably never see again, that work is defenitely non-materialistic. And, to think of it now, it gives me so much peace of mind when I come back home, tired after a day of service. But again, does it matter? Does it make a difference?   	We went and built a whole community kitchen in the town of NorthEast, PA - we didnt just supply the money and the materials, we actually BUILT the building together with the townsfolk. At the end of the day, you feel you have accomplished something - something that was done not with a view to impress anyone, not with a view to getting a monetary or professional reward, but something that is totally not materialistic, something done because you want to help your fellow human beings live a better life from what circumstances lead them to live. You are not used to manual labor - your body aches in a million places, but your heart feels like its made of gold!   	Life is most certainly both extremely complicated and extremely simple - I guess it just depends on how you look at it. Ask a priest and he might tell you that devotion to God matters more than anything else, ask the same to a soldier and he will tell you its training and discipline, ask a miser and he will tell you its money thats most important - it just depends upon how you look at it. But then, all these people are but looking at the lowest and most materialistic side - Do they really know what matters???????  	But then again, do we need to fight materialism? Maybe not, but I feel we need to atleast do SOMETHING that matters because it is done for the common good and not with selfish interests in mind. So I urge anyone who reads this to go out and help the people around you, make a difference and then see how you feel! I assure you, once you realize it, you will keep doing it!!!!  GoodLuck!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>