<Blog>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The drugs began to take hold.... We were somewhere We were somewhere We were somewhere When it all took hold We weer somewhere This story must be told RED SHARK!!! Mescaline, Lsd, only missing PCP Only exsisting to exist Only looking for the american dream we were somewhere (spoken by Zaph) As your attorney I advise As your attorney I advise As your attorney!!! I ADVISE!!!!! Back door Beauty? Back door beauty? Lizards and a twenty foot nazi One hand WASHES THE OTHER!!!! I FEAR NOTHING!!!! We were somewhere We were somewhere We were somewhere around barstow when the drugs began to take hold.... Back door beauty??? Honkey FAGGOT I CANT HAVE THAT!!! I ADVISE I ADVISE I ADVISE I ADVISE I FEAR NOTHING!!!! Back door beauty.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (quazi spoken): If I'm lucky my neck well snap If not its suffacation maybe this is what i need An eternal vacation  I'm sorry if its hard for you to understand Im sorry if you dont realize I am but a man  I'm sorry if you realize that there is little i can do I try my best, do what i can, do everything for you  I wish I had the power to make all the pain go away I wish i had the knowledge and the right thing to say  I wish I had some magick, a special little spell I wish you knew no evil, i wish you knew no hell.  Follow me, i cant promise, its the right way to go I can only say: THIS IS THE ONLY WAY!!!!  If I'm lucky my neck well snap If not its suffacation maybe this is what i need An eternal vacation  I am a dumb little boy I am useless I am just a Toy So not completely useless  I am just a stupid kid i dont know what im doing What i give is what i get What i give i'm losing  People all around say that im insane  People all around claim that Im insane  people all around ME!!!!! Claim that im INSANE!!  maybe im insane out of my mind Im just dumb and trying to find some happiness  I'm just a stupid kid a dumb little boy  If I'm lucky my neck well snap If not its suffacation maybe this is what i need AN ETERNAL VACATION!!!!!  Stupid boy foolish boy stupid kid such an idiot  I'm sorry if its hard for you to understand Im sorry if you dont realize I am but a man  I'm sorry if you realize that there is little i can do I try my best, do what i can, do everything for you  I wish I had the power to make all the pain go away I wish i had the knowledge and the right thing to say  I wish I had some magick, a special little spell I wish you knew no evil, i wish you knew no hell.  Follow me, i cant promise, its the right way to go I can only say: THIS IS THE ONLY WAY!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Single mother was my ma 'cause my father, he ran off he just packed up and left and left me, his little mess no father figure no need for one forever and always a bastard son no father figure  no need for one forever and always a bastard son My father, met another now she is, my step mother and they have a baby boy he treats him nicely, buys him toys im up here, he tries to visit offers me money i dont resist it some retribution for running away he gives me money he owes, he pays but money doesnt fill the void and ive always been a bit annoyed by the fact a man can leave his kid maybe he'd come back.... he never did No father figure no need for one forever and always a bastard son dont call him "dad" cuz hes not one to me hes just a  broken condom im an accident so just leave me im an accident  so let me be i dont need a family I dont need your charity i dont need your sympathy I just want some clarity wish  you took responsibility I've got along through life so far and when im sixteen youll get me a car maybe to replace a year or two of lost time of lost love of lost memories but it wont help your just a check  Just a check No father figure, no need for one always and forever a bastard son       
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *slaps Twik*
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Firetruck yeah im talkin about firetrucks Myk loves firetrucks I love frogs Twik loves guys, but thats okay TWIKS gay! Yeah but thats okay Fire trucks and frogs And Mitch hedburg Loves koalas! I Love frogs! Myk loves......Firetrucks! AND VIRTUOSITY!!!!! AND SNORTING SUGAR!!!!! but i love frogs dont even act like i didnt buy that firetruck i put it in a frog and twik was all like (spoken by twik) Im so gay! FROGS FIRETRUCKS!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a very serious subject.....pants..... Pants(repeat 30 times) And thats all im really trying to say!!!!! PANTS!!! PANTS!!!! (spoken by twik) Pants???? NO!!!! PANTS!!! PANTS!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the song, Myk made up for me, To sing very, Dramatically, I cry for you and your lack of pants Fooooooorrrrrrrrrrrr youuuuuuuuuuu, Need Some Pants You Need Some Pants(repeat for 2 and a half minutes) Seriously, dude. Put some damn pants on. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need some pants.(repeat 14 times) (Spoken by Twik) ummmm.....turtles? NO!! I need some pants.(repeat 15 times) 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish I had a bag of boxes. If I had a bag of boxes I would Have a bag of boxes in each box would be a bag in each bag would be more boxes And this would go on for ever and eternity and always yeah me and my bag of boxes Now i have a bag of boxes ANd inside this Bag of boxes there are more and more boxes and more bags and boxes Bags!  BOXES!!! (spoken by twik) ....ummmm Barrels? NO!!!! Bags and boxes Bags and boxes We need not barrel barrel need not apply im a bag and box kinda guy I wish I had a bag of boxes forever with my Bag of boxes eternity with my bag always with my bag of boxes Bag-Of-Boxes-Be-infernally-eternal! B-O-Boxes Bag-O-B's Bag of boxes be infernally eternal I wish I had a bag of boxes. If I had a bag of boxes I would Have a bag of boxes in each box would be a bag in each bag would be more boxes And this would go on for ever and eternity and always yeah me and my bag of boxes Bag!!!!! of BOXES!!!!!     
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are slits on your wrist  while i yearn for your kiss and you claim that nobody loves you I wish you understood that i can be good I wish i could make you see I want you do you want me? There are tears in your eyes I just want you to smile you say your alone ill be here for awhile I might not exist I might not matter But i'm here when you need me youll see i want you do you want me? We both cried  when we lost each other and when i got back you were with another better then me and smarter then me and i dont wanna stay  Jack without Sally Im sorry, truly you say you are too. but memories just dont go away they just stay and make things worse so much time spent was it all in vain? You have slits on your wrist  whilest i yearn for a kiss and you claim no one wants you yeah im here for you always Jack without sally yeah im here for you always Jack without Sally   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Love, Fuck it, fuck it hard, listen to me your freindly bard (repeat twice) Fuck you! My emotions are your toy. Fuck you! I guess im just a dumb little boy. You were never my girl. Fuck you.... Make me wait oh so long, there for a moment then your gone. I just need some time alone. I just need to find a home. I just need someone to hold. I just need to be told....those three little words.... I just need some time alone... I just need to find a home. I need someone to hold..... I loved you, but fuck you, but fuck you....fuck you. Fuck you. I just need some time alone. I just need some time alone. I just need some time alone. I just need to find a home. I just need someone to hold. I just need to be told....those three little words....
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Geni Sauce By Zaphlon ( zac roberts)  Part One.... Genesis This is a story A completely true story None of it’s made up Except for the parts that are Verse 1 Long ago when Evil cattle lived in Atlantis They ate lots of broccoli and hunted wooly mammoth  But the Evil Cattle king had no Evil cattle Queen He went to America  and set off the country’s balance It sunk into the ocean and ryhmin to balance is not what I do Verse 2 The cattle king went to Indian land, and there he went to the chief At first, it was cool, but he wanted to turn the evil cattle king into beef So the Indians summoned a monster But when the monster spoke He told a joke And nobody laughed The lil monster got mad So he went home and told his dad His dad came back and killed them all That’s how baby’s are made in the monster’s ball END,yo 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Culture Lesson by Myk Doolin  (Spoken) I had to shoot it to make sure it was dead  (Verse 1) Cut through the neck and became an apparition, Lightsaber vs. taser would make one big collision Gained more power and knowledge through being alchemistic The Faust that has become me, no soul, just optimistic Don’t ask how, just know why, it’s confusing, but still try, understand the ways of defeating the albatross simple and low loss, state of mind, you’re your own boss hack life, make it work at your own cost fault phantoms spread like viruses throughout the human race tracing and erasing the truth, and the real face, one big lie, waiting to be envisioned through our eyes when we die but yet, everyone seems to still have pride, why? You may ask this, but really it’s common sense, they’re all blocked by a misleading monolith  (Chorus: Faith No More’s Epic) You want it all, but you can’t have it It’s in your face but you can’t grab it     (Verse 2) some people perceive me as a herbal twister maybe it’s the way I think creativity is my girl and I can’t resist her immortality came back when I lost my top and died listen up you primitive screw heads, are you outta your mind do you even know your kind find yourself, makes life divine  out of time, wait a second, I’m in a time machine,  I got all the time I need, wanna go back, and make time for me? Haven’t ya seen, the buzz you can get from caffeine Methamphetamines make minds obscene like a latrine The unknown third bean in the salad, watch out Stab you in the back with a phoenix talon Didn’t expect it, you shoulda wrote it down in blood with a pin Visional arithmetic, how every human wants their kin  (Chorus: Faith No More’s Epic x 2) You want it all, but you can’t have it It’s in your face, but you can’t grab it  (Spoken) You might not know what this is…………But, you know you want it……..and you know you can’t have it, but you’re willing to do almost anything to get it…………Sometimes, you gotta work around what doesn’t come…………but, always remember, it’ll get there soon enough.   Traffic  I’m gonna walk out into traffic With no red lights I’m gonna walk out into traffic With no yields or stop signs A walk out into traffic My life 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paradox, Double cross, never ends, never stops It doesnt go but always rock watch it go slow fast now your mind will blow  Yeah it's time enough at last. when did you last laugh? when did you last smile, yeah it's been awhile  I'm always here so have no fear.  Yeah it's time enough at last. when did you last laugh? when did you last smile, yeah it's been awhile  When I'm all alone, it's the twilight zone when im all alone the twilight zone   Yeah it's time enough at last. when did you last laugh? when did you last smile, yeah it's been awhile 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not rap. no im hard rock, yeah emo thats me I'm not hot but your so damn sexy im not cool but you are and this i see I love you baby.  Yeah ya rock, rock my f***in socks off yeah your so cool, baby I love you  I feel out of place, i once was last, now im winning the race. oh i love your face smile,laugh and all your traits Yeah i think you should know. I'm losing all control.  Yeah ya rock, rock my f***in socks off yeah your so cool, baby I love you 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The label says take one. so what if I take four? the label says take one. so what if I took more. the label says take one. but thats a bit too late the label says take one i already took eight.       I need my little pill       I need it to sit still.       Helps me to be happy.       My little pill. The label says take one there are no more to take the label says take one that is far too late the label lies i need more one is not enough i need more the label says take one i need more.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When Spring dies, summer grows fall comes, and then it goes winter comes, and then it snows there is no escaping, those are the rules there is no escaping, those are the rules The seasons change and so do we. we all do. we cant stay we all must move we live, we die we smile, we cry winter,spring,summer,fall you want one and get them all so I die, you will live, you have so much more to give so i smile and you cry perhaps its time for me to die? winter,summer,spring and fall. i have lived through them all.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Small slashes by zac roberts.  They cover your arms. (why) they bring such harm. (why) why the yearning? (to die) Small slashes, little lines, on your arms, all the time. bleeding red on skin so white helping to get through the night. Small slashes, Little lines bleeding red on skin so bright bleeding down all through the night can they make everything right? these little slashes on skin so white.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, this is the official M3Z blog. Not much yet. Soon i will post lyrics to all of the songs I (zaphlon) have wrote. Here's what to expect:(songs i have finished, expect up in a week or so) 1.Time enough at last 2.Bag of boxes 3.Love song 4. F*** you 5.Four seasons 6. Small slashes 7. Pill song .......these will all be up in 1 week.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can't do anything Can't do anything Can't do anything I'm a loser an unobtainable love a forever out of reach I'm a loser You don't want me you don't want me you don't want me I was never out of reach I was never unobtainable I was always there when you needed me And I always will be allways be there I've been a bastard you've been a bitch I've been there tho and always will be I'm a loser You dont want me I'm a loser You dont want me Be happy and move on Be happy and move on and maybe at some future time I've always been yours But you'll finally be mine Can't do anything Can't do anything Can't do anything  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want you to know I'm just waitin til you die waitin til you die so i can write a sing bout it I want you to know I want you to know I'm just waitin til you die waitin til you die so i can write a sing bout it I want you to know I want you to know I'm just waitin til you die waitin til you die so i can write a sing bout it I want you to know 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Little light little burn pass around take a turn spin the wheel spark spin the wheel spark spin the WHEEL!!! spark Im sorry man, im insane im sorry mam, im insane im sorry, ive got a fetish for the flame  the flame  I love the fire love the heat love the burn love the sound smell so sweat I love the turn ing of the wheel spin so fast cuz a spark make a spark hits the gas make a spark make a spark make a spark make a spark  a fetish for the flame a fetish for this game a game of pain sorry mam but im insane sorry man im insane sorry sorry sorry make a spark make a spark metal sound calming metal sound so soothing metal sound uplifting metal sound.... MOVING!!!  IM SORRY MAN IM SORRY MAM IM INSANE  IM INSANE IVE GOT A FETISH FOR THE FLAME!!!!! make a spark...   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (sung slowly): Me and my buddy Steve We went walking down the street We saw this old women with green hair it was neat Me and steve walked into a bar and saw this chick we asked for her number, she said no.... i said: Well okay...then ummm.. STEVE FUCKING STABBED HER (sung slipknot esque): STEVE FUCKING STEVE FUCKING STEVE FUCKING STABBED HER ............... (spoken by twik):Really I've known steve my whole life? YEAH STEVES FUCKING CRAZY (spoken by zaph): He's insane man.... STEVE FUCKING STEVE FUCKING STEVE FUCKING STABBED HER STEVE FUCKING STEVE FUCKING STEVE FUCKING STABBED HER   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Emotions devoted To everything that’s been coated In my hate for this macabre life You Fight You Die Or just got forget about Want something more? JUST FUCKIN FEEL ME NOW  Time is passing Nobody’s Lassie No one on the street is gonna STOP AND HELP YOU OUT They take one glance And you’re critiqued  Their judgment is settled UNABRIGED AND COMPLETE  CROWS Can make What’s wrong RIGHT With these Words I will FIGHT  Ball up your fists Protect the whole clique Wanna take risks CEASE AND ASSIST  (Chorus) With these words  I will  FIGHT With these words I will IGNITE With these words  FIGHT x 6  Emotions devoted To everything that’s been coated In my hate for this macabre life Time is passing Nobody’s Lassie No one on the street is gonna STOP AND HELP YOU OUT You Fight You Die OR JUST GOT FORGET ABOUT Want something more? JUST FUCKIN FEEL ME NOW They take one glance AND YOU'RE CRITIQUED Their judgment is settled UNABRIGED AND COMPLETE  (Chorus) With these words  I will  FIGHT With these words I will IGNITE With these words  FIGHT x 9 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck it. Fuck her. I don't need this. Fuck it all. Fuck it all. Fuck you. Fuck it. I don't need this. Fuck it all Fuck it all. Fuck love. I don't need it. I don't need this I don't want this. Fuck it Fuck this Fuck this very negative emotion Fuck it all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dream of reality Of simpler things and Fantasies Of every thing that cannot be and everything i believe should be I dream of reality Of simpler things and fantasies I dream of Love Life I dream of thee I dream of reality   I need to get a grip, emotions and words slip.  If i trip I will never rise just lay there and close my eyes And slowly fade to black never coming back I see no need to be a prisoner of reality a prisoner of what people say I want to live on my terms and allow others to do so too i wanna be happy thats what i wanna do I want to mean and i want to live i dont want to just merely exist in a sea of people, they pass by millions dying, millions cry That i dont know and never will reality is a jagged pill bittersweet forever wish things were better wish people knew like they could see im not insane im just me your all insane im just me  I dream of reality Of simpler things and Fantasies Of every thing that cannot be and everything i believe should be I dream of reality Of simpler things and fantasies I dream of Love Life I dream of thee I dream of reality  I need to find someone to hold so i can be told "I love you" and "I love you too" that is what i need to do a lover a friend a companion someone who's love will never end I may be young and foolish it all may be untrue its the only way to live its the only way  I dream of reality Of simpler things and Fantasies Of every thing that cannot be and everything i believe should be I dream of reality Of simpler things and fantasies I dream of Love Life I dream of thee I dream of reality  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zaphlon has written all but the following songs: Pants 1 and 2 Culture Traffic and Pure sounds of entertainment.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hehe, it's Loky, I'm going to post a song that I wrote. If I find out it was stolen, I'll hunt you down and kill you. Have a nice day.   I've got scars you can't see A past of misery Then along came you You changed everything about me Now you're out of my life again How can I still be like you wanted me to be?  It comes down to this You wanted this you wanted that I gave, I gave, I gave, I gave I never asked for a single thing Now is my time, I want You to know, how bad I am doing, without you All I wanted, was you Now you abandoned me I'm alone once again  I've got scars you can't see A past of misery Then along came you You changed everything about me Now you're out of my life again How can I still be like you wanted me to be?  I want to be numb again But this pain will not go away You've screwed me over To many times before I refuse to fall this time You can not win anymore Because I have grown immune To your words, to your pain I've grown immune..... TO YOU  I've got scars you can't see A past of misery Then along came you You changed everything about me Now you're out of my life again How can I still be like you wanted me to be? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>