<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      damn its going to rain here and im so damn tired.... yesterday, my mom, sister and some dude went to the amusement park and it sucked cuz there was a lot of damn niggers and skaters, and that sucks. i mean, those people suck major sheep ass. anyways when we got back to home i was running to the bathroom to take a piss cuz we drank a lot of soda there. im so damn tired today and i dont know why, but certainly i only want to lay down and sleep. today at skool we got in trouble for "fighting" i mean we were just playing but a dude slammed another one against the wall and since the walls are made of rocksheet, it like moved and the teacher in the next classroom went to punish us and my punishment consists in 1 week of no lunchtime. ah fuck it, i guess its not that bad though. also we had only half day of skool today cuz the teachers had some conference and my friend sid and i came to my house, we were on the pc and then we were wrestling. he is cute but damn he is straight. i love the fact that he has no problem at all with me being bisexual, he is like my bodyguard at skool lol. he rules, i took a pic of him with me today, click  urlLink here  if u want to see it, he looks a lil fucked up there but today he is gettin a haircut and i bet he'll look better, so we'll take another pic tomorrow. well i'll post later see ya all
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, i deicided to use my programming skills and learn a little more and i just created my lil "company", darkstone soft. basically i will be developing games, image editing programs, file encryption tools and a lot more. below are two links to the software i've already developed.   urlLink DrawIt v1.0 : create shapes and logos in this utility.   urlLink Maze v1.0 : the typical maze game but this time its bigger and funnier
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      those days suck. lol its not like im in trouble but its warm as hell!! i hate when its so damn warm cuz my mom tries to make me use short sleeves and i can0t cuz i got a tattoo and i dont want her to see it. its not big though, its just a small lizard, and its not even complete, its just the shape. but anyways if my mom ever sees it im dead!today its very hard to get a job if you have tattoos or piercings, dunno why but thats it. if the boss finds out u have one you wont get the job. o well i dont plan in being an electricist anyways so i dontt hink that the tattoo is a big problem, also im saving money to get a laser surgery so i can get rid of the tattoo, i dont think it'll be expensive. today we went to the "black market" and i bought office 97 lol. i had no office in my computer so i wanted to save hard drive space and purchased an older version, i already sticked it in the computer and it seems to be working well. by the way i made some game in flash yesterday i think you should check it out its free to download and i made it all by myself, just click  urlLink here 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today at skool there's this kid who im always beating lol, his name is richard and well today we kinda... flirted lol. he is straight i think but suddenly when i was writing in my notebook he rubbed my leg with his hand an i was like "hell, whats is him doing?" lol but i must admit it: i got horny. maybe he was just joking, maybe it was serious, but what i know is that he did it several times, and so did i to him. i'd give anything for it not to be a joke but well he failed the fingers test. wanna know what it is about? ok here it goes: when a guy's ring finger is bigger than his index finger, he is a real macho men, but, when a guy's ring finger is EQUAL to his index finger he can be either gay or bi. now that if his index finger is bigger than his ring finger then his penis is small.  this kid's ring finger was bigger than his index finger so he is str8 cuz this test never fails. o well lol my index and ring finger are equal so thats how i know this test works. so girls here's ur chance to know if the cute guy you see at skool and u like is gay or not. and gay guys now have a way to find out who could be theirnew relationship! lol see ya all later.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      looks like things are gettin kool in skool. im gettin better in every class, and even though i'll need to do an extra exam to pass math, my sister who is just so kool is teaching me algebra, and im very proud of myself lol, now i understand it and i learnt algebra in 2 days. anyways there are more things to learn about equations and im going to study it hard, cuz my sis is the best teacher in the world. the only thing that still sucks of skool is the fact that my classmates are assholes. always pickin on me and messin with my stuff. today like at 12:10 am they took my backback and kicked it and i just didnt notice that until a fucker told me that happened but he was one of the people who did it. then they took my blue sweatshirt and also kicked it and stepped on it, and now its all dirty! they pick on me cuz they know im not good at fighting and cuz im the american guy at skool, and that sucks. i always respect their stuff and never do that to they, but this time they really crossed the line, i went and told the principal but he just ignored it. now even the teachers are against me? fuck it... o well i will just focus on having good notes and i wont care about anyone else. the only people who are cool with me are my best friends, daniel and sid. they will never do shit like that to me cuz they know i always help them with everything. one thing i know is that when this skool year is finished, and that will be soon, i will go to another skool, a real skool. i'll give my best to show people who i am. but also i feel lonely, cuz the guys i was talking about in my last post are just not paying any attention on me, wich just makes me feel like crap. o well i guess i must keep searching, and even though i have an online g/f who i love the most, i need someone who is really next to me, nt just cyber kissing lol. i hope u understand so i'll see ya all later.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yesterday i saw a video that completely disturbed me, shocked me, i was about to cry. it was an american man who i can't remember his name, getting beheaded by a gang of fucking iraki terrorists. the video was disturbing as hell as he was being executed. i can't believe there is so much fucking crazy and evil people who can do that to someone. and the worst thing is that the person executed wasnt a militar, it was a CIVILIAN. i hope someone drops a fuckin nuke at irak and blows all the fucking place, because the terrorism is growing everyday and soon the whole world will be plagued of terorists. if there was a thing we could do to stop all this stuff... its sad you know.... i mean i dont know if that guy had kids, and its so fucking horrible when the executioner holds the head of the person to the cameras..... ok if you want to see the video go to  urlLink http://www.ogrish.com  the video is availble for download in the main page. i'll post again later.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      stockholm syndrom... i bet you've heard about this before, dont ya? well if u dont know what does this mean, the stockhol syndrom is when you get in love of your enemies/adversaries. the reason why im telling u this, is cuz i just found out i have this syndrom. i got a crush on one of my enemies, i dont know how did this happen. i dont even know his name! lol. the thing is that we're enemies cuz he is the friend of someone im not and that friend of him and i are the worst enemies too. he was trying to kick my ass just cuz i got in trouble with one of his friends. it was all like a gang trouble. 5 against 1. anyways, to not get in trouble, all i had to do is to let the dude throw me to the ground and done, i "lost". im not willing to kick a 12 year old ass just cuz he was messin around. im not that much of a fag lol. so the friend of this dude who im in love with is mexican, and he might not be white, but i find him... sexy and cute and i dont know why. i'll take a pic of him soon, i'll try not to get caught while doing so. one thing i know is that i dont have any chance with him since i dont believe he is even bi or gay. right now im begginging to feel more attracted to guys than to girls. and its not like thats a bad thing to me but i hate when people makes comments. i only know the nickname of this guy, his nickname is ridiculous: "yu-gi". i've been told that his nickname is that cuz he likes the stupid "yu-gi-oh!" show. and even though i make fun of him with my friends, inside myself i feel kinda... strange, its an unnamed feeling. like i hate him but i love him. and we dont even talk or anything! but o well, its a "platonic" crush, cuz i'll never be able to get to him. now, there's also this other guy in the front classroom, he is one of the 7th graders lol. i used to think he was kinda... stupid but since i've been watching him and hearing stuff about him like evryone says "he is gay" "he is a fag" well i got turned on lmao. j/k but the thing is tha the isnt ugly either, and he is white heh. i'll take pics of those guys pretty soon so just wait and judge. o well my father is on the living room with my mother talkin about i dont know what but i don't really care, when i was walking thru the living room i saw him but i didnt even say hello. hope he dies today in a wreck.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      heh, i switched skool again. same old plan. right now im so bored that i didnt found anything better to do so i came here and posted some stuff in my blog. i hope my teachers don't suspect that i escaped cuz if so then i'd be in trouble, and also i hope that my best friend sid did not tell anyone that he saw me cuz when i was heading downstreet i saw him, we talked and i told him not to fuckin tell anyone he saw me. o well anyways im cool, warm in my house, enjoying a ciggarette and posting here. no one's online right now, so im bored as hell. so please someone login and save me from this boredom! hey i forgot none of you switched skool today. but thanks to... uh.. satan! its friday and that means tomorrow is saturday! lol. by the way why don't ya all get a blog like this? blogs are great, free and u can post all the shit u want. well see ya all later, bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok enough of the old entries this time i'll just post the new ones. if you have any other idea about my website improvement just tell me and i will update everything as fast as i can. also, you can leave me a messae by using the small shout box on the right side of this page.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok i did it. my dad is gone. no more of him. goodbye! i told him to fuck off and this time he really fucked off. he tried to beat me again but he couldnt do it. looks like this time i was the punsiher. i didnt even thought i could have enough strenght to hit him so much times or even the guts to do it. but o well now without him everything is going to be better unless we consider that im not going to have more money on sundays and no milk box. but o well i can buy that myself so i dont think i really need him. right now all i am concerned about is skool. i gotta do my best to pass to 9th grade. cuz otherwise i'd be sent to that boot camp. anyways i also have to settle down things in my house, i dont want to keep fighting against my mom. last night we were figthing over me going to sleep with her. it was the MOST stupid thing in the world. it was all cool until i was falling asleep in the couch and she went with this blanket and started hitting me. thats shit heh. but anyways, last nite rocked. my lil cousin came by with his mom, my cousin alex who is so fuckin tall lol but so cool. and also there was his gf. they're having a kid and i didnt even knew! now there was also my sister, her boyfriend and my cousin's mom boyfriend. it was all a mess cuz since yesterday was my sister's b-day they went to drink as much as they could lol. my sister was all ugly today heh, and she is usually hot rotfl.  Well my cousin is 13 years old and he is so kool, mean and kiddish, lol, wich is the part of him i love more. its not like im in love with him but we were lving together for so much long so we kinda got used to each other and when it was time for him to leave with his mom i wanted to die lol. not really but he is the person i care the most in my family, i'd never let anything happen to him. well so u be asking "how would that kid look like" huh? well go to www.freewebs.com/y2kut/pics.html and go to the very end of the page to see a pic of him i got three of him. he is a lil cutie and he is very sweet.  ok enough of that lol. now... dont u think that b letting u know everything that happens in my life im giving u too much info? lol well i dont mind that but at least would u consider voting for my blog at rankmyblog.studentcenter.org? you just have to click the button on the right and vote. ok so see ya all byez.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      this week has been a  little crappy cuz my mom and dad went to sign my skool qualifications, and i failed math once again, im going to make another math exam at the end of this skool year so i can save it, but last night i had to listen to my mom and dad sermon about skool and i was all pissed off giving bad looks to them, and the truth is that i dont feel any interested in keeping on skool. i think i know enough yet, dont need algebra. i was thinking a while ago about telling my mom and dad to take me to a fucking boot camp, where i would finish studying high skool and thats all i'd need. but certainly, being locked in there one more year would suck. i dont eben know if i would be close to a computer anymore if i was there but i think i need to change my behavior, im a rebel right now and im starting to think im worng, but if i runaway from home, i dont have anywhere else to go, and if i saty here like nothing is happening, i would end up killing myself or something. i hate the fact that my father is in my house again, he hasnt beaten me as he used to do, but since we are going to a shrink everything is fucked up. after... 9 years? of not counting on him for anything, now he wants to do his father job? hell no, im not willing to change my lifestyle and give up everything i do now just cuz that asshole is back here. i dont feel safe with him around, its like i dont really need a father anymore, i never needed him, and when i did he wasnt here, im not going to let him get into my life again, i dont fuckin love any of my parents right now, not even my mother, she was so stupid in taking him tothe shrink and coming back, its all bad now. i feel kinda sad, unconfident, strange and i have so much anger inside me right now, nothing is the way i'd like it to be. i dont know what to do right now, all i want is to be far from them, i dont want to be subdued by any rules in my life, but i just cant be free.    ahh fuck it i'll go to my backyard and think about this for a while. bye all.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hello kids and potheads out there lol. today we are going to study one of the most important themes in the teenagers life: insults. what is a teen without insulting? its like a broom without the stick. what happens when someone insults you and you dont know what to answer? you are ridiculized, minusculized, INSULTED. well, here is the best, failure proof answer for any insult, its pretty simple, short and fun: yo mamma. the words "yo mama" are certainly the only thing that can leave someone in complete silence. there is nothing someone can respond to a yo mamma. nothing! nothing at all! when you receive a "yo mamma" you are fucked up, screwed, insulted, ridiculized and more depressing shit. thats why before doing anything stupid like fighting or insulting back, think about this tip, just say "yo mamma" and walk away. its not like running away from combat, its avoiding a violent situation by using your brain. remember not to add any other insults like "yo mama is so...." etc cuz that will get you in trouble.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      heh, funny. last night my mom wrote a note for the teacher wher she explained why she did not go to my skool and the she would go someday. i gave it to the teacher and lmao, he believed me and said "tell your momma to come to sign your monthly qualifications the next week" and i was like "yea i'll tell her" there was no problem at all, and the god thing is that im going good at every class. less than math. i dont know anything about math, algebra and all that shit.  the good shit is that i dont have classes tomorrow so if someone doesnt come by or i get somethin to do i'll bore my ass out sitting here. o well at least i got pizza. by the way there is now a lot of new pics at my website, check em out if u want to at www.freewebs.com/y2kut. the new website wont be built until i get my internet back, i think that will tomorrow friday 30. i'll make a better website so you'll have more fun ok? see ya later ppl
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i hate skool like never before. i was told totake my mom to my skool on monday so the teacher could talk to her about some stupid shit that happened on friday. some girl named jessica with who i play a lot at skool like if i was "humping" and touching her, she did shit. she used to play and i never disrespected her. i have never touched her in any way cuz i dont feel interested in it, i dont even like girls.  she was playing and then she decided to tell the teacher about the game and i got all fucked up.  cant believe that i would be blamed for something i didnt do, i mean...  fuck! after a goddamn year of playing like this she decides to fuck me, what kind of a friend is that? i dont think i need this shit, and since my mom did not go today to skool i was told that im not going to skool tomorrow but anyways my mom is gonna write a note for the teacher so he will stop fucking. anyways, there was another, the natural sciences teacher just got an enemy on me from now on. a classmate named Diana had the teacher's list on her backpack. i dont know what the fuck happened but it appeared broken. someone broke it and a friend of mine and me got blamed for something we didnt do, and the bitch did not even let me say it wasnt me, the bitch also said she knew me but the truth is that we have had her class only 4 times in this year. only 4. and she said she knew me, about me being a disaster wich isnt true. i can be a bad guy, naughty, but never a disaster, i've never done anything to her but anyways the director said we must give him a little piece of paper where we tell him everything she does to usl, everything she has said to us so they will kick her ass out the skool. wich reminds me to do my note right now so she will be told to fuck off. i can't wait for tomorrow lol. i have said a lot of shit to this people of skool about their incompetance, crapness and a lot of shit. when i finish this year im gonna go personally to every of the teachers to tell them to go fuck themselves.  BY THE WAY I NEED A GODDAMN BOYFRIEND/GIRLFRIEND QUICKLY!! LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hello everyone. today i escaped from skool cuz dave told me to lol. he said he wouldnt go to skool either and that i should stay with him chattin. lol its 11:22 am and he still hasnt signed on, i wonder... would he change his mind and go to skool? i'd be so pissed off at him if he did so. i run the risk of gettin my ass kicked on monday if my mother finds out i did not go to skool.  If she doesnt go to my skool the next monday to some math demonstration i wont be allowed in until she goes there. that sucks major ass but o well who cares. i think im gonna flunk this year... i dont want to! lol i guess i'll have to do my best this tme to pass every class or at least flunk 2. math and geography maybe. the thing that'll help me is the fact that i went to some spanish language contest, u know ortography or spelling and reading. i participated in reading and we were 4th place thanks to me. if i was in the spelling one things would have been better. but o well the spanish teacehr said its kool and that im gonna have a big 10 this time wich is so good, i wont have to do the exam!.  lol if u want tips on how to escape from skool, here are some, this is my escape plan:  1- plan everything since a day before u do it, where you gonna go, with who, when etc.  2- make sure your friends are coming with you if some of them will. keep in contact with them by cellphone or any other way and tell them the plan with clear words so they'll understand  3- if you use skool uniform, make sure you take a different shirt and maybe a jacket or sweater if its cold, when u escape from skool you must not be seen with the uniform cuz people can report you.  4- try to take a knife with you, people may see you with your backpack and stuff and there's a lot of thiefs out there, have something to defend yourself with! and i mean it  5- once you and your friends meet somewhere you already planned, like any street corner or park, act quickly, take a bus to where you're going or just run but this is about not gettin caught.  6- make sure you have somewhere to put your backpack and stuff in, like the house of one of your friends or check your possibilities of hiding it somewhere.  7- take enough money with you, a cap to not be recognized so easy, and all your valuable stuff ( discman, cellphone, keys, money etc.. )  8- if you're planing to go to your house cuz your parents will be at work, do it, but be careful to not be seen by any of your neigbors who can tell your mom, enter your house quickly, dont make unneeded noise that everyone can hear and suspect of. dont answer the phone for any reason, just dont, you can get caught by the social worker or even your mom. if your little brother is at home, make sure you have something to threaten him with, or some candy to keep his mouth closed, and if you're gonna have fun make sure you include him, brothers are dicks and they'll tell your parents what you did without him.  8.1- if you're planning to be late to skool so they wont let you in and you'll return home, the fun is gonna be small. your friends might go to skool and you'll be alone in home like me...  and the final step is one of the most easy and important of all: HAVE FUN.   movies, music, computer, videogames ( play station, xbox etc..), TV, weed/alcohol/tobacco allowed lol, masturbation lmao, sex... whatever that can keep you entertained is gonna be cool.  personally i stay at home and give u tips like these ones lol. the secret for a really cool skool escape is ORGANIZATION. thats all you need, organization and a good plan and thats all.   the plan i followed today was the most simple and old of all of them. since my skool is almost in front of my house, i just gotta cross the road and a small garden and there i am, skool. this time i acted like normal, trying to be late to skool. since it was pretty soon, i get in skool at 7:00 am and my mom leaves home to go to work at 7:30 am, i just instead of walking to the skool i followed the way inside my neighborhood. i just walked like 10 minutes to a park to sit down until it was 7:45 at least. i was sitting in a chair in that park next to a big factory watching the sun rise while listening to "creedence clearwater revival" on my cd player and smoking a cigarette. it was good to feel fresh morning air in my face, followed by those flashing big white lights of the factory, they looked like and airport. birds flying, people sleeping, lone streets, like an abandoned town. and in the middle of grass, trees and birds there was me watching a clear sun rising from the east... or west? lol i dont remember. then i walked back to home and asked an old man what time was it. it was barely 7:30 am. i kept walking like for 10 minutes and i got here. now im all bored and hungry!!!!!!!!! o well dave hasnt signed on yet.... fucker lol.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      meh, today like 20 minutes ago, there was this lil "trouble" with an ex of my girlfriend called Matthew. ha, i still remember his words:   "she is a good girl" "i hear one more bad thing about you and i'll show up your balls to your throath" "you *fukin* bitch" "i dont know what does she like of you" "you *fukin* stoner"  man, im just gonna tell you something: fuck off and leave me with my deffects, if i get high sometimes, well its not of your business, and dana does it too so, whats the deal. also i never pushed her to do it, if she is smelling that fingeranil polish its cuz she wants, not cuz i said "hey dana, smell your polish and lets get high". im not like that dude, but certainly i dont give a shit about what ever you say.  and if dana is with me its cuz she likes me, she loves me and more stuff that you might don't have, and thats why she dumped you. im sorry if you're jealous, but well, the fact is that you SUCK.  i dont even know you and you're talking shit to me, wich just shows how pissed off you are cuz i have more luck with girls than you. being jealous just shows how stupid you are. why dont you get a life and let everyone else live their life as they want to. that way we would all be happy. why dont you just fuck off and die? by the way, im not scared of you "man" if you wanna fight you can bring it on, i'll show you how a real man fights. but anyways, you cant come here to "kick my ass". im too far away from you but anyways, bring it on.  but what would i win by kicking the ass of such a piece of shit? nothing, absolutely nothing at all! so why dont we lite up a blunt, relax and have some fun, and you matthew, why dont you shut down your computer, go out, take a deep breath and go fuck yourself. thats all for now, i'll make  a new post later, good nite to everyone. dont forget to check out my personal website at http://www.disasterpiece-kurt.cjb.net 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey people, as you see, this is my brand new web log at blogspot.com, isnt it just great? ad-free, cool view and so much shit. so forget about the older blog i had cuz this one is the one i choose forever so stay here and dont stop voting, just click the button! by the way i'll be posting the older posts i had in the other blog so if u see the same with a new date its cuz of that.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We too feel alone  That place in my mind Is that space that you call mine That place in my mind Is that space that you call mine  Where have I been all this time Lost enslaved fatal to climb I've been waiting for this to unfold But The pieces are only as good as the whole  Severed myself from my whole life I cut up the only thing that was bright What if i never saw you again I'd die right next to you in the end  That place in my mind Is that space that you call mine That place in my mind Is that space that you call mine  I won't let you walk away Without hearing what I have to say Without hearing what I have to say Without hearing what I have to say
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    cute?  Posted By RaMmStEiN 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    the pic of me that my mom took at huatulco's beach hotel  Posted By RaMmStEiN 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    what do u think bout my body huh?  Posted By RaMmStEiN 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Chaos - It's just the beginning Every promise I made is rescinding Center mass in the middle of the monster I'm getting tired of drowning in the constant Cry for help - It's debatable The only reason that you love me is I'm hated by all Come on - Come see dysfunction I guess we're gonna lave it open for discussion  Who am I? And where am I going? Maybe I'm looking in the wrong direction Maybe I'm looking for any direction  This is not my war - This is not my fight This is something more - This is not my life (This is not my) Revolution (This is not my) Convolution (This is not my) Expectation (This is not my) Desperation  Holed up, scarred and tamed for the hell of it Look at me - I am the glorified malcontent Save me? Save this! All I gotta do is give up and all is forgiven I'm sick - Of being the but of a cosmic joke And I don't get the punch line A million people lined up for miles To see the great big mouth shut up and apologize  This is not my war - This is not my fight This is something more - This is not my life (This is not my) Revolution (This is not my) Convolution (This is not my) Only reason to question why  Today, I said goodbye! Goodbye! Oh I didn't need to leave to stay right here Today, I said goodbye!  I'm the pariah (Break me) I am the liar (Save me) I can take anything (Make me) Accuse me of everything (Take me) Cut off the system (Shape me) Deny my existence (Waste me) I won't be afraid (Try me) I won't be unmade (Deny me)  So come on - Break it off Come on - Buy the lie Come on - Say it, say it Come on Say goodbye! Goodbye! Oh I didn't need to leave to stay right here Today, I said goodbye! Goodbye! Oh I didn't need to leave to stay right here Today, I said goodbye!  One - One Two - Two Three - Three NIL!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      uhh yeah... today my mom went to the skool to sign my final qualifications and i... i flunked math but thats not all, all of my other qualifications were low and i know why. my mom was all freakin out cuz now i wont be able to go to the other skool i wanted to. and also she said she is thinking about making me repeat the 8th grade cuz no other skools are going to accept me with those notes, im so pissed off and dissapointed at myself, i cant believe im so lazy.. now i dont know what im gonna do cuz i really wanted to be a 9th grader and now i dont know if i will. i hope there's a skool where i can go and this time im gonna study for real, no more lazyness. wich means i wont be able to be on the computer the same amount of time i used to be. and its not like i dont know anything i know a lot of stuff and im the smarter dude at skool but im just lazy, i should do all my homework and that stuff becuz that means good notes and i want to be a good student and make my mom proud but nothing i do is right im just an asshole and i cant help it im the worst son in the world. sometimes i wonder why i cant be like all thos eother dudes who have good notes at skool and why im not a good guy :( nothing i do is right. im depressed and i dont know what to do, i hate myself so bad... i bet my mom is crying and i hate it when she does that becuz im not able to make her happy. all i do is dissapoint people and that makes me sad... i'd love to be a better person but i cant change, im not brave enough to give up on stuff i like to do. im just a stupid kid i need to die but i'll give anything to change and make my mother proud. goodbye...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok i wasnt on msn, aim or anything today becuz my mom and i went to my sister's house, and she took us to Subway to eat, then we went to the movies and watched shrek 2 lol its a great movie. i thought it would be stupid but hell no its funnier than the first one. lol the only bad thing was my mom there with her stupid attitude. she starts acting stupid and stuff... i hate it when she does that. tomorrow i will still go to skool cuz i'll get my final qualifications, and my mom has to sign them. i hope i didnt flunk math cuz if i do i'll need to study in vacations for the extra exam we have to do when we flunk a class. i guess that way i'learn what i couldnt learn from math. there is a lot of things i didnt understand but thanks to my sister i know some algebra now. but also there's something i didnt knew about this skool: WE ARE DOING OUR FINAL EXAMS IN VAIN. yeah one of my teachers told me that they already gave the final results to the P.E.O (Public Education Organization) and well that means i will for sure flunk math... o well i just dont give a fuck. i would like to quit studying and work, doesnt matter where but i dont like skool... and i've been told im very smart and i know it, i know a lot, actually im the best at skool in every class less than math, but well... i dont think i need to be wise, i just want to get money and spend it the way i want. oh well as i said, who cares lol. by the way i took a new pic and all my pics are now in a photo album, just click the image that says photo center and stuff and there's a page with all my pics and pics of my friends, wich means i'll be deleting my other websites soon and just keep this one with the photo album and the badass hoes pranknet site. i'll just keep these ones cuz i think updating every site takes a lot of time and effort and im not willing to work for unnnecessary stuff so yeah say goodbye to freewebs and fateback and all that shit. oh well im going to bed so see ya all, bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ahh shit... its exactly 2:12 am and im still awaken and lol... my mom's friends are in my living room drinking and smoking and yea, i dont like her friends lol they only talk about their work and stupid stuff like other ppl wich is just BORING. lol i guess i'll go to bed soon cuz im sleepy but i wanna have corn flakes before i go to bed, but i must wait till her friends leave cuz i dont wanna say hi. by the way, we need more members at the badass hoes site so please join its free and by joining you can have a free cool blog, a free profile, access to forums, chat, downloads and our funny pranks archive. just go to  urlLink http://badasshoe.tk  and join as i said its free and u get cool stuff in there. also i reccomend you join GoLiveWire.com, there is a lot of funny stuff there like tests, free email and cool forums. lol im a geek i know. by the way i created a poll about if i should stop smoking or not so please check it out and vote cuz people is telling me to quit but i dont know if i want to, click here to vote.  urlLink http://usuarios.lycos.es/linkinhack/modules.php?name=Surveys&pollID=2 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      oh yeah, i can finally say im now a 9th grader and soon, a badass 15 year old lol. i hope i dont flunk math cuz if i do then i'll have to do an extra exam so i can pass that class. i worked so hard to learn algebra so if i flunk it then i'll have to study more to pass the extra exam cuz if i dont then i wont be able to get in a new skool. i wanna get into a new one so bad...lol i dont want to be surrounded by nacos* anymore, my mom wants to get me into a good skool where they dont wear uniform, they teach you french, tae-kwon-do instead of gymnastics, but uh... damn they also force you to play chess and i hate chess, its a game for 98 year old people lol. also i'll get my ass yelled there cuz they're so strict but oh well maybe i need that to calm down and stop being a rebel.i wanna meet new, cool, preppy people like me lol. also i cant wait till 5 july lol, my birthday. my mom is going to give me slipknot's new cd and i will invite my skool friends so we'll have fun! lol im tired rite now so see ya later.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      She seen trust in all of me, stretched across my shame. All the torment and the pain Leaked through the cover in me Id do anything ever to myself Just to have her for myself Now I dont know what to do, I dont know what to do when she makes me sane.  She is everything to me The unaquited dream A song that no one sings The unobtainable, Shes a myth that I have to believe in All I need to make it real is one more reason I dont know what to do, I dont know what to do when she makes me sane.  But I wont let this build up inside of me I wont let this build up inside of me I wont let this build up inside of me I wont let this build up inside of me  A catch in my throat Choke, dawn into pieces I wont No, I dont want to be this  But I wont let this build up inside of me I wont let this build up inside of me I wont let this build up inside of me I wont let this build up inside of me  She isnt real I can make her real She isnt real I can make her real 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok ok what the hell... i stop blogging for a while and then this place becomes a mess. girls stop fighting goddmanit. and its not like i care but STOP FLOODING MY TAG BOARD with long messages its not nice and if you keep it going i will have to ban you from it and you'll never post again. if you all wanna fite then go to msn, aim or whatever u all want but STOP FUCKING WITH MY SITE i'll get pissed off and you wont like it. by the way check out all the sites i've made.  The Badass Hoes --- http://badasshoe.here.ws My new site     --- http://y2kut.fateback.com                 --- http://y2kut.atspace.com  Also you can get a free blog at the badass hoes site, just register for free and go to journals, that way you'll get a profile and a cool blog.  //-Out lol
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i changed my hosting company and my personal website for one i made all by myself, go to  urlLink http://y2kut.atspace.com  so check it out and tell me if you prefer this one of the old freewebs site.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Link to My Msn Profile Click Here  lol this is so dumb but i felt like it, i wanted to do it so leave me be lol.  ~~ WaTsUmArA In Da MoRnIn' In Da HaUsE! ~~ ~~ Se MeTiO Un PeJeLaGaRtO ChIcO! ~~ 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      one of my older cousins, Frank or Francisco, died two days ago cuz of a strange disease that killed him in one week... its sad cuz they say he was so cool and a good person, i personally didnt know him well cuz i only saw him two time sin my life, so i really didnt feel very bad abut it, but everyone who saw him in the coffin ended up crying so damn hard. o well life still goes on for me so its no big deal. and i managed to see my lil cousin again hehe. that damn kid rules. we had to travel to mexico city, where he died and we had to sleep in the same room where the coffin was. i mean.... damn couldnt we go to a fuckin hotel? why is my mom so fucking annoying, religious and stupid? oh well i guess she is just a fuckin mexican. lol i got in trouble at skool today for skippin a class... lol some friends and i ran to a prank where some of our partners were and we were chillin for a while, until the principal came in his goddamn car and screwed us up... lol but the director of the skool is so damn cool that he helped us and now we are not in trouble anymore. anyways tomorrow we'll have to talk with the teacher so yea, all i want is to have my final exams and pass this year, so i'll go to a new skool with new people. i'll miss everyone from the skool im rite now, everyone became a part of me even when they wer emean or anything, they will always be in my heart. ah fuck that shit lets not get soft and keep rollin lol.  ~~ WaTsUmArA In Da MoRnIn' In Da HoUsE! ~~
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today has been a good day. except for my mom and sister renting some julia robert's movie... i hate her so dman much lol. yesterday my mom was a complete ho, she fuckin threatened with killing my mouse if i killed a goddman fish... its so embarrassin that i dont even wanna post it here lol. the thing is that i hate my whole family except for my sister. i mean... she is the only one who understands me, and everyone makes a fuckin big deal of everything and she is the only one who gives me good advice. my mom and my family are so fuckin stupid, my sister rules. she is the only cool one there, my mom acts retarded and my father IS retarded... jeez im lucky of not being retarded lol. by the way you ALL SHOULD add my msn bot... cuz it rules and its fun come on dont be an ass and do it. o well i'll post again later, good nite.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey, i wanna tell ya all that i just created two bots for aim and msn, these bots are really cool, the msn one got a lot of stuff and you can chat with people online. the aim one is good too, a little complicated, but still great the two bots have been developed for my current project, the badass hoes team. here are the adresses, you just add them, you send a message and start talkin.  msn bot: badass_bot@hotmail.com  aim bot: TheBadassBot  enjoy and make sure you tell your friends about this bot.  -- Kurt
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today everything was going so good... until i dont know what happened but the "my documents" folder got deleted, and there was my sister's fles, my pics, other stuff... thanks to satan, the website files i was working on were not saved in that folder cuz if not... i would have kicked the goddamn pc out the window. anyways now all my pics and files are back but i had to re-build the folders and shit. those days have been cool, no trouble at skool, nothin bad has happened. and the badass hoes website is now done. check it out  urlLink here . the site is running properly and it works so good, it got a lot of stuff and even though the pranks are still being uploaded to the website, the other stuff in there is very cool, i hope you like it cuz i made it myself. 3 days ago i saw the movie "the day after tomorrow" and i gotta say its a great movie. the effects, the fake wolves lmao, and the whole movie rules. if u haven't seen it yet, you should. a friend of mine named daniel introduced me one of his cousins, her name was viridianne (its a she lol) and well she is hot, lol i wanna hook up with her but uh, i must do an effort to do it. and also like one hour ago, one of my best friends, another female named Lorena told me she liked me and that if i wanted to be her boyfriend...... jeez now it looks like im having luck with gurls, wich is not bad at all. i'll see what to do with these girls and take my dessicion, cuz i got to. o well i'll see ya all later.  urlLink http://badasshoe.here.ws   
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      lmfao, u all are so gullible, i aint marrying no jordans lol, its a joke we decided to make to everyone and see how many people we freaked out. i mean.... just check the tag board, its so damn funny... ahh i guess thats what happens for being such a badass hoe. the badass hoes team is conformed by jordan, dana, sid and me. i made the badass hoes website and you can see it  urlLink here . we the badass hoes make pranks to everyone all the time, and even though we are just starting we have good shit up in there.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    yea, thats me, sexy as hell lmao  One of My Best Pics Huh 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      im marrying a dude named jordan, he is the one with the nickname Death in my tag board. he is just so hott and sweet, he thinks just as me and well we have been friends for so much time and we finally hooked up. im so happy cuz i finally found love, he is just awesome and he rules major sheep ass. we mess around alot and he seems to be a very good guy. the thing about the marriage is serious we will stay together 'til we can do it. he fucks so good..... damn im in deep love!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i was just watching a website that i did not know what it was about, and they were so fuckin racist! they even sold t-shirts with the hitler's swastika and shit, they even had three huge&nbsp;pages with "nigger jokes" and also mexican jokes. it sucked i felt insulted after reading all of them, ya know, im half mexican and that fuckin website sucks. God they are americans and they were supporting racism and nazi shit.. its fuckin stupid when people does that, if they even had an idea of what hitler did, they wouldnt be so fuckin racist and happy of selling those stupid symbols. Im sorry but that really pissed me off and its not fair that america has fallen into racism like this... i mean yea bash christians and jews but leave the mexicans and the black people alone, it snot nice or funny to fuck with people like that, and after all, we ARE AMERICANS, ther eshould be equality for everyone in the world, now i see why the world is so fucked up, but i hope everyone thinks like me and stop racism, terrorism and every bad thing that ends with ism lol. black ppl are cool, and so are full/half mexicans and there shouldnt be that kind of websites. lol ok im outta here, see ya all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      damn... lately, i dont know whats up with my dad but he is being nice and cool to me. in the beggining of this attitude i didnt let him talk to me and stuff, but since i saw him and said hi, he like... feels happy, even my mom told me he had a strange reaction. but this is weird ccuz after all the shit he did to me, now he wants to be a father. i'll give up on hating him and try to go on this way, of course that doesnt mean i'll low my guard, im gonna keep takin care. By the way people, lol i had to make a new tag board cuz cbox suck'd, sorry if this one doesnt have smileys but its waaaaaaay better than cbox and it doesnt crash cuz its located into a good server. I'll get a better one soon, so yea post ur messages in that tag board while i setup a new one. byes ppl 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        OK. I am going to tell the people who read this something most people don't know. It's not like a huge deal but i guess to me it is. When i was with Kurt he like totally changed me. I mean i even got high. i mean it was on fingernail polish but i did it. I am so over him. How did i fall for that @$$ hole? I think it was his pretty eyes and just his beginning sweetness... he totally changed. I will miss my Boo but Kurt i can't stand him. He told my cousin he was gay.... the best for him. If any guy is stupid enough to go with him best wishes for them.   You might wonder who said all that shit huh? well it was the stupid ass dana, i was reading her diary at student center to see what kind of shit was she talkin about me and i found this out. I think thats not nice, dana if you're reading this, i never told you to get high. And you know it, just becuz i emailed her once to tell her i got high, doesnt mean she had to do it too. Now if i tell her to jump off a cliff, im sure she will do it. Never thought someone could be such a backstabber. Yes, i used to get high on wood glue, but i dont think i ever told anyone to do the same, i never changed anyone, its not the way i work. and i never told that faggot i was gay, NEVER. And dana, you're one who gets the fucked up relationships, poor idiot the one who dates you. I fuckin hate when people does this.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       well since i have nothin to do, i decided it would be a good idea to make a post. in this post i will write everything that has happened to me, so if you're interested read it and if not then dont.  2 years: i got my first doggie at my b-day, her name was candy, then i dont know what else cuz i dont remember that age too well.&nbsp;     3 years: i saw a real monster, i remember it but duhh i didnt care too much about it, we were at some kind of market or something at night but i dont remember anything else from that age   4-5 years: i got first beaten in my life by my mom for being a bad kiddo. also&nbsp;we moved from arizona to mexico, cuz my dad worked there so yea thats the reason why im&nbsp;here now.&nbsp;     6 years: went to the elementary skool and it sucked cuz everyone hated me and i dont know the reason, it was weird cuz&nbsp;one day someone was my friend and another i was a stupid ass. wich was not nice,&nbsp;i hope all of my ex-schoolmates are dead now cuz they were really mean to me. they discriminated me for being american and white and they were like all brunettes and rednecks it was the WORST experience of my life.     7-8 years: damn, certainly, this was the worst time of my life. when i was 7, i was at skool, and when i went to the skool bathroom to take a piss, one of the fuckin 6th graders who was 12 years old, came in and raped me. yes, rape means being fucked with violence and against your will, i used to be straight before that happened, i still remember that day and it will forever be stuck in my mind. i got over it but anyways its like a mark carved in my mind that i will never be able to erase. during several months i was depressed, with suicidal thoughts, but i kept everything that happened secret, no one knows about this, only my friend sid and some people online, and now you all are reading this... i decided not to tell anyone becuz that motherfucker threatened me to death if i said anything, and i think it was the best i could do, not tellin anyone so i'd keep alive. then when i was 8 years old i had a very rough time at skool cuz everyone like... ignored me and that sucked becuz i felt so alone by that time, no one was cool to me then and i dont know why. also i got in the first fight of my life, against the same one who raped me, i hit him in the face really hard with my fist, he like... black'd out lol. but im lucky he didnt kill me for doing that. then, at summer vacations, i went to a place where kids go to at summertime, to have fun and play sports, but its like you are subscribed into a team and you did fun stuff like playing basketball, soccer, practicing judo, tae-kwon-do, and so at this place i met this kid named homer, lol he was discriminated becuz he used big glasses, he was bashed all the time and his nickname was "the beaver". i got so pissed off at the guys who were bashing him all the time and i decided to talk to him, and so we started a great friendship, and when that summer activity finished, i never saw him again until... read a little more down.      9-10 years: still isolated, in my own world where no one understood me but me, i was always sitting in the dark, under that tree at skool, thinking about why i was so hated, so weak, such a coward, and started wondering why did i started to like my&nbsp;male classmates, why did i had that weird desire to kiss one of them specially... i still didnt knew what the hell was that feeling, i tried to forget it, and i couldnt, but as always, i kept it secret. i started hearing all these comments about gay people and stuff like that, but didnt knew what meant gay! i was still a kid, what would i know about this? still i liked girls so i began to think it was just crazy thoughts and i kept going on.    11 years: as always, i was still alone, with no friends, no company, and i kinda liked to be alone... its like no one was making noise, laughing, talking...&nbsp; but at the same time it felt like shit cuz i was so lonely, i felt the need to find someone to talk to. and so i did, i got this friend named daniel, he was cool, but he was like... weird, there was no tv's at his house,&nbsp;they only listened to the radio, her mom was like.. strange, he was very preppy, smart and &nbsp;kinda cute anyways, so well i didnt care too much. we used to hang around the neighborhood riding our bikes, and it was cool, cuz he was the first friend i had in my whole life. And then, we stopped seeing each other cuz he got sick of a weird disease, i was sad for a while but i forgot about him later. So when christmas arrived, i was at this party in the neighborhood where i met this kid, michael, we wer eplaying with some other kids who were my neighbors, and well we started playing alone and talking, he was wearing a blue mouthcover like the ones the docs use, so i could only see a half of his face... so i invited him to my house so we could talk and i could see his face... he was... damn he was so fuckin hot, and well we got along very well and we were hangin out like for one month, and one day, he came to my house and we started doing "stuff", and well we both looked at each other and... kissed... then it all became a wild, wild gay sex scene. im not embarrased or ashamed of saying it, after all, this is me and i dont have to say what people wants me to say. so that guy and i started a relationship, boyfriend/boyfriend lol and i can say it was the best time of my life.        12 years: darn, i entered the high skool, and michael too, and we were in the same skool! yeah it was great...&nbsp;one day, at skool, i saw this cute boy&nbsp;who brought me memories, but i didnt knew who it was! so i talked to him and omfg it was HOMER! yea! he and i were so fuckin happy we met again, and so&nbsp;michael met homer and we were the coolest, punkiest and messiest boys of the neighborhood. we acted so gangsta and&nbsp;shit, we the three were really happy by that&nbsp; time, we also went to the mall to steal cd's haha. i remember&nbsp;one time when&nbsp;homer and i went to the stadium, we live rite next to&nbsp;it so we went there and entered it WITHOUT PERMISSION damn we&nbsp;were like playing this&nbsp;"metal gear solid" game haha, it was so great, we were on the main rooftop, we were&nbsp;jumpin and running there, our objective was to&nbsp;run a full lap to the stadium, we were doin it cool&nbsp;until i fucked it all up by throwing a light bulb to the seats, damn we got caught but we made our way out, and we had to deal with the cops. we all had great times when we were together, we smoked, we drinked and a lot of stuff and homer didnt even knew that michael and i had a relationship. it was all&nbsp;nice with the three of us&nbsp;until we fucked it all up when&nbsp;michael and i decided to make some graffittis at a park and we got caught, the neighbors told our moms and they decided to seperate us... i was so sad cuz i never saw him again, but i enjoyed all the time i spent with him. later, homer and i also got seperated cuz he was gettin kicked out of skool, so once again i lost a friend. he was like my brother too. and well i kept at skool, i was doing bad at skool too, i remember i always flunked like 8 classes every fuckin month. so i me tthis boy who's name was alex, we were cool and we both loved the band "queen". yes the band where the singer was gay and he died of HIV, they were great. but well once he came to my house, we started doing "dirty stuff" lol, as straigh boys, when suddenly he started... ya know, jerkin me off... and so did i to him, and it ended up into blowjobs and stuff. but we never had sex, cuz he said he was straight and that he was just curious, and ok, anyways i liked that experience. so i assumed i had a&nbsp;very big attraction to guys, bigger than to girls. but still i was confused about my preferences and all that stuff. anyways, i flunked that year becuz of my rebellion against every teacher and for not doing anything in class. so i got kicked out from there...&nbsp;   also that year my mom got a boyfriend named daniel, they still are together, and i love that dude as if he was my real father, cuz he cares for us like if he was. he is now also an important part of my life cuz he is so cool... doesnt matter if he is mexican as all the people i've met he is a good guy. my mom got this relationship when she got divorced from my father, cuz he drinks too much so he was just&nbsp; alittle violent IN THE BEGINNING... the bad stuff is just a few more years from there        13 years: jeez... well since i flunked&nbsp;7th grade, i had to repeat it, so i was sent to another skool, the crappiest skool indeed.&nbsp;at the beginning it &nbsp;was a little hard to get used to the new people, but anyways, after some months of being with them i got new friends, specially this lil guy named henry... lol he was weird too, but he was cool... well not really he didnt have a good taste in music but o well. also i got this friend named daniel lol i've met tons of daniels but lol this one liked nirvana and since i love nirvana we got along by that song "you know you're right" lol i remember we used to sing it all the time when we were at skool... weird lol he knew a little english so it was cool. so anyways, the skool once took us to a trip to veracruz, one of the most famous beachs of mexico, and we had a lot of fun, also a dude who i met at the other skool moved to that one, it was funny shit cuz we were on a bus to that place,&nbsp;driving a tnight so yea we were singing stupid songs and it was so fuckin funny,&nbsp;when we reached our destination&nbsp;we had even more fun, we swam at the beach, we&nbsp;got a few drinks lol, we visited the ruins of "tajin" it was very interesting to see all these pyramids and stuff, then we saw a show that&nbsp;is typical of that zone, named "the papantla fliers" its a bunch of people who go to the top of a tower and tie their feet and they&nbsp;start spinning on the top of the tower&nbsp;IN THE AIR man its something cool and pretty interesting, and when the time to&nbsp;go back home we were again singing those ongs lol. also all&nbsp;the guys who were&nbsp;at the same seats i was started jackin off lol it was funny&nbsp;cuz i was surrounded by all these "dicks" haha so i did the same. and also&nbsp;the daniel dude (the guy from skool) did something i didnt expect him to do: blowy joby lmao. god it was weird but cool at the same time. i know this sound slike an erotic stroy lol but it isnt, its just that im remembering all the stuff i did and to give an explanation of why im bisexual. anyways some days later that dude and i had sex and blah blah lol im not gonn say a lot about that. and when&nbsp;my b-day came (july 5) the skool was already over, i was glad i was able to reach the 8th grade. i kept goin to the same skool.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   14 years: yea thats when i had the roughest time of my life, exactly by august of the 2003, my dad came by very drank, and he started beating me for no reason. i know i was an unwanted child, but just by him. he didnt want me to be born but oh well i was lol so screw him. anyways as i was saying he started beating me, it was horrible cuz he was kicking me and hitting me and damn i was not able to do anything. and he also threatened me to death if i said something of this to my mom. i had bruises and all but i told my mom i got in a fight at skool and she believed me. i remember a day when&nbsp;he and&nbsp;i were playing this game, ya know measuring strenght, and of course he won, and he started calling me names&nbsp;and shit, so, my mom went with some of her friends and we playe&nbsp;d again, a friend of mine was at my house so he tickled him and i won, so i called him names too a she did to me and he started beating me IN FRONT OF MY FRIEND. yea i told him not to tell anyone.&nbsp;and that torment kept going until december of the last year, when i decided to kill myself. i had that gun in my hands, loaded, ready to shoot... but some people helped me to get out of that situation when they told me that suicide wasnt the answer, and that it was not worth it, and they helped me. of course suicide is a quick and good answer, cuz you'll never be tormented again like that. but still,&nbsp;2 weeks before&nbsp; christmas, my mom wasnt home, she went to another state with my aunt and i was left with my father so he would "take care of me". that night became the worst, when he started beating me as usual, i did the worst thing you can do when a situation like that is going on: fighting back. i hit him hard in the face and he just looked at me, pulled out that gun and shot me in the arm. i blacked out due to the pain that the bullet caused to me. but i was able to get that bullet out at the hospital, i went alone so no one would find out. and my mom came back 2 weeks later, my arm was already healed when she came back, and for some strange reason my dad decided not to come back. the reason why i couldnt tell anyone about the way he treated me was becuz he is a cop, and he is the "most accurate" unit at his job, he got a lot of connections at the government, a his job and everywhere. so it would be useless. so i didnt see him for a while, but then he came back, this time i locked myself in my room, so he wouldnt do anything but it was so strange... he came cuz he wanted to apologize for being "bad" with me and for not caring when i needed anything. he wanted to come back but i didnt let him come back. but he kept coming to my house to bring food and money and everyhting we need. its strange cuz after all that torture he now wants to be my father, to wich i responded with a fuck off. and he kept coming but i always locked myself in my room.     15 years: this is now, im 15 years old, and well about my father, he keeps coming, i decided to talk to him and be nice, anyways he doesnt deserve it but this time i only talk to him for basic stuff, and i dont let him be with me alone, cuz that'd be like suicide. or i dont know but i think im better now... except for skool. im smart and all but i cant deal with algebra, and im so lazy, so it doesnt work. so this was all my post, i hope u had "fun" reading, and well to keep reading about my 15 years, just keep comin lol. see ya all, and dont cry when ya finish readin all this heh. byes     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       damn... its been like a week since jordan&nbsp;, my best friend and bro, left. he was taken to a foster home and he said he wont be able to get online until he is 21 year old and he is only 15. That'd be a lot of time and im not sure if i'll ever see him again. Its so sad, why do the people i love the most have to go away? its like this time i lost someone who was a very important part of my life, he was the best person i ever met. but well since all the "badass hoes" is now fucked up becuz of my fight with dana and jordan's leaving, i had to permanently delete the badass hoes website. it seemed like a very cool and nice project, but becuz of these "events" i had no choice. so i decided to start a new website, this time its a hacking website and its in spanish, at least i wont have to worry about updating other websites becuz i now only have two. but still i felt so sad when i deleted that site. oh well i'll try to get over it and i hope i see him again. i dont care about dana but jordan is really important... oh well i'll just keep going and thats all, but i'll miss that dude. so if you know some spanish, check out my site  urlLink http://www.sliphack.tk  it rules. See ya all later, i gotta study for the extra exam of math that will be on monday of the next week. I need to pass it so i'll really be a 9th grader, so goodbye people.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      duhh today is boring. maybe its cuz its 11:27 am, so i dont think anybody is up or willing to get on msn. when there's something inportanto to blog about i will so see ya later.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      since i stopped talkin to dana and told her to fuck off, im feeling soooo good... i bet she is now locked in a sanatory for schitzophrenic people. after all she deserves to die cuz she was using me to do the things she was not brave enough to do by herself. but finally i got rid of that whore and i'll be able to live my life as i want, i'll do whatever the fuck i want, i wont stop smoking and i wont do what other stupid people like dana wanted me to do. im free now and i wont let anyone control me.   Dana:  (die whore)i never wanted anybody more than i wanted you (i know)the only thing i ever really loved was hurting you   see ya all laters.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i was so pissed off yesterday cuz my mom was going to send me to a summer skool today cuz of the math thing. i thought my vacations were going to get fucked and i'd be studying but lmao today we went to that skool and oh surprise mommy, there were no vacant places in that skool to study that math shit. haha from being sad, mad and confused i came home with a big smile cuz im not going to any summer skool now. but anyways im going to study math here at my house on my own, maybe my sister will help me but i have a book and tomorrow i'll get some copies of the extra exam wich i will use to copy in the exam so i'll pass with a good qualification. i'll study in the mornings instead of the noon cuz that way i'll have time to be online all the day. well i'll post again later goodbye.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      lol oh yea, i wanna say thanks to the people who sent me ecards and happy b-day messages. yesterday my hotmail inbox was FULL and i was there reading mails and viewing ecards like for 3 hours. thanks to uh dana, dj osiris, soulbad, sam, student center, lycos, yahoo, my cousins, my sister, my bro, lol jordan u didnt say happy birthday o well ur my bro anyways. and thanks to everyone else who sent me emails and stuff i really appreciate it. but well, its july 6 now, today im going to somewhere lol i dont know where maybe we'll stay here or something i dont know. lol my "friends" from skool didnt even call me so fuck em all who cares. damn its cold here and its very soon no one's awaken at this time of the day i think lol. well see ya all later and i love ya people, less than dana of course.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      lol im so fuckin happy! im now 15 years old lol since 01:00 a.m haha. lol but my mom's b-day is in july 7 so i'll tell my family not to celebrate anything today, but tomorrow so my mom and i will be the kings lol. jeez i've been waiting for this day so yea lol im excited (not in the way u think lmao). uh yea now im a big, badass 15 y/o and this rocks. lmao im gettin older and today i wanna mess with people if i see my friends. but also i gotta pay 3 bucks today to a great frind, soulbad. he is the webmaster of this website http://www.tlshack.net just enter if you know spanish. the reason why i gotta pay is cuz he is letting me have my show at his internet radio station. so in order to keep it going i gotta pay but its worth it. to listen to the show and chat with us go to http://www.tlshack.net/radio/ lol once again, if you know spanish or at least some, check it out. i have my show on monday, wednesday and friday from 3:00 pm to 4:00 pm and if they need me to keep broadcasting i will so listen to me lol. damn happy birthday to meee, happy birthday to meeeeeee, hapy biirthday to meeee, happy birthday to mee! lmao. see ya all later lol. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yup!! tomorrow i'll go to veracruz beach with my sister where we'll catch up with my cousin John and his wife and we'll have a lot of fun and i cant wait.... well not really lol it snot like im pretty excited but yea its cool. lol like 2 hours ago, daniel, my friend from the old skool, came by to visit me! i wa slike "dude what the hell are ya doin here?" and yea it was cool we were remembering the old times and talkin about how are our lifes now that we are older. From being a loser kid and a nerd, he has became a real motherfucker hehe, and i like that, he's cool and umm here's a pic of him, he's not that cute now lol, but yea he's really cool:    he looks better with his glasses but o well he's crazy. Anyways, like a hour ago, ym mom and i were talkin cuz she founf out i was drinking and that i smoke... she said she doesnt want me to drink when im alone, and that she understands i wanna try out stuff but that i should do it with her permission, that she wont be mad or anything, she understands it and also she just gave me permission to smoke but she told me not to do it too often or too much, but if i do it, she said i should do it here, in my home and not in the streets like hiding from her or anything, she said i should trust her and that i should not drink cuz its badder than smoking. Its kool, now i dont have to hide anymore when im smokin, cuz she is lettin me do it, of course, always inside my house cuz it suks to smoke in the streets and u look shitty. Its kool. But okay, the topic of this message was to tell you that im goin to a trip tomorrow and i wont be on until monday, when i come back. So see ya later, have fun and miss me while im not here Mwahahaha lol. Bye Bye!   "Get it stuck up your ass motherfucking son of a bitch!" HaHa BiAtCh!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Now its time you see me, Kurt, like a real fuckin goth, thats what i am, i know this pic suck but o well, no one is perfect.      lookslike if i was fuckin high! lol. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>