<Blog>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You think you know me, but you don't.  You do not know they way I think, the way I care, the way I dream.  You do not know how much I have fallen for you, and you haven't even noticed how much you mean to me.  You do not know anything about me that really matters, and guess what? Who cares.... because the truth is that I don't even know me.  I have yet to find the answers.  I have yet to find out why I do the things I do and think the way I think.  The truth is I want to know me, and I want you to know me.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So.... I have now jumped on the bandwagon and stepped away from the world of buddy profiles to a more direct form of communication.... live journals.... yeah, this shall be interesting
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yeah, I have no earthly idea what was up yesterday.  I suppose everyone has those weird i-am-mad-at-the-world days.  Hopefully none of us will deal with those often.  But today was quite the opposite.  It was a great day.  A normal one.  But a great one.  I went to marching band and for some strange reason it doesn't bother me that I spent my Saturday morning standing in a parking lot.  And I went to a bunch of various places with my closest friends: the Library, the Mole Hole, Sonic, Dragon Stadium, Seven  Eleven, and my trampoline.  It was just one of those relaxing days that I love and wish I will always have.    Laughter has got to be one of the greatest things on earth, too.  I mean not only do you burn cals, but it makes you happy.  However, the key is being able to stop.  It is horrible when you have one of those silent laughing fits and you can't stop.... or breathe.  And sadly I am one of those who will keep on going.... and going.... and going.... just like the energizer bunny.  That, or I will stop laughing and a few minutes later I will burst out laughing out of no where just at the memory of whatever was so funny before.  And of course it isn't quiet.... it is one of those PPPPPPPPPFFFFFFFFUUUU!!! (with spit flying all over the place) and everyone in the room turns their heads in bewildered amazement.  But hey, what have I got to be ashamed of?  It's good, funny times....  hehe.... it's great. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Wow.   I am horrible.  I can't believe I actually posted that thing.  Sorry.  I am weird and out of control complainy lately.  My apologies....  I haven't been my normal me lately.... more self centered and whining.  And I have to reason to be!  Okay.... when i am better i will write again... bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Second day of rookie camp. It went better than the first.  Saw the Bourne Supremacy.  In a bad mood.  Being selfish and I don't really care about anything cause no one else care either.  Sorry I am being mean. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp; Yeah, twice in one night.... &nbsp;&nbsp; Wouldn't it be incredibly awesome to have a secret code with a close friend?&nbsp; Like in an office situation, you walk up to your close friend's desk and say, "Can you bring the Leopolf file up to me office later?"&nbsp; And what you really mean is I got something we need to talk about.... &nbsp;&nbsp; Of course this wouldn't be in a work-type situation.&nbsp; Afterall, it is only high school, and&nbsp; not even almost done.... halfway through high school.&nbsp; But it would be cool, no? &nbsp;&nbsp; Speaking of only halfway through high school.... I think I am ready for college.&nbsp; At tech, I would walk down the streets alone absorbing the atmosphere, and I want that atmosphere.&nbsp; I want to get away.&nbsp; be me. become me.&nbsp; See what is really inside there....  &nbsp;&nbsp; Oh and a mystery was solved.... engaged 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp; I love sun showers.&nbsp; I don't care how dorky it sounds.&nbsp; It is sunny, yet it rains.&nbsp; It is one of those surreal comforts I have found in my life.&nbsp; It is kinda funny because it is like that for my whole family.&nbsp; All of a sudden we all yell, "SUN SHOWER!"&nbsp; We are true Floridians. &nbsp;&nbsp; Yeah, so today was the first day of rookie camp.&nbsp; I had my screw ups of course.... but hopefully it will be better tomorrow and Saturday with the whole band.&nbsp; And that's about it there.... &nbsp;&nbsp; So, does everyone have little secrets?&nbsp; I just finished a book that was written by a British author and I loved it.&nbsp; I love the way they talk and use words like dappy and posh.&nbsp; It makes me smile.&nbsp; But I tried thinking of all my little secrets and quirks.... &nbsp;&nbsp; When I am alone in my car I turn up the music and sing really loudly &nbsp;&nbsp; I do the same at home in my room : ) &nbsp;&nbsp; I can sit away in my room and read for ages &nbsp;&nbsp; I get jealous quite easily &nbsp;&nbsp; I loose my temper a lot &nbsp;&nbsp; I will spend an entire day watching the "Anne" movies.... Anne of Green Gables, Anne of Avonlea, and the third one.... oops, I can't think of the name.... Gilbert Blithe wins me over everytime! &nbsp;&nbsp; I like lighting candles and playing with the wax &nbsp;&nbsp; I will let my room get as messy as my mom allows me to &nbsp;&nbsp; I love to laugh &nbsp;&nbsp; I think about a lot before I fall asleep and the thoughts often comfort me and make me smile &nbsp;&nbsp; I like to sit in the garge and watch the rain &nbsp;&nbsp; I borrow my sister's clothes &nbsp;&nbsp; I like to be happy &nbsp;&nbsp; When I was little I used to run around the house tilting my head side to side with my pointer finger pointing up and each hand alternating with my head.&nbsp; It is hard to explain, but we have it on video when I am in my ballet recital costume.... it is really funny.&nbsp; And I still do the head bit.... and people always ask me "What the heck are you going," or they laugh at me! &nbsp;&nbsp; I am quiet &nbsp;&nbsp; And I know a lot of those aren't really secrets, but they are little tidbits of me....&nbsp; I mean, what is the point of hiding who you are?&nbsp; Why be afraid?&nbsp; Don't know?&nbsp; Well, neither do I....  &nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp; I know I am gonna sound lk a complete nerd when I say this.... but I had a really good time at the freshmen kickoff tonight.&nbsp; We divided into ten groups,&nbsp;each with around four section leaders and about six freshmen.&nbsp;And we had to come up with a team name and cheer.&nbsp; We were the Exploding Magnesiumites.&nbsp; And we started off at the side of the stage, and I climbed inside a box (I was the only one small enough, and considering I was around all freshmen that is kinda sad, but....) and crawled to the middle of the stage.&nbsp; So it was just a box slowly moving across the stage, mysteriously.&nbsp; Then..... BOOM! I popped out of the box and yelled "BOOM!"&nbsp; It was really funny.&nbsp; Then the rest of my team came out and cheered&nbsp;a lil chant-y thingie.&nbsp; And it was an all around good time. &nbsp; But oh my.... it is kinda late and I got to get&nbsp;up early.... so adieu for now....  (I know this was a short, lame post.... but I have been kinda busy today.... my apologies) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Huh.... i liked my hair.&nbsp; Key word.... liked, as in past tense.&nbsp; I am getting a lil worried/self concious about it now.&nbsp; Perhaps it is better longer?&nbsp; I am kinda confused.&nbsp; Oh well.... I suppse there isn't much I can do about it now.... It will grow out eventually.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello.... &nbsp;&nbsp; 'Twas a good day today.&nbsp; Chopped off a bit of hair, read, and learned a lil grammar.&nbsp; Surpsrisingly, this encounter at KD was better.&nbsp; One of the workers knows me by name and was kidding with me saying that I was banned and wasn't allowed to come.... lol.&nbsp; "I was lk okay" and he laughed.&nbsp; And the class was huge, and had some funny kids in it.&nbsp; I also talked with Shyam and Lauren there.&nbsp; It is awesome to see friends that I haven't gotten to see&nbsp;much this&nbsp;summer.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; And I love my hair cut.&nbsp; It is shorter than i had planned.... but i love it!&nbsp; It is kinda funny b/c I got my hair cut, Craig got his hair cut, and Liz is getting her hair cut tomorrow.&nbsp; I thought that was an interesting coincidence. &nbsp;&nbsp; And.... hmm, that's about it.&nbsp; Mmmm.... I feel kinda guilty because I missed a tee-shirt meeting and we had to have three sketches done by tomorrow.&nbsp; I hope it is all okay.&nbsp; I will give Stephanie a call tomorrow.&nbsp; Yeah.... &nbsp;&nbsp; Perhaps that is all.... busy solving a mystery.... (that reminds me of Sarah McLauchlan's (sp?) song building a mystery) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp; Everyone is back now!&nbsp; It is soo awesome that they're all home.&nbsp; Even though I don't get to see them all that much this week, it could be worse, no?&nbsp; They could still be gone.&nbsp; And I got to see them all today which was great.&nbsp; I had missed them so&nbsp; much.&nbsp;  &nbsp; So at the moment I am great, which I am sure you wanted to know....&nbsp; I get a hair cut tomorrow too!&nbsp; Sounds kinda strange, but I look forward to hair cuts for some reason... dunno why.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; I never realized how much I like to be the center of attention.&nbsp; It is horrible.&nbsp; People will be talking and I will always interject so the conversation turns back to me.&nbsp; Or I try to be good and quiet and that turns the attention back to me, still.&nbsp; I feel bad about that.&nbsp; And it has gotten worse over the past few weeks.&nbsp; I hope that this journal will help.... because all I do in here is talk about myself... me, me, me. &nbsp; Jasper is great.&nbsp; He is Liz's dog.&nbsp; He is incredibly good mannered and well-behaved.&nbsp; When I first got there, he didn't jump or get over excited.&nbsp; I'm happy he is such a good dog and has such good owners.&nbsp; Okay... i go now 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp; Okay... we have gotten a start on my room!!! The bed is down and out along with the curtains.&nbsp; I have the gruesome (I know I spelled that wrong) task of cleaning my closet tonight... ahhh!&nbsp; Well, yeah.... so I am gonna go do that... eventually.... &nbsp;&nbsp; This is the last day of summer! But it was a good last day.&nbsp; The weather was nice and I got to drive with the windows down.&nbsp; I haven't been able to do that in ages.&nbsp; 'Twas nice.&nbsp; And I will hopefully get to talk to Liz and see how Jasper is!&nbsp; I can't believe she is getting a Great Dane!! I am soo excited.&nbsp; Which may seem kinda strange as she, not I, is getting the dog.&nbsp; Oh well... &nbsp;&nbsp; I am getting a good start on the all-state music.&nbsp; I can't play worth ____.&nbsp; But that's alright.&nbsp; I  will  be able to play come auditions.&nbsp; So... not much interesting to talk about today.&nbsp; Which isn't that much of a change from every other day.... hahaha... i crack myself up.... so sad... &nbsp;&nbsp; Well off i go to clean and practice.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp; Oof... this is my last day of summer!!!!&nbsp; Because from tomorrow on out, I am going to be busy beyond belief.&nbsp; Tomorrow we are painting my room and finishing up house work.&nbsp; Monday, I have a lesson, Karen Dillard Workshop, and a presentation in Dallas on Yale.&nbsp; Tuesday, I have a hair cut appointment, and more Karen Dillards.&nbsp; (and Craig comes home, but I won't get to see him.... grrr) Wednesday, I have leadership 10-4,&nbsp; then Freshmen Kickoff 6-9.&nbsp; Thursday and Friday.... rookie camp and Karen Dillards.&nbsp; Saturday... FULL BAND!!!&nbsp; So that basically take us the week.... &nbsp;&nbsp; Unfortuantely, I will be visiting Karen Dillards quite a bit.&nbsp; I went there yesterday to make up lesson 11, and there were originally four people in the class, but three were out of the county. And, the fourth kid showed up late.&nbsp; So I had around 15 minutes alone with the instructor.&nbsp; And she asked me if I had had her in class before.&nbsp; And I said "yes, last summer".&nbsp; Then she asked me if&nbsp;my scores had improved.&nbsp; I said, "a lil, bit. I think...."&nbsp; Then she gave me a look and said that she could&nbsp;check the&nbsp;charts and see.&nbsp; So, she looks and&nbsp;tells me&nbsp;"no they haven't, but I also see that you haven't been attending workshops or doing practice tests.&nbsp;&nbsp;this is like band.&nbsp; if you don't work then you won't improve." and on and on she went.&nbsp;&nbsp;And basically made me feel extremely stupid.&nbsp; So of course, I was incredibly relieved when the other kid showed up.&nbsp; &nbsp;But she wanted to pick on me because I was a "slacker."&nbsp; So we worked on sample problems and such.... and because I was incredibly frustrated and somewhat downtrodden, I answered them all wrong at first.&nbsp; Way to boost the self-esteem.&nbsp; But anyways, my socre was pretty decent in the end.&nbsp; But I will be going there a lot more now just to prove her wrong.&nbsp; I will do better on the upcoming SAT and PSAT.&nbsp; Plus... I was "making up" a lesson.&nbsp; I obviously haven't been around all that much to go to the workshops and do full length tests.... oh well.... &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;That was my ramble for today.&nbsp; Everything is cool though.&nbsp; I am talking to Leonie, my bud from England.&nbsp; She is awesome, and I can't wait until they come over from England. Three months from today! I can't wait.&nbsp; And Liz is getting her great dane, Jasper from Austin tomorrow.... more Yay!&nbsp; So , that's about it.&nbsp; I  can  keep going... only two people I know&nbsp;of actually know this journal exists, but I think I will go find some food that I shouldn't be eating in the first place.... I used to have self-control.... dunno where it went.... it would be cool to be teeny again... oh well.... maybe one day with band camp perhaps helping me along a bit.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Suppose I said I am on my best behavior And there are times I lose my worried mind?  Would you want me when I'm not myself? Wait it out while I am someone else?  Suppose I saidColors change for no good reason And words will go From poetry to prose  And I, in time, will come around I always do for you  Suppose I said You're my saving grace? &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; -John Mayer Room for Squares "Not Myself"  &nbsp;&nbsp; I was trying to get a&nbsp; move on the All State etudes as they have come out!! (yikes&nbsp;as it was especially horrendous (spelling?) because I haven't played the E-fer in a while)&nbsp;when I heard this song (it was playing in the background b/c I am weird and like to have background music while&nbsp;I practice).&nbsp; And it gave me a thought that I have been considering quite a bit today:  &nbsp;&nbsp; Are people different while they are around different people.&nbsp; And if they are, which one is their real self?  &nbsp;&nbsp; Liz and I talked about this today, saying that we act differently by ourselves than with a group.&nbsp; And I noticed that it is quite a valid point.&nbsp; For instance, when I am with a group I am more on the sidelines.&nbsp; I observe and watch everyone else.&nbsp; I take notes of what everyone's personality is like.&nbsp; But then, (and this is a new thought.... i may get a lil jumbled here, and if you get confused don't worry b/c it is likely that I will become confused as well) I am seeing how these people are in a group setting.&nbsp; There is a good chance that the people are different in a one-on-one situation.&nbsp; But anyways, I see them, and they see me.&nbsp; They think I am quiet and shy.&nbsp; But really, I normally have nothing I consider worth adding to the conversation.&nbsp; In actuality, I am quite the opposite.&nbsp; I am a fool.&nbsp; I make fun of myself and kid with my closer friends.&nbsp; I suppose I just take time to warm up to people.&nbsp; But once I do, I don't care what they think and go all out weird.&nbsp; I'll bet that they wish I hadn't warmed up to them at times.... heheh!!! Too bad for them... just kidding.... at least I hope they don't... oh well, they would let me know anyways.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp; But yeah, who is the real me?&nbsp; Who is the real you?&nbsp; The fun outgoing person at the parties?&nbsp; Or the best friend who always provides a listening ear?&nbsp; Or both?&nbsp; Hmmm..... food for thought. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp; Is it sad that I am counting down the days until the 26th?&nbsp; It probably is, but what can I do to help it.&nbsp; It has been ages since I have seen my friend..... well actually only two weeks.... hmm.&nbsp; Have I gotten too dependent on that person?&nbsp; I mean I don't seek his approval on everything (sorta) and I am not completely, crazy obsessed.&nbsp; It's just good to be in his company.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; But it is getting better.&nbsp; My other great friend came back.&nbsp; So now we are in a state of missing him together.&nbsp; 'Tis a shame that he left us to our own devices..... hehe.... actually more funny that we are on our own.&nbsp; We (when I say we I actually mean I) am kinda weird when left to our (my) own devices.&nbsp; Oh well.... &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; But don't get me wrong.&nbsp; I am not complaining.&nbsp; I know that I have a great life, and it keeps on improving.&nbsp; Who knows how great it could be in the next ten years? &nbsp;&nbsp; But how many times have I said "I" in this passage?&nbsp; Fifiteen times! Wow.... there has to be something better to talk about than that.... &nbsp;&nbsp; Perhaps later.... I have work for my college prep academy... Karen Dillards. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mother, sister, father, sister, mother Everything's cool now Oh, my life is good I've got more than anyone should Oh, my life is good And the past in the past I was living in the shadow Of someone else's dream Trying to find a hand to hold but every touch felt cold to me I'm living in a new day I'm living it for me And now that I am wide awake Then I can finally be Don't feel sorry for me  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Oddly enough.... an Ashlee Simpson song.... kinda liked the lyrics, but never heard the song.... oh well.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep... it has been ages since I last wrote in here....&nbsp; Over 2 months!! ahh... &nbsp; But tons has happened during those two months.&nbsp; I have gone to leadership camp, band camp (yeah, no comments please), started marching band, danced with 20 guys I will never see again, became an auntie, gotten sunburnt, died on the trampoline and lived to tell the tale, and oh so much more.&nbsp; The summer is basically over and it makes me quite sad.&nbsp; But the ending of my summer means that band started and it is going to be a good year.&nbsp; I didn't really go anywhere this summer which is cool, because it would have added even more chaos to me hectic summer.&nbsp; I got to hang with my friends most of June, and July has been more of me hanging and keeping occupied outside the dynamic trio.&nbsp; Also, all region music comes out!!!! I am definitely gonna be living off the E-fer b/c i really want to make state.&nbsp; Afterall, I am following Michelle's reign.&nbsp; And she has made state the past two years.&nbsp; I am not the strongest player (wait.... lemme rephrase musician) so it is gonna take a bit of work to get there.... but i am up to the challenge.... yeah.&nbsp; Well I am gonna go somewhere....  Also, the past note had no general audience of author.&nbsp; I was just blabbing away.&nbsp; I was kinda in a weird mood and went at the keyboard.&nbsp; Yup.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Some people make you happy.  Others make you sad.  Some make you angry.  Some people will surprise you.  Some people will always be predictable.  There are some you can't live without. And others you can't wait to get away from.  Some who will overcome great odds and some who will get past their personal obstacles.     And then there is that someONE.  The some one who makes you happy, sad, and angry.  Someone who surprises you beyond belief yet is still predictable. Someone you can't live with or bear to be without.  Someone who overcomes all odds.       There is a wide variety of people.  Many you will get along with.  Most of whom will be simply aquaintances.  A few will be opponents.  And even fewer will become the ones you will always be able to turn to and depend on.  But all of them make a dent in your life.  Mold a little bit of it like a ball of clay.  Sooner or later to become a final product.... you.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "There are no sure things in life.  That is the one sure thing I know."       -Charlie from  A Beautiful Mind              So I watched  A Beautiful Mind  with Liz and Craig today.  It is an excellent movie and has really good views in it.  The quote above is from the main character's (Russel Crowe) "roomate."  Who does not truly exist, but he is a good guy.  He is played by the actor who acted as Chaucer in  A Knight's Tale . And I, bringing out the analytical part of me, remembered this quote.    For the most part I agree with it.  A majority of the components in life are arbitrary.  Nothing is set in stone.  All you have in life can be taken away.  And everything wrong in life can take a change for the better.  And no matter how many times you promise you will always be there for someone, or that you will always love someone, it always has the chance of changing or something or someone else can come along (as horrible as it sounds, it happens).     However, it seems kinda pessimistic at times.  For instance, my life is at, possibly, the highest point is has ever been.  But then, it isn't sure.  It can always change and become worse.  My best friend's situation proves that.  All of a sudden things were fine, and now they're not.     I prefer the optomistic view.  That even though things seem perfect, they can improve even more, beecome a degree of greatness that I can't even imagine.  I like thinking at all is well and will always be.  It may not be entirely healthy.  I mean I acknowledge the bad things in life and face them with the best of my ability.... it just helps at times to wish they weren't there.  And it seems kind of sad to me when I think that things can change.  Because I have so much that I couldn't bare to lose.  I have all that I need and more, and I know that I don't deserve them.  They are too good for me.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "It's when you cry just a little but you laugh in the middle that you've made it And don't it feel allright. and don't it feel so nice."        -Jason Mraz, "Tonight, Not Again"    I think that summarizes my mood and day at the moment. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chihuahua, small dog, chihuahua introduces...  We are the S.O.'s, you've got it made, we're here to give you, a serenade,  A Serenade!  Big circle, little circle, big circle little circle, EXTRA LARGE CIRCLE, extra small circle.... NOW BUST IT!  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So back when I went to leadership camp at UTA, there was a middle aged man named Scotty.  Now, Scotty was the morning arerobics teacher.  He was about the age of the modern teengager's father, but had the body of the average teenage girl's boyfriend.  And in our early wake up aerobic, Scotty said that what ever you expend you will recieve back.  Of course he was talking about exercise, but couldn't it apply to life in general?  No, really.  This may seem kinda dorky, but when it is considered it makes a tad bit of sense.  See, if you are happy and concerned, then those qualities will somewhat rub off on those around you and they will be happy and caring, too.  Maybe.  Because, that is how it works in band.  If the leaders are psyched and engergetic, then the section picks up a bit of that chagre and become energized themselves.   Yeah, band talk.  But band definitely has its good points, even if we all have to wake up mondo early and stay there uber late.  (hah, I used "mondo" and "uber")  But we have now finished the first hard week.  Things are going to ease up in difficulty, if we mantain our spirits.    Tomorrow i get to see a couple of my friends that I haven't seen in a bit.  Now, of course a bit may not be that great amount of time, but I am looking forward to seeing them.  Yeah, I am out of topics, and I know it has been a lil bit since i wrote in here last.... but I am out of stuff to talk about.... (shrug) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So the band has made it through the first two days of band craziness.  Only.... three more to go!  But we're learning the show after tomorrow so it is all good.  And that is all for the band update of tonight....    But i have a question.  What makes someone pretty/good looking?  Did someone come up with a certain list of what makes someone easier to look at? And if so what is the distinguishing line between ugly/cute/gorgeous?   Because today at the ortho one of the new ladies, who i guess, doesn't know my family all that well said i was as cute as a button.  But since when has a button been cute?  Don't get me wrong i appreciate the compliment.... but that phrase always striked me as interesting. But i seriously wonder why it is that one person is good looking while another isn't.  I mean did we just evolve into a twisted society where we seek thin, tall, tan perfection?   Society now a days is based a lot on looks.  Why? Is that all there is?  It is kinda frustrating and I dunno..... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Life is great.  I am great.  Everything is great.  Not to sound incredibly happy-go-lucky, my-life-is-so-perfect-and-i-am-rubbing-it-in-your-face. Because my life isn't perfect.  Is anyone's?  So, life may have its imperfections, but that doesn't mean it can't be great.   Band is going really well.  The other section leaders are awesome.  Cathy is just crazy funny with her "ring tone." And Sarah pumps everyone else up.  And Katie and the guys are awesome too. Wow.... i sound as cheerful as a Frangos.  Hmmm.... kinda creepy. But Liz is in band now too.  And my other buds in band too (except Kelly) so that makes it even better.    It is kinda sad though.... my life has become entirely band.  I realized that the only time i spend at my house is to sleep, shower, and eat.  The rest of it is spent on a parking lot, at school no less.  But what do i care?  I am having a blast, and if i am ridiculed.... bleep them!!! (yeah, I am a wuss and don't cuss.... so shush.)    Yeah.... well I go now....
     

    
</post>


</Blog>