<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Growing up I always knew my Mom was special. She had served in Viet Nam as a nurse. She held the hands of many soldiers that were dyeing. She was their mother, girfriend, wife, or any name that they called out when death was at their door step. I want this blog to be a place where I can tell my Mother's story as well as having other nurses, not just from Viet Nam, to tell their stories. This is not meant to exploit you in any way. I just want it to be a place where women from war can come together and discuss the things that happened to them.   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       My mother's first assignment was an Air Force base in California. It was here where she was first taught the rules of being a flight nurse and how to run codes in the military. She said that she saw a lot of asses because the first two weeks she was on vaccination duty.&nbsp; This is also the place she met her first husband. I have never met this man. I only know that his last name is Davis and that they weren't married for very long. My he and my Mother flew to Vegas and got married much to the dismay of my grandparents. I haven't searched for him because I wouldn't know what to say. I also don't know if he survived the war. I do know though that he and my mother were divorced with in a two year time span I believe. If anyone reads this and it sounds like you, or your father please let me know. I'd like to know a little bit about my Mom's first husband.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My mother then went to boot camp. Not the regular one that you've seen in the movies, this is for NCOs. They learned to march in a straight line and to fire a 9mm. At this point my Mom was okay, but then came the day that she had to learn to repel. Somehow she got her self upside down and then she started to panic yelling for the instructor to come and help her out. My mother cried and said that she didn't want to die. Well about half an hour later with the instructor ready to go AWOL she made it right side up and down the side of the wall. Needless to say my mother has never repelled again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So my mother decided that she was going to join the Air Force. My grandparents were totally against the idea, so she waited for them to go out of town and she signed up. When my Grandmother found out she broke down and cried. My mother was the first child to leave the nest. Grams knew that she would never come back and be the same person. She was scared that war would some how kill my Mother's inner spirit. My Grandfather who was a WWII and Korea vet felt proud and knew that it was one of the ways that my mother could leave. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After her stint in California my mother was transferred to Ramstein Airfoce Base to care for men who were to sick to go home but well enough to be flown out of a war zone. It was here where she learned to drink good wine and beer. This is also where Mom started to change. I know this because the time line begins to shift. There are gaps in to talk about and things that she doesn't. I believe here that she started to develop her PTSD. I understand now how difficult it is for her to live with some of those memories. 
     

    
</post>


<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went down to my home town today to see my father and stepmother. They seem supportive of me managing my depression. It's hard to talk about it tough because my father seems to think that the depression doesn't come from his side of the family. All I have to say about that is I had an Uncle who tried to jump off a bridge in Pittsburgh. Not much more to say now. See you on the next post. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I feel all out of sorts. We had a power outage last night so I slept through my Doctor's visit. Then my husband wanted to make love. He was so gentle and kind. He held me and told me that everything was going to be okay. It was that intimacy that only a husband and wife can share. He seems to know exactly when to hold me and make me feel better.   As I look out the window of our office I see white tree pollen falling it looks like spring snow. It's beautiful to look at but we have to get it out of our yard or we'll have so many weeds we won't know what to do with them. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it happened. I fell into that low deep depression that is just displayed all over my body. I'm tired, hungry, and lonely the three things that can spell danger in a depressed world. I'm going to try to meditate to see if it will make me feel better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is one of those days where I'm trying not to fall into a deep depression. I want to just lay on the couch and do nothing. I've decided that I need to take a short walk just to get my energy up and working. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was talking to my therapist today about making peace of things that happened when I was little. I wrote out who I wanted to forgive, and why they had caused me pain. Then we took it outside and burned it. It was almost like giving a sacrifice to God. I feel better now because some of that was released today. He advised me to keep doing it until I feel better about certain situations. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a long one. I simply just wanted to get out of the house and do something, but my anxiety kept coming in waves. I would make it out to the car then I'd have to turn back and go inside. I know that if I don't go out tomorrow we will be totally out of milk, toilet paper, and printer paper. Aha the necessities of life in a small town.   I really want to just quit sometimes. It seems so easy. Yet I always hold on by some thread of hope that tomorrow will be a better day. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am trying to make amends with my family. It is really difficult. When my brothers and sisters were little there mother died suddenly. Then my Father mend my Mother and was re-married shortly after (2 years). My brothers and sisters were much older than I was when I was born. So at that point I had a disadvantage. I was the only child by my Mother and the youngest of 5 by my father. When we were growing up I didn't understand the tentsion in the home. It always felt like I was walking on egg shells. As I aged that feeling gave way to anger. My parents divorced when I was 19 and the rift grew in my family. My older sisters and brother refused to talk to my Mom. My brother who was closest in age to me really didn't know what to do. This left me and Mom alone together trying to figure out how we were going to live on our own.  Now that I'm older I want to mend the rifts between my sisters and brother. It's hard. I leave messages on answering machines but no one calls back. I keep wondering if I'm doing the right thing. Should I have supported them way back when when the separation first started. Or should I let things be. I have no idea how to do this. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I woke up this morning I found that my cats had made muddy prints all over my comforter. In a way it was cute, but I also wanted to make little furry bath mats out of both of them. Cats are so easy to forgive though.   My depression is back. I'm just feeling a little down right now. I've found out that I've gained a lot of weight because of the medications. It seems though I can loose the weight if I do give it a try. I refuse to go on a diet because they don't work. I'm going to make some lifestyle changes. My stepmother works with overweight teens so I'll follow her plan.   There are some days that I just want this to be over. I'm sick of taking medications, and going to doctor's offices. It just is a reminder of how difficult this can be. I've read up on Merton's Sick Role. I've found that I can have deviant behavior and still get better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I found this beautiful picture of glass beads. Just thought that I'd share
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was watching a TV program today about the human genome. This doctor had it mapped out on a huge piece of paper, he then started to point out specific genes on specific chromosome. I suddenly realized that my Manic Depression was one of the little specks. I finally saw it visually. It was like a light bulb went off in my head. Manic Depression is only a speck compared to the rest of the information my DNA contains. It just made me feel slightly better about my self. I also know that there are doctors out there that are trying to find some sort of cure for it as well. My doctor has said that sometime in my lifetime that there will be better medications for Manic Depression. I pray that he is right. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night it rained really bad here. But I was asleep when it happened. My husband comes bursting into our bedroom and starts to shut all the windows. I think that I did end up damaging some things that are in our room but I have to wait for him to wake up before I can tell. The reason I couldn't hear the storm is that my meds had put me into some type of coma where I hear nothing and don't move in the bed. It can get scary sometimes because I have slept through  the smoke alarm.   On another topic I saw Bend it Like Bechem last night. I highly recommend this movie if you are going to an Indian wedding. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My husband and I were snapping at each other today. We had to take our nephew to his baseball pictures. Let me draw you a little picture of what it is like: take all the children ages 6-12 from a 30 mile radius, cram them in a hot room with photo equipment that is somewhat like a generator, then add cookies, cupcakes, and soda charging huge prices that would make the US government blush. This is my first time doing this so now when Soccer season comes up we should be better prepared.   I can feel myself starting to level off, but there are warning signs that I can see. I'm wanting to be alone a lot, I'm tired all the time, and I have had difficulty with anyone touching me. There are, however; have been improvements I am not hearing voices and the scratching in the walls has stopped. I've also started to do my relaxation therapy.  The worst part of this is learning how to openly feel my emotions. I've never been good at doing that. I've been good at taking all of the negative thoughts, feelings, and actions and putting them away where no one can see them. My Mother used to always say "Heather, Smile" well it was really difficult to smile when I was thinking about taking a whole bottle of aspirin. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's the kind of day that my Mother would say that "God gave us this beautiful day.. so use it!" Then I would be pushed out the door to play with kids that didn't like me very much.   I had this little house that was set back on my parents property. The kids, because they didn't like me, burned it down. They seemed to think it was a joke and that they would get off scott free. Well surprise they did. After that happened my Mom let me stay inside and read no matter what the temperature was.   Books became my shield. I was able to transport myself to many different places. It made me think that everything would be okay. In some ways it helped. In others, like social skills, it made me lacking. Part of it was hard as well when I figured out in high school that I was smarter than some of my teachers. That's when I knew that I had to get out and get a real education. First from books, then from being on my own. Responsibility so to speak. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My husband seems to think that I'm a horrible driver. Now here are the straight facts. 1)I've never been in an accident that was my fault. I've been backed into twice. 2) I have had 1 speeding ticket in my life. He had his license suspended because of so many speeding tickets. SO HA!  Other than that things are gong well. I wonder if it's gong to rain today. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I finished up the day, and now I'm completely exhausted. The medications have done me in again. Sometimes I feel totally dependent on them. It's like my Doctor is my drug dealer. At one point in my life I had to hide one of my meds because a room mate of mine would take it for fun.   It's hard to understand sometimes. I can just go upstairs and curl up and not want to be around anyone. Other times I feel like having party.   That's it for tonight folks.... see you on the flip side. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so today I'm really Manic. I feel happy and it's like I can take on the world. I know that I have to be careful, or I could shoot myself right into a depression. Some good news is that I've stopped hearing voices and noises that weren't there. The medications have taken that down. I just have to wait for the rest of them to kick in. I wonder who would I be with out Manic depression? Would I just be a plain Betty that is like some sort of Stepford Wife? I don't know. I do know however that it does help define my life in some way. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I awake today from a med induced haze. I swear sometimes a bomb could go off across the street and I wouldn't hear it. I've actually slept through the smoke alarm in my house before.   At any rate I'm finding that the Spring light is making me feel slightly better. I can go outside and smoke with out having to wear a parka and ski mask.   That's all for now. See you in the next post. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           I want to create a place where I can be completely honest about my Bi-Polar disorder. Sometimes it can be the best thing that has ever happened to me. I am really creative and can see colors in their brightest hue. I can write poems that come from such an emotional place that I look back at them and wonder who wrote them. It is also my worst curse. I rapidly cycle through my phases. I can go from Manic to Mania in less than 24 hours. My husband has to keep all of my banking information, my checks, debit card, and credit card so I don't spend us out of house and home. Sometimes I feel like I'm 14.       The worst part of it all is that I feel so lonely. I know that only 75% of us make it. I've been in group therapy where there have been other Bi-Polars, but because of the rarity of mine I still feel isolated.       I want to create this place to keep me going in some of my darkest times. I know that there are others out there who are going through the same thing. I just want to find them. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I have to go back to group therapy. It's Monday-Friday 9am-3pm just to make sure that I'm not hurting my self any more. I think that this is completely stupid. I'm not going to kill myself or anything. I'm just sick of it. In fact I'm sick of this whole damn thing if I could just be diabetic or something that is more controable I'd be much happier. God dammed I'm sick to death of all of this total crap!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a phone interview today with a company. During the interview the guy said I sounded way too young to have the position. Knowing that this was an illegal way of obtaining my age I decided to tell him that I was a college graduate and had been in the work force for two years. He grumbled and then said that it didn't seem like I was a good fit for the job, and that he was sorry that I wasted his time. Right... bastard. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I swear I had all my pills lined up in my head then logic kicks in. I've already tried this once and it didn't work too well. I looked in the mirror and saw a little part of myself that I understood, so I stopped and called my Mom. She made it seem better I will leave my job on my terms and find something different. I relaxed, then fed the baby (not mine I live with room mates that have one.. I just baby sit). I feel so lonely sometimes. I know that this is a sentence that I write over and over again, but it is so true. I'm alone most of the time. My head swirls with thoughts that I can barely control. It's not easy, but then again no one said it would. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My job just sent me a letter today saying that I am out of FMLA leave as of May 31. Well being June 1st I have no idea now if I am being paid or what is happening with everything. I have gone into a panic cycle. I have no idea if I have a job or what I am being paid. My stomach lurches every time I go near that letter. God I wish I could find a better job that understands what I am going through. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So as most of you know I hate my job. I now have a new manager that seems to think that we are all his work horses and that we are to be at his beck and call. He set a daily limit of how many questions that we can ask him. He also said that he doesn't know how to work half the systems that we work on so he is going to need us to teach him how. Okay I've worked at this company for two years, and it's gone through a lot of changes but me teaching my manager how to use our systems is a total testament to the Peter principle. This guy has just been passed along until he gets to a spot where he has no idea what he's doing.&nbsp; UGGGG!!!! I'm going back to school and thats all there is to it.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so it's almost 3am and I can barely sleep. My cycles are all off again. I'm jumping at everything and having nightmares again. I really just want this all to stop. It hurts inside to even say this. Personally I think if I just go up to my bed and lay there it would be better than sitting in this dark room with this glow in the dark keyboard typing out all of my thoughts. But I did make a promise to anyone that is going to read this that I was going to be honest about bi-polar disorder and all of it's oddities. Next week I could be feeling just fine so I have to kind of take each day as it comes. We'll see how the rest of this day goes. Oh and if any of you want a good glow in the dark keyboard for your moded out computer www.thinkgeek.com has some of the best. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had this long conversation with my family today. My husband and I have decided to not have children because of my bi-polar disorder and a lung condition that is genetic in his family. My parents took the news well... His didn't. His father really wants a boy to carry on the family name. His mother wants grandchildren from us. They kept saying that we'd change our minds and that one day we would be parents. I've decided along with my husband that we would adopt when the time was right. I want to adopt a child out of the American foster system. I feel that being bounced around from home to home is awful and so does my husband. I just want to give a kid a chance that he never would have had. My stepmother said that we should really adopt from an Asian country. Yet, that would mean that we would get a girl. I feel so lost now. I think I just need to sleep on this so I can make my decision later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it's been over a month since I've been able to write. My husband and I are celebrating our second wedding anniversary this weekend. I'm excited about that.   The bi-polar disorder is still rearing it's head occasionally. My meds appear to be working but I haven't been stable yet for over a year. I just want to stay in a hospital so I can get better but insurance wouldn't cover it. I've thought about that so many times. Just going to the hospital and checking myself in. I know I can't I have other responsibilities. It sucks but that is the way that life goes.   Is anyone else out there that feels the same way I do? I'm reaching out here. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm learning that working for a large company is not something that I want to do. I'm seriously thinking about quitting and working at a local bar. I'd get tipped and I could set my own schedule. I just get this feeling that my life is going in the wrong direction. I now feel like I have the power to make this happen. I don't know if it came after I've been doing all this therapy or if it's always been there and I'm just discovering it. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>