<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    As a collector of quirky product ads from late 19th-century to 1950s, I find this one for children's medicine both amusing and disturbing...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here's a treat for you, Terrette: Rufus, the hot gay man I wish were straight.  :), April 20, 04 at The Drink nightclub. He was so close I almost peed my pants!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The dumb cityslicker has relented...but Bear hunts are still bad!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks Chris for reminding me yet another memorable moment in the disaster of Troy. I present to you a taste of the Oscar moment to come: Prince Pansy tries to convince us that he'll be a great manly provider to Helen, the face that launched a thousand ships (or just a German actress with too much kohl around the eyes).  Paris: With me, you'll never be safe.  Though I'm just a useless prince, I'll provide for us. We can live off the land! Be like those nasty peasants who--you know--catch rabbits and grow things...no more of this life of luxury for us! Now if only I could figure out how to pitch this tent.   Helen: (swoon)Oh Paris, you're such a hunk. Take me now. The end.  (the sad thing is that I didn't change the words much, honest)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the toilet speaking. No actually, it's Matthea, making fun of Kate Naus.  Why do I have a butt shot of you on the internet? Because Nickelback told me to do it.  He likes your pants around your feet.  Sigh, how'd the hell did we end up like this? Simple.  You put on a wife-beater, grow a mullet, and call yourself Achilles.  Or Brad Pitt. Whichever doesn't seem to matter.  Because there will be a day, when Nickelback will find you. He will pinch your ass and wink, "Now you're a juicy fella." And you won't be able to get away.  Only the pirates will mourn your fate, hobbling over the industrial wasteland of southern ontario scowling "yarr" and "criminy." Your pants will end up at your feet and Nickelback will be there.  He is always there...BWOHAHAA! The end. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Kate's butt says, "I like your pants around your feet.  Nickelback is my best friend"
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Kate on top of the world--Bruce Penninsula, Tobermory ON
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Asian Christina's Trailer Park.  A Happy Ho embracing her name on the board. "Yes, this is MY fellowship!"
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I slept today in my usual spot where I like the smell of leather shoes and musty coats by the radiator.  The human females in the house had left on some peculiar outing--even the old one who never goes anywhere, but who I like because she feeds me scraps from the kitchen when nobody's looking.  Ah, the promise of peaceful sleep soon overcame me, and soon I was having the most delicious dream about catching that blasted Tinkerbell, the pussycat next door, and chewing her tail off. Just as I was going to tear off a piece of my precious catch, that blundering fool of a girl snatched me from my sweet reverie.  I awoke, smothered against this most irritating human and being groped all over.  "Oh, what a cute BABY! smoochie smoochie..." For the love of god, girl! Can't you see I'm a dog? Ugh, these humans.  I'll remember to pee in her shoe next time she's out.  Better yet, I'll leave her a present in the closet.  Stupid bitch.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wondered if I had made a big mistake.  I asked my mom and grandma to see the tulips with me today at Dow's Lake, and it all seemed to go fine until mom began harrassing grandma about what she was wearing, then going on a rant about how she can't do anything, even dress herself.  "Give her a break," I said. "She's eighty."  But what can I say? Mom never listens to me.  I guess going out for a walk in the park is never...a walk in the park when it comes to my family.    Well, we got to Dow's Lake in relative peace.  I'm glad my grandma got a chance to get out.  I wanted to take her because she's always stuck in the house, she can't speak English, and can't walk very far.  All in all, it wasn't too bad at all. Mom cooled off, and we took pictures with the tulips and I bought us a Killaloe sunrise Beavertail.  We sat on a bench in the park, munching on cinnamon covered fried dough.  I can't remember how it began, but we started talking about how grandma got together with gramps.  Apparently, he was 13 when he began to "pursue" her...when she was 16.  What a whippersnapper.  At 27, she finally married him.  Man, that's a long time to go after someone!  Thinking about it, I can't believe it was 1939 when she was my age, watched Charlie Chaplin movies in Hong Kong as a child, and lived through the Japanese invasion.    I guess it's always a hassle when you have to deal with family, but when you slow down, listen to your grandma talk about a life she lived seventy years back, it's worth the trip.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Do you know what's waiting beyond that beach? Immortality! Take it! It's yours!" (Brad Pitt as Achilles).   There are too many places in this movie where I could not stop laughing.  I guess once you sign up for a movie named TROY, you're asking for cheese piled in heaps, rotting under the mediterranean sun.  Perhaps I'm being a little unfair; I did, after all, agree to see Troy because I liked the idea of watching muscle-flexing and sword-wielding for two hours, but the movie would not have been so funny had it not taken itself for more than a male meat-fest.    From the swelling music of Jack Horner (composer for the dreaded Titanic) to the annoying insistence on the power of looooove, TROY vomits melodrama to the highest degree. Who shall I butcher first? Let's see.  There's Paris (Orlando Bloom), whose girly curly locks grace a chin that can't decide whether or not he can grow facial hair, Hector (Eric Bana), fresh from Shrek - oh, I mean The Hulk - whose facial expressions range between the "I'm serious" pop-eyed look and the constipated frowns he makes as evidence of his "good acting."  Even the "mighty" Agemmemon looks like the neckless ram-man from He-Man cartoons who's shorter than a midget.   And Brad.  Go back to Fight Club.  Please. True, his biceps have grown to a ludicrously juicy size, but that doesn't mean his acting abilities follow. But, Brad, poor Brad.  Maybe it was the script writers' faults for giving you lines like "Immortality! Take it! It's yours!" It's just as cruel as giving ice-cream the dumbest names (like Rockin'razzmatazzfricken raspberry)and making you say them when you order.  But then again, it's not like Brad's standing in front of a Baskin Robbins counter...he's being paid to say these lines. And I paid...to see him being paid to say them.  man alive...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am looking at this blank page and wondering why the hell I'm making a blog.  It's not a diary so it's not exactly confidential, and nobody's going to bother reading it, so what's the point? I can only hope that by writing the events of my mundane life on the internet, some future computer nerd in the year 2500 will dig up these old blog entires of mine and archive them as some great archeological find.  It's a question of self-preservation, baby. Yeah, that's right. Get outta my Van Halen tshirt before you jinx the band and they break up. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, I turn red after downing a beer.  Yes, I get dizzy after the neck.  That was me seven years ago.  A million and a half years later, this is me now.  So why is it that many Asian people can not tolerate alcohol, like they can't handle lactose products?  Dairy has never been a problem to me (maybe that's why I'm considered "huge" at 5'6" in Chinese terms), but alcohol, my love, my darling, I can't handle alcohol.  I did go through a phase where I thought my tolerance had gone up where three drinks (wow!) wouldn't touch me. For some reason, however, I've returned to my cheap drunk status and I don't know how it happened.  The second last time I went out, I had two drinks after a heavy pasta meal.  I stood up and nearly toppled over.  Yes, I am sexy when I'm drunk, and wouldn't you know it.  Now really, that was quite sad!  So why, you ask, do I continue to drink?  Well, why do other people drink? Cuz it's yummy and it buzzes yummy.  It's not like China has a shortage of alcohol like dairy.  Japan has Sake. And everyone else, I'm sure, has some form of moonshine carefully refined in a bathtub somewhere.   It's a conundrum I hope someone out there can explain to me.  Is there a Alcoholaid like Lactaid that I can take so I won't become a beet after having three quarters of a Smirnoff?  Can I ever savour a Stella Artois as much as the Belgian on TV who says, "Mais papa! Il m'a sauve ma vie!" ?  Well, it IS a good thing to be a cheap drunk...otherwise I might end up like Nickelback or Vin Diesel in the next Garfield flick and then who knows where I might be? Smoking pot in a yurt on the coast of BC?  Why, the fun starts tomorrow!  Can't wait for the flight at 8AM, hungover with period cramps. Yes, you all needed to know that. Good night! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Vin Diesel as Garfield
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My question is WHY????  Who asked for a movie version of Garfield?  I can't remember Garfield being very popular when it was popular, so I must wonder why this movie ever made it to existence.  The same question goes to The Chronicles of Riddick, the sequel to the mindless sci-fi flick, Pitch Black.  Did someone take a public interest survey and discover the demand for the revival of a cantankerous cat and a musclebound killing machine?  I've never written any survey of this kind; I certainly have never heard of one either.  So, WHY?  This question ranks with the likes of, What is the meaning of life? Is there a God? Do we live in a matrix? Why is the sky blue? And, Do I really need these shoes?  Yes, central to my existence is the need for the answer to movie-making travesty.  Can I save the rest of humankind from being forced to watch The Chronicles of Riddick just because they had to choose between Mean Girls and Another Olsen Twin Movie?  Seeing as I keep paying these moneygrubbing moviemakers to crank out more brainless films, I doubt it.   By the way, Garfield II will come out next year, featuring Vin Diesel as the fat cat himself.    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If only I were a hitman.    So it hasn't been ten years yet since I left highschool.  But, the ever-so pleasant alumni association has graciously sent invitations to every Lisgar graduate in its 150 billion-year old existence (135 years or what?) for a massive week-long reunion, one which I would only attend if I were a professional killer.                                                But wHY NOt!?!   Why not revisit those memories of long ago, when you were young and full of hope, and love, and passion, and lust, and envy, and beer?(that wasn't me, honest) Or play catch-up with all those hugely successful graduates who are now living the yuppie life to the fullest? Why not rub shoulders with former classmates you once thought were so superior to you and show them once and for all the gReatNeSS of YOU?  But...  the past always haunts us, doesn't it?! You walk down the old familiar hall to your homeroom, and spot a photo layout labelled 1994.  Further down the hall, there is a crowd of people, their faces contorted in what seems to be anguish. As you get closer, you can see that they are laughing, hideously, with their hands clutching their bellies, eyes squinting tears, arms squeezing sides.  You tap a woman from behind. What are you laughing at, you ask.  When she turns, you know the face, but cannot place her because it's as though she has swelled.  She takes one look at you and bursts into guffaws. She steps aside and points to a picture, a picture of a hideous, loathsome creature with big glasses, an oversized t-shirt, and an expression of a dying groundhog lying helpless by the side of the road, asking you to kill it quickly.  That picture...IS YOU!  Alright, so I might be exaggerating.  The thing is, going to a highschool reunion for many, is like trying to travel back in time to erase the past by replacing it with the present.  It's like saying, "Hey everyone, I'm not a loser.  I am now ridiculously good-looking. And members of the opposite sex like me a lot."  Little do people know, that by parading oneself with the sole intention of showing their new and improved selves to the cool kids, they prove to the world that they are just as loserish as they were ten years ago. And you see, this is what would happen if I go.  Yes, I would want them all to know, that I, Matthea Orr, am no longer that dying piece of roadkill with the glasses.  I now have social skills, and the ability to converse in full sentences.  I speak of cool things, like music and travelling and literature. I am going to grad school in September, for, ahem, postcolonial studies.  I will be a TA and my kids will love me.    I am the Queen of Bullshit, hear me roar.  And they will all see me for the loser that I am.   But that's ok, because I have Nickelback, and he loves me.  And Brad Pitt too.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    1979. London Calling by The Clash, one of my all time fav albums
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The awesome indie Band, TANGIERS.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so I will always love The Clash.  People call them "The Only Band that Matters" and to some extent (for me) it's true. I always feel like I was born a decade too late. I missed the eighties, being just a tiny tot listening to the newly released "Like a Virgin" on the school bus,and "Locomotion" by the then-younger Kylie Minogue.  I'm sad that I missed the days of The Clash and all their optimistic anti-establishment glory.  But, there is TANGIERS to make up for my tardy birth. Chris and I went to see them play last night at Zeephod Beeblebrox's.  AWESOME SHOW.  Critics call them a "full-out rock threat" with the sounds of a post-punk Rolling Stones.  I can deal with post-punk.  That means that punk and its great flare for rockin' the house has not yet died.  And Tangiers rocked.  They have a hint of The Clash, 80s Brit punk, Rolling Stones, and something else I can't put my finger on.  They've got strong vocals working for them, and every one of them are great musicians.  A tight indie band.  Their newest album Never Bring You Pleasure is a solid piece of musicianship, but it doesn't give their live act justice.  If you're sick of overplayed overrated totally unoriginal poprock junk like Nickelback on the radio, check out TANGIERS for some great tunes and great times.      
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My dad sent me an email regarding the box of smoked salmon I had sent my mom through the post. "She's a fish nut," Dad said, adding a characteristically mischievious "he-he" afterwards. "She hasn't opened it yet, she likes to look at it."  I can imagine mom taking the bubblewrap envelop and nipping at its corners with her flying fingers until, at long last, she pulls out the boxed salmon and holds it out gleefully before her, arms outstretched and lips curled from ear to ear. She'll give a gutteral growl, "MMM!" while smacking her lips loudly. You see, my mom is most definitely, a fish nut. When she eats one, she'll savour its white, soggy meat and suck on its bones like a badger. The worst part, or best part according to her, is when she munches on the fish head she saves for last. "It's your loss," she'll say as she bites down on the eyeball and grinds it loudly between her molars. She even loves the foul smell in the fish markets in chinatown; it's that very smell that reminds me of summers in the East Coast and the stinky tubful of shells and crab carcasses we would gather from the shoreline. It's a smell I hate; a smell she adores. I believe it's a trend of hers, this affinty for putrid smells, because she also loves durian, a large spiky fruit the stench of which she once lovingly described to me as "cat poo." Yum, mom.  I don't hate fish, but I do hate seafood (sushi is an exception).  People often look shocked when I tell them this, especially when I'm now living on the West Coast.  Unknowingly, friends have set me off to B.C. saying, "Take advantage of the seafood while you're out there" as a last goodbye.  I have to smile weakly and nod like I'm happy about it every time.  I often wonder how people can eat things that look so much like insects.  Could it be the taste that overrides the look, texture, and smell of them? Or are people such devouring carnivours that they'd eat anything that once moved?  After years of being the reason why my family can't order such a "delicacy" at restaurants, I have tried so very hard to enjoy seafood.  My aunt in Vancouver had me over for dinner one night and served us a huge plate of giant crabs.   I can do this!  I thought.  Surely there's something amazingly delectable about these things, what with their harmless spiny pincers, bug-like exoskeleton, and appendages of a giant tarantula... My stomach lurched.    It has to taste good, it has to... My aunt ripped off a crab's arm and plopped it on my plate.   Good god, is it still moving?  I must have been staring at it for quite a long time, because my cousin was holding his belly (a result of his Playstation and Xbox) and laughing.  Finally, my aunt gave me some crab meat she had just de-shelled herself and held it under my nose.  Smiling in an attempt to keep myself from retching, I gratefully accepted it and placed it in my mouth.  It was warm.  soft. sickeningly sweet.  It tasted like what fish in the market smelled like.  Gross.  I kept eating, mind you, trying to be polite and all, but my aunt soon remembered my reaction to the giant prawns (with heads attached) she had ordered the last time we dined together and stopped giving me the crab.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I've been a Vancouverite for a month now.&nbsp; You figure after coming to a new city that I would have tons to blog about.&nbsp; To tell you the truth, so much has happened that I hardly know where to start, but I guess the best way is to begin with the now and present.&nbsp;&nbsp;Well, I've found a&nbsp;house and I live near the beach (ocean, really) that faces north to the mountains.&nbsp; I've discovered the joys of real fruit bubble tea, Malaysian curry dishes and little India's fabric stores.&nbsp; I've bought a bike and named it George, which goes for all other beloved inanimate objects that I own, such as George the guitar, George the backpack, and George the swiss-army knife.&nbsp; Putter-John, my family's Toyota Tercel, is the only exception.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;IKEA has become good friend of mine, supplying me with a much-needed bookshelf and Value Village always comes to the rescue when looking for cheap used furniture like study desks and chairs.&nbsp; I've also experienced the joys and confusion of The Daiso store that sells two floors of two dollar Japanese and Chinese homeware, office supplies,&nbsp; gardening tools, craft materials, and hydrogenated Asian junk-food such as prawn flavoured chips and wasabi crackers.&nbsp; A good place to visit once if you're trying to buy stuff for a new house; otherwise, it's two floors of two dollar uselessnsess.&nbsp;   Have I hiked any mountains yet? Unfortunately, no.&nbsp; I can see them everyday, but I haven't attempted the Grouse Grind just yet.&nbsp; I have heard, however, that you can actually use the public bus system to bus to the mountains.&nbsp; That's very weird, but very cool.&nbsp;&nbsp; A car was very useful for our trip to Tofino on Vancouver Island, but the ferry is extortion!&nbsp; $40 for one car, and about $10 per passenger.&nbsp; It cost us about $80 just to get our car on one stinking boat!&nbsp; The drive to Tofino is absolutely amazing though.&nbsp; We drove straight across the island&nbsp;through real mountain ranges and winding past sparkling lakes and massive trees.&nbsp; Tofino, on the otherhand, is like being on the edge of the world-well- it marks the end of this country anyhow.&nbsp; The Trans Canada highway pacific terminus is there, and it's an interesting testimony to how big this country really is.&nbsp; Anyhow, Tofino is a stunning place where the waves are large enough for surfing and the shore allows for glimpses of gray whales and nesting bald eagles.&nbsp;&nbsp; Rainforests surround the area and make a convincing double for a Jurassic Park backdrop.&nbsp; Fall into a fern and you might never find your way out.&nbsp; Strangely enough, you'll only find racoons and black bears here, but I swear rare and unknown species of Canadian monkeys live here, or my name isn't Nickelback.   It hasn't started raining yet, and the residents here tell me that this weather is rather freakish.&nbsp; I'm crossing my fingers and hoping for the sun to ward away the perpetual downpours I am told frequents this location.&nbsp; I've blabbed enough--for now, I'm gonna try to befriend my new roommate's bratty&nbsp;cat, George - er- Pandora.&nbsp;&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The following is an excerpt from something I scrawled before boarding the plane to Vancouver, dated June 18th, 2004:    Flight's at 0800.&nbsp; So this is my first trip on a plane...alone.&nbsp; Not that that's an issue.&nbsp; Airports are just mind boggling places that make me wonder if I'm actually a terrorist and I didn't know it.&nbsp; Maybe I packed a M-16 into my knapsack in my sleep?&nbsp; Will they confiscate my nail-clipper and post my picture on CNN as the new Asian threat? Well, this isn't the States, and that's not where I'm going.&nbsp; Thank god.&nbsp;&nbsp;The guy at security tells me to take out any electronics in my carry-on.&nbsp; I smile innocently as I&nbsp;pull out my cd player, my cell phone, my laptop, oh- and my camera.&nbsp; As&nbsp; security begins dusting my things, I think to myself "Oh, I have a bomb in my cell phone.&nbsp; Fancy that."&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;But, no alarms go off, no red alert.&nbsp; The sweat starts to recede back into my pores as I turn and give a thumbs up to my parents waiting behind the security area.&nbsp; I give a little wave and it's done.&nbsp; So it's goodbye Ottawa, and hello Vancouver.&nbsp; Ah, the second chapter of my life, I suppose.&nbsp; More school . . . the comfortable, all-encompassing security of school --&nbsp;the best way I figure to stall the decision to choose a career.&nbsp; Chris said it best yesterday during our conversation at Zaphod's:&nbsp; "The working life seems like eternity," she said.&nbsp; "You feel like you're trapped in a damned routine that's -- endless."&nbsp; So, do I really want to be in her position?&nbsp; Work 9-5, Monday to Friday, lather, rinse, repeat?&nbsp; How would that be, I wonder.&nbsp; A life with no studying or homework, papers or lectures, and all the things I'm so sick of right now?&nbsp; Maybe I could join the army like that guy sitting by the window over there?&nbsp; He seems to have it all figured out with his snappy little buzz cut.&nbsp; But, besides getting a free education, I don't think I could let the army have my ass for five years that easily.&nbsp; I might as well get a lobotomy, which, in comparison, doesn't seem so bad.&nbsp;&nbsp; No.&nbsp; The grad student option is my choice and it will have to be -- for now.&nbsp; The future is undecided, and much like chocolates in a box a la Forrest Gump, you never know what you're gonna get.&nbsp;  Shrimp gumbo?   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>