<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...turned out to be down to faulty PC hardware, so I was in fact beating my head against a rock, or it's equivalent.&nbsp; Oh well.  In other news, I've finally got around to assembling some more "real robot" ( urlLink http://www.realrobots.co.uk ).&nbsp; I've had up to issue 76ish delivered, but only got around to assembling up to issue 32 until last week.&nbsp; Nearly caught up now, only 6 issues to go.  Added a Commodore 128 to my old computer collection.&nbsp; I used to have one back in '86, but sold it to help fund an Atari ST in '88.&nbsp; It's nice to have one back again.  Want to build an arcade cabinet and put MAME in it.&nbsp; Probably just a whim that I'll never get around to doing, but we'll see.  Re-read Asimov's I, Robot book in preparation for the film.&nbsp; Originally read it many, many years ago and couldn't remember any of stories unaided.&nbsp; The film has nothing to do with the book.&nbsp; Except for the title and they both have robots in them.&nbsp; I read somewhere that Asimov invented his three laws so that he couldn't write any "turned on their masters" type stories.&nbsp; Oh dear.  Also been watching "Wonderfalls".&nbsp; It's really good. why'd it get cancelled?&nbsp; Not fair.&nbsp; Even worse is that the DVDs are very unlikely to get released over here.&nbsp; Bum.  Oh well, best get back to work - shame it's so dull at the moment :(   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sorted out XP with a CHKDSK, but it died again.&nbsp; Tried&nbsp;another CHKDSK but it didn't work.&nbsp; Tried the "last known good", and apparently the last known good configuration was halfway through the first installation, because that's what it did.&nbsp; Weird. &nbsp; Anyway, got the work done on time (just!), so I'm a very happy chappy. &nbsp; Been to see Around the World in 80 Days (OK) and Spiderman 2 (quite good). &nbsp; Having the weekend off for a change! &nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Got some XP boot floopies, a floppy drive and some electric string with which to attach it.  Will try later.  Nearly took out my monitor at work with a yo-yo.  Oops.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Not having fun :(  PC decided to reboot and reboot and reboot and reboot.  Last Know Good doesn't help.  Safe Mode gets as far as mup.sys then reboots, as does networking and command prompt.  To make matters worse, it's a machine that came with XP installed, so the only CD that comes with it isn't a Windows XP CD, it's a "recovery" CD, which wipes the HD and makes everything all shiny and new.  Got my data backed up, so that's OK but it'll take hours to re-install everything.  I can make some boot floppies, but it doesn't even have a floppy drive!  It never a good time for this sort of thing to happen, but this really is the absolute worst time.  Why don't Microsoft put in a console mode which doesn't have to load a pretty much fully working version of XP before it can start, huh? 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>