<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It is amazing how the time of lunch comes so slowly. At work the time seems so relative, that I feel like I understand Einstein's theory of relativity, and I could even make my own contribution if I hadn't been so hungy. Sugar levels are dropping. Concentration diminishing.  As I correctly predicted the weekend was indeed cold and rainy and on the weather side really nasty. I have seen all types of rain on that day, and I do not care to see them that soon again. But otherwise the weekend was great. I was training my fiancee in driving on our fresh new car and on Sunday we went to see Kill Bill vol. 2 to another country and it was good.  Today my sister is doing university graduation exams and it seems to be going well. Not for me though, because it is hard to type when you are keeping your fingers crossed :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, it is Friday. I am at work hoping that I am successfully pretending to be working. I do hope it works. My current job is easy to spot. Just go to  urlLink Pravda.sk  and a lot of what you see is a result of my clicking and typing. Yes, you've guessed it right. I am an online journalist surfing the news agencies for the fresh news that I may together with my co-workers offer to the hungry Slovak online audience.   Today is one especially dull day as Fridays often are. So I watch the bubbles bubbling in my mineral water bottle on my desk. It is quite relaxing, but it makes me want to pee too often. That is the price you pay.  Fridays are often filled with expectations of the coming weekend, but not today. See the rason:  The forecast forecasts forbiddingly nasty stormy rainy ugly weather.   That would not worry me too much, but it has been so nice and hot during the working days when I just had to sit here and satisfy the hunger for the news of several thousands of people. Oh well, I should better be going... read you later.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One day this was bound to happen. So it is just as well that it is today May 21st 2004 that I open my very own blog. I hope I will enjoy it, and I hope you may all just as well. Keep your fingers crossed for me and my words. Soon you will know more about me than my email account knows, my personal page knows and my mobile phone knows. And that says something. So just keep your eyes on pavol.blogspot.com and you may be surprised.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>