<Blog>


<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why hasn't medical science created a break-up drug?  I mean they have given us drugs for most ailments right?  They even continue to make up their own new "conditions" or "illnesses" and sell us sugar cubes with fancy names and pages upon pages of legal extensions in an effort to cover up how effective the placebo effect is in the general public's psyche.  ADHD is a perfect example of this.  I know all these people with young siblings who have been prescribed it.  This is some crazy sh1t man!  KIDS ARE HYPERACTIVE BY NATURE.  Who the hell wasn't when they were young.  I mean think about it - childhood is the only time in your life when you can talk to imaginary friends and live in your own beautiful world and actually be looked upon that you are "so imaginative" and "advanced".  Go to your local park and watch some 3-8 year olds.  It is great!  Kids acting out what they truly feel and see.  Innocence  - absolute disregard. Then the thought-po-po  teamed up with Pharmacia Americana and saw a win-win situation:  Mind control and profits in little sugar pill!  It's easy to scare American parents who know social security isn't going to be there in 25 years and they have not made the best investments and will not be able to live in anything but state owned housing for the last 7-15 years of their lives which are constantly being overextending by new drugs that actually do work but do not take into account that maybe people should die by the time they are 98.  These parents then know that they only have their spawn who will be able to take care of them later in life, (not taking into consideration how much hate there is in out culture for elderly people and chance are your kids are going to jump at any opportunity to put you in state-owned housing).  But they hang on to the thought of living the last years of their life in a nice guest house on their offspring's beach house.  So when a teacher and school psychologist come into the room and give you the worse case scenario about how your child is hyperactive and at this rate they will fail in life and only be able to hold a job as a jizz-mopper at the local adult bookstore, the parents' selfish dreams of their children making so much of themselves fall into a dark pancake-batter smelling hole and they are ready to drug their beautiful children into conforming waking-serving zombies. )*Note - I don't blame teachers or the education system, I mean unless it's your kid who is bouncing off the walls, it's really fvcking annoying.  And teachers do not get paid enough to put up with that - so yeah, if I was in education, and the fed's will make sure I never am, I say drug the little bastards!) Anyways, I think this sort of drugging of our youth is insidiously wrong and greed is at the root of it.   So to come full circle, why has the pharmaceutical industry not made a drug that could be prescribed to you when you have to go through a break up.  I mean there is always drinking and pot but those aren't the best vices, especially when it is so easy to find purchase firearms these days.  Not to mention how the wonder internet has made it so easy to find people - anyone really - as long as you have some $$ to blow.   I could use a good break up drug write now.  Just something to make you forget.  No anti-depressants or sleep aids.  I just need to forget about the last three years, maybe that is why I joined this board...  Talk to you soon       
     
    
</post>


</Blog>