<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sleep.  Soft, wonderful, dream-filled, night-passenging sleep.  How elusive.  How estranged from this mortal being.  There are nights when even pills don't help.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If it isn't one thing it's another.  First I start having trouble with my lower back and now my right shoulder is giving me pains.  My diet isn't working, the cholesterol medication the doctor gave me has painful side-effects, it's allergy season and my landlady is being a bitch this weekend.  I can't get a minutes peace even when I leave the house.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here it is another Friday and I feel like this was another useless week.  It doesn't matter how hard we work in this office it is like there is never any progress.  Kids still get hurt and parents still lie.  Other states ask for help, we ask for help, everyone asks for help.  And the help never comes.  So you pick up another doughnut or soda or candy bar or . . .   And such shining examples of denial.  We have a father that come in to visit with his two year old daughter and screams for dear life during the entire time and he tells the Judge that the visits are going fine.  Kind of hard to keep that "professional attitude" going when even the psychologist is laughing at the guy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A sense of humor is very important in this job.    They want me to do more work.  BUT they aren't paying me more.  AND I am supposed to be happy that I have a job.  My benefits are decreasing.  But my needs are increasing as I get older.    Next the insurance premium will increase.  But I won't get a cost of living increase.  That's always good for a laugh.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well?  Why not?  I don't feel good.  And I will probably feel worse tomorrow.  Can't this just go away and stop?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know, reliving childhood nightmares is supposed to be an OPPORTUNITY.  I know, I should be addressing the "inner demons" in order to make a full recovery.  I know, Susan can't read my mind and cannot possibly know what kind of nightmare I was living through.  But gee, does this kind of event have to be so brutally EFFECTIVE?  Oh wait, you mean if  I  wasn't in such deep denial then this wouldn't have been quite so bad?  You mean if  I  were taking care of my problems this might not have even happened?  Damnit!  Why does everything always have to be my fault?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1) I am not perfect. 2) I am not well physically. 3) Money issues are forcing me off of my Prozac. 4) The leasing company is fucking with me. 5) Showering in the morning is becoming an "issue." 6) I am regressing again. 7) Where is Danni anyway?   8) Last night Susan called it her computer. Of all the horrible images that raised in my mind.  My childhood came rushing back at me and I saw my parents taking away my best-loved toys because someone else wanted them.  I was so devastated.  If you haven't experienced the horror of being an unwanted child just try and get a clue.  They always took away the things I liked and used.  They would say "You're the child we never wanted."  To this day it still hurts.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here it is June already and I am just now finding Christmas ideas.  I am usually more organized than this.  But then this has been a very chaotic year.  Overwhelming debt,  moving, theft and puppies and God only knows what else is yet to come.  Does this mean giving up the Internet?  I don't know but I can no longer afford to pay for it.  So I borrow access from others.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I see myself in a house and I am surrounded by friends.  The house has a brown tile floor with plush area rugs.  I am walking toward the sliding glass door to go outside.  There is a small pool and a large grass area.  Perfect for playing.  There are trees and a small garden in the yard.  It is never too hot or too cold and the rain never lasts too long nor gets us too wet.  My friends are the pets that I have known over the years.  Omar, Twinkle, Bear, Buddy, Princess, Samantha, Jasper, Muffy, Sampson, Tinkerbell, Bruiser, Romeo, Honey Bear, Chase, Critter, Mattie, Augie, Barney, Wit and Charm.  We are walking out to the backyard so that we can play.  Bear gives me a kiss and I thank him.    This is a happy visual that I can use to combat depression.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A month goes by and suddenly everything is different.  Well, . . . maybe not so suddenly.  I have been reading Dr. Ornish's book about reversing heart disease and had a comeuppance or two.  Or three.    I am forced to admit that I am the unwanted child.  From infancy I have had to force myself on others to be accepted.  Other people never like me they just tolerate me.  The only reason I am tolerated is because I am useful in some way.  It is necessary that I admit this is my problem and that I need to accept this reality and learn to live with it.  I am forced to admit that there is an invisible wall surrounding my heart that will not open.  It is protecting my heart from me.  Nothing has changed.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>