<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yea. the day after tomorrow. Heck. whole day screwed up man.
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heck. It was hell Okay. My parents spent 1hr15mins talking to the chinese teacher. I dunnoe what to say. it's like, starring at my watch for that long and listening to her mumbling all the way 2 my parents on how lousy and shitty my results were and how bad i've done in my class tests and she keeps on saying about "attitude problem". WTF. if i could kill her i would F**king kill here on the spot wif a hockey stick. She was like telling every single thing to my parents. n i dun like that at all. Cos some of what she said was untrue and horrendous. Murderous whould be a better word to replace horrendous. Damn. i swear pixiang was in the class for about 2hour plus. Mr K got lots of things to say to his bro. n i noe he dident like it at all cos K was drooling all about how he has been in class, and the printing on the result slip Stares at him and he stares back.....Wtf again. Actually everybody got screwed. and someone getting 8/100 for A Maths fricking Pro.  
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Die Liao. This time really die liao. I'm not going to expose my results. All i can sae is it is totally like SH*T. I mean, this year everyone's results totally like sh*t. siao liao. now really dying liao. haven tell my parents yet.
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shid tomorrow got aschool again. So boring. And Getting back the results summore.. Shit.
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes Yes. it's killing me, and all other fans out there cos it's been like a day already. Wanna train my Crusader. www.dragnarok.net yay pls visit. pls Support. Hahax
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Think i'm gonna screw A maths and Chemistry Liao. Yiyang pls dun screw up the Chinese paper leh... i no hope already..(BUT i noe u gonna screw Physics Heh Heh)
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sianz.....went to cut hair just now.. Then now my hair a little like funny funny like that. Guess wad. the barber said i was fat. F**King B*stard. All i could do was to give her a freeky smile. Walked to Westmall after that and returned my Library books. Sianzzz...The place looked very hyped up. Since when did dey open Mosburger at the ground floor? SiAnZzZz.. i dident even know. That shows how long i havent been there already. Alamak. Westmall got show again. Channel U. Dunno what show it is. but I saw kinda lots of Celebrities there. People r all crowding around the stage. Stupid Girls Screaming. Stupid old man starring.....  
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He can take 3600seconds/60mins/1 hour to go through 6 MCQ questions. I mean....WTF!!!!???? 6 u noe. And for the wole lesson he just goes through that Sh*t and everyone seems to be sleeping(Anyw almost everyone sleeps in his class so what the HECK) and he dosent giv a D at all. Oh. And he told us he is "Single, Unmarried And Unwanted". We understand him and he should understands us cos um...hello we r Failing our Chem papers here..Hehe. 
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MR K is VeryVeryVeryVeryVery VeryVeryVeryVeryVery VeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVery VeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVery VeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVery VeryVeryVery VeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVeryVery VeryVeryVery Boring!
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry. Typo Errors. Hereen is spelt hereen or heeren? or heereen??? See lar. Now im confused liao. 
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sooooo...what did we do after western dining? yesyes. Went to Hereen cos it was just beside Jack's Place. I mean, exams are not over yet so why the hell did we go there in the frst place then....? Dunno. I think we were just curious. Trying to get some relaxxxation before the exams. Yea. Pixiang went for the IJ girl in the Adidas shop. Wow, we have to admire his courage but at the same time pity his taste for *that* kinda girl. Here's the fun part....Jamming Elevators. It was the first time that i went out wif friends n dey jammed elevators for the sake of jamming them. Sigh. Anyw it was kinda fun n stupid seeing the security guard making sacarstic glances at us while bending down to press the little red knob that resets the elevator.
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Abt that day during Sec3 western Dining.. heh. YY n our whole bunchies were practically making lots of noise when the steak was served. Toppled a glass of water. Kidnapped Pixiang's Reebok Sling and read all the SMSes in his Sony Erricson. Some were kinda stupid and mushy bt is was expected from him cos he's dat kind of ppl. Hehe sorry ar =D
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh sian...ppl wan me to get a blog so i get one lor.
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well...oops. yea. will be flying away on this Sunday, the 13th. How unlucky the number is. heh. so. haha. okay. see u guys when school returns. my plane will b flying off at 10am so if u reallllly wanna come down. Just kidding la dun come down. hehe. bye guys. bye PX. no more horny fon calls at night :P. and u Yiyang, pls. just forget about it larx. hehe. So long. Ora Et Labora. In the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit. 
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yea..so. um. i said i'm gonna leave a message fur u and here it is. haha..Wun be seeing you fur 2 whole weeks. and when sch re-opens again we'r all gonna be busssy.. Hahaha. Din catch up wif u much. I hope you'd enjoy your trip to some island :p. I'm going out to westmall 2 get some stuff for camp. so sorry i couldnt go online when u r online. have a nice time during your holidays. Man...seriously. i'm gonna miss u fur 2 whole weeks! hahaa. i'll try to message u when im in china. Keep your phone on! till then. See u soon. 
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay....so. i will be going to China next week. So sian. Half of my hols gone. the 3rd week going 2 china. 4th week....got LLTC camp. But the good news is that i've kinda finished all my homework already :P hahahahahaaahahaha So SORRY YY n PX!. i finished Everything Liao!
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YES.YeS. yEs. I just cannot contain my excitement. Greece won. Why did portugal loose? Okay larx. Ppl think that the refree a little biased towards the dem but yah. Fair share of ppl getting the yellow cards what. The one nad only goal was totally sensational. From a flying corner kick towards the penalty box and a beautiful header by the Greek Striker (damn i furgot his name already), which, surprisingly, caught the Portugeese goal keeper completely off-guard, and thus, the goal was concieved. U guys should have watch the replay man. It was damn nice lor.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha. Not as though i hate her la. It's because she keeps on failing me for tests and picking on me in class everytime. Whaddeheck. She took over Mr Lee cos mr Lee went to teach the lower sec classes. She made the class suffer. So sickening. Corrections have to be done and re-done for some tiny and insignificant mistakes. Dots were totally not allowed cos shw will "misinterpret" it as an extra chinese character stroke. I hope she has a stroke...She wanted file check. We had to copy the content page ourselves. I swear my Chinese compo has more red ink then blue ink. Failing was normal. Failing badly was appreciated by the class. If you got a zero for anything, you will be treated like a hero..  We tried our best to tell her we r stressed, but in the end nothing comes to light and my chinese file comes back half soaked in red ink. I could open an ink factory specialising in red ink man. She comes into class today with a bag of corrections. *Gasp* Somebody in class faints. Another person got choked in the process of drinking his water. YY fell of his chair......  If u could really understand us, u would feel the pain we go through everyday in chinese lesson.(except wednesdays, cos theres No chinese on Wednesday u moron) Wednesday is super shiok man..Anyw, if u wanna see her, go visit her at KK Women's Clinic D  (:
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ahh finally after such a long break, i back wif a blog. Sigh. nothing much interesting happening these few days. Now i realised sec 2 was so slack man. But now every day at least got homework from 3 sub teachers...i'm now trying very hard to squeezeeee time for blogging and less time spent on 1.6. Speaking of 1.6, i heard that ValvE cloased down all WON servers..is that true? how sad. I bet 1.5 was more fun and challenging than 1.6. Not much of any graphic improvements but a few new kill toys thats all. And a shield. how sickening. You can't even shoot ----T-h-r-o-u-g-h---- a shield(Anyw it's supposed to b a shield rite?)so how the heck do you suppose to eliminate your enemy when he hides behind it all the time? Puzzles me why the developers never tought of it.  
    
</post>


</Blog>