<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This has been a busy weekend! On Saturday was Erwin's 75th birthday celebration. First, we had a mass in the afternoon for him. The church choir sang as a surprise, and Johannes and I decided to cantor everything about an hour before mass, so we had to learn everything really fast. I'm discovering that singing during pregnancy is rather difficult because I can't take deep breaths. The baby must be squishing my diaphragm. The mass was nice though. In the evening, we went to his party. There were tons of people there, and even more food. There was a buffet with vegetables and seafood and fruit and lots of other stuff. Johannes and I ate so many appetizers that we barely had room for the main course. After that, there was a dessert buffet. It was so popular that we ran out of small plates and had to use dinner size plates. After I finished my dessert, Johannes was still hungry, and came back with a dinner plate filled with dessert. I was surprised because he had already had 2 plates, just like I had. He ate it all though. Then came the entertainment. There were lots of musical things and a couple skits. Ludger, Brigitte, Johannes and I played something together- viola, guitar, recorder and flute. There was a funny skit at the end that Helga thought of. It was about saving time during ironing. It involved cutting up a shirt that Michael was wearing so that only the parts that show when you have a suit on were still there. Then Johannes, Ludger, and Christoph came up at the end, and they all took their jackets off and they all had these strange looking cut-up shirts on. It was pretty funny. I think I have a picture of Johannes in his.  On Sunday was Pentecost, and the choir sang again, so I had to get up early to go to practise. I was really tired from the night before. It was a nice mass, and I was glad to be up in the choir loft, away from the incense. Afterwards, Johannes and I were both feeling pretty lazy, and we took some leftovers from the buffet from the night before out of the fridge, and put them on the table outside and ate as much as we could. There was a lot of food leftover, and not enough people took leftovers with them, so Johannes and I ended up with a lot. It was a nice day, so Johannes and I enjoyed the sun and then went for a swim at his parents' place.   Today was also a holiday here. It's Pentecost Monday. It's also our anniversary, so it's nice that we are both home to celebrate. We had church this morning, and afterwards went downtown to eat in a Mexican restaurant. The weather isn't that nice today, and Johannes was falling asleep on the bus, so we decided not to walk anywhere, so we came home and slept for a bit. It started pouring during that time, so it's a good thing we have a nice tenant who brought in our laundry from outside. All my pants are out there at the moment, and I don't want to wear a dress to work tomorrow. Later, we ate cheesecake and watched the wedding video and lit our wedding candle. I sang along with everything and did all the church responses too. Johannes was laughing at me. I also had to pause the wedding video because I had forgotten what my wedding shoes looked like, and I had to find them.  So, it's been a good weekend. Coming up this week is our first birth preparationn class, my first water gymnastics class, and the new Harry Potter!! I'm hoping to see it next weekend, but I'm not sure when it will be availabe in English. I might have to wait until June 15 to see it, but if I'm lucky, I'll be able to see it this weekend. That's all for now, I think. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to my first post. When I woke up this morning, I had no idea I would be creating a blog today, but that changed when Hannah came online and talked me into it. So here I am. She has one now too.It's at http://hanniverse.blogspot.com/. While making my profile for this blog, I noticed that my website had been deactivated because I haven't updated it in so long. I think I will work on it today, because my name is wrong and the picture of me isn't very good.  Time for a pregnancy update. Everyone asks me about that, so it must be interesting.I'm 30 weeks pregnant now, which means there are 66 days, or 10 weeks until the baby is born. It sounds like a lot, but I think it will go by fast. I only have 3.5 more weeks of work, and then I can start organizing the mass of baby stuff which is taking over the basement.This morning, I organized the cupboard full of baby stuff in our rooom because it wasn't shutting  properly. Yesterday, I bought 4 cute baby outfits for a really good price. I hope the baby is a girl because they are all girly. On Monday, I have my doctors appointment, and I will be getting an ultrasound, so hopefully I will find out the gender this time. I also have to get a shot because my blood type is negative. Other than that, I have no idea what will happen. Hopefully my iron level has improved.  Let's see...what else is happening? Next week is Pentecost and Erwin's birthday party. Johannes, Ludger, Brigitte, and I are playing some music for that. My flute is broken, so I have to borrow one for next week. I hope it's not too different from mine. Our wedding anniversary is also coming up soon, and it happens to be a holiday here (Pentecost Monday), so Johannes and I are going to go out somewhere to eat, then do something that we haven't decided on yet, and later watch the wedding video. Then it will be June. The first week is exciting because we start our childbirth preparation class, I start water gymnastics for preegnant people, and the new Harry Potter movie comes out on the fourth. I stop working on the 16th, and then Ludger and Brigitte get married on the 26th, and soon after that, it's July. Two very exciting things are happening in July. Well, one for sure. Anne is coming to visit on the 26th. Or the 27th. I have to check. The baby will be born too. She's due on July 28th, but she might decide to come in August, or earlier in July. We'll see.  The cats went to the vet this week. It was the first time they ever met a German vet. She lives on our street, and a few days ago, we found 2 ticks on Sara and couldn't get them off, so Johannes went down the street and rang her doorbell, and she told us where her office was. We went the next day, and the cats got vaccinated and Sara got his ticks removed. They didn't enjoy it much, but they did enjoy the free food sample that the vet gave them. We also bought tick/flea stuff that they get every month, and a tick remover.  Anyway, that's enough for now. I'm hungry and lunch is almost ready.   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a pretty quiet week this week. My cold still isn't gone, so I've been feeling lazy. The weather was really hot for most of the week too, which only increased my laziness. It got so hot that Johannes dragged the extra bed up from the basement, so we have 2 single beds to sleep on, so that we don't have to sleep in our extremely hot loft. The only problem is the beds are right next to the window, and as soon as it gets light, I wake up and can't get back to sleep. I don't really like waking up before 5. The curtains don't seem to help much.It cooled down on Friday though, so it is possible to sleep in the left until it heats up again. I think it's supposed to be hot tomorrow. The kids at work will like that, because we turn the water pump on for them when it's really hot, and they play with water and sand and make a huge mess. They really enjoy it. I only have three days of work left. Wednesday is my last day. I'm looking forward to sleeping longer in the morning and having time to organize stuff around the house and to actually have time to cook interesting things.  Let's see...what else did I do this week? Wednesday was childbirth prep. We practised sitting on the birthing balls and breathing. I didn't enjoy that much because she kept saying to breathe through my nose, which wasn't possible and I was supposed to sit so far forward on the ball that I could barely keep my balance. We saw some pictures too, and they were black and white, and illustrations and not photos, so Johannes couldn't find anything to complain about. They all had english captions, which was helpful so I had some idea of what the teacher was talking about. There are still a lot of medical words I don't know and Johannes doesn't know how to translate them all. We also did a couple of relaxation exercises, but I kept relaxing too much and falling asleep. I don't think that will work during labour, so I should learn how to relax and stay awake at the same time. Thursday was Corpus Christi, which is a holiday here, so I didn't have to work. It was a very hot day, and we had mass outside, and that was follwed by a procession around Marienborn with lots of singing. I skipped the procession though, because it was very hot and my legs were hurting. Poor Johannes had to wear an altar server robe and carry a heavy speaker. He invited all the altar servers to his parents' house in the afternoon for a swim, since they were away for a day, but it started pouring 10 minutes before everyone was supposed to come, so no one came. There was thunder and lightening, and it was a really cool storm.Johannes and I went swimming by ourselves, and it was fun to listen to the rain pounding on the roof while swimming. The lightening made Johannes a little nervous though. On Saturday, I finished up the baby shopping. My bus pass expires on Thursday, and I won't be getting another one. Since it takes me forever to decide on baby stuff, I decided I should finish it before my bus pass runs out. The only thing left to buy now is cloth diapers, and Johannes and I are planning to get those on Thursday. I haven't done anything interesting today, only a lot of eating and being lazy. Anyway, time for bed now because I have to work early tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the doctor today, and everything went pretty well. My iron is still a bit low, but at least my thyroid is normal. I had an ultrasound to check how the baby is growing, and she's grown a lot in the last 2 weeks. She's only 1 week too small now, which is pretty good. She weighs about 3.7 pounds. I have 2 new pictures, which I will scan and put on my website soon. Not much else is new. I only have a week of work left.I'm looking forward to having time off so I can get all the baby stuff together. It's really hot today. It's about 32 degrees, or maybe more. I have to be outside a lot at work, and there isn't much shade, so I get really hot. Johannes and I went swimming at his parents' place after work, but the pool was over 30 degrees as well, and it felt like a bathtub. Time to go cook now.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The new Harry Potter movie came out this week. After weeks of waiting, it's finally here! It came out in Germany on Thursday. There was actually a showing right at midnight, but that wasn't very practical since I had to work the next morning. I couldn't go Thursday night either, because I had to go to my water gymanstics class. So,we went last night, which was Friday. It was my first time ever in a German movie theater. The one we went to is the newest one in town, and the biggest. It has at least 10 theaters in it, and I think it's bigger than Silvercity in Victoria, but I'm not sure. They sell lots of food there, and there's even a restaurant so you can eat before you see a movie. Right before the movie starts, someone comes in and sells ice cream so you don't have to eat it before the movie starts. The most exciting thing about the theatre itself was the chairs. They are huge and comfortable, and the best thing is they aren't all individual with hard plastic arms. Some are big enough for two people, and the arms are all soft, and the back of the chair goes all the way up to your head. They were really comfy. The screen was really huge too. German popcorn is really weird though. You can buy either sweet, which is sort of like caramel popcorn but not really, or salty. I wanted butter for mine, and no salt, but that didn't work. There was about half an hour of advertisements before the movie actually started, and after they were done, they turned all the lights on again, and the ice cream person came in, and then a few minutes later, the movie actually started. There was a break in the middle of the movie. It was kind of annoying because I wanted to keep watching, but it wasn't too long, and it gave me time to go to the bathroom without missing everything, so it wasn't so bad. Very practical for pregnant people.We saw the movie in English, mainly because we could get better seats there than in the German one. Another neat thing about German theatres is that you can buy the tickets ahead of time, and pick your seats. Also, you can buy a booklet with 5 movie coupons and use them whenever you want and it's cheaper than just buying two tickets whenever you feel like going. I really liked the movie.It went really fast, and they left out a few things I wanted to see, but it was still good. I think the ending especially went too fast, because I think if I hadn't read the books, I would have been a bit confused about some things. I won't say too much more because I don't want to ruin for anyone. After the movie, we had to wait forever for the bus, and met this drunk guy who was complaining to us about a dying pigeon that he found and he wanted to give it to us. Then the bus finally came, and I was watching all the crazy drivers out the window, and this one car turned a corner and cut the bus off, and we nearly ran into it. Mainz at that time of night is a little too exciting for me, I think.  The movie was probably the best part of my week, but I did do a couple of other interesting things. One was getting a bad cold, which is more annoying than exciting. I've been all stuffed up since Wednesday,and my throat's sore too. I stayed home from work on Thursday because my head hurt so much that I didn't want to be around screaming kids. I went back on Friday, but I wasn't feeling all that much better, but I don't have all that many days of work left, so I don't want to miss that much.   On Wednesday, Johannes and I went to our first birth preparation class. It was a bit hard for me, because there were lots of new German words that I didn't know, and we had to do strange exercises and I couldn't figure out what I was supposed to do, but it was interesting. I  think Johannes liked it too, except for when we were doing all the stuff where I had to lean on him. I think I'm a little too heavy for that. We also practiced breathing, which worked pretty well, except that I couldn't breathe through my nose. On Thursday, I went my first water gymnastics class. I really liked it. The swimming pool was super warm, and it feels really good to be in water. I feel so much lighter there. We threw balls around, and had bike races on noodles, and did strange leg exercises.  I had a bit of trouble understanding instructions, but I eventually figured everything out. I sure learned a lot of new German words this week.  I didn't do much at all today. I've been really lazy, hoping to get rid of this cold.Johannes and I also started working on picking some music to play at Ludger's wedding reception. Yesterday afternoon, I explored a music store downtown and found a book of flute duets that would work for Johannes and I. He has a tenor recorder, and I have my flute. It's hard to find duets because flutes usually play high notes, and the tenor recorder doesn't go that high. I finally found a book with duets from the 1800s that works. We picked a couple of them, and then worked on a piano duet, and then Johannes pulled out one of his old organ books, and I played the top part on my flute, and he played the rest on the piano. It was interesting sight reading- tons and tons of sixteenth notes that were really high for me to play. I think it would have worked better if I could breathe through my nose. I don't know how much of that stuff we'll actually play for the wedding, but it was fun to work on.  Anyway, that's enough for now. I should really try to get some sleep.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>