<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmm, can't remember too much about the dream, but I do know it was action packed. It started of with a young Obi wan and Anakin being killed by these weird ass aliens that were like giant slugs. Some had human form, some more disgusting, some that branched out like crazy ass vines made out of slug.   Me and the others (I forget who) were running around being attacked by these things, some being eaten by the monsters. We had killed some ourselves, but they outnumbered us. We found the boss slug, and on a chance, fed it a young baby slug. For some reason this started a reaction that hurt it, but not killing it all the way. We learned that the ones that had a human form, if injured badly, would attack the boss when given food. Thus, we won.  Move on to a mall in TX. I was there to check to see if I got my job in Austin or not. Along the way I had lunch with the old guys from the refinery. The mall was VERY colorful when I was there. Lot's of bright lights, I remember lots of red for some reason. I never did check to see if I got that job. 

						
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was driving my own truck in the beginning. I drove around in the country enjoying the truck. I made a right turn at one point and turned in front of one of the county blue trucks, and saw some of the guys I used to work with.... Chico being riding in the middle.  I ended up at a piano lesson with my old piano teacher from when I was in 4th grade. She wasn't there yet, so I was left waiting. I noticed a book while I was waiting. The book was huge and green and called "Tobacco Chocolate". I remembered that my teacher was against tobacco and gave many seminars on not smoking (this is only true in the dream). The book had a little sign on it that said it was from Satan.   I sat down across the room from the piano and waited. There happened to be a bunch of kids playing Texas Hold Em in front of the piano on their own round table. My piano teacher showed up, gave me a big iced tea, and we began to walk to the piano to play. I had to get around the table of kids. The kids had to lift the table a little to let me through. My piano teacher and I then sat down to begin the lesson.  THE END  

						
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just woke up from a dream where, oddly enough, I was a young girl back in the 1800's or so who committed a murder somewhere in the woods. What I can remember of the dream began as a police officer (maybe the town sheriff) was asking questions about two murders: the one that I committed and one that happened right before. I don't know what the motive was, but I had memories and I knew that I was the one who killed a retarded girl in my town. This retarded girl really existed in real life Rootstown..  The dream started off with the unbelievable feeling that I was going to get away with murder. The cop didn't suspect me whatsoever, and neither did anyone in my family. I believe no one in my family knew. At one point, however, my mother pointed out that I should clean up the bloody stain on my dress, a bloody stain that I pointed out must have come from helping to slaughter pigs. The dream took a turn at that point, because now there was blatant evidence, and I had to burn the dress.  I went into the basement of the house, to fetch some matches and some gasoline, and somehow think of an excuse to get out of the house to burn the damn dress. I found the old container of gasoline, which was in a pretty small container that I tried to fit in between my shirt and pants (even though I am wearing a dress, not the dress that needs burning). It ended up that my father, who happened to be blind, needed to drive to his friends house, and needed me to be the eyes of the horse and buggy. I was happy to go, his friend's house would be a perfect place for the burning.  Before we left, I snuck into the woods to burn the dress. I poured some gasoline on it and tried to light it, but it just wouldn't light. So I was off with my father.  We showed up at the friends house, which was in the city. I went out to the street corner again, as dusk was settling in, to burn the dress. I finally got it lit and burning when my mother came out and my sister came out to talk to me. No one questioned about the dress, as if they knew what I had done and why I now was doing what I had to do.  The end of the dream consisted of my mother, my sister, and I 1000's of feet in the air lying on a giant bed of round little rocks that were slowly filtering down and lowering us down. The bed was along a cliff, but there was really nothing keeping the bed in the air. My sister and I marveled about the beauty of the world and the wonders of life, when our mother blurted out: "But you do not yet know either about the HIV or the blindness".  We asked what the hell she was talking about. She let the secret slip:  "Girls, the book of your lives has already been written"  With that, she explained to my sister that she would be stricken with HIV and blindness. I opened a copy of the book and skipped ahead to see that yes, tragedy would soon come to us all.  THE END 

						
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was at the movies, and I decided to leave. Nothing was playing anyways. I was in the lobby when the phone rang.  "hello?" "What's up man, its Adam. What's up?" "I'm at the movies, but nothing is playing. I'm outta here"  A nice pretty girl came up to me and interrupted. "Just give me fifteen minutes!" She wore jeans and a T-shirt, with dark black hair and white skin. She ran into the bathroom, so I took a seat on an old counter that was in the middle of the lobby. This part of the theater hadn't been used in years, and they had never bothered taking out the old counter, so the kids started sitting on it when hanging out. Right now I was the only person using it.   She came out of the bathroom and came and took a seat next to me on the counter. She sat next to me. She wasn't wearing a tshirt after all, but rather a while button shirt, unbuttoned just enough to show the perfect amount of cleavage. She started the conversation.  "So what do ya do? You make a lot of money?"  "Well, actually I don't make any money." I wasn't making any money at that point in my life. "I actually just graduated. It's only been a week and I haven't yet found a job".  "Oh that's cool. I think that we should turn this into a little date. I came here to catch that new Tom Hanks movie, but it doesn't start for about 45 minutes. Let's hang out and get to know each other a little better, and you can come with me to catch the movie. Even though you probably don't really want to see the new Tom Hanks flick."   The Hanks movie was a romantic comedy, so I wasn't allowed to see the movie without a girl. Male protocol. I could kill two birds with one stone here. I was stoked. So we sat around and talked a little bit. That's when he showed up. He was tall, with blond hair, and a relatively unattractive guy. He also had braces. But he physically just came up and ran into her.  "Oh, I'm sorry" said he with a filthy french accent. Like all girls who are female, she saw passed all of the ugliness and the fact that the kid was a complete retard, and fell for the accent that always turns em on. I was in for a battle. He offered her a massage. And of course she went for it. Now what the hell do I do?  The massage stopped as I started talking. I told old frenchie that I too had been to France. Instead of punching him, I decided to take that approach instead. It seemed to work as she walked away from him and came back to me, showing some interest. In fact, as I pretended to be civil with the frenchie, I asked him about his favorite part of America.  "Ze ??????? down South." He replied.  I didn't know what the ??????? was. The girl refreshed my memory. "The ?????? is the underground railroad network of tunnels down south." My mind flooded with memories of the long complex underground tunnels that were now a grand tourist attraction. As I thought about that, our french friend gave up and left us alone. The ushers opened the doors to one of the theaters. The music from the credits filled up the lobby. "Let's dance" she said.  I of course was a little apprehensive, but she was all about the dancing. So we started to dance. The girl felt very comfortable in my arms, just a very warm feeling as waltzed around the snack counter, which was in the middle of the lobby. All of a sudden I had a growling dog at my leg. "Charlie let go of him?" The girl shouted.  Charlie turned out to be her dog. She decided to take him out to tie him up. That's when I saw her. Janelle, she was sitting on one of the benches along the wall, blended in with the rest of the crowd. She was looking at me and gave me one of those "I see what you are up to" looks.    I had to see how I was doing in my situation, and it had to be quick before the girl came back. "Janelle, how long have you been sitting there?"  "Long enough to see what you are getting into. Who's the girl?"  "You wouldn't believe it! I was about to leave when she asked me to stay here with her and catch a flick."  "Huh. See Jason, aren't girls cool?"  "Yeah. Anyways, you gotta help me out. Things are going good but I really want to make this work. This girl is really cool and pretty and everything else, and I don't want to fuck it up like I do any other attempt."  Of course she had some advice. "Listen Jason, I've been watching ya, and you seem to be doing things right. But you really ought to talk about her more, give her some compiments, and not some fake compiment that she'll see through. She'll know you're just trying to get into her pants. Give her a real compliment. And let it be true and original, not just the average "You have pretty eyes" routine. Don't be afraid, have fun, and make her feel like a woman."  I realized that I had talked a lot about myself in the conversation. The girl came back in. She had no idea that I had a coach sitting 5 yards away. Compliment Jason, you have to think of a compliment. But I didn't really need to think of anything. It came naturally, because I meant it.   "You know, I really love that outfit you put together for yourself. That white shirt, the way it fits on you and how you wear it, the jeans that fit perfectly and show your hourglass figure. The way that your black hair seems to flow right with the outfit. You're really attractive with a nice touch of class added on. But how did you get so cool and smart too?"  She smiled and took my hand. "The movie is starting. We can talk about it afterwards. If we have time for talking". She gave me sexy smile and a wink and took my hand, and we walked through the door. Before the door closed I looked back at Janelle. She gave me the thumbs up, and I gave her the "You the man" point. It was going to be a fine evening.   

						
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maroon 5 sucks
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to find a TJ Maxx bongo drum~
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, finally the weekend has arrived. First, a couple of cool things. I put my equipment on eBay and I'm getting some good bids, so the digital piano is in the future. Sweet. Second off, I went to get my haircut today and Jim, the barber, who is an old rock n roller, was listening to this fucking sweet cd. Turns out it is some local guy from Columbus back in the 80's, and it's some of the best stuff I've heard in years. Jim let me borrow the CD, and I have to admit I haven't enjoyed a cd this much since pre-napster. Jim also mentioned that we should jam sometime. I'll put money that I can get a lot of musical inspiration from the guy.  I tried calling NI today but Nora was out. I guess I'll try again on Tuesday.  I'm going off to Portsmouth tonight to visti BWaggz. I guess he has some kind of DJing gig or some shit at a bowling alley. I'll have to go check out to see what that is all about, and yes, I'll be taking the red condom of syphillis.  Catch ya.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm putting my Les Paul, my amp, and my keyboards up on sale on ebay, all for the prize of a digital piano. I want to get good on a real piano again, and that's the best I'm gonna get.   I went to Jeff's to take pictures of the instruments. Thank god for that kid. He knows exactly what he is doing. Now I got some sweet looking pictures for the sale.  I kicked ass on my systems analysis midterm today, and the grader also let us know that our work was the best on the class diagrams and sequence diagrams. Knowing my greatness I was not surprised by this.   I'm worn out. Night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We lost our Hockey Game 3 to 1. I am really disappointed, and I thought I played awesome tonight...One of the best games I've played. Hopefully I'll be able to keep on playing. I don't know where I'll be in a few months, so we'll have to wait and see what happens.   Cassie called me again tonight, and left a text saying that she messed up and thinks of me and wants me to call her or something. I don't see where she messed up really bad. I asked her one day if I would ever see her again, back when we were dating, because we really didn't hang out, we just fucked. She would send me these long boring ass emails about shit I don't even know what she was trying to explain about, before I got an answer that it wasn't working. WTF? Get to the damn point. And I think she should get to the point now that she just wants it. No weird emotional BS. I don't have time for it. She fucking drinks way too much anyways. I don't think I can deal with hanging out with a girl with no aspirations, no dreams, and two 40's strapped to her hands. Sex? That's a different story.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, this time we know for sure we have a hockey game tonight at 1:15. The real deal. Unfortunately, I have a midterm/homework due tomorrow that I haven't studied/started on. The midterm and homework are both for the same shitty class, systems analysis, and it is an absolutely horrid class. It's an MIS class. Nothing but a complete waste of my time. Oh well, we'll get through it.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just read that Al Queda is planning another "Grande Attack" this summer. I'm really unsure what they are planning to achieve through this attack, because any attack they bring is just going to make it that much harder for those in the middle east and harder for muslims worldwide.   America is a wonderful place to live and our people, for the most part, are peace loving individuals who DO NOT want to give up the conveniences of living in this country.... Right now, American people don't want innocents in the Middle East to be harmed because of a fraction of extremists. But if these extremists keep on killing our innocents, which will lead to a nation of people who are scared, scared for their lives because of what these religious nuts claim is work in the name of "Allah", if they keep it up, you can kiss the Middle East goodbye. This country will never appease to the terrorists. We have it too good here. Leaders in the middle east had really better be recognizing this, because a couple more attacks on US soil, there won't be a middle east to lead. The US is not Spain. We aren't going to pray for peace when nut jobs blow us up. We're going to go on the offensive. And a couple more attacks, no one here is going to give a shit how many Middle Eastern women and childern are killed by our nukes, because we will be trying to protect our own.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uh, yeah, showed up to the hockey game on the wrong night.  > 
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man, playing a hockey game at 1:15 AM is a bitch. I'm starting to get a little worn out here waiting...  I needed to prepare the notes from one of our client meetings for our lame CIS project, but one of the team members didn't come through with his recording. Great. Can't wait to graduate.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Classes are really starting to burn me out. Six years of this shit, I have three weeks to go, and I'm almost willing to just stop now because I am absolutely losing my mind doing pointless group assignment after pointless group assignment. Don't get me wrong, I think I've learned a lot in college, but I'm to the breaking point of pretend life.   I stopped by and looked at a digital piano today. I can feel the music coming back to me now. As all of the frustrations and time consuming details of school are being released, along with the first taste of real freedom coming around the corner, I feel the motivation almost greater than that of high school. It's been 6 long years, but the music is coming back.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a wonderful hot Saturday and I just got back from a night of jamming with Paul. Watched school of rock, which was an awesome movie. I think I'll go for a run today and then see what I can get into tonite.....
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my degree today. An engineering degree. Something to be proud of. Something I worked hard for, had to sacrifice for, and now I'm free. Free to do anything. I'm not sure how it will turn out, but it's the beginning of a new adventure. Everything is new. There is no path that I am blocked from. An adventurer, that's what I am now.  Commencement today, as I watched the awesome raising of the flag, the rivalship between the business school and the engineering school, the massive people, I fell in love with life again. The music provided a soundtrack, and now I'm ready. All my old friends are married. New friends await. And so do many, many women. Tomorrow is the first Monday of the new chapter.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've graduated. Six long freaking years, and I've finally graduated. Now what? Well, I don't have a job, so right now I'm kind of free to do anything. Big Mike wants me to hang in the poco for a month, but I just don't know about that. It might be good though as we can train together. That would get me into shape fast training with him.   Went on senior crawl last night, and one of Cory's classmates was looking pretty good. She was alright, nice booty on her. What a waste and a little cock tease she turned out to be. And she had a boyfriend! Some idiot she's with out of an obligation because he was there for her when she had cancer. Let me tell ya something honey, if you are staying with a cat out of obligation, and go out grabbing my dick in the club, you got yourself some problems and you better be getting the HELL out of that relationship.  I caved and let Janelle visit yesterday. I hate the fact she's so hot and I get along with her so well, but the shit wouldn't work out.... Damn her straight to hell. Straight to hell!!! She had some cool video tapes from her travels though. Looked like a lot of fun. I also got to hear some new music. Gnarly.  Alright, I'm going to bed now. Monday is the start of a new time in life. Maybe in NC. Maybe in NY. Maybe in ROOTSTOWN. We'll just wait and see.     
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok. So now it seems as if I did not get the job in Austin. I graduate in a WEEK. No job. No plan. No money. No clue. One thing I do have now, however, is a digital piano.  That reminds me that using UPS to ship things is absolutely ridiculous. RIDICULOUS!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is not a good sign for our hero...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and at 4:30 we'll know....
     
    
</post>


</Blog>