<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I personally don't have problems being friends w/anyone from any other schools, but when I tell people from my school that I have friends @ s.v. they flip out and say they hate them cuz they beat us at sports...and I'm like, uh...that's a stupid reason to hate them... and one kid told me people from s.v. are a bunch of crack-heads, but I honestly hope/don't think that any of you are that way! but... you know lol I'm just less biased than other people I guess...w/e  this summer...I'm working...and going to campraise like I have every year for the past 8 years. :) nothing too greatly exciting. oh, I'm getting my license too! that's exciting! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's good you don't hate people from Seneca...this is new to me, do most people from other Western PA schools hate us???  now i know SV and NA have a history of rivalry, but i have a friend from NA... the only reason they have to hate us is cuz we kick some brass when it comes to band stuf ;P  as to include the rest of y'all... what are you doing this summer?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I go to Knoch...it's ok that u can't remember that cuz it's just a stupid ghetto school in the middle of nowhere. :D haha  don't worry tho, I don't hate ppl from Seneca Valley like most Knochers do. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hannah... i added you to my aol buddy list, we'll definitely have to talk sometime... we can share sob stories together... where do you go to school, obviously not seneca, but where, if you've already said that, i just don't remember... lol, sorry!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dunno rachele, it's just...depressing...probly cuz I can relate to it or w/e...someone who hasn't been through any hard, heart-breaking thing would just read it as another name, but ...i dunno i guess it depresses me cuz i can relate to it...so...yeah.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi aj im pat
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay.  Welcome Aj, you know me!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      come to think of it, it depresses me too...
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      why does it depress you?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How cool am I?  I just got home...at...uh...9:30...for the first time since I left for school this morning!  ...it sucks!  but...yeah...rachele, your new user name depresses me!! but it's also something I can very much relate to, sadly. :-(  hey aj, I'm hannah, I don't really go to your school so you don't haveta worry about tryin to figure out who i am. but um...yeah
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it worked...yaaaay...  but anyways... i got stuck with the mellophone since i play the French horn and i was kinda forced into bein in Marching Band...  as for singing... i used to be able to... but now i just sing to myself, while i'm listening to the radio, and in front of people i know who won't make too much fun of me... oh and i guess i should say that i am what used to be rachele... and don't take the new name too personally, i chose it as my epithet in october :/
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i haven't been here for a few days...but yeah... i'm just seeing if it worked and i have a new user name...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi i am aj. for the record, i also happen to be sal's girlfriend, and that's so all the band people here now know who i am.  see, i am not non-exisitent. and who is everyone again? help me out here, i know no one in our school basically. i was new this year.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Run...me...ha..ha..ha!!!  My sn is, you guessed it, wierdkendogirl.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all, I have been requested to change the blog name, this is what I came up with.  If you have suggestions post 'em.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow...running derffinately isn't my thing.  I'm on track, but I only do throwing events. hee hee... today in gym we had to run a timed mile...it was crap...but oh well.  I think I got a good time...w/e lol
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm on IM all the time. My s/n is SVrunner13 because that's what I do when I'm not on IM. I run Cross Country, Track, and Indoor Track for SV :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lol the only time I ever sing is when a good song's on the radio or else at camp...we do a lot of singing there and it's fun...but oh well.  Most ppl have heard me sing...cuz my friends and I like to make up retarded songs in our spare time...we have one called "Paranoia" and it's awesome! :-P  Hey does anyone else here have AIM?  if you do and you ever wanna IM me sometime my sn's sillyKUHNIGGit44. :-D Cuz I have no life and i'm usually on almost all the time.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yea, there is a big difference from singing good and singing bad but as long as you sing and dont care what other ppl think it shows.  Also, the reason some ppl cant sing is because they have never had proper training.  I think i sing ok, a lot of ppl say i am a wonderful singer.  I really dont care cause i like to sing and a persons opinion dosnt matter.  Zack hasent heard me sing, and neither has amanda, or any others at school xcept the kids in chior and shannon.  Mwahahahahaha!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's awesome! I love singing...but I suck at it...so I just don't even try. :-P
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I play the vocal chords.  Meaning i sing.  In 4th grade we had to try out instruments to see if we wanted to be in 5th grade band.  I nearly suffocated myself trying to play the flute and the trumpet.  I broke the reads on the clarinet and sax. Then broke som strings on the violin.  I tried the guitar but i didnt get it.  I also tried the piano but i (lets see, apropriate word??) SUCKED!!! So i cannot play an instrament.  My dad however playes the saxes, he was as short as me in freshmen band (NO comment Zack) and played the barry sax, he owns an alto and tenor.  When he was in the army he played in the band.  he played the clarenet and flute also.  To clear up the word bando- california term- i will give you all a definition  Bandos- Not band geeks because they are cool/nice enough to hang with choras kids. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sweet, pat! I wanted to play french horn this year but stupid Maydawg wouldn't let me...he said he needed me to play bassoon for the musical...it ends up, I went on a cruise during the musical anyway and he was mad at me but oh well. :-P   I got stuck playin mellophone cuz when I was in 8th grade one of my friends from basketball that was on the varsity team asked if I would and one of my good friends decided to play also so...yeah.  At the moment I'm the oldest mellophone player and uh...I haveta teach all da newbies how to play. lol fun stuff  How'd you get stuck playin it?  Maybe I'll see ya sometime at a marching band thing if S.V. goes to any of the things Knoch does...not that I'd recognize you or anything lol
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i play trumpet and flugle horn.  i could play baritone if i wanted but i dont want to and im gonna be learnin the french horn pretty soon.  my mom is a band director so shes gonna teach me
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i play French horn and mellophone... yeah i know i feel so dumb only having like 2 instruments when like sal and murph play like thousands... but yeah... so how did you get stuck playin mellophone?
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, I'm sorry Rachele, but almost anything you talk to Hannah L. Limbaugh about is guarunteed to be crazy... maybe I should just leave the blog... lol j/k I meant weird kinda crazy, not arguments over politics crazy hee hee   I play paino, clarinet, bassoon, mellophone, baritone, and trumpet and I'm in the process of learning trombone. :-)  What dyou all play?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      um, as fellow blogger and somewhat co-creator of this blog ...i make a rule: NO POLITICS, please ...we have oli and adam's blog to argue and bicker about politics and christianity...i would like this blog to be peaceful, we can have discussions but nothing evil or crazy...  thank you, carry on ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all! I am at last part of this blog! I am Oliver, and I have my own blog at http://cheesythoughts.blogspot.com/. Adam has a blog too at http://adamswurd.blogspot.com/. I hope to chat to you all soon   -- Cheesy
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a band? nope...lol, but some of us are musically inclined, myself, sal, pat, limbaugh...speaking of which what do you play?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are all these ppl in band?  If so i feel really...out of place.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, Salopek, let me give you a little advice here: never question anything I do...if you know me and how weird I am, anything is possible.  I'ma nut so obviously, I have my own me-sized shell. My dad has a laptop that I use more often than he does so I can just kinda open my shell and bring it in with me anytime I feel like stayin in there for awhile.  I have everything about me posted inside mah little shell so usually I only go into it when I need to disclose personal info about myself.  I'm enough of a nut as it is, I don't need a shell to go with it...so I the shell isn't used too very often...I mean...I like scaring people, but not  that  much...I don't want to scare them completely away...you know...I wanna have SOME friends.  hee hee Ok that's all I haveta say for now. :-P
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm kinda a new bloggee, i guess, so im not sure if im doing this right. i think i have a blog thingy? but i screwed up the name and email thing, got lost on the internet, and here i am. so yeah. hey guys. -Marin
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well sal, the "price-less" sunglasses and watch would be yours, under two conditions...one if i had a million bucks and the other the world will never know and neither will you, cuz i'll prolly sell them before you could find out...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hannah, how on earth do u type from inside a nutshell, do you have a laptop?  and where on earth did u get a nutshell that big. Do you need help getting out?  :-)  and rachele BOO HISS to the person who won a sunglass and watch set (that will remain pricless) and didn't give it to me!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lol I never even wanted to be in county band...Madar just walked up to me one day and's like "congrats, you're in county band" and I was like uh... when  did I sign up for THAT?! But oh well...I knew half the songs already anyhow...and it was fun...  What instrument dyou play in the wind thingy Rachele?  well I haveta go ttyl
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ah yes, county band... i still harbor harsh feelings towards Matchett and Armstrong for that one... i mean i'm in Wind Ensemble as a freshman... shouldn't i get to go? he only sent people from freshmen band... BOO HISS, no offense to anyone who went...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Rachele I'm Hannah lol I go to Knoch and I know Salopek from...from...OMB WHERE DO I KNOW YOU FROM?!?!?  OH county band...haha sorry, sped moment :-P  And anyhoo he invited me to join this blog cuz...cuz... cuz I'm just that cool I guess. hee hee j/k but it makes me feel special! lol and uh...yeah that's me in a nutshell. :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so yes...brother sal has enlightened me with the new found knowledge that if two kids are twins then they are also siblings... DUH... a blonde moment by rachele :P
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If their male and female can't twins be brother and sister too?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      but if you think about it, we'd be twins, not brother and sister...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      definitely not brother and sister...that would be too weird, we just have the same most awesomest day of the year birthday.  but who are all these people? obviously i'm rachele, sal is zack, and pat i'm guessing is pat...but as for the rest?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ummmmm hi.  im now supposively apart of this blog so yea.  bye
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey fig c are u talkin about me and rachele?  If you are the answers no.  I don't have any sisters.  If you aren't, o well.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HI everyone! I'm part of this blog! I feel so special!!! YAY!!!! *ish very happy* 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey are you brother and sister?  I am Jenn or Figure C. This is another random blog and i like random things.  Like Penzoil.  it is such a random word in a conversation.  Anywhoo, i am happy to be a part of this blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you can be in charge... but i'm older *cough cough, only 5 hours...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey this is a blog that I am in charge of.  I am God in this blog.  Mwahahahahahaha.  Talk about whatever and I'll have fun screwing with it all (cause I can :-)  This should be fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KENNYWOOD!! Ive only been there once and it rained.  I hope 2morrow is better.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't let the boring-ness get ya down, pat.  Just wait for Cedar point, it'll be a blast I was there 2 weeks ago and it was awesome! I heart roller coasters. :D  have fun!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll   im here in charlotte doin absolutely nuttin.  goodness it is so boring  o well. i'll live
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm goin to Philly this wednesday b/c my sister's graduating from college...and I wanna go visit my other sister n my brother in NC sometime over the summer but I dunno if that's possible now that I'm working so much...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not really doing anything since my parents said that i cant go to California. *tear tear*
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so u guys goin newhere this summer?  im goin to charlotte this week and then cleveland and cedar point  ttyl pat
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hallelujah!!!  I hear the chorus of angels singing. HAGS to all!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SCHOOLS FINALLY OVER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  now we just have to figure out what to over the summer.  hope everyone has a great one -Pat
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      True, seneca is a very "crack" oriented school.  Why do you think i moved here, JK
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't worry... i'm not disappointed... so are most of the people @ Knoch, including one of my own family members...but...we're not gonna talk about that cuz it just makes us want to bring injury upon that certain person..........
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Hannah, I don't mean to dissapoint you, but the truth is that most of the kids at Seneca  are  crack-heads. :-)
     

    
</post>


</Blog>