<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally heard from Michael today.  Lo and behold he is not avoiding me.  I didn't really think he was.  I knew he was busy with work, I just found it very peculiar that the internet junkie hadn't been online all week.  His parents banned him from the internet once they found out about something he had done while we had been dating.  It's worse than that.  They are actually forcing him to move out.  I'm not surprised, but I don't know where he will go and where he will get the money.  I know, it's not my concern.  You fools, have you not learned anything!!  I love the man, so I make it my concern.  I will not lose sleep over it, but it concerns me.    I had fun at the party tonight.  Jill even tried to get Michael to come down to go out to the club with us to watch the drag show, but he couldn't.  He explained to me later why.  Another culmination of problems from his past unemployment.  I didn't know she had called him, but there isn't anything I can do about it now.  I may see him tomorrow.  I know, I know.  What the hell am I thinking!!!  I'm thinking that he needs someone to be there for him and it's time I stop wanting for myself and do what you truly do for the person you love.  I am going to focus on getting better, please don't worry about that, but I can be there for him, too.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I left the house around eight last night once my depression hit again.  I just couldn't stay in.  It's like this house sucks the happiness right out of me.  I drove for a little bit until I decided to call my brother.  He was camping with his friends out at Fish Lake and he invited me to come out.  I had continually declined every other invitation he given me, so I accepted.  Besides, how bad could it be.  It was time I ventured out to meet more people than the two people I hang out with here and Melanie who I talk with online.    It was a good experience. I met Shawna, a good prospect for a friend.  She is so sweet.  She also seems to be extremely open-minded, which is something I need.  Everyone in my past who lives here is not so.  It's so much of my depression.  I hate it.  I can be okay with me, but I know they never will be.  It hurts me so much.  However, it is something I will have to deal with.    I will post more tonight or tomorrow, for there is more in store for the day:  another party and a drag show. So much fun!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, I missed yesterday.  I bid your forgiveness.  I will make up for it tonight.  I was able to sleep an extra two hours uninterrupted yesterday before going to a group interview.  I hate those.  There is too much pressure for someone who suffers from performance anxiety.  Alas, I must bear my way through it.  However, I had to take their version of a math test.  I say their version because it was really a visual "how many are there in this picture" test.  I failed it.  I now have to wait a month if I want to re-take it.  I feel triumph in just having gone to the interview.  This is truly how bad it has been the last couple of days.    The afternoon proved to only get better as I spent it with Jill, while she purchased her new vehicle.  I was able to help her get a special discount because of my father.  We arrived at the dealership around half past five.  A salesperson wasted no time coming out to help us as we walked between vehicles.  He introduced himself as Scott.  We walked with him to the models she was specifically looking for.  I truly behaved myself until he had to say that it was a BAD thing that I was getting a divorce at 25.  I wanted to slap him upside his damn head.  "You obviously don't know my husband," was what I also wanted to say.  I didn't though.  It did spurn me to start the abuse that soon began in his office.    I don't remember every evil thing that spouted out of my mouth, but my proudest moment and I truly wish Melanie had been there to see it, was when he looked at me like I was the biggest bitch in the world.  I wasn't trying to be.  I had only pointed a mere fact out to him that he had overlooked.  I wasn't being nasty or mean.  I finally convinced him that I wasn't just messing around with him, that I was truly serious.  There wasn't a battery in the vehicle that he wanted Jill to test drive.  It wasn't my fault the service department put it on the center console!  He remedied the problem by finding another vehicle exactly the same as the one we had found earlier, WITH a battery.  By this point it started to drizzle and it was quickly turning to a harder rain.  He kept whining about the rain as if he would melt.  It took every ounce of strength in my body to hold my tongue.  I only said, "It's JUST rain."  What was running through my head was, "You were a Marine, I'm sure you had to deal with worse than this..."  Once an Air Force wife...  Sorry.    I awoke this morning able to get through That Particular Time by Alanis Morissette without crying.  A great triumph for me for the week.  I went back to sleep feeling pretty good.  I looked at the picture of us and the pictures of him and I didn't cry.  I didn't hope.  I was a little sad.  I wasn't ready to get ready of them.  My depression returned this afternoon.  Not as bad as it has been.  I couldn't cry but a few tears.  Either it's getting better or it's evolving.  I think it's the former.  I feel so much like myself before I moved back home.    My interview tonight went well and I have a second one there.  I won't know when until they call back to schedule it.  I'm happy about that.  I think, however, I have truly damaged any hope of having a friendship with M.J.  I called to talk to him tonight and he was leaving to go out.  He said he would call back or email me.  I know I am probably being paranoid.  Time will only tell.  He will never know how much he has meant to me.  He will never know that he was my first regret. I know I cannot go back and change anything.  Okay...  I'm truly worried about Jill.  We talked about her self-perception.  She does not think highly of her physical appearance.  She's tired of being the size that she is.  She had first asked me if she looked as bad as she thought she did.  I told her no.  Later, I explained I knew it didn't matter what I told her because she would believe about herself whatever she believed.  It's something she has to deal with.  I can't change it.  I've tried with other friends and failed.  I discussed with her the possibility of her seeing a therapist.  She is seriously considering it.  Unfortunately, she will have to do it without her insurance.  She doesn't want it to affect her career.    I bid you all a good night.  Hopefully, I can go another week feeling the way I do now.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What little progress I had made was lost in today.  No attempt was made to contact Michael so that was a good thing.  However, every emotional breakdown I could possibly have had happened today.  This was not easy since my grandmother arrived today and this makes me want to be even stronger around her.  So, I leave the house every time I feel the need to breakdown.  I drive to the park where I sit and write in my journal, or sit on a bench and take in everything and cry.  I have to be one of the worst people to walk by.    What makes everything worse is that on my way home from my second trip to the park, I called Mike.  This is not the same as Michael.  From here on out I will refer to him as M.J.  I have been trying to re-start a friendship with him in the last couple of weeks.  I don't know what possessed me to call him tonight.  I had made an oath to myself that I would not put this on him.  I called him crying.  A minute and a half into our phone call it ended.  I don't know if his phone died, or what, but he is not the type of person to hang up on someone.  At least he didn't use to be.  Then again, he could have changed.  I don't know.  I am lost in the woods again, not feeling so strong, feeling more like Alice looks.    How do I heal?  I used to know the answer.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      About two months ago I tore my mother's kitchen apart to paint it.  This included taking down the cupboard doors.  Sadly, they have not been a part of the kitchen since then.  Tonight, however, they rejoined the kitchen after I drilled new holes for the hardware and put them back up.  Much rejoicing!  Too much labor.  I am finishing a project I started too long ago.  This is a good thing for me.  It is unlike me to have let it go this long.   Otherwise, today was quite unproductive.  I really don't have much of a life to speak of.  It's quite sad.  Anyone who could ramble on about their life and live the one that I have, well, kudos to you.  So, as my ex seems to think, I will live in my dream world for the moment.  To do so, though, I would, for once, have to think of a dream world.    Since no dream world exists for me and at this point it would simply take more energy than I care to expel after my project and shopping expedition with my mother, I am retiring for the evening.  Shopping is usually quite enjoyable.  However, do it often enough with my mother and it will become a chore.  Please, trust me with this one.  Meghan, should you read this, I warn you: we share the same room for now, do not tell her I said that.  I love her, but you too know how she is shopping.  I bid you good night.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I need to take Melanie up on her offer to send me to Mexico.  I've never been there, but to have no care in the world would be really nice right now.  Of course, I told her the trip wouldn't be complete without her.  We both need to lay in the sun, soaking the rays, enjoying the scenery...and frozen drinks with little umbrellas.  Alas, there is not enough money for both of us to go and I need to get a job.  Reality hits and weighs my shoulders so far down there is this great pain.  Where is a free masseuse when you need one?  Hmm...today was not so bad.  After all, how bad of a day could one have when they do not have a job to speak of?  I do have plenty of other stressors, though.  It seems Michael is not talking to me at all.  Well, fine.  His choice.  I'm finished trying to talk to him.  Funny kind of friend it is that doesn't answer the phone when you call, though.  Melanie, however, has always had this great knack for cheering me up.  And Jill and I spent some time together tonight.  Overall, today was good, regardless of what some other people.   Mexico would still be nice, though...                             or a nice beheading.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Not exactly a day to remember, so to speak, but I'll cope. If I could only purge Michael, my love of four years, from my dreams, it would make my life easier.  The whole situation with him is so complicated.  I just wrote it all out on paper, hoping to cleanse myself, and I don't know if it worked.  However, I seriously need to focus on myself right now.  Sugarcult's Pretty Girl seems to speak to me so well right now.  My sister listened to it with me in the car today, looked at me and said, "That's you."  I'm scraping my way out of the pit I fell into since I moved back home.  My wit is returning.  I actually made my family laugh today.  This is a huge achievement for me because I have never been the funny one in my family.  Exhaustion is claiming my body, so I bid you good night. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
                   YOU ARE CORDIALLY INVITED TO   THE                                MUCH DESERVED BEHEADING OF MICHAEL.                           HIS HEAD WILL ROLL AT HALF PAST TEA TIME.                             TEA WILL BE SERVED AFTER WITH BISCUITS.                            THE VERY UNLUCKY CARRIER OF HIS UNUSUALLY                              LARGE HEAD WILL BE COMPENSATED WITH                                A LOVELY HOMEMADE TEAPOT COZY                                             AND                               A CASE OF CADBURRY HAZELNUT BARS.                             NO NEED TO R.S.V.P. THERE IS PLENTY OF ROOM FOR ALL.                                      HOPE TO SEE YOU THERE!                                                        THE QUEEN
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My bills fall behind another month.  This is not something I am proud of.  In fact, I hate it.  I am so anal about paying everything and everything on time, that this is truly killing me.  I keep looking for jobs and interviewing, but nothing has openend up for me.  I want to kick myself in the ass at times for having left Virginia and my job there, regardless of the fact that I was scraping by with what I was getting paid.  However, I was, at least, getting paid something.    Now, I had an interview yesterday at a drugstore.  It was to be the second one.  I was so elated that I had done well for the first one and had gotten this far.  I arrived at the store twenty minutes early.  (I told you I'm horribly anal.)  I sat in my car for about ten minutes and then went inside only to find out that the manager I was supposed to see wasn't there.  In fact, he wouldn't be there at all.  He was in Michigan.  I know I had the date and time right because I repeated everything to the other manager when he had set up the interview time with me last week.  So, I am now awaiting a phone call to hopefully set up a new interview time.    I am still working on my incredibly small bedroom.  That may, in fact, be my problem.  I have to find a place to put everything that I have in such a small place.  However, I am making great headway.  I should be finished by the weekend.  At that point, I may have to start helping my sister with her room.  Otherwise, Meghan may never finish.  I would like to see a finished product before she leaves for Germany on the 23rd.  By the way, the yellow is amazingly growing on me.  There is much work to be done and found... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Five days have passed since I last wrote anything.  I was in Michigan again on Thursday evening.  It was a very good evening with Michael.  He made dinner for the two of us and we talked.  We had spent Tuesday evening together, too.  We discussed our friendship and the relationship we have with each other.  He explained why he broke it off with me at the beginning of May.  Not many people would understand, I suppose, but I do only because I know how horridly, emotionally weak I had become.  He knew that if he continued to be my crutch, I would only get worse.  I needed to be on my own for awhile and he recognized that.  He said it was the hardest thing he had to do and he never stopped loving me.  Five weeks from Friday we can start dating again.  I know it sounds anal to put such a stupid time limit on it, but it it better for me to do so.  I will be stronger and it will give us a better chance.    That gives reason for one day.  When I got home on Friday, my sister and I attacked our bedroom and the attached room to it and rearranged it.  Our beds are now in two different rooms and it was a huge project.  We are still, in fact, working on it.  Yesterday, we painted.  Melanie, you will be so proud.  I taped the ceiling and the floor off before I started painting.  My room is soothing and you could easily fall asleep in it.  However, Meghan painted her room lemon yellow.  Can we say bright?  Yes, it's bright like the sun yellow.  She turns on the lights in her room and you are blown away by the color.  I can't wait till she puts the things back on her walls. Sorry, Meghan, had to tease you here, too.  No, it does look nice and she'll have cherries painted on it, too.  That's her plan.  (So, we're going to have curtains hanging between the rooms, too.  That'll really help.)    Okay, so I'm rambling on about nothing and I have so much work to do before I go to bed tonight.  I thank you for your understanding in my absence and bid you a good night.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday was actually a pretty good day.  Meghan was preparing to graduate and I attacked my boxes of clothes.  I had to do this so I could find something to wear.  Plus, I needed to re-organize the boxes so we could eventually get to the window.  We had a lot of fun goofing around.  I pulled out two costumes and told my mother and grandmother that I would wear them to the ceremony that night.  They laughed.  One was my renaissance costume; the other my belly dancer costume.  I was in a very good mood.  I found a couple of dresses that fit and was trying to decide between them.  I curled Meg's hair for her and she left a little after four.    The graduation was like it was the last ones I had attended for the high school, mine included: loud and obnoxious.  I don't understand why these people just can't keep there mouths shut so you can hear what's going on.  It's not that difficult to act like civilized human beings.  I had a near migraine and the noise would soon onset one of my panic attacks.  Thankfully, I was doing my best to focus on my sister and her achievement.    So, you are wondering where the guilt trips come in?  Earlier in the day, I had called Michael to ask him a question.  I was not expecting him to answer his phone at 9:30 in the morning.  I had planned on leaving a voicemail, but he actually answered.  We spoke briefly.  Later, while waiting for our table at the restaurant, Michael called me back.  I was in an obviously good mood because of the evenings events, still a little shaky, but in a good mood.  He told me not to call him in the morning.  I apologized.  He re-iterated his point.  I emphasized my apology.  Then he said he got off of work at 6 (today) and he would call me then.  We have plans.  Now, how is this a guilt trip?  Coming out of his mouth, it is.  Plus, I skipped a bit.  And he was ornery as hell from working a very long day.  I AM NOT excusing him or myself.    After the phone call, I excused myself from dinner, knowing my panic attack that had been waiting was now coming.  I don't like having them in public.  This morning my mother came in and made me feel really bad for leaving.  I explained that I didn't really feel good.  I will have to find a way to make it up to my sister.  However, I know there really isn't any way to do that.  It was a one night thing.  She means so much to me.  To think that she believes that she isn't that important to me really hurts.  I'd give up my crown to be Tweedle-dum, if she'd agree to be Tweedle-dee.  That's how much she means to me.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I missed yesterday because I was out of town.  I don't particularly care to share the events of yesterday, because Scarrlett already knows and she is the only one I care to know right now.  I would like to address the comment made the other day.  I think that I have been misunderstood slightly, or I have misrepresented myself.  So, this is what I intend to do today.  Never did I want ANYONE to feel sorry for me.  I have my close friends who help me with my problems.  I am simply using this as another means to vent.    Michael, on the other hand, I will defend to my dying day.  Even though the last four months have been extremely rough for us, he has been there for me when even my family wasn't.  He has seen me through an abusive marriage and encouraged me to stand up for myself.  The only thing he wants me to do is to recognize that if I'm not happy that I am the only one who can change it.  He would also never cheat on anyone seeing how his ex-wife cheated on him FOUR times with his best friend.  There is a first time for everything, but not every man cheats.  He has a lot of selfish people in his life demanding his time.  Don't automatically jump to this conclusion just because it's what our society has so easily escaped to doing.  Cheating would also mean that we are still a couple, which we are not.  If you might have noticed, I've been trying to get over the break-up.  We are still friends, however.  Scarrlett made a very valid point in her comment.  To be honest, though, he most likely, would not allow me to be there for him.  He usually is very self-sufficient when it comes to his emotions, or so he says.    So, I will keep my whining to a minimum.  However, I do request that if you are going to make such a bold face comment, know one thing about me, love:  I HATE run-on sentences.  My grammar may not be perfect, but it's decent.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And the trumpets blow... or maybe not.  However, there is a soaring in my heart that I have missed.  I have been working now for two weeks.  It's a good feeling.  Granted, it is only part time, but another job is possibly landing at my feet, too.  I couldn't truly be happier.  Well, that's not entirely true, but I feel so much better than when I started here.    Now, I don't know if the rest of you would like an explanation for the invitation that you received for Michael's beheading.  I have not lost my mind.  I will say that I am done with his games.  Unfortunately, there is still love for him in my heart.  I know, strangle me, but that doesn't go away overnight.  He pissed me off none-the-less.  I am clear-headed enough now to know when enough is rightly enough.  I cannot and will not take any more emotional beatings from him.  That is why I left my husband.  I deserve better than that and will accept nothing less than what I deserve.  He has not chosen to speak to me, yet, and when we finally do, it will most likely be goodbye.  It is a sadness everyone deals with many times in their lives.    Moving on...friend's are slowly multiplying and that makes me happy.  Liz is a kindred heart.  I am protective of her just as I am of Mel.  Perhaps more so because I sense a fragility in her, yet.  She has more rebuilding to do than I did.  Melanie helped me with mine.  I hope I will be of service to Liz.  She is strong.  She knows what needs to be done, it's just doing it that scares her.    Well, off I go to reign over my small kingdom... Peace to you all. 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>