<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, my exam is finally over.  I can shout and dance in joy.  I am free for the summer.  Well, at least free from school.  My boyfriend came to visit.  I ate enough to feed all the hunger in the world.  It was very good, ribs, crepe, ice cream.  Moderation was key as usual.  We then went to see Shrek I never though I would like it as much; it was a very sweet movie.  One of those movies that makes you come out wanting  to hug your neighbor and smile like a fool, that is until you realize your neighbor is insane and likes to smoke too much pot while having wild parties and shouting that he is going to kill you when you complain about it, good times.    On the disturbing news front,  urlLink a men  committed suicide after having sex with a hen.  Perhaps the hen told him that she was seen somebody else.  The villagers afterwards killed the hen.  Maybe they wanted to save her from the mental turmoil or maybe they were simply hungry.  We have the fake news in the form of journals like The Onion and yet amazingly enough real news can be just as bizarre.   I am trying to steer away from TV which I usually don’t usually watch but the power is too great.  I love watching the cold case files, and seeing how they catch somebody after many years.  I think that is quite a morbid taste but I can’t stop watching.  I wonder what that says about me.  I was reading the other day that  urlLink 1 in 75 American men are in jail , what depressing bit of news.  A country where crime is lower and lower every year but where more young men end up wasting their lives in prison.  Sadly it is probably the fault of society, we are so obsessed with entrainment and only the most chocking will do.  Whenever there is a murder in as city as safe as mine it plays in the news weeks and weeks on end.  People start to believe that our cities are unsafe that we need to be tougher on crime that smoking a joint deserves years and years in jail.  I am probably part of the problem with me liking shows like the cold files. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Currently on page 600, 600 pages to go, 2 days until exam.  Feeling somewhat better but still coughing like mad.  Today in class: what do we look for in the sigmoid colon, apparently that is where some people lose their vibrators.  Our instructor claims that when that happens he just looks for the medical student with the longest thinnest fingers.  Am I ever glad that my fingers are short and stubby.    Last day of stage I in medical school, one more day closer to becoming a full blown malpractice case.  I can't wait.  Night spend partly doing yoga.  My male yoga professor was talking about how badly he needed a pedicure.  I think I need one too.  I like this whole metrosxual thing happening, maybe in the future I will be able to go for pedicures with my boyfriend and male friends, quality bonding time in my opinion.  The rest of the night was spent at the anatomy lab, looking at cadavers in very poor shape and learning the blood supply of the abdomen.  I can't stand anatomy, I hope I never find out I really want to be a surgeon that would be the death of me.  I would have to learn all the names of things named after the old anatomy masters, at least they had fresh bodies and not the formaldehyde ones, they smell of the preservative is just too much for me.    urlLink Stephen Harper  promised to finally lower taxes not only below US levels but the lowest taxes in the world!!!  I am dancing in joy.  Things that are useless and that my tax money will not pay for anymore:   1)	No more decent public education for anyone! At least Canada can be number one at something, illiteracy baby!  If you are teacher you will be expected to work mostly pro-bono.  Those lazy teachers finally will get what they deserve. 2)	With illiteracy there will be no more informed patients to whine about how your management of their illness sucks.  Finally unquestionable control, the reason why everyone became a doctor 3)	No more publicly funded health care, fantastic! I can charge whatever I want for my services !  A cow, a horse or a BMW!! 4)	No more road safety, no more road repairs.  If you can't afford an SUV to go over the holes in the roads well you are a loser who doesn't deserve to drive 5)	Decrease the pay of police.  Well, those good for nothing cops can get their salary like every other hard working police entrepreneur in third world countries, they can simply stop and bribe people, hello free market!  6)	No more welfare.  All those mothers with young children that can't afford health care on their minimum wage salaries can just put their kids up for adoption or to work, pickpocketing has never looked so good. 7)	The best part is that my taxes will go to important things like the army to support our best friends and closest allies, the United States of America (I really like Americans but their government I can do without).  I always wanted to die for big oil!   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The countdown continues, 3 days to go, currently on page 450, 750 pages to go.  Still feel like someone hit me over the head with a hammer and fed me 200 liters of straight vodka. Common cold 200, Silvana 0  Classes were interesting to say the least a discussion on gastrointestinal pediatric cases.  All cases sounded very similar to each other, child shows up and is irritable in the emergency room.  The symptoms described were so vague and my studying not so in depth that I could not think of the potential diagnosis.  Neither could most of my classmate, the professor was starting to get irritated "c'mon guys, the exam is on Friday" it is a "classic presentation for intussusception", "classic!", and somebody turns to me and asks what is intussusception?  As my usual perusing of news occurred today I stumbled onto possibly one of the most important  urlLink news  items of our age, apparently somebody after taking a look at illnesses such as HIV, cancer and antibiotic resistant tuberculosis decided that our efforts and research funds should really be focused on studies about how much bacteria doctors carry on their ties.  Now, if that is not earth shattering I don't know what is.  The news item carefully explains how previous studies have shown that doctors carry germs on their hands, clothing and pencils.  But could ties also carry germs?  I was really under the impression that ties were made of magical, germ repelling substances but to my surprise ties were found to carry potentially "evil" germs.  The author of the study suggests that ties be banned from the realm of health care while the author of the news article suggested that doctors start wearing bow ties (wouldn't that be sexy?).  I have a better suggestion as the fashion adviser of Queer Eye for the Straight Guy pointed out why not wear ties as belts, now that is something that would perhaps be more hygienic and launch medicine as one of the most fashionable professions out there.  Now that problem has been solved and somebody found the cause of bad hair days, apparently a gene called  urlLink frizzled , stupid frizzled!  I feel safe in the hands of science, maybe genetic engineering will come and solve the problem at the very root. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Time until final exam 4 days.  Page that I am currently studying 300, pages to go 900. I am liking my lecture on bacterial overgrowth, Go Bacteria!  I woke up this morning and had to go out for dim sum, for A's birthday.  I was so tired from being up half the night worried about being so behind and the other half the night coughing up a lung with this horrible cough that I am having.  I am trying to do everything in my power to make it go away.  I have even turned to remedies I said I would never use such as  "ALTERNATIVE MEDICINE", indeed will I be put at the stake and burned down?  I have tried using halls, echinacea, codeine but alas nothing has worked.  As I am ever so perceptive I happened to leave my codeine cough syrup out in the light so I doubt that at this point is good for anything other than it's awful taste.  I will do pretty much anything to get rid of this cough if someone was to tell me that showing my naked bum to the full moon while at the same time bathing in goat's milk would cure my cough I would do it.  In any case dim sum was pretty good, as usual I ate too much.  The title of this journal should really be "the adventures of a woman who eats too much and goes to med school to try to teach others about self control and healthy choices".  Yes, I am an example to be followed by all, moderation is my motto.  I tried the fried chicken feet.  I thought it was ok (not my favourite in flavour) but some of my friends could not eat food that looked like a foot.  Which kind of makes me think of the way boars used to be presented at banquets in the past, with the apple in their mouth.  Maybe the apple was supposed to be the salad.  They may have though wow that pig looks like it used to be a nice healthy pig who enjoyed apples.  Maybe people in the past were more connected to their food.  There was no reason to hide the fact the pig was alive at one point, its form may have been beautiful.  It seems like in this culture we don't want to know where our food comes from, we are disconnected from the fact that some food use to have a beating heart, and some may even have had feet.  The most interesting is when people tell me they can have fish, well it has big eyes that are looking at them.  If only fish like chicken feet would make themselves more attractive, the possibilities are truly endless with genetic engineering: chicken born without feet, fish that will not look at you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I have decided to start a journal on-line.  I think this will take some time away from studying.  Not that I need any more time to procrastinate but why not add to the craziness.  The most difficult part of this thing was what to name my blog.  What is it about me that is most important.  I really don't think that being a medical student defines me but really is what takes most of my time right now, by default it becomes the name.  I have a gastro intestinal(GI) exam on Friday.  My very last exam in second year.  I am very afraid being weeks and weeks behind and having no hope to catch up.  So in order to celebrate being so far behind I decided to go see Troy.  I had very, very low expectations about the movie so I was not hard to meet them.  But overall I though the movie was not bad.  They could have done a much better job with the cinematography but I was too enthralled by the sight of the men wearing the sarongs...  Some men should only be allowed to wear sarongs, Brad Pitt is one of the lucky ones.  There was a bit too much killing for my liking and the scenes with the burning dead reminded me of the anatomy lab.  When Hector is in the pyre and his father is placing the coins on his eyes I though Hector is just going to snap out of it and bite his father (very odd though in hindsight).  I feel the same way in the anatomy lab, the body is just going to wake up and shake my hand.  I came home and called my boyfriend, he had also gone to see Troy with his best friend.  How funny.  At some point in the movie his friend turned towards him and said that he was no longer sure that he was a heterosexual.  I am the queen of procrastination having spend so many years wasting time.  My favourite way to do it is reading the news.  I tell myself is good for you.  You don't want to be one of the med students that knows nothing of the world.  If you were not to have found out that the roof of the Paris airport collapsed would you still be a complete person?  The worse is that I am starting to have a reputation for my procrastination, my friends are calling their procrastination pulling a Silvana. I don't know if that is a compliment or not. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So that is my new nickname.  I rather like it.  Today a nurse in the unit called me that and she said that she didn’t know my name but because I was always smiling that should be my name.  I think for my optimistic outlook in life I have always been called strange names bubbly one, are you high on something, and now sunshine.  The third one is the charm.  I supposed is good to wake up in a good mood most days but it really sucks when you are having a bad day, everybody knows and then I get all the questions, what is wrong with you?  How come you are soo sad (even when I am just too tired to smile, people assume I am just upset).  But sunshine, that is winner.  However I did feel high today.  I was trying to secure my bike rack to bike today and the bolts were covered with silicon, so being the smart person that I used to be prior to the following incident, I decided to burn the plastic off the bolts,  I placed the bolts on the stove and proceeded to put the temp at the highest setting possible.  The bolts now secure my bike beautifully but I am afraid the plastic smell has ruined my lungs, who would have though burnt plastic smelled so bad? Silicon can’t really be all that bad for you, some women use it for the breasts, other for their lips, I just happen to take a skin deep approach to beauty and place it in my lungs.  I bought the bike rack before the bike, as I had already bought my rack I saw a street sign advertising a bike sale.  I was just going to take a look when I tried all the bikes and the one that felt the best was this hot pink bike.  So, now I get to ride my hot pink bike, I will be stilling in pink, if I were to have a pink biking shirt, the entire I wish I was still 8 years old look would be going on strong.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have just spent my weekend doing nothing.  I was really trying to read for next year.  I am supposed to look up a different illness every day and the management (according to my self made schedule).  But all I did was watch TV and eat.  I think I am like a bear getting ready for hibernation.  I love it.  Usually during the school year I watch 1 to 2 hours of TV per week, but I am making up for lost time!  TV and me, reunited at last as if not rift between us had ever happened.  So far I have managed to look up the management of aortic stenosis and HONK.  I love the name that illness, what a great acronym.  I have been at work for 2 weeks and have looked up 2 illnesses, to get through Harrison's I would need 2000 weeks at work!  I guess the summer is just too short.  I am really enjoying my work, mostly because I get to hear patients stories and see how somebody presents with something as supposed to what we learned in class.  The only boring part for me but really good for the patients is that there is not much in the ways of adverse outcomes to report.  My confidence in medicine is restored.  In fact none of the patients I am studying has died in 2 weeks!  That is really excellent.  People usually ask me if I am taking care of some patients or if I am a resident, I get all giggly and say no.  hehehehe, me no.  I guess in less than 2 months I will be taking care of patients, and in less than 2 years I will be a resident.  What a scary though.  Something really sad happened the other day.  An immigrant woman showed up with her only son to the ER she was dying but still fully competent and alert.  The doctor knew things were going bad and told the son that as soon as his mom would get intubated she would not come out of it and that he should try to talk to her prior to intubation because it would probably be the last time he would speak to her. He started to panic he had no idea how bad she really was.  Coming from an immigrant family I could relate and I felt so sad for him, I don't know if I were to lose my family what I would do.  It is just horrible.  Prior to med school I used to love watching those "life in the ER shows" and it always made me angry when doctors that came from really affluent families commented on the fact that they felt really sorry for their well to do patients when they went skiing and broke their neck or something.  They would then add, this people are just like me as supposed to the teenager that shows up with a broken neck from a bullet wound.  I supposed I am just like them I felt so sad for that guy because I can relate to him, I guess we are better able to empathize when we can actually put ourselves in the shoes. ! 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh sweet, sweet, sweet computer how much have I missed thee, at long last we are reunited.  It feels like a century.  After moving downstairs in my building I have been as they say disconnected.  I missed the sweet smell, the nice feel of my darling computer.  School being finally over for the school year I can now go to work, while trying to enjoy life.  I am doing research on adverse events caused by medical error.  It is quite interesting, the literature research points out that more people die from medical error than from car accidents.  Makes you feel good.  Although it worries me I can see how complex care is, so many people involved that it is a miracle that no more mistakes occur.  However, I am sure we can do better.  As part of my work, I get to sit in on rounds.  It is so exiting.  Lady walks in with a swollen foot what is your approach to a swollen foot?  Men walks in with low salt what is your approach to low salt? (add cheetos maybe?)  But in all seriousness it is really interesting despite the fact that it occurs at 8 AM and that it is not mandatory for my work.  I can’t wait until next year for me to start doing these things or thinking of my approach to different problems.  There are some interesting moments where I can laugh at what goes on, for example one doctor was discussing a huge testicle and to demonstrate the size of the appendage he used his hands to show the volume and describe his own volume  as a normal reference point to further our education.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>