<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today a friend of mine sent me a link to the graduation speech that Jon Stewart made at William and Mary.  There's a lot of silly stuff in there, of course, but something he said struck me as very true.  I'll quote it:  "So how do you know what is the right path to choose to get the result that you desire? And the honest answer is this. You wonÂt. And accepting that greatly eases the anxiety of your life experience.   When I left William and Mary I was shell-shocked. Because when youÂre in college itÂs very clear what you have to do to succeed. And I imagine here everybody knows exactly the number of credits they needed to graduate, where they had to buckle down, which introductory psychology class would pad out the schedule. You knew what you had to do to get to this college and to graduate from it. But the unfortunate, yet truly exciting thing about your life, is that there is no core curriculum. The entire place is an elective. The paths are infinite and the results uncertain. And it can be maddening to those that go here, especially here, because your strength has always been achievement. So if thereÂs any real advice I can give you itÂs this.   College is something you complete. Life is something you experience. So donÂt worry about your grade, or the results or success. Success is defined in myriad ways, and you will find it, and people will no longer be grading you, but it will come from your own internal sense of decency which I imagine, after going through the program here, is quite strongÂalthough IÂm sure downloading illegal filesÂbut, nah, thatÂs a different story.   Love what you do. Get good at it. Competence is a rare commodity in this day and age. And let the chips fall where they may."  Indeed.  It's like one big huge elective.  I am currently taking German ;-)  If you are interested in the  urlLink whole speech .  ***  While Matt was visiting me, I got a letter from the United States, the address on the envelope penned in my own hand.  Aha - I knew what that meant - it was one of my SASEs returning from a submission to the US.  This time Ploughshares of Emory college was writing to me to let me know that my poems had not been accepted.  Not a problem - Matt was in town and I was feeling fine.  And sending out poems for publication is like sending out resumes.  Once you start it gets easier as you go.  But receiving that envelope reminded me of an exercise we did in the tenth grade.  It might be a standard thing that high school teachers do.  Our English teacher was trying to teach us that defining your gprecisely precicely helps you realize them.  She told us to write down some goals we would like to accomplish within that year.  She said she would send us the letters during the summer and we could look back and see if we had accomplished what we had wanted to do.  We all laughed at the assignment, but once we got our pens and papers out, we were hushed and concentrated in the heady-aired North Carolina classroom.  I remember what I wrote to myself - something about getting together with a boy - initial P.D. (By the time I got my letter in the summer, his allure had faded and I was on to another crush).  But I found the exercise very interesting.  Not too different from the development plans I am turning in to my bosses these days.  What do you wish?  Define it, hone it, and go for it.    Related to the Jon Stewart speech, I think defining that goal is the most difficult.  It's a rite of passage to come to terms with the uncertainty entailed by total freedom of choice.  "Great, but it is the  right  choice?"  No one to tell you but you.  "It's hard to score if you don't have a goal." (Quoted from a quirky little book by Paul Arden - "It's Not How Good You Are, It's How Good You Want to Be")  Treading water on dry land won't get you anywhere - but jumping into the pool - well - at least you're treading water in something.  Threat of drowning but also chance to move somewhere.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is why I like French women, and am glad that my mother is one: "French women believe in feminism, but not at the price of femininity. They still want to be wooed and seduced. The idea of hating men or wishing to exist without them seems ridiculous to the vast majority of French women. What is the point of flaunting fashion or flair if men aren't around to admire them? Where is the fun or frisson in life if men aren't around to play their part? The approach is perfectly acceptable to most French men, who are as excited by women's brains as they are by women's bodies. The ideal combination for a Frenchman is mens sexy in corpore sexy."  - Quoted from The Xenophobe's guide to the French
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Attempt number two at starting a blog.  I had one going strong for a few weeks in early 2004,... and then technical problems stepped in.  And I don't have patience with technical problems. That, and I misplaced my login to the backend.  But enough about the past - this is about the future.  The future of the Blog.   I just got back from a trip to Paris with my good friend Matt.  It was his first time outside of the United States and he behaved like a Prince.  I'll have to sort the tidbits of our trip in my mind so that I can include the prime discoveries here.  Right now it is still a kaleidoscopic blurrr and all of my colleagues are wondering how I can return from vacation looking so happy yet so tired.  To me, that's the sign of a successful vacation - but I am not the kind to hang out on the beach for days on end.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Crazy things sometimes happen to me.  The sorts of things that are so unbelievable, yet true, that you wish you had someone to turn to - lift your shoulders and stare at with bug eyes that say: "did you see that?!?!"  The most recent of these events happened last Thursday as I was walking home from the grocery store.    The evening summer sun was shining as I scanned the street to cross it with my grocery bag in hand.  An orange-toned car approached and I was trying to read the driver's face to see if he looked like he was about to speed up or if I had the time to dart across the street.  We made eye contact.  Even though he was folded up into the driver's seat of a European compact, I could tell that he was sportsy and attractive.  My natural reaction was to smile.  And he smiled in return.  Boy - what a smile.  One of those little connections that make you think - "Yes, life is beautiful and it is good to be young."  As I crossed the street after he passed, I smiled at his back bumper, the lingering thought in my mind, the smile still on my lips.  I thought I caught a glimpse of him crouching slightly in the front seat to get a look from the rear view mirror.  I felt myself blush.  One last look down the street and then I rounded the corner, towards my apartment.  One step, two step, three step - honk.  A decisive loud - honk.  I turned around and saw that the driver had put the car into reverse and was honking at me from the mouth of the one way street.  (The lines of Missy Elliot's  "Work It"  song were running through my head "Is it worth it, let me work it...flip it and reverse it").  I started walking towards his car and he emerged to his full height.  Tall, broad-shouldered and smiling.  The car was still running, the key's in the ignition.  He left the door open, disturbing the flow of traffic and walked towards me.  "We don't know each other yet," he said to me in German.  "No, we don't" I said and took his extended hand.  "I'm Swen."  "Kristine."  "Do you want to learn to play Badminton?" He asked.  The look of shock on my face was probably visible.  Several buff men in German have told me they play Badminton - which to me, evokes the image of well behaved British children playing in white shorts at the edge of a cricket field because they are too young to participate in "the real game."  Our high school German exchange student had also proudly told us that his sport was badminton.  His physical presence and the high pitch of his voice (blame puberty) had simply confirmed my suspicions about badminton.  And now, I was in a land of tall and strong men - the most impressive of which tell me they play badminton.  They might as well answer in their deep baritone tones - "Yeah in my free time I play freeze tag."  I stare in response to his question.  "I give lessons every Tuesday and Thursday.  I'll give you my cell phone number."  I pull out my cell phone.  "So what's your last name, Swen?" To put it in my cell phone.  "Oh, you don't need my last name." As he says this I am thinking -  Ok - so he's a total player whose reputation is so ruined he can't even hand out his last name   "How can I tell you apart form all the other Svens in my telephone then?" I say innocently.  "I'm Swen with a 'w' - I'll be the only one in your phone spelled that way"  Aha.  With that I had nothing to do but type in his number, labeled - "Swen"  As he walked away from me (his car was still running, open-doored, blocking traffic) he turned back to me and said, with a wink - "Don't delete the number!"  "I won't," I answered.  I walked the 20 meters towards my front door - I was about to be late for my English student arriving in 15 minutes, and the apartment still needed a little touch up with the vacuum.  As I put down the groceries, I wanted to write an SMS as proof that I had not deleted the number, and so that he would have mine.  I don't want to call him up to do something, after all.  I typed my SMS - "My phone speaks English.  Did not delete number.  Now you have mine."  And then instructed the little mobile to send to SWEN.  The little mobile then answers me:  message not sent.  incorrect number   In my nervousness and surprise, I omitted one digit in the telephone number.  And that, gentlemen, is why you always give your last name to a lady.  My encounter was to be a mere memory.  ***  Back in the office on Monday, I thought I would ask my developer/buff-badminton-playing colleague if he happened to know a badminton player named - Sven.  Sven with a "W".  He answered that he didn't, asked me if I was interested in badminton.  One of the female developers in the room pipes up: "There's a Swen with a "w" at our company," she says.    "No, no" I reply - "he doesn't work for Intershop".  I know everyone at our company, and particularly note the handsome ones (this is an IT company after all), and knew that I had never seen "Swen" with a "w".  Just for fun, I typed "Swen" and a wildcard for the last name into our employee search (including pictures). What do I see?  Badminton man is the new marketing intern!  As I type this, I can imagine that it may not seem funny.  In order to try and make you chuckle, let me explain how I interpreted the news.  You know the classic comedic foil - lets take the example from "Working Girl" with Melanie Griffith.  Melanie Griffith's character, the secretary, meets Harrison Ford in a bar.  One thing leads to another and then end up in bed together.  The next morning as she rushes into the office to see Harrison Ford at the board meeting, the big business guy.  *gasp* Oh no - they had no idea of their identities.  Dramatic  Tum TUm TUM . So this was that kind of funny situation because the roles were a tiny bit reversed since I have already been working for the company for four years.  And for someone who didn't want to divulge his last name... well, it didn't last very long.    I think I will walk into his office tomorrow and give him a little surprise ;-)  * I have to accredit that freeze tag joke to Jason.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Top 5 daily private moments :  &nbsp;&nbsp; 5) That first sip of coffee  &nbsp;&nbsp; 4) The smell of my own&nbsp;perfume (very light) as I am working in front of my computer.  &nbsp;&nbsp; 3) Music, music - any music. (Even if it&nbsp;is overhearing someone humming to themselves in the elevator)  &nbsp;&nbsp; 2) The rustle of thick cool sheets when slipping into them at night.  &nbsp;&nbsp; 1) Dreaming, dreaming, dreaming - uninhibited, in full color with a score in stereo. What are yours?    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With "High Fidelity", Nick Hornby emblazoned a few words in my mind: "top five _".    Top five fill in the blank.    A wonderful pastime between friends.  This morning, as I was humming the tune of a song before I even knew what I was doing, I thought: "Kristine - top five most defining pieces of media that have come through your life".  But before we hit that topic.  Let us do a different top 5 list.  Top five silences:  5) The silence inside a car right after you shut the door on a summer night - the cicadas and crickets strumming in the dew outside.  4) The silence due to the lag time on a very long distance telephone call: "hello?"  ...... "hello!"  3) On one of your favorite CDs, the silence before the best track starts.  When the previous track has ended and your body has premonitions of the chords about to strike.    2) That electric silence before a first kiss.  I wish, I wish, I wish..... spark.* splash - Oh no! hmmmmmmmmm  1) This one:    "Tell me something nice"    *silence*    "Is there so little about me you like?"    "No. So much"  Anyone care to play?  Come up with your own top 5 list?  I've got several others in store.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I am planning on moving to the US in October... and am looking for an interesting job... and scan Craigs List every now and then for jobs in cities in which I would like to land.  This is how I came across the announcement for the reality show casting call." A&E Cable Network Reality Show Casting Now... A&amp;E Cable Network is looking for people who have always wanted to work in the entertainment industry but have never had the means to do so. If you think you have what it takes and are at least 21 years old then contact us immediately....Only a select few will be chosen to come out to Hollywood to work as an intern at some of the most sought after internships in the industry. Our camera crews will be following you beginning to end as you discover exactly what it takes to make it to the top. Make sure to email us a recent picture as well as a brief bio about yourself and why we should choose you. While on your journey, all expenses will be paid. "  blah blah blah you know the rest.  And I got to thinking - how silly, how funny.  These reality shows are getting out of hand.  Will the 20-somethings of today swap stories in five years about how they answered a casting call for a reality show back in the early 00's?  And then I thought - Ooooooooo film editing, Ooooooooo screenplay-editing, Ooooooooo audio mixing, Oooooooooo script screening... and I knew I had to put together a little letter to sent off.  And for your entertainment, here was my attempt:  ***  You’re very busy, I know, so let me make this quick:  You:    Reality show Executive/Casting Agent looking for someone to pull up ratings, by either capturing the audience’s heart or evoking their hate.  Looking for someone like me: memorable, charismatic, alluring, confident yet vulnerable, passionate, and hungry  Me:    The stuff of happy endings, good girl with bite  Aspiring screenwriter  Fun to watch and willing to put her heart into any behind-the-scenes entertainment industry internship you put her way (writing, production, editing, distribution, PR…)   Traits I posses that are interesting to us both:    Creativity  Full engagement in everything I undertake  Healthy self-confidence combined with just enough self-doubt to be endearing  A great smile  Mellifluous laugh  Good vocabulary  Talent to make others laugh  Voracious appetite for all entertainment and media (from indie to chart-toppers)  Ability to deal with stress  Can play hard and clean up nice   The hit-list of most interesting tid-bits:    Just spent 4 years in the former East German Republic as a Process Engineer in an IT company. I taught German Engineers, known for their Teutonic precision, about processes. As a young woman with a BA in English, I did this thanks to charisma, charm, determination, and the ability to render the mundane entertaining.  A dual citizen of the US and France (have lived in the US, Germany, France, the UK)  Speak English, French and German  Wrote a play that was staged in Studio I at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill in 2000.  Wore only skirts my entire eight years of high school and college  Moved to Germany the month after college and successfully survived the IT crash  Not afraid of boys (neither in sweats, suits, or the leather chairs behind an executive desk)   Why me? Because once you meet me, you’ll want to see more. And so will your viewers. And you want your viewers to come back for more.  Because I am consistently infuriated at how reality show participants waste the opportunities handed to them.  Because my heart beats a little bit faster at my favorite sounds: The Paramount Pictures movie intro, The 20th Century Fox music intro, the MGM lion’s roar.  Let me be the reality show participant who takes the chance and runs with it.  Weren’t you entertained? Want more? Meet me, meet me, meet me.  ***    I'll let you know what they say  Please send me any job leads you have... and save me from reality show banality ;-)   
     

    
</post>


<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       First Off , on the subject of magazines. When  urlLink Maxim  rolled around some five years ago, they were pretty cool.  After the 90s, they had a very refreshing attitude: Guys are guys--the straight ones generally like beer and sex and girls, and (here's the important part),  there is nothing wrong with that .  Very unsophisticated, but brutally honest and entertainingly written.    But that was then, and this is now.  I just tore 4 damn scratch-and-sniff ads out of this month's issue, which was additionally packed with ads and in-copy placements for hair product, clothes, and accessories.  Don't get me wrong--I don't care about ads or product placement, I just don't need to be told how ugly I (apparently) am each month.  It's no longer Cosmo's Evil Twin, it's now Cosmo's co-conspirator;  I expect a quiz next month on my feelings about my relationship with my cat.  The whole magazine has become a metrosexual shill and will  not  be getting renewed.   Next :  urlLink The Bourne Identity  is a great movie.  It has all those cool elements that I've wanted to see in a movie for a long time.  Black Ops guy takes on the entire CIA, we get to hear office leadership guys say things like, "He's alive? That's impossible!" and "Activate them all...I want him in a body bag by sunset," Nice resolution, very satisfying.  Not particularly intellectually challenging, but very satisfying.    And Finally,  (speaking of The Bourne Identity) I was reminded of the excellent young German actress,  urlLink Franka Potente .  I saw her first in  urlLink Lola rennt , and then in  urlLink Anatomie , and now in the Bourne Identity.  There is, of course, a documented weakness on my part for cute (pixie-esque) women who can speak German.  But I think she's a good actress independent of my bias.   Many folks find the German language to be "scary" or "angry".  I'd say they've watched  urlLink Raiders of the Lost Ark  too many times--as far as I know, Germans don't actually run about shouting, "SCHNELL, SCHNELL!!" every chance they get.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just finished reading this  urlLink article / interview  with J. Allard, head of the Microsoft XBOX group.  First off, I want to give him credit for a terribly clever plan.  He demonstrates once again that Microsoft's strong point isn't software but strategy.  While I am not certain his plan will be successful, for reasons I go through below, I do respect the vision of his plan.  Mr. Allard, from one evil genius to another, I salute you.  Anyway, enough with that, let's get down to brass tacks.  J. makes the argument that the gaming industry will eventually reach a common format for games, like DVD or VHS for watching home movies.  I won't pretend that you don't already know who would control this super-format.   Now I remain unconvinced that any other console manufacturer would support  urlLink XNA  (Microsoft's proposed format), given that a) Microsoft makes its own line of consoles, and b) Microsoft has a reputation for employing what might be called  dirty pool  to crush competition.  But there's another reason for Sony and Nintendo to resist such a move. It's the same reason why smaller console manufacturers might find it appealing, but should resist it, too.  And that reason is the question of  urlLink Fungibility .   If there were a common console gaming standard to drop from the sky and be implemented by everyone tomorrow, the market would become instantly commoditized, and margins would drop to the razor-thin levels seen in consumer PCs.  Only the largest players, or those with deep enough pockets, would be able to afford the economies of scale required to compete.  You would see Nintendo get marginalized and perhaps surviving ala Sega (a console manufacturer turned games-only).    Which would leave Microsoft and Sony...but wait, there's more!  Once a common platform exists, the barriers to entry drop away.  Folks like HP/Compaq and Dell can turn their lean, mean, PC manufacturing engines to producing consoles. So can Samsung, et al, up on the Korean Peninsula.  Sony builds some loverly TVs, but who's going to care what their console looks like, as long as they can play the same games on it?   If this common standard is adopted everywhere, all consoles will be equal.  Except (if this standard is controlled by one company) some consoles may end up  more equal than others .  Maybe Microsoft and/or its partners somehow manage to  magically  build faster, better, smoother-running consoles.  These better-running consoles would sell with the same thin margins, just in larger quantities.   Meanwhile, back at the ranch, once there's substantial market penetration of this new standard, Microsoft can start making money by charging developers more for the tools.   Allard makes a lot of statements about flexibility across a diverse array of devices, but what he means is flexibility across a diverse array of Microsoft-powered devices, much like Microsoft's consulting arm considers "WindowsXP, Windows2000, and Windows98," to be a "heterogeneous environment".    I'm guessing that this whole idea grew out of J. Allard kickin' it old school with the big B. Gates.  They were playing a little Halo 2 and then Notorious BG says, "j0, J--it would be 5up4-1337 if w3 0wn3d gaming like w3 0wn PCs,"  Innovative new software, or old school  urlLink guile  and  urlLink http://www.yourdictionary.com/ahd/c/c0285400.html">chicanery ? You decide.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Apple has succeeded in building, with OS X, a great OS.  I made fun of Apple for years, enjoyed crashing macs with the ol' ping 'o' death, and generally maligned them. I would spit and curse if I had to use one.  Intuitive and easy to use, my ass! Maybe originally, but not then, and certainly not from my perspective.   Then came OS X along with a bevy of hardware icons--Ti Powerbooks, the Cube, the redesigned iBook, the redesigned iMac...Apple was becoming the closest thing yet to  urlLink SandBenders .    So when it came time to buy a laptop and set an IT direction for the firm, I said, "Let's use Apples," and we did.  Which hopefully explains why I am writing this on a  urlLink Powerbook .  For the most part, I love it.  I am ecstatic with the switch from WindowsXP.    So now, I've got this great machine and I'm happy with it, except some cracks are starting to appear.  No, not actual physical cracks, but reading about Apple,  I start to wonder about some things.  Dell's consumer sales account for only 17% of their revenue, whereas Apple's consumer sales probably count for a much larger percentage (not many companies are buying iPods for their employees, now are they?).  The enterprise, the MBAs will tell you, is where you can make your money.    Eventually ideas percolate upward through my brainpan.   Now, my goal is to stay balanced, stay reasonable, I don't want to be one of those crazy "APPLE NEEDS TO MAEK A 2BUTON MOSE AN SELK OSX FOR X86" guys.  So, I actively seek an informed opinion.  Regular visits are paid to the Apple news sites, and to a few blogs like  urlLink drunkenblog  and  urlLink a few screws left over .  Above all, I try to think critically about the situation.  And now there are a few things that need to be said.   Next time:  Silence and Security   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was about to write something regarding Grrls in Skirts, when I realized that I really didn't have a solid definition handy for you regarding Grrls. So come with me now as we check a few online sources on the subject:    urlLink Wikipedia  references a genre of hardcore punk,  urlLink Everything2  associates it with individualistic women, and the requisite googling turns up  urlLink grrl.com .   Of the three, I'll recommend  urlLink grrl.com  the most. While I have never come across  urlLink Ms. Bonnie Burton  before, but she is certainly an intriguing and accomplished, ahem,  'content developer' (which sounds like she escaped the dotcom crash).  She also pulls off looking like  urlLink Bettie Page , which is definitely  something .    Go check out the story of  urlLink Cape Boy  in the dating section.  I could be wrong, but I think she's saying that guys in capes are hot, hot, hot. So all you other guys run right out and pick as many capes as you can find, and start wearing them at ALL TIMES.  This will cause the ladies to start flocking immediately.  I'll grab my own just as soon as I finish this thing with the stuff for that other thing.   I promise.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I know, those are the four most hated words in the American vernacular.  But don't worry, I'm not breaking up with you, America.  I love my country as always.  Our relationship is just going through a rough time right now, what with all the problems and international opinion turning against us, etc.  So please don't tell me that you didn't see this coming, because it's been out there for a long time.  I kept hoping that you would realize on your own and for yourself, but since you're so darn stubborn, I'm going to have to confront you with some tough love. You see, America, you have a real functional deficiency...You can't drive.  To be fair, I'm not talking about all Americans, just a significant percentage. There are probably more people can't drive than voted in the last election.  And I'm not talking about simply people who drive too slow or carry out other annoying but basically benign habits.  I'm talking about staying between the lines, about not changing lanes in the middle of an intersection, about going with the flow of traffic in a parking lot.  I'm talking about being able to parallel park and not tailgating people just because they piss you off.    What's that you say? You don't have a problem? You're a safe driver?  Denial is the first stage, America.  I would say that only when you can admit you have a problem can the healing begin, but we don't really have time for that any more...The situation has escalated.  You are a danger to yourself and others, and you need an intervention.  Hand over the keys to your SUV, I'm calling you a cab.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You may be familiar with Newton's first law of nachos, which states that nachos are simply tostitos covered with tasty things.  Similarly, Einstein's theory of TexMex states that a taco is a tostito wrapped around tasty things.   Since then other researchers have built on Einstein's work to produce the fish taco, the pizza taco, and the sub-atomic lepton-based taco.  I, however, was among the first to theorize the possibility of a Tostito-Taco, wherein a tostito is wrapped around a tostito, creating an infinite loop of taco/tostito duality.    Following upon that revelation, I am moving forward today with presenting my most stunning and controversial theory to date: The Grand Unified Nacho-Taco theory.  It proves mathematically that a tostito which has been wrapped around itself not only has a single expansive "side" (much like a Klein Bottle), but also that that side can be partially coated in tasty things.  The resultant construct would be simultaneously a tostito, a nacho, and a taco.   Members of the Nobel Committee can reach me at my lab as usual.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Because a certain individual asked nicely, let's talk about skirts for a second.   A skirt is, perhaps, the simplest item of clothing--a piece of cloth wrapped around the body.  Any piece of fabric, (sufficiently large or small, depending on one's goal) can be made into a skirt.  In modern western culture, the standard is that while men wear pants, women wear skirts or pants, drag queens dress like Bette Midler, and crazy Scotsmen (who wear kilts) threaten death and/or dismemberment to anyone who calls their kilt a skirt.   Yet, in spite of its simplicity, there is an unmatched appeal to a woman in a skirt.  As an illustration, I present a piece of dialog from  urlLink Firefly .  It occurs between a gun-slinging, ass-kicking wife and her husband:   Wife: [That dress has] too much foofarah.  If I were going to wear a dress, I'd want something with some  slink .  Husband: You want a slinky dress? I can buy you a slinky dress--Captain, can I have some money for a slinky dress?!   I think you see my point.    ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Life is an Elective  Today a friend of mine sent me a link to the graduation speech that Jon Stewart made at William and Mary. There's a lot of silly stuff in there, of course, but something he said struck me as very true. I'll quote it:  "So how do you know what is the right path to choose to get the result that you desire? And the honest answer is this. You won’t. And accepting that greatly eases the anxiety of your life experience.   When I left William and Mary I was shell-shocked. Because when you’re in college it’s very clear what you have to do to succeed. And I imagine here everybody knows exactly the number of credits they needed to graduate, where they had to buckle down, which introductory psychology class would pad out the schedule. You knew what you had to do to get to this college and to graduate from it. But the unfortunate, yet truly exciting thing about your life, is that there is no core curriculum. The entire place is an elective. The paths are infinite and the results uncertain. And it can be maddening to those that go here, especially here, because your strength has always been achievement. So if there’s any real advice I can give you it’s this.   College is something you complete. Life is something you experience. So don’t worry about your grade, or the results or success. Success is defined in myriad ways, and you will find it, and people will no longer be grading you, but it will come from your own internal sense of decency which I imagine, after going through the program here, is quite strong…although I’m sure downloading illegal files…but, nah, that’s a different story.   Love what you do. Get good at it. Competence is a rare commodity in this day and age. And let the chips fall where they may."  Indeed. It's like one big huge elective. I am currently taking German ;-)  If you are interested in the  urlLink whole speech .   So, danger boy, what is your current elective?  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Evil is such a strong word.  I think I'm more "live" than "evil" - can I be the "us live genies" part of the blog?  It uses the same letters as "evil geniuses" ;-)   I'd like to hear what dangerboy has to say about those grrls in skirts.   Or anyone else for that matter.....
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As you are aware, People generally need 2000-2500 calories a day if they're not training or dieting. To gain fat, you simply eat more calories than your body burns. Your body obligingly stores some of the extra calories as fat, and you can be considered overweight.   By now, you may be saying, "Dangerboy, I'm a go-getter.  Why would I settle for 'overweight' when I can go for 'MORBIDLY OBESE'?  Overweight and obese both sound pretty limp until you throw the word MORBID in there, then it starts to sound like an action or superspy movie.  You know, like, 'This summer...Wesley Snipes  is   MORBIDLY OBESE ,'.  What's the fastest way for me to be like that?"  About 'Morbid'; you keep using that word--I do not think it means what you think it means.   Anyway, how can you become morbidly obese on a shortened timeline?  I would point you towards Taco Hell, McDonald's, et. al., but then you'd have to leave the house and burn precious calories.  Luckily, there is another way that will require short trips to the grocery store only on occasion:  urlLink The Hungry Man All-Day Breakfast .    1000 calories of fat-filled glory: three pancakes, three sausage, a pound of eggs, two hashbrown sticks, and an indistinguishable amount of bacon. Throw some syrup on top for good measure, a tall glass of OJ at the side, and I bet you can get this sucker to 1500 calories.  One-third of these calories will be from fat.  Eating Just one of these per day would help, but I went ahead and checked with Hungry Man and they won't mind if you eat two or three a day if, you know,   necessary .    Just keep an eye on your sodium intake--these each have 2000mg, and you shouldn't have more than 2400 a day or you'll, um,   increase your risk of heart disease .   Vaya con Dios,  ~db  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok, maybe i'm about ten years too late to make this observation, but the BBC version of Pride and Prejudice, with Colin Firth as Mr. Darcy, is fuckin' awesome.  The romance in that series melted out of the tv set like a grilled cheese sandwich with an extra kraft single in it.  Even though i know the story really well, there was tension and, even though it was a pre-Victorian English story, there was palpable passion.  loved it.  even though i hated the book when it was required reading.  i went shoe-ing this afternoon, but shoe-shopping sucks so bad.  i hate how stores don't have the models i want in the colors that i want and in the size i need.  what is your problem shoe stores in boston?  how come you suck hardcore?  i think i really miss buying shoes with my dad, though.  my dad used to sell shoes in the family department store in a tiny town in NC.  he has a surprising number of shoes for a guy.  and he knows his shit and doesn't tolerate crap.  if he was only willing to spend upscale money on shoes, he'd be the perfect shoe buying partner.  so, instead of getting shoes, i got a bunch of shirts and some shorts to fill out my meagre (using the english spelling here because i'm still under the influence of Lizzy Bennett) summer wardrobe.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      and now i can't get the spanish translation out of my head - aire condicionado.  I just like the way the middle syllables lilt off my mental tongue.  i like another spanish word a lot - bodega.  i think all little neighborhood stores should be called bodegas.  that's what they call them in new york city, it doesn't matter what the nationality of the owner is, korean, pakistani, they all operate bodegas.  in cincinnati, they're called pony kegs.  in cambridge, they call them spas.  my AC unit is sweet.  all the windows in my building go from the ceiling to the floor.  There are none that have window ledges.  So traditional window AC units won't fit.  that means we're SOL unless we buy the super-expensive european models, the ones with long, inefficient exhaust tubes that sit in the middle of the room rather than on a window ledge.  this one cost $800.  originally.  but this one has been handed down through the ages, from student to student for maybe 6 years.  i got it for a song, or $100.  really, i just paid her the money.  i've got it on dehumidify mode right now.  my room feels pleasant and climate-controlled.  i love it.  while i'm on the subject of european appliances, my grandmother's old flat in beaconsfield had a clothes washing machine that switched to drying the clothes once the cycle was over.  it was in the extremely efficient (and by that i mean everything there was small and cheap) kitchen, next to the dish washer.  my experiences with this clothes washer/dryer were not very successful.  i believe i had to hang my clothes up throughout the apartment.  i shouldn't denigrate european appliances, it may have been user error.  but if we can't come to a meeting of the minds over how to wash clothes with a machine, how can we bridge the yawning gulf between our two cultures and disparate polities?  from air conditioning to geopolitics... how do you like that?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have done quite a bit of cleaning over the past couple days.  I washed all my clothes.  I emptied a box of articles and placed them in a filing cabinet, almost a year after I moved, which freed up a whole, huge shelf in my closet for me to fill with crap that is either on my floor or packed in other boxes.  I have done a ton of dishes, some of which were dirtied by me.  I took a ton of empty beer bottles out to the recycling bins.  I emptied all the trash cans and took them to the dumpster.  I'm going to stay up late tonight and count my clothes so I can figure out what I need to buy so that I have a full summer wardrobe that doesn't look like it has been worn by a slovenly college student for the last 8 or 9 summers.  What has been the purpose of this blog entry up to now?  There is none.  From now on, I'm going to start talking about The Cure.  Just a fantastic band.  Their two greatest hits albums have been in heavy rotation in my cd player all week.  I'm trying to decide which song is my favorite right now, and I don't think I can.  I love Just Like Heaven.  And Fascination Street.  But then I also love In Between Days.  And then there are all the poppy songs that are all nearly perfect, like Killing an Arab, Boys Don't Cry, Lovesong, and Friday I'm in Love.  What I want to know is why people don't talk about The Cure as one of the greatest groups of the 1980s and early 1990s, along with U2 and REM?  Can I think of anything ridiculous to say to make the reader laugh?  Apple butter.  It's tasty.  If you haven't had any before, get yourself to a place with Amish people and purchase some from a little Amish bodega.  It may be one of my favorite things to put on toast.  (other good toast toppings include strawberry preserves and marmalade).  Oh! how lovely!  I just got an email from Rachel.  I'll give up on this entry for now.  This is more rambling than I would have liked, and it's not on a single topic, but that's how I roll.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      They are, perhaps, my favorite food.  Yes, I think I have decided.  If I were ever to receive the death penalty, my last meal would be this:  1 tall glass of crystal clear ice water.  One bowl of fresh, washed raspberries with natural whipped cream.  One piping hot bowl of Campbell's condensed tomato soup, mixed with 2% milk.  1 large, greasy grilled cheese sandwich.  1 box of Cheezits.  1 box of unsweeted Mini-wheats.  The final three menu items are to be dipped into the Campbell's soup.  After having written such a strange and morbid first entry into this exercise in group procrastination, I feel as though I can only maintain my present level of non sequitude.  And so that brings me to masturbation.  I was watching my dvd of the first season of Curb Your Enthusiasm, and at one point, Larry David jokes "I've never come so close to death as when I masturbated with a 104 degree temperature."  This routine made me laugh hysterically.  And I'm sure it's because it touched (no pun intended) upon an aspect of the universal human experience with masturbation that, perhaps, had never once been uttered out loud before that moment (captured on video) - the fact that when you're sick and laid up in bed, sometimes you have nothing better to do.  I'm sure it has at least occured to everyone who has ever been sick (and I phrase it this way because I believe it is more likely that there are people out there who have never been sick than people who have never contemplated masturbation)... but Larry David was the first man who was willing to share this thought with others... this willingness to speak the unspeakable is the source of his brilliance.  I don't know if I have much to say about women in skirts.  But I do have a weakness for women in cool glasses.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Lou Reed and the Velvet Underground entered into my limited purview for the first time during my freshman year in college--which counts as a long time ago for me.  I heard 'Perfect Day' in the soundtrack to  Trainspotting .    But this blog entry isn't about  Perfect Day , it's about one of my absolute favorite romantic songs (makes me think of freshman year for a different reason),  Pale Blue Eyes .  There is, of course, the refrain:   Linger on, your pale blue eyes Linger on, your pale blue eyes   More importantly, let me share the opening verse:   Sometimes I feel so happy, Sometimes I feel so sad,  Sometimes I feel so happy, But mostly you just make me mad...  Baby, you just make me mad.   Doesn't remind you of romance? Are you sure you've been in love?  You might take issue with "mostly", but you have to admit that the people who get deepest under your skin are also the ones you can't walk away from.  There's probably a true story behind this song, but I don't want to know;  I'd rather have my own feelings about verses like:   Thought of you as my mountaintop Thought of you as my peak Thought of you as everything I've had but couldn't keep... I've had but couldn't keep.    This song makes me pause, reminds me of success and failure in love, of both the beautiful and the awful times.  Like Pulp's F.E.E.L.I.N.G.C.A.L.L.E.D.L.O.V.E., it presents a conflict of emotion.  But where the Pulp song is about helplessly falling, Lou Reed is singing about the memories at the end.  Maybe there's a future for the couple in Pale Blue Eyes, but I've never thought so.    By the way, in case you missed it, the refrain is not about the color of his lover's eyes.  ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Remember Married With Children?    Love and Marriage,  Love and Marriage, Go together like a horse and carriage...   All about a dysfunctional family in Suburbia, USA.  A husband and wife who hate each other but remain Married...With Children.  I recall the theme song better than the significant plot points, so please forgive my immediate segue, I want to write, instead, about Working...With Children.  This is not 'working with children' as in daycare, this is "with children" in the sense that here I am, working, and over there, quite nearby, there is a child.  Ever try that? It's difficult, I assure you.  Should you ever have the opportunity, you may gain a new respect for those who brought you up--I certainly have.   Numerous studies have shown that spending time with pets lowers a person's stress level.  I can vouch for this--picking up my cat (you did know that I live with a maniacal maine coon, right?) lowers my stress level.  One particular study (that I am not willing to find the link for right now) compared the stress level in adults attempting complex arithmetic problems.  Those working nearby their pets experienced lower stress levels than normal.  Those working near their children experienced higher stress levels than normal.    Why is working around children stressful? Let's compare it with working near standard office furniture. While you're feverishly pounding away at your laptop, what are the children doing?  1. Screaming. 2. Sensing your affection for them and launching a plan to off themselves by climbing rickety man-high pile of sharp and pointy things.  You may perhaps believe that you'll just stop the child from destroying themselves and receive a third option.  This is the crux of their brutal,  evil genius : Try to stop them from killing themselves and you will Go Directly To The Screaming. Do not pass Go; do not collect $200.   Meanwhile (back at the ranch), What is the office furniture doing?  1. Staring at you blankly. 2. Being stolen.  For me, I like the kids, I just wish I could get a few hours of work without them.  I don't know what I would pick given an either/or option; they are such  excellent  little demons.  For you?  That's just a decision you'll have to make yourself.  What do you think--Children or Office Furniture?  Somehow I knew that you'd pick the chairs.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The recent golive of the Serenity  urlLink website  has reminded me to post my Firefly vs. CSI review.   I spent some time, a while back, catching up on TV shows via DVD...I don't watch television, as a loose rule, but I do own a PowerBook.  The two series in question are Firefly and CSI (Original Series).  Perhaps it was the influence of the wine cube, or the prolonged hour, but my expert opinion is that Firefly was some good [insert expletive here].    Comparing the two is an important juxtaposition.  They have both generated rabid fanbases, they both use an ensemble cast in a variety of combinations, and they both willingly leverage their characters' personal lives (unlike Law and Order).  But CSI (produced by Jerry Bruckheimer) is wildly successful with two spinoffs, and Firefly (produced by Joss Whedon)  died on the vine.   In Firefly, the mercenary crew faces questions of right and wrong woven in a complex tapestry; is the enemy of your enemy your friend? Are you sure? In one episode, the crew steals a cargo twice...and it's arguable that both thefts were the right thing to do. This complexity lends itself to a complex, more subtle dialogue.   CSI is far closer to home and the characters easier with which to empathize.  They also explain the various forensic principles to each other, in spite of the assumption that they are portraying (supposedly) skilled professionals.  I don't think I'm giving anything away when I point out that the explanations are actually for the audience members who flunked high school chemistry.  They even wrap up each case with the 'criminalist' confronting the criminal in a pedantic monologue straight out of Sherlock Holmes.   And yet, that may be what ultimately sunk Firefly--it's not easy.  CSI walks you through the steps to the conclusion of the whodunits of the week.  There's very objective criteria to the CSI world.  They're good and they catch the people who are bad.  Then they tell everyone how they did it.  Serenity's crew charts a murky course by comparison.   To be fair, I like CSI and I'll probably watch more of it.  But it feels like intellectual cotton candy next to Firefly.  There's also the fact that, being a mechanical engineer by training, I feel the need to [insert expletive here] Serenity's lovely mechanic like nobody's business--but that's a personal problem.   ~db  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Fear my terrible evil.  And my simian genius.  This is my first ever blog post.  Today I went shopping for cleaning supplies.  Also I ate some food.  Also I worked at my job.  After this post, I will sleep.  The end.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if today had a theme, it would be 'naming names.'  because of a couple things i've been reading lately and a few movies i've seen recently, i've been thinking about what would happen if i was put in a position where i had to choose between being able to live a normal life and going to prison and/or being executed on a matter of principle - like refusing to finger someone as a spy or Communist or being unwilling, as Sir Thomas More was, to betray a deeply held moral precept.  how much hypocrisy would i be able to tolerate in order to save my own skin?  tonight i saw a documentary made by one of the granddaughters of the Rosenbergs.  they had apparently been given a choice by the FBI while they were on death row, name the names of these suspected Communists and we will commute your sentences to life imprisonment and your children will not be orphans.  and they died rather than implicate others.  which, viewed one way, could just have indicated how deeply held their loyalty was to the Communist Party.  but is it easier to believe that these people were so morally vacant that they preferred to serve an ideology than to be able to see their boys grow up or is it easier to believe that they were too honorable to endanger another group of innocents from the excesses of the Red Scare?  we know now that Julius Rosenberg probably was a spy for the Soviets and that he gave military secrets to the Russians, at least during World War II, though there is no evidence that they had any access to nuclear secrets and ample evidence of prosecutorial misconduct on the part of J. Edgar Hoover and Roy Cohn - and the government's star witness (Ethel's brother) recanted his testimony on 60 Minutes several years ago.  This is a really interesting moral dilemma to me.  personal values against the state.  Is there any more modern conflict?  when marlon brando named names to help the police break up the dockworkers syndicate in on the waterfront, elia kazan wants us to think this is a heroic act - and in a way, it is.  whenever you stand up against coercion, it's heroic, sure... and the syndicate was criminal.  kazan named names to HUAC.  simply participating in an organization is not criminal and he did not provide evidence of criminal activity, like that of hiss or the rosenbergs, and he did it with full knowledge that the reputations (at least) of the people whose names were named would be harmed.  that's certainly an awful thing to do.  was it heroic to stand up against the hollywood omerta and break silence to assist the government?  no way, not unless the Reds in hollywood were actually materially assisting the Communists in any of their crimes against the United States or humanity.  I mean, if Kazan had said "dalton trumbo helped stalin kill millions" and that was true and the hollywood omerta was keeping that secret, then he would be a truly brave man.  but that just wasn't the case.  i've been rambling in this entry, but i just wanted to write down some stuff that i think is interesting and i don't know what i think about it yet.  maybe i'll figure it out later, or with the help of anyone who decides to comment on this.  by the way, today was the anniversary of the murder of James Chaney, Andrew Goodman and Michael Schwerner.  RIP.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A few years ago, Margo and I sat down on a drainage pipe on a beach in South Carolina and argued about state's rights (within the context of the US constitution).  LIke many ideological arguments, we didn't really convince each other as much as we provoked thoughts.    Which is my goal, today, in linking to Lawrence Lessig's latest book,  urlLink Free Culture .  Lessig is one of the leaders on the side of loosing controls; the side which opposes the those fighitng to strengthen the rights of producers and creators (the MPAA and RIAA, among others).  Lessig has argued before the Supreme Court of the United States in his quest to relax copyright controls.  Regardless of whether your adore or revile him, you should read Lessig's book and try to understand him.    Lessig's book catalogs the history of copyright within the system of English law upon which United States law is built.  Along the way, we encounter striking anecdotes from English and American History, and we learn that the United States is built upon a pirate heritage which protects those who 'borrow'.  Whatever side you come down on, whether you agree or disagree with Lessig, the book is telling in its history.  And, in keeping with his beliefs, the book is available (through the link above) online for free.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       No one played so far, so I'll continue my installment with...  Top 5 daily private moments :  5) That first sip of coffee  4) The smell of my own perfume (very light)&nbsp;as I am working in front of my computer.  3) Music, music - any music. (Even if it&nbsp;is overhearing someone humming to themselves in the elevator)  2) The rustle of thick cool sheets when slipping into them at night.  1) Dreaming, dreaming, dreaming - uninhibited, in full color, with a score in stereo. Someone else come up with a top 5 list.    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      With "High Fidelity", Nick Hornby emblazoned a few words in my mind: "top five __".    Top five fill in the blank.    A wonderful pastime between friends.  This morning, as I was humming the tune of a song before I even knew what I was doing, I thought: "Kristine - top five most defining pieces of media that have come through your life".  But before we hit that topic.  Let us do a different top 5 list.  Top five silences:  5) The silence inside a car right after you shut the door on a summer night - the cicadas and crickets strumming in the dew outside.  4) The silence due to the lag time on a very long distance telephone call: "hello?"  ...... "hello!"  3) On one of your favorite CDs, the silence before the best track starts.  When the previous track has ended and your body has premonitions of the chords about to strike.    2) That electric silence before a first kiss.  I wish, I wish, I wish..... spark.* splash - Oh no! hmmmmmmmmm  1) This one:    "Tell me something nice"    *silence*    "Is there so little about me you like?"    "No. So much"  Anyone care to play?  Come up with your own top 5 list?  I've got several others in store.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am of the humble opinion that it is the smile that makes the mate, whoever you are.  There are, of course, those who prefer legs, breasts, asses, arms, shoulders, etc.  But for long-term value (in the appearance department) and return on investment, my money is on the smile.   Think about it this way--your smile is a facial gestalt, involving hundreds of muscles as well as your eyes.  As we age, we wrinkle our faces in the same way over and over (this creates crows feet from laughing, forehead creases from worry).  Our eyes never really age.  Your smile, excepting for injury or surgery, is timeless.    And the smile is what we hope to evoke in our lovers.  To love, it has been said, is to choose someone else's happiness above our own.  I don't know about such a complete subjugation of character, but I do know that loving relationships are rewarding and not just on occasion or on the average.   If things are going well, you'll see that smile a lot.  Even as our bodies fade with time, you'll see that smile.  In photographs, in memories, in person, you'll see it over and over.    I guess I'm just not a day-trader.   ~db
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I am planning on moving to the US in October... and am looking for an interesting job... and scan Craigs List every now and then for jobs in cities in which I would like to land.  This is how I came across the announcement for the reality show casting call." A&E Cable Network Reality Show Casting Now... A&amp;E Cable Network is looking for people who have always wanted to work in the entertainment industry but have never had the means to do so. If you think you have what it takes and are at least 21 years old then contact us immediately....Only a select few will be chosen to come out to Hollywood to work as an intern at some of the most sought after internships in the industry. Our camera crews will be following you beginning to end as you discover exactly what it takes to make it to the top. Make sure to email us a recent picture as well as a brief bio about yourself and why we should choose you. While on your journey, all expenses will be paid. "  blah blah blah you know the rest.  And I got to thinking - how silly, how funny.  These reality shows are getting out of hand.  Will the 20-somethings of today swap stories in five years about how they answered a casting call for a reality show back in the early 00's?  And then I thought - Ooooooooo film editing, Ooooooooo screenplay-editing, Ooooooooo audio mixing, Oooooooooo script screening... and I knew I had to put together a little letter to sent off.  And for your entertainment, here was my attempt:  ***  You’re very busy, I know, so let me make this quick:  You:    Reality show Executive/Casting Agent looking for someone to pull up ratings, by either capturing the audience’s heart or evoking their hate.  Looking for someone like me: memorable, charismatic, alluring, confident yet vulnerable, passionate, and hungry  Me:    The stuff of happy endings, good girl with bite  Aspiring screenwriter  Fun to watch and willing to put her heart into any behind-the-scenes entertainment industry internship you put her way (writing, production, editing, distribution, PR…)   Traits I posses that are interesting to us both:    Creativity  Full engagement in everything I undertake  Healthy self-confidence combined with just enough self-doubt to be endearing  A great smile  Mellifluous laugh  Good vocabulary  Talent to make others laugh  Voracious appetite for all entertainment and media (from indie to chart-toppers)  Ability to deal with stress  Can play hard and clean up nice   The hit-list of most interesting tid-bits:    Just spent 4 years in the former East German Republic as a Process Engineer in an IT company. I taught German Engineers, known for their Teutonic precision, about processes. As a young woman with a BA in English, I did this thanks to charisma, charm, determination, and the ability to render the mundane entertaining.  A dual citizen of the US and France (have lived in the US, Germany, France, the UK)  Speak English, French and German  Wrote a play that was staged in Studio I at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill in 2000.  Wore only skirts my entire eight years of high school and college  Moved to Germany the month after college and successfully survived the IT crash  Not afraid of boys (neither in sweats, suits, or the leather chairs behind an executive desk)   Why me? Because once you meet me, you’ll want to see more. And so will your viewers. And you want your viewers to come back for more.  Because I am consistently infuriated at how reality show participants waste the opportunities handed to them.  Because my heart beats a little bit faster at my favorite sounds: The Paramount Pictures movie intro, The 20th Century Fox music intro, the MGM lion’s roar.  Let me be the reality show participant who takes the chance and runs with it.  Weren’t you entertained? Want more? Meet me, meet me, meet me.  ***    I'll let you know what they say  Please send me any job leads you have... and save me from reality show banality ;-)   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>