<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember when we were little people and life was simple. Our bodies were young and new, imaginations were fleeting, big decisions were made by our peers, our drawings were primal and love was simple. We chased the boys we liked and when they chased us we would run and holler...in secret sheer joy. We were praised for our lopsided coil pots and cheered on as we attempted to capture the well guarded flag. Birthdays were celebrated by all, sleepovers were spent and play dates included digging for bugs, building forts, running around barefooted in the grass waving sticks in the air and on the rainy days, classic Nintendo games.   As time eventually passed, we became curious.   I remember one day clear as rain. I was in the eighth grade and I was waiting for my mom to pick me up from a sleep over. I was wearing an oversized tee shirt and knee length Umbros, one leg was pink and the other was blue. As I sat down on the sticky leather seats, she told me that I needed to start dressing like a girl. That day she bought me a "My First Bra," which basically consisted of two pieces of triangular cotton and a strap. I don't know what it was supposed to be supporting. But I can understand, she wanted to buy pretty dresses and sparkly stretch pants, not Haines boys tees and Levis.   Today, I can proclaim, self assured, that I am a shop-o-holic. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First and foremost, I admit. I have been lured by Manhattan's pre-war architecture, my dear Sullivan Street and timeless fashion modes. I am guilty of neglecting the L train and bypassing great Brooklyn parties to attend pretentious chic Manhattan gatherings. So, it only happened once, and I felt so uncomfortable, we ended up spending a much enjoyed evening in Fort Greene.  So I guess it is my time to come out of the closet and admit to the world that I will be a Jersey City girl in less than a month. It is perhaps, my worst nightmare...coming true right before my eyes. I remember all you Syracuse girls shunning me for not joining your sorority. I remember.   My point is that, Brooklyn, Jersey, Manhattan, Queens...we are not that far away from each other. We act as if Brooklyn is another state and when I mention Jersey City people give me hugs wishing me best, sending me off as if I am moving to Egypt.   I feel compelled to lure you with our future ping pong table, front porch, enormous living space, grilling area, two bedrooms and two enormous living rooms to lounge in, but I'm going to restrain myself and know that you will come visit because of our true relationship.   My heart sinks when I think about leaving my beautiful street. I will miss the laundry folks, the Tibetan shop man who I swap basketball tips with, my homeless man, Christopher, the Mudhoney salon folks who give me crazy mullets and orange bangs, my horribly organized video store, my neighbor who spins at parties for Kate Moss, the old lady who's garbage I take out for her, the bodega crew and the lovely ladies at The Flying A who greatly contribute to my fashionable wardrobe.   So, my hats are off to you. Thank you for such a great time on Sullivan Street.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since sophmore year of college I have dreamed of moving to California. Every time I visit my heart slows down and I begin to feel the love again. The raw earth under my bare feet, the exploding sun tanning my body and the cool evenings.  I would live close enough so I could smell the ocean and my income would come from my art and jewelry. What more could a girl like me ask for?   But I am slightly, well very worried about my move out west because I am afraid that NYC has scarred me for life. My patience has slowly diminished, my smiles are smartly rationed out, my trust for people and things has slowly been wrung dry, and I fear that I am just not California material now.  I've been caught in the middle of a fight between high school kids beating up an old Korean man who worked in the local market when I lived in Brooklyn. I've encountered vomit on every street and subway I have walked and ridden. (I have emetophobia...http://www.emetophobia.org/default.asp) I've had almost every virus known to man.  And the bugs here...cockroaches and those centipede things...they are super human...you couldn't kill a roach if you smashed him with a 40 ton hammer.  Not even my Dr. Scholls wooden clogs could kill them. The one success story I can tell was when I was working in a printmaking studio. We injured one, taped it to the floor and poured varnish and oil based ink all over it.  That was a victorious day for many people. So anyways, I am not trying to discredit NYC, millions of people love it and millions visit every day. But I feel trapped in the middle of my nightmare sometimes. Like the nightmares I had as a kid where it would always be someone chasing me, trying to give me a shot, and I could only run in slow motion.  So has NYC scarred me and prevented me from becoming the west coast girl I have always been at heart? I don't believe it has. Our souls don't change.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://cicadaville.com/ - these are cicadas gone wrong. all wrong.  So, Christopher, the homeless man who I give change to every morning admitted to me that he spent the money I gave him on booze. He promised to me that he would get on the wagon and sober up. So, I've been offering to buy him juice or water, but he'd rather have the change. It's understandable, he may need new socks or cigarettes, but I just hope he doesn't fall back off the dreaded wagon again. When I was at the 2000 New Year's Phish show in Florida, people brought this boat that they hauled around behind their truck. They drove all around the parking lots and camp grounds picking up party people. It was classic. We'd be hanging out round our hibachi, which later got stolen by hibachi thieves, and we'd hear the party boat coming up, people yelling, "Get on the party boat!." By the early morning, people where hanging over the sides half sea sick and hung over, but the spirit was still there. The party boat lives on. Anyways, the point of my story is that, it shouldn't be just getting back on the wagon...but rather getting on the party boat. Even if it is the sober party boat, it will still be a great ride.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My days as a Dead head hippie are long gone, as well as my days as a free loving artist. Have I really become the hypochondriac, germaphobic bubble girl blogger? 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Adam and I worked on a new song I wrote last night,   urlLink "Bloatation   urlLink Device."    It's got a great punchy punky  edge to it which Adam amplifies as he busts in with his power cords. Sweet stuff, sweeeet stuff. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was my very first performance at an open mic night in nyc. To start at the very beginning, I am walking down Prince street at 6pm. One and a half hours before I draw a random number at the Sidewalk. As I nervously tiptoe down the busy street, the straps on my guitar case are digging into my neck leaving unattractive hickey-like marks. What could possibly calm my nerves, I look down at my shaking hands and realize that it is nearly impossible to play the guitar with such lengthy, tattered nails, I must get a manicure. I walk by the sparkling store front on Sullivan street and decide to treat myself to this tiny morsel of relaxation. It's a basic haven for those looking to avoid the real world for that much longer. Procrastination. Everyone is curious about my guitar and by the end of my second coat of peach colored polish they have misunderstood and thought I was playing my own "concert" in about 45 minutes. Everyone rushes to shoo me out and congratulate me.  OK, so that wasn't too relaxing. My nerves are flying out the permanently locked subway windows and permeating through the sticky plastic seats. As I arrive, I can see Adam standing out front. I feel a temporary wave of relief as he greets me with open arms and a confirming voice. I grab a Dos Equies to calm my nerves and get in line with all the other guitars and performers. Swirling the tiny scraps of paper swimming around the deep end of the gutted mandolin, I draw number 39. (out of 60) Thirty nine. I'm shattered. I won't be playing until 2am, at best 1am. I plunge my back into the corner seat and take a large gulp of beer. 39.  As the first performer begins to set up the stage I hear the mc calling my name over the robust speakers. As I approach the booth she yells to me, "You're on third." That's it. I'm on third. 3. I grab my guitar and run downstairs to attempt to tune it but my hands are shaking too much. Ok, now I sort of feel like I am going to be sick. I hear the roars and whistles for the first performer and decide there's no time like the present to play in front of a crowded house of talented musicians. Sure, I'll be fine. Sure. I gather my shaking fingers, cringing stomach and barely tuned voice and head back to my seat before I go on. I place myself close to Adam, attempting to pillage his source of complete cool and calm through osmosis. No luck, my arms and legs are frozen. At least they stopped shaking. The Elemental Wizard is a fantastic act. This is going to be hard to follow. Damn the Elemental Wizard.  So from here on in, it's a whirlwind of setting up the mic stands, sitting awkwardly on the wooden stool, chatting with the mc about jersey city, being blinded by the spotlights not being able to see one ounce of the rustling crowd. All in all, I think I pulled it off. I even hustled myself together last minute and introduced my songs. Sidewalk rules entail each performer to two songs, so when I began, "I will be playing two songs," a flutter of giggles snuck out, but it's only natural for a first timer to experience some form of initiation.  I was elated to hear the audience laughing at my subtle jokes and a mild roar of laughter when I began my second song singing, "I still work at Scholastic..."  And I was deathly afraid they wouldn't hear my trembling voice, but apparently, Adam reassured me I was clear and strong. I managed to flub multiple times, but plowed right through the mistakes.  After my two 30 second songs, I literally ran off stage forgetting to thank my audience. The mc even told me to come back and play again.  I then scouted out some friends who had come to see me play and thanked them profusely and felt utterly guilty about not being able to call the people beforehand who were hoping to come. But there will be a next time, and perhaps a time after that.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Commuting music: Led Zeppelin, Houses of the Holy album, Rain Song, on repeat.    I have a major case of the Monday's. I wore my turquoise Tibetan frock for my performance this evening because the woman told me that turquoise brings your energy, but on the subway, I realized it's splattered with muddy water from playing barefooted basketball after Friday's rain storm. Great. But this week, starting tomorrow, Adam and I have decided the theme to be, "Let's get healthy." Maximum of two beers each night, yoga for me in the a.m. and ease up on the cigarettes. It's time to shed the winter sub-zero layer.      
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The first day I rode the bus to the Path station in Jersey City, I stood at the edge of the sidewalk and watched my bus, #80, speed right past my teetering feet. I immediately surveyed the surrounding area, looking for other frustrated and confused faces for comfort, but nothing. As it goes in Jersey City, you have to hail your own bus. None of this, stop at every 'designated' location shit.  Don't get me wrong, I'm not one to brag, but put me on any street corner in Manhattan and I can hail you a cab before you can even think of surrendering, pulling out your subway map and looking for the nearest station. Even when my parents come into town, my dad throws me a ten and tells me to work my magic.  But hailing the #80 bus is simply incomparable to any taxi. It's a colossal piece of machinery you are shepherding towards you. So, for now, I remain a bus hailing beginner. I must admit though, that on Tuesday, I botched my first chance to gain some experience. I could see the 80 creeping along the empty street as it's neon sign flashed Journal Square. I willed any being with all of my might to suddenly appear and help me flag down this slinking creature slowly edging towards me. I then continued to inch backwards towards the store fronts, pretending to root around in my bag looking for something I may have left back at the house, as it then sped up and left me breathing it's exhaust. An older woman showed up not long after I had made an embarrassment out of myself and she showed me how to work it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I snuck out to enjoy a mid-afternoon summer american spirit under the scaffolding on Crosby Street away from all the corporates. As I watch model types and business suits stroll on their lunch breaks, a guy wearing camo pants, ski boots and a winter hat comes stumbling by. I smile to myself because we've all been there. He then stops and stands on the corner of the bustling intersection and proceeds to melt as his knees give out and then buckle back up to a some what upright position.  He occasionally elbows a bystander and quickly says sorry but continues to repeatedly liquefy. It's almost as if he is virtually snowboarding down Pike's Peak, hugging the curves and feeling the earth beneath the snow of the trail. A bike messenger skids by and yells, "Wake up!" as a pre-teen hollers, "Falll!" far enough away in case he happened to wake up and start to chase her.  I smile to an older man sitting near me as he observes the show, but startles me when he says, "What a waste of life,"  then gets up and leaves. I feel mildly sad at that comment, but everyone has a right to their own opinion. As the ski bum begins to lean on a post and assume the vomit position, I decide to end my afternoon break a bit short.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Finley Quaye  kept my mind at ease on the commute this morning, so much so that he even persuaded me to surrender to a two minute snooze between Journal Square and Grove.  Though, the 9:59am arrival to my desk still remains to be the most captivating part of my day. A Jack of Spades and a green plastic devil head lay, waiting for me to show. So I showed and I am intrigued although not entirely surprised.  Jose immediately fessed up to his donation of the green devil head. The  urlLink card  however may remain a mystery. It was shuffled in between some papers, so maybe it was a fluke drop off or perhaps my desk is the hub for midnight janitorial poker games. That would be great. I haven't gambled since I was 14, when my parents took me to Las Vegas.  Considering the rap I got for playing Keno at the breakfast table, I have smartly veered from any gambling what-so-ever. Except the occasional weekend at home when my dad and I bet on Saturday horse races. And I love those scratch off tickets. Lucky 7's, Tickled Pink. It's almost guaranteed if you buy 5 you'll have at least one winner in there.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning's commuting music consisted of  urlLink Van Morrison's Astral Weeks   and the  urlLink Talking Heads . Not to mention I woke to a familiar voice this morning on NPR. Strange to hear a familiar voice vibrating through the stereo speakers. Adam tactfully amped up the volume for me to hear the commentary while I was bathroom.  But on my way to work, by the time I got to Track 6 on Astral Weeks, I had encountered an exceptional assembly of similar creatures of habit. Or are all of these instances just  coincidences that keep happening everyday?  9:00 am: The same wall street type waiting for the bus smoking a cigarette.  9:05 am: Tired individuals respectfully line up and board the bus with the gratified plastic seats in back. 9:10 am: Blind woman carries her breakfast in a brown bag and her cane in hand through the path station. She books it pretty fast though, so I hesitate to say she is fully blind, but perhaps, legally blind or maybe she just lives in the station. 9:15 am: The young couple waits for the path train. She gets off at Grove, he, World Trade. 9:30 am: I stand, waiting for the R train, posed in front of a part of the ceiling that goes up to the street to catch a slight breeze. 9:45 am: Croissant, tea, work, and then it all begins in reverse. I was even purposefully late yesterday to break the cycle, and I still ran into the same people.  I am a creature in need of constant change so tell all these other creatures to buckle up and break the cycle.      
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Next Monday I will be playing at the Sidewalk Cafe on Avenue A. My first live guitar performance. Well, I played Blackbird at my Nana's funeral, but that is all in all on another level of gigs. More so a, sending off to a better world gig.    But this night, soon come, I will be playing two Scarlet originals, "I Work at Scholastic" and its sequel, "I Still Work at Scholastic." Having worked at Scholastic (can I say Scholastic one more time?) for nearly two years, Harry Potter has managed to pussyfoot his way into my life...each and every minute of my nine hour day. So I have created two melodies about the scandalous affair between me and Harry.   I just hope my short term memory doesn't stalk me while I'm trying to remember my lyrics on stage.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One bus, the path train, one subway and three pickers.  Granted, we all have our subconscious habits while riding the subway sans book or newspaper to keep our fidgety hands at ease, but the pick...why the pick? Why do some men think that this is allowed in public? Don't eat it! EW!  First of all, you are shoving all the dirty germs on your finger up your nose. Secondly, if you've got a bat in the cave, use a Kleenex and blow, no picking please.  Pick in private. Thirdly, this will in no way increase your chances of  getting a date. In fact, it may be the last time you ever see a woman.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't mean to beat a dead horse here, but last night Adam was away, so naturally, I painted my nails, watched Sex in the City episodes and ate ice cream. But all of a sudden out of the corner of my eye I spot a roach making a b-line across the sheets to crawl under my nest of blankets. I took the remote and surprisingly executed it in one swing, well, maybe three or four, it all happened so fast I can't recall exact numbers. Guts smeared all over my sheets, I ran to the front porch calling random phone numbers. Despite the fact that it was 1am, I even called Adam's parents. I still don't know the purpose of the rapid redials and phoning, but I guess I was just yearning for someone to console me and relive the nightmare with me so I wouldn't have to go it alone.  I changed the sheets and this morning I threw them out (dramatic, yes, but I was planning on buying new ones). I also ordered a bed frame from Sleepy's. Adam asked if the frame was aesthetically pleasing. For $20, no, but it serves a superior purpose and that is to provide me with a roach free bed and a sounder sleep. We'll work on aesthetics later.  If I make it to later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I enjoyed several Red Stripes on the water in a boat with a group of genuine people. It's been a while since I've had one of those New York moments. They never fail to be excellent.  Speaking of which, I later experienced a Jersey City moment, which seemed to haunt me through all hours of the night. Roach in the bed, ROACH IN THE BED, GET IT GODDAMNIT BEFORE I LIGHT THE BED ON FIRE!   After hours of twitching I finally fell asleep, only to have a ridiculous nightmare that Paris Hilton stole my boyfriend. That Bitch. I remember waking up and cursing at Adam who was sound asleep. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why am I convinced that the egg salad sandwich I ate today is going to give me food poisoning on the first night Adam and I have planned to eat dinner together in our new apartment? I sit and count down the listless hours after lunch, in hope that my chances of becoming ill will be less likely as time passes. My safe haven of hearty health remains hidden in a remote region of bliss. When I am there, I believe I will be punished for overexcessivly frolicking, so I relish each moment in silent joy.  Having lived in New York City for two years, I have learned of many unspoken rules. Here are my top ten, mind you I can list about eight nine and then some.  1) Never hold onto the poles in the subway. For that matter, try not to touch anything. During winter season, gloves offer a solution for those who don't have the balance to surf the screeching curves. Spring and summer seasons, if you must, use a newspaper or a napkin to wrap around the pole for a buffer zone. But do keep in mind, everything that touches the pole must be disposed of or washed pronto. 2) Do not put any food in your mouth that has been sitting in a buffet style manner in any facility. Those flimsy windshields may offer a certain amount of protection, but germs can flit and scuttle around any obstacle. If you must, pick foods that are further back and untouched rather than the stuff right under everyone's noses.  Also, I'd recommend sticking to the veggies.  3) Dirty water street dogs should be eaten at your own risk.  4) Try to avoid bar fronts on Saturday and Sunday mornings. Chances are there is a good amount of vomit lurking and lingering. 5) Do not share any drinks or foods with anyone, especially around flu seasons. 6) Be sure if co-workers are using your phone and computer anytime to be sure to clean your desk, keyboard and phone to rid all foreign germs. 7) The fancier the restaurant, the more food handling occurs. How do you think they prepared that tiny artistic sculpture on your plate...with sterilized tongs and tweezers?  8) The dirtier the restaurant, guaranteed, dirty food handling.  9) Avoid going to over crowded, confined spaces (museums, gyms, subway cars, office buildings) during flu and cold seasons. 10) Wash your hands too often. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I posed as a teacher in a photo shoot with four mildly tame children. Positioned in the center of the frame, I held a bunch of grapes in one hand and an apple in the other while wearing blinding bright patriotic colors. The pictures will be used for a voting magazine issue about children in a classroom, voting on whether they'd prefer grapes or apples for their snack of the day. Imagine adults using this technique in the modern day, mocha triple fudge macchiato with chocolate shavings OR vanilla chai double latte with froth? These kids have it easy. It was a unanimous vote in favor or grapes, except Benjamin who preferred cookies all in all, but later revealed to me that he only ate oranges.  Having previously posed as a football player and a 12 year old girl with excessively hair gelled pigtails doing a gummy worm experiment, I thought the teacher role would be a cake walk, but I was dead wrong.  I was quietly enjoying my morning tea in my day glow outfit, when the photographer came over and began explaining that I would have to engage the kids attention at all times, ask them questions about grapes and apples and if needed explain all about the voting process. My interest for all of this rapidly plummeted due to the fact that I had not prepared a mini lecture on voting for four tiny people who were convinced I was an actual teacher.  I spent the majority of the time trying to make shit up, while trying to remember their names so I didn't have to unnaturally jut my chin out in their general direction when they raised their hands. I also have a most unfortunate habit of talking to the majority of children I am forced to encounter as they are new borns. I can't explain why, but I assume it is similar to those  who feel they have to shout when they are trying to communicate with people in foreign countries, as if these poor bystanders will eventually comprehend our repellent accent at elevated volumes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Three roaches and counting. We were guaranteed our home was "roach free," but I concluded after having found an infinite supply of those toxic hexagonal black traps arranged in our drawers and cabinets, that perhaps "free" actually defines the bountiful and liberated roaches gallivanting all over our new fucking floors.  Our bathroom lights haven't been installed, so, my new daily routine consists of trying to successfully create a decent lather while attempting not to splash any water on the 70 year old reading lamp propped up and hanging from a hole in the wall two feet away from the bath in fear of being electrocuted. I'd also like to mention the fact that I still have last Tuesday's conditioner loitering and oiling up my hair. Let's just say, it's as if someone were spitting at you from above. Perhaps even two people's spit, but three would be stretching it. But this is minor. Between the hours of, arriving at home until 11:30pm, it's as if I am living beneath a runway for overweight and temperamental elephants who never lift off. To where? Anywhere, but here. Damnit, it's 10pm and do you know where your mini divas and aspiring easy riders are? Yes, they are running around like banchis above my head when they should be in bed.  Also, just a word of advise: when you holler to your baby that, "there is no crying allowed in this house," I'd have to go with my first instinct that she...ehh...probably can't understand what you are saying. I'm over all of that shit. I didn't  leave Soho to live with tiny roaches stalking me and my oily hair. Anticipating that these dark clouds will eventually part, I have further begun to entertain the idea of keeping my newly purchased Path train plants alive for more than a month.     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Carnegie Hall, first row balcony. We catch a glimpse Mr. Byrne pacing behind a slightly ajar door before anyone else sees his slim figure and shimmering silver hair stand before us. My heart is wildly pacing as I begin to feel like a teenage girl again, lusting after Chris O'Donnell. But this lust is filled with pure and utter respect. Never in my life have I respected an artist such as much I do Byrne. But, not only for his musical talent but as a     urlLink ">graphic artist, sculptor, photographer and filmmaker.    This man is pure genius. His performance was far beyond any expectation I have ever had. Two cellos, four violins, two percussionists, a base player and himself, all dressed in the same simple brown outfit. Here, everyone is equal and it is the music which fills our ears and hearts with pure exuberance.  Byrne's flawless singing and infinite energy filled the arena with head bopping, shoulder shimmying and toe tapping fans. Noting that this tour was the celebration of his latest album,        urlLink ">My Backwards Life,    Byrne continually made spirited roundabouts, jogging backwards around the stage, while his buoyant essence brought everyone to their feet. His sporadic Elvis-cat-like moves brought me to pieces. Not to mention his five minute running man during Psycho Killer which tore the house down.  The energy Byrne exuded is something I cannot fulfill with words. It is a certain life about him that makes me feel alive and in lust.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here I am. My first night in Jersey City has passed and it's 3pm, I have watched two movies and 1/4 of How To Lose a Guy in Ten Days. My opinion, it should be titled, "How to Lose a Viewer in less than 10 minutes."  So, officially, my three first nights in Jersey will be spent in a friends house, animal sitting. Our patients are, one beautiful old giant of a dog, Deiter. Staney, the watch dog cat who sleeps outside and has unfortunate allergies. It is important to foresee his sneezes to avoid his showering love all over your leg. Daine and Bunny, both felines. Bunny happens to be about the size of a 16lb turkey.  It is so quiet here. And my hallway didn't smell like italian sausage this morning. Nor did I hear my neighboor and his beatnik friends playing bongos and their eclectic electric guitars. See, I have what you may call a "big house complex." I avoid all basements and attics. I sprint down long hallways. Avoid sitting near big windows at night. I used to check all closets before settling into bed. And, let me clarify that I haven't don't this since third, well maybe eighth grade, but I have set up boobie traps. Bells on door handles, micromachines strategically placed on the floor and the occasional, simple yet effective, barracading of all doors.  It's 3:02pm and I should be window shopping. And visiting all those crazy boutique owners who trap you in their store because they haven't talked to anyone for the past three hours and you have to listen to their stories about their old crazy cats.  I was even debating on whether I should go get my hair braided at the local hair salon. Though, I figure it would give me a wicked headache with all that tugging and weaving. In fact, it's like your paying for your own personal cat fight with another woman.   *Interlude* What is with the honking people. In Manhattan, you get fined $50 for layin on the horn. I should go collect my pay. Seriously, get out of your car, walk up the two foot driveway up the three steps and knock on the door. It's a great way to get your cardio in. *Interlude over*  Well, I should fix that towel rack I broke last night. I barely touched it when it came flying out of the wall at my head, I swear. What if I were unknowingly She-Ra. That would be great.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I took my final jaunt from Sullivan Street to Broadway. It had to be the most over dramatized and emotional five blocks I have ever walked. Stepping out from 150 Sullivan, I gaze at the silent church across the street and Pepe Roso's red awnings. The weather is beyond perfect. I then stand in front of the dry cleaners furiously waving my arm back and forth until the laundry guy finally sees me through his glasses and gives me a warm smile and a friendly wave back. Having picked up scones and muffins for my coworkers at Once Upon A Tart (to celebrate my three minute walk), I begin my final decent upon Prince Street. There, in the distance I can see Christopher asking busy commuters for spare change as they ignore him. He then notices me and starts yelling, "hey sunshine." But as I approach him, I see that another man is walking aside me holding out a dollar and we both convene around Christopher. It is obvious to me that he will be fine without me. Christopher then points out that me and this man are wearing similar outfits, which is awkward.  So Christopher and I share a final hug as he wishes me his best and I continue onto work.  But now, I find myself standing in front of Legacy, my most favorite vintage store, ever, I'm telling you, ever. Perhaps with my rent decrease, I will be able to get that short yellow silk flowing Grecian-like dress I have gazed at in the window for a year now. My feet won't budge. They must have laid new cement down this morning. Having realized my feet were not buried into the sidewalk, I find myself hurriedly walking, passing people in the left lane and jumping into the street to avoid early morning tourists when I realize...slow down. This is it, Scarlet. Enjoy it while it lasts.  So I made my walk last, 15 minutes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I am hosting my very first tag sale. I have unknowingly enticed my female co-workers with snacks and booze fearing it may turn to a bust.  I will be selling all of the wears that have laid stagnant too long in my over crowded closets. Don't get me wrong, they have been lying stylishly stagnant. My homemade jewels will also be on the market and I even offered a free pair with any purchase. (I am desperate people)  I do feel as if I am in some way insulting everyone by inviting them to come buy my old clothes, but all the proceeds are donated to the kind movers who will hopefully be willing to move my life over to Jersey City.  Last time I hired movers, I was physically unable to sit and watch them schlep my things up and down then down and up so I jumped in on the action and started a rally of hand offs. They finally told me to sit down because my lower back went into sporadic spasms. I think they were mildly impressed until the spasms started. It will be hard watching some my dresses go, but realistically, I hadn't worn them since the first day I bought them. Like the red dress I bought in France...7 years ago, only worn once but beautiful. And the shear ivory beaded slip dress. OK, so I'm not run you through the gamut of Scarlet's dresses past, present and future but they all provide such classic moments in my history.  So if you are in the New York area and feel the urge to experience a small town tag sale in a big bustling city, please come. Everyone is welcome.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I watched, what had to be the worst reality dating show ever. No, I am not talking about The Fifth Wheel, but, The One Who Got Away. The show was based upon on a man plucking his mate out of a group of  women he had either dated or had a crush on in the past.  What boggles me the most is the fact that this Southern cheeseball actually had so many women in his past and most importantly, the fact that all these women were willing to come on the show, knowing they some of them had indirectly kissed one another. The only redeeming factor of this show was that the lucky winner was an Asian American woman. It was just refreshing to see. I actually felt as if I were in some way victorious. I threw my arms up in the air and looked around my empty apartment to see if there was anyone I could spread the news to.  I quickly got over the painstaking finale and watch a documentary on the Hole in The Wall Gang, one of whose directors is Paul Newman. The camp is for children with cancer and other life threatening diseases to come and have a wonderful summer filled with new friendships, fun and time to be just kids. I wish my finances were stable enough so that I could simply volunteer for the rest of my life.   If I won the lottery, I would donate money to: (Keeping just enough to buy a printmaking press and supplies to build a log cabin)  Cystic Fibrosis Foundation http://www.cff.org/ Alpha-1 Foundation http://www.alphaone.org/ Helping Animals 101 http://www.helpinganimals101.com/ Save the Rainforest http://www.therainforestsite.com/cgi-bin/WebObjects/CTDSites Breast Cancer http://www.thebreastcancersite.com/cgi-bin/WebObjects/CTDSites Save the Whales http://savethewhales.org/ http://whales.greenpeace.org/ Dress for Success http://www.dressforsuccess.org/ Adoption Agencies http://www.adoptionstogether.org/default1.asp  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad just called and told me that our kitty, Jamaica, has had kidney failure. I am actually very upset at this news. And more so when I think about Tobasco, our old tabby boy who has treated Jamaica like a daughter all of these years, cleaning her up and napping together. Jamaica had always been skittish around us, but she slowly became accustomed to being around people. Soon enough, she began camping out on the dining room table, waiting for one of us to pass by and see her arching her back and dancing along the edge, "pet me, pet me." Once, she nabbed a button off a hidden peyote plant and disappeared for a few days. Or so we believed after seeing some claw marks in the dirt. She's had her tiffs with Asia, my brother's cat who resides with my parents, but it was always at night when they would be on the prowl and mistakenly cross paths. But, three cats and a dog...it wouldn't be home without the four of them. We call it the "animal retirement home." 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      David Byrne's hand, the man who's music and art I emphatically respect. I spot his yellow helmet cruising down Mercer Street on his slick bike. We trade two quick glances. After what felt like hours of concurring with my inner stalker, I decide to let her loose. I pull a tight u-ee and flee back down the sidewalk in my flip-flops. I follow him into the Gourmet Garage, a hip, trendy organic grocery. Out of breathe, I fling the door open, and there he stands, right in front of me. His eyes pretty much said it all..."...You did not just sprint down two blocks..."  With my out of control bed head and intense look in my eyes, I must look crazy.  So I made it quick, "I just saw you riding your bike and I just wanted to tell you I'm a big fan." That's all you got Scarlet! We practices hundreds and millions of various phrases you could say to David if you ever saw him, and this! What a disgrace.  "Hi...David," he says as he shakes my hand. Right, I think to myself, I know. I have practically melted into the floor by now from stage fright and the humidity. "Hi... Scarlet."  He then turns to pick out some fresh bread, and I get the message that it's time to leave the scene of my humility. I run out the front door and tear it back to work, breaking into a full sweat.  I feel ultimately guilty for disturbing his afternoon, so I tucked away my batty inner stalker. For good this time.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you ever find that woman are excessively friendly upon exiting a bathroom stall they just polluted? They either give you a look as, "Dang, someone just dropped a bomb, but it sure as hell wasn't me," or "I admit, I took a dump, but please don't judge me." Or you have the women who just sit on the toilet and wait for everyone to leave to do their business. Sometimes you have the occasional "Sit-Off." Who's going to bite the bullet ladies? They either go for it, or go to another bathroom to sit and wait for their turn.   Women even reduce their wash and dry time to escape familiar faces or god forbid the forced bathroom chit chat. I simply don't understand how women can carry on any conversation while being encompassed by such offensive odors. Get in and get the hell out. No time for banter, this is pure business. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Marshalls, or Chez Marshall as some calls it, is a mecca for designer clothing gone slightly wrong. But it's all of the tiny imperfections in life that make living in this arid world interesting. And if these miniscule imperfections hang on sad, lifeless, swinging plastic hangers for 70% off, shame on society for shunning the imperfect, but advantage discount shoppers.  Sometimes I browse the eternal aisles of shoes and practice walking in various heel heights. They look beautiful. But as I step forward, the heels surf over the waxed floors, and it ain't so pretty anymore.  Your time spent frolicking among the infinite aisles is similar to looking for a needle in an entire barn filled with hay. If you've got the time, you embody the determination and embrace the Chez Marshall you may very well surface a winner. If you become easily discombobulated, claustrophobic or are prone to panic attacks, I do not recommend diving in the jungle of J-Lo's tight ass denim, Sean John's oversized tees fit for Andre the Giant and the occasional blouses with the horridly offensive patterns. But for those who find it therapeutic, it's shabby doors lead to many tiny hidden gems. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After a perfectly cool, rainy afternoon of athleticism on the tennis court, Adam and I packed up our balls and hit the park paths back to our apartment. Adam scooting and myself on the beach cruiser, we pass three adolescents sitting on a bench, up to nothing at all. Despite being skeptical about the kids around our neighborhood, I smile at them. No response no smiles. It's nothing new, I'm used to it now. But as I glide past them I hear one yell, "GET OFF YOUR BIKE BITCH."  "Excuuuse meeee, don't talk like that to me," I say as I turn my head and stare at them. One of the kids points to the overweight boy lounging on the green bench. "Yeah, alright" I yell as I leave, who needs this from 13 year old kids. I see Adam tearing up a U-ee as he scoots back to me. "What did they say to you?" Adam, 6'5, infuriated from one too many wise ass comments directed towards us in our new neighborhood, slings the metal scooter over his shoulder and starts barreling towards the four foot boys. They run, it's hilarious. Adam later revealed to me that it didn't occur to him how he was holding the scooter over his shoulder, but it really looked like he was going to beat them to a pulp. As soon as we turn our backs the kid yells to Adam, "White Fucker."  "Your mothers taught you well," I yell at them as we ride away in fury and rage. Granted, it's not the most ideal comeback, but honestly, who talks like that to a complete stranger. It takes an afternoon or therapeutic baking, an evening of relaxation and Henies to heal the unnecessary anger these ignorant kids left lingering inside us.  Of course, it's only necessary to ponder about what you should have done...  Dream Sequence #1:    "Get off your bike bitch," Overweight boy #1 yells.  Scarlet demounts her bike as it rolls passengerless, until it eventually falls to the ground.  Boy #2 points to Boy #1 indicating to Scarlet that Boy #1 was the one who called her a bitch. Boy #3 sits there in fear as Scarlet approaches. Walking slowly towards them, Scarlet tears her tennis bag off her shoulder and reaches inside pulling out her lightweight Wilson Pro Hammer 4.0, "What did you say to me little boy?" she says as she pulls out her second racket, an old school Prince. Bearing a racket in each hand and wrath in her eyes, they flee, hoping they will never cross paths with her again. They make a mental note never to fuck with this bitch ever again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last Friday I walked by a woman beating up an innocent pay phone yelling, "Shut up, shuuuut uuuup," at it. Deep stuff. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seasonale is telling us that our wild inner bitch will only emerge four times a year as opposed to 13. Ironic, lucky 13 times we have to endure seven days of  abomination.  As of now, I have no intention of procreating tiny monsters, so why must I abide to these barnyard functions. Right, right, it's a beautiful thing...but really, it ain't.  It's not so beautiful when your cubicle quad is synched up, creating a pre-week  of cat fights and hissing and then a week of post traumatic stress. Ever notice how your typically stylish sense of outfit selection alters.  You pull out the loose fitting jeans to ease the bloatation and sport the oversized tops to conceal the bloating.  Strap on those sneaks, there's no point suffering in heels when you already look like a Dallas Cowboy linebacker. It's as if someone turned on the ugly switch.  But, FDA approved, Seasonale admittedly states to those ladies interested, to wait a few years to see how the long term effects pan out. Great, a magical pill to cure a not so magical period is at our fingertips, but no, I'd wait a few years to give it a go. Well, for what it's worth, I think I may give it a try. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most mornings I catch up on worldly news, teetering on my tiptoes looking over shoulders at the elongated  pages of the New York Times.  Sometimes it's the Star, other times it's Fabio-esque steamy romance novels but most of the time it's about J-Lo's lucky husband of the month. This morning's over the shoulder reading material was different. Usually unfazed by the bible preaching individuals who plant themselves in every subway car and recite Bible verses from Mark and Luke to disgruntled commuters, today's was a silent bible bomb. The title read, "Evidence the Bible is True." Sure, why not, the woman to my right proceeded to ogle at her newly manicured hands so I decided to take a peek on over to the left. I read, "Evolution survived despite the lack of evidence because they wanted to believe it was true."  I squint my left eye, arch my right brow and scan the subway car only to find a dozen or so half asleep passengers who have no idea that I have been Bible bombed this early in the morning.  I keep repeating the phrase in my mind...am I getting it?  Maybe some peyote fell into my rice milk this morning, but is this book trying to convince it's readers that the concept of evolution has only stuck around this long because "we" want to believe it's true? Also, is the author referring to non-believers of the Bible as, "they?"  If so, that's just blatant discrimination. Ooh I know, *poof* Adam and Eve *poof* you, me, the milkman and my dog. Please, don't get me wrong, I fancy the idea of their being a higher being up in the sky. I especially hope someone can at least hear me when I pray for my family's heath almost everyday, but evolution. How can one deny, at the least, the possibility? OK, I understand if you don't believe in evolution and I respect the individual ideals of each being, so now I feel guilty for preaching about my beliefs. I guess I'm just an evolutionary kind of gal.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Due to my cubicle claustrophobia, I yearn for foreign travels and barely manage to conquer my insatiable cravings for jungle expeditions. To satisfy these appetites, I daydream of   urlLink quiet forests,    urlLink wildly rolling fields,   urlLink isolated beaches  and   urlLink surfers  while catching up on the latest journal entries of   urlLink Volker . One of the most profound moments of my life was at  urlLink Point Reyes National Seashore Park  in California. The cool air of evening approached as Adam and I just finished setting up our site and Sky Camp. Our temporary abode for the next eight hours overlooked the tree tops and the still earth below. As the sun fell a  urlLink thick fog  unhurriedly cascaded over the tree tips, devouring the land below leaving a thick white blanket of fluff for us to frolic in. It was perfectly awesome.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just want to agnowledge the fact that a   urlLink political debate   has suddenly errupted on my blog. Where have I been? Am...am I even here...or is this just all a bloggin dream?   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While you thought you were having a killer Saturday night, I was witnessing the most erotic, wild primal  intercourse up on Aimee and Kris' front steps. Slug love making. Oh yes, slugs. I was captivated, fascinated by their oozy compassion. They hung by a taught strand of hardened slime and wrapped their elongated slippery bodies around each other. Then the most incredible part of the show was when white glands came out of their necks, knitted themselves together and continued to gyrate around and around. After they were done, they ate the strand of slime they had formed to hang in midair. Imagine that,  just like we do.      
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yet another Friday has arrived. It is indeed a time to celebrate, and perhaps think about growing out our facial hair. There are so many possibilities you see.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love how on my blog page they have ads for, "Excessive Armpit Sweating," and "Cure Hyperhidrosis ('sweaty palms, feet and underarms')." How did they know!?  Sheesh, you'd think I was a walking sprinkler or something.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The doctor told me on Tuesday that I have an infected tonsil. It's my annual curse. Last year it was pharyngitis. Same month to be exact. July 2003. Point Reyes National Seashore Park in northern California. We packed our gear for a three day expedition. I tend to pack light, impressing the airline check in folks, but in this case, packing light was not so much ideal. When I traveled to LA and San Diego earlier this year, I crammed all of the dire travelling necessities I would need into my tiny Brooklyn Industries backpack. It's great and all, until you have to get your tooth brush out of the bottom and as soon as you open the bag, all of your shit comes flying out and is strewn across the floor. Your underwear sprinkles the floor space near a strangers foot and you awkwardly heave yourself at his legs to try and capture the evidence. Jesus, what an idiot. So, our first camp site at Point Reyes was on sea level, a stones throw away from the water. It was beautiful. It was bitterly cold. Adam and I had packed shorts and a few tanks and tees for the anticipated sun struck Cali weather. I froze. Luckily a pair of my dad's old dress socks were stuffed into one of my side pockets, so I sported those for the evening. I may have even had two pairs because now, I recall Adam wearing knee high dress socks and his birks. Mine were purple with light purple polka dots. Despite the warming factors of the knee highs, I still managed to get pharyngitis.  So now I am on antibiotics, and the pills are literally the size of a peanut shell. Not just the peaunt itself, but the entire shell which encases two whole peanuts. Did my doctor mistaken me for a horse, and now I am required to chuck this hockey puck down my sore throat?  All I know is that my Peronis are having a leisurly time, quietly frosting in my fridge. I can have a-ah beer right? 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've begun my new yoga routine. It all happened when I went online about a month ago and saw the tape I had been using for the past three years. It said in emphatic quotations, "Susan Deason's weightloss yoga tape is great for beginners." Beginners? This is a hard thing for me to admit folks. I actually thought myself to be a hip yoga addict. Three years, three years of naivete. Past apartments I've inhabited flitter through my head as I remember how I was certain to reserve a coveted space for my daily routines. Syracuse, Brooklyn, Soho. Had I lived in a pod for the past three years? But Jersey City has turned over a new leaf. A strapping and foxy leaf at that. I have now officially enrolled in Yoga Zone's Power Hatha yoga for strength and endurance. Lisa Bennett, my new invigorating and high strung yogini will now be whooping my body into shape. Sorry Susan, but it's time for me to move on. In fact, it's about two years overdue now. In all honesty though, Susan did help me shed the pasta weight I gathered from 6 months basking in the Italian culture, so grazie to you and arrivederci. For some reason though, I imagine  urlLink Susan  and  urlLink Lisa  having a Yogini-Off, like a dance off. I picture the two tied up like pretzels and fighting with their wildly limber legs as they walk around on their hands. All the while they are meditating and chanting "om."    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A preemptive apology to you, for the following rant. But what is it with them men in nyc? Why is it so hard for them to keep their tiny penis heads tucked into their pants all day.  Winter: Despite the layers of undershirts, sweaters, jackets and long underwear we pile on, men still seem to pick out the curves of our coveted be-hinds. Even when we are skittering along the ice looking like deranged Michelle Kwans and covered in street slosh, we still manage to turn heads and entice skeevy whistles. Spring: The minute we step foot outside, showing some forearm and ankle, oh, here it comes. Watch out boys, I've got some hot pinky toe action going on in my flip flops, gather round, let's all take a peek.  Summer: Multiply winter by 10 fold and spring by ten hundred, add them up and voila. What we have here ladies is a giant cock walking around NYC grabbing ass, drooling on himself and slapping other giant cocks high five as they induce whiplash on themselves. Granted, many of these women are aware of their pretty plumber's butt and luxurious boobs, but modest ladies like me, can't wear trench coats all year round.  Also, any man who has survived thus far and is still reading this, you must know that I understand, all men are not like this. Trust me, I know that.  But how much are we expected to take? Why is it that we are now trained to accept this abuse? The most unpleasant situation I have ever been in occurred on the 9 train, 9am, rush hour and unnaturally packed into a moving can. I feel the corner of someone's brief case jab me in the hip. OK, now it's nudging my ass. I turn around and some jack ass has taken his dick out of his pants and has felt the need to poke me with it. OH-KAY. I turn around and slowly begin to fill with fury and disgust. He has the nerve to continue treating me like a jack off post until I pivot my victimized body around and put my enraged face up to his eyes so he can feel the hate I am breathing onto his face and stare right through to the back of his head. He had the nerve to stare back for a half second but he turned his head away and got off at the next stop. Good riddance. So to all those ladies out there who can appreciate this tiny rant, I hope you know you are not alone. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You think you hate it now. The insufferable  urlLink freezer on wheels , playing hideous tunes of evil clowns. But wait until that absurdly humid weekend after courageous souls brave the sultry air, attempting slightly sporty activities. The sweat beads gather at the nape of your neck and above your lip. You marvel at the fact that you actually put jeans on this morning. You wonder if your friends will see your butt perspiring when you peel yourself off their deck furniture. Pit stains are a give in, everyone wears them in this heat. Stray leaves and abandoned flower petals are adhering themselves to your damp skin. You are like a walking glue stick. Even the two straps of mesh on your flip flops are making you perspire, barefeet are necessary. Are you daft to want a cigarette. Yes. You have one anyways. Your speech slowly begins to slur and your thoughts become dense clouds of yearning shade. Your friend asks, "Remember when we played basketball without feet?" Spirited laughter erupts as we picture ourselves wildly tumbling and teetering on our footless stems. "You know what I mean," as we exhale, sigh and begin to sweat again. As you hear evil clown music in the far distance you notice heads perk up, eyes widen and hands scour the depths of endless pockets for spare change. Your childhood instincts bring you to your feet as you begin a full sprint, arms flailing towards the street. A perfect solution to a perfectly hot day, the  urlLink ice-cream sandwich. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To end this monotonous work week on a high note, deepest thank yous for everyone who inquired about my dad. He is doing magnificently and I know he would appreciate your concerns. It's the summer of BBQing and Red Strips. So cheers to you all enjoy your blissful 48 hours of unattached commitments.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After a relaxing drink on the water last night, windblown hair, captain seaman style, we headed back to Jersey City via the super sleek, orange and brown seated Path train. As we reach Grove Street and I hear a useless argument erupting, mainly consisting of a bundle of "fuck yous" and "go fuck your mothers."  Mind you, all in Joisey accents. To my knowledge, the drunken, sporting shades in the subway, garish Hawaiian shady shirt type became irrationally frustrated with this man, whose slightly overweight body spilled into the neighborhood his seat. "Yea, fuck you, go fuck your mother when you get home," the overweight man yelled as the Hawaiian shirt exited and then choose to stand outside, pounding on the glass behind his head. Je-sus, I think to myself, when is it ever enough. As the doors close, some woman opens her mouth and asks the overweight man, "Why are you so rude, you can't move over at all?" "Fuck you,"  he replies. "Shut up," she rebuttals. Damn, this had to be the most competent and engaging conversation I've heard all day. This man was squashed as far into the corner as humanly possible. OK lady, I think, just shuuuut uuuuup. My insides are beginning to race across my chest and up and down my spine. "It always comes back to the fat thing, let's pick on the fat guy, it's so easy to pick on him because he's fat, " he voices as his words vibrate through the subway car. My heart spills for this man. "Just shut up," she chimes in. Good one.  Then, the real stupid shit begins. The African American man sitting next to the witty mouthed woman gets involved. He verbally threatens the overweight man, telling him not to talk to women like that and how could kill him, blah blah blah, you're so great and strong, oh save us all. An ignorant yelling match begins, Match, Set, Point to overweight man. As predicted, egocentric superman is a sore loser. He gets up and starts strangling the winner. Now, this is enough, it's ridiculous, I unravel. "Cooome oooon," I yell at their brick heads. Adam holds me back as I try to lunge into their vicinity of masculinity and testosterone.  "Don't," Adam says to me. Aimee and Kris have remained calm the entire time and I feel awkward for not being able to retain my cries of anger and frustration towards this useless act of hate. "Cooome oooon, this is so fucking ridiculous." Alright, so no props for my use of language. A sturdy African American woman plunks herself between the heated animals and says, "He's not worth it, you are a black man and he is white, YOU will be arrested and go to jail, he's not worth it." I am enraged. When did things become black and white? YOU attacked him so YOU will go to jail because YOU tried to strangle a man, not because you are black. It's as the overweight man yelled to the huddled crowds of passangers, "We all paid $1.50 to ride this train and we all have a right to our space." Everyone is equal. We are all humans, flesh and blood.  I've had enough. We get off the train as the men begin to wrestle on the platform. Enough already. It's beyond me. I am in disbelief at my angered reaction. It was just so fucking ridiculous.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having moved to Jersey City nearly a month ago, I had no idea that I would be packing up to camp out in my original homeland, the Philippines. Well, perhaps my homeland away from homeland...in New Jersey. Familiarizing myself with the new neighborhood, I strolled down West Side Avenue and was dumbfounded to see the large wooden sign overhead the local store with the carved lettering, Filipinas Market. Wait, that's Me. I'm a Filipina. I even have perfume called Filipina. The extraordinary woman who arranged my adoption back in 1980 gave it to me a few years ago for my birthday. I only use it on special occasions, hoping to make it last until the bottle is bone dry. And even then, it's like the puny little puddle of molasses like shampoo that might take days to finally ooze out, but if you add a little water and shake it up like a martini, voila, you have yourself watered down, bubbly, yet officially usable shampoo.  When I first started riding the bus to the path station, I found myself surrounded by distant relatives and familiar faces. And my nose! When I was young, some kids would ask my why my nose was flatter than theirs. It never bothered me, I was used to it, and as a tomboy, I could beat up the biggest boy in my class. In fact, up until high school I was known for being able to throw the ball farther than all the boys. OK, now I'm just bragging. But I would usually shrug off their perfectly innocent question and resume digging in the dirt, looking for gold using a twig.   When I was 14, my parents took me back to the Philippines, which allowed me to embrace the culture and to see my heritage. Granted, I was at the age where it was embarrassing to be seen with your parents and especially agitating when you have to wear a fanny pack, but it wasn't difficult to see that the Filipino people embraced a sweet demeanor and donned warm smiles. That would explain why I got the rep for "Always Smiling," in my 8th grade year book. I had to change schools after that, since every moment after that, when I did not display the freeze frame all whites Crest smile, people asked if I was OK. Recently, I have acquired more of a "Don't mess with me, on subway, walking or anywhere look," for city life though.  Waiting for the bus this morning, I met a woman, who knew from Adam and Eve that I was Filipino. She didn't believe that I worked in Manhattan, telling me the dreaded, "you look like your still in high school..." tell me something I don't know. I tried to explain that I was from Connecticut but I think she may have been slightly confused. She was sweeter than a butter cookie and she made me feel right at home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I apologize to anyone who browses my blog because I have not written an entry in quite some time now, or so it feels. Last week my father had an episode which mimicked the exact symptoms of a heart attack, spent the day in the emergency room while doctor figures observed his progress. He had woken up with tightness in his chest and arm, contacted his doctor who called a cardiologist, who told his doctor to tell my dad to go to the ER immediately. Did you know that the esophagus lies directly behind the heart, therefore it's symptoms can impersonate such symptoms as a heart attack and such? Anyways, unaware of the situation, I had been trying to call them continuously throughout the day since I would be driving home that weekend. I am always sure to confirm that they will be home since they seem to spontaneously elope to Italy and Jamaica frequently. It seems spontaneous to me, but in fact they have all these trips planned and seem to forget to tell me sometimes. I guess it keeps things interesting for us, "Hey kids, were going to Spain, you have to stay and work and no I will not pack you into my carry-on." They do happen to be the most significant people in my life, so you can understand why I was anxious when no one picked up all day. My dad is usually always typing away at his desk at home, adding words to his most recent novel or reciting his upcoming commentary, swiveling around in his worn down leather chair with the high back. He has always been a quick draw with the phone since it rests on the desk beside him all day. You know the feeling, when your stomach sinks as the phone rings at 3am. Has grandma fell down the stairs sleep walking? Has the cat been hit by a car again? This is what I felt for 6 hours. My dad finally answered and told me the story I just told you. Thankfully he was well and alive to tell me all about his uneasy experience, but I listened will all ears and drove home as soon as I got out of work. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up this morning thinking it was Friday. I really  urlLink hate   urlLink when   urlLink that   urlLink happens. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had this awful dream last night that the weekend was over and I had to go back to work today.    Oh yea, damnit. If only it were a dream.   As I went to pull out my metrocard pass to take the W/R train, I realized my metrocard had expired, I had absolutely no cash and my credit card and ATM card were still in the back pocket of the jeans I wore to Bushkill Falls yesterday. I regretfully picked up a few stray cards laying on the floor to see if they had any rides left, but no luck. Ashamed that I was left scrounging around the dirty floor to find a way to get to my dreaded cubicle, I stood up, exited the subway station at  World Trade and started walking in the wrong direction. After surrendering to a nearby doorman, I ask where Canal Street is. He points in the opposite direction and tells me to just keep on walking.  Right, so I walk, and it's hot out, not like the Poconos, where it was blissfully chilly, like fall, it was heaven.  I call Adam to share that I am a complete idiot.  He tells me he is nearby so he meets me, walks me to work and hands me a twenty.   Despite Adam being my guardian angel and personal ATM machine, I still feel depressed. I think it's just because it's Monday, and I really hate Mondays.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm taking tomorrow off to spend a weekend in the Poconos with 8 crazy lads and lassies. I'm thinking, naked kayaking. Sweet. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't write an entry yesterday because I thought you might get mad at me.  On two separate occasions yesterday, I was undeniably yelled at.  My first scolding was on the Jersey City bus to Journal Square. The bus was packed to the brim with children and briefcases, so I tried to smush myself into the crowd to remain behind the white line. But there was no smushing room to be allocated, even for my tiny ass. So, I compromised with the white line, and allowed myself to hold onto the back of the bus driver's seat to prevent any events of flying through the windshield from occurring. This is Mistake #1. Never cross into the bus driver's turf and most importantly, don't go touching their shit.  "DON'T LEAN ON MY SEAT,"	she belted, loud enough for the surrounding Hudson area to hear. I understand, she can't have anyone leaning all up against her stuff, but maybe a please, or maybe you didn't have to yell it across America? Since we had achieved psychotic clown car status she proceeded to bust by all the designated stops. It was humoring to see all of the sidewalk civilians waving and jumping up and down for it to stop. I felt like waving back. I could even see a few people swearing back at the bus as we left them standing in a cloud of exhaust. My second scolding was at work. The copy lady. The color printer ran out of 8 1/2" by 11" paper, so I was scrounging around looking for a few stranded blank sheets. With no intentional prompting she asked me what I was looking for. I told her, 8 1/2" by 11" color printer paper.  "WELL THIS PAPER IS ONLY FOR THE XEROX MACHINE SO DON'T EVEN THINK OF PUTTING IT IN THAT PRINTER."  Alright already, what's with the hostility today? I wasn't even near her and the stupid Xerox paper. Mistake #2. I don't know how to solve this one. I wasn't even looking at her, she just decided to bud into my life and make me feel stupid. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Washington, DC, it's, "Who do you work for." In New York City it's, "Where do you live?...and just curious, how much is your rent?"  I love how open we city folk are, asking perfect strangers their yearly incomes and dishing about the thousands of dollars we shell out of our empty pockets for our pint sized studio apartments. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This   urlLink is   urlLink for   urlLink real   urlLink folks  Cool, slick shade for those pups who enjoy feeling the wind in their hair.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I bought an  urlLink Us Weekly  magazine for the subway rides this morning to keep my mind from focusing on the fact that our tiny island, mecca for millions, is under a terrorist threat...today...until the Election. Co-workers huddled in their quads this morning murmuring to one another about whether they were scared or not. And how this is all a gigantic plot to delay the election to sway voters to re-elect Bush since many believe, "he can keep this country safer than Kerry." Yea, safer. He couldn't keep a  urlLink caged bird  safe if he tried. But as I was walking through the World Trade Center Path station this morning, I became irrationally angry at the tourists, standing, ogling at Ground Zero with this sad look in their eyes as if they felt they had to be melancholy. I just wanted to yell at them. Get out of here. Aggravated because they are here staring at the remains of our horrid past when there are threats of truck bombs being planted all over midtown and the financial district. For their own safety, LEAVE, and if you happen to live in California, take me with you.  The commute seemed to take hours this morning. I was hardly able to focus on Hollywood's latest dates and break ups. Even Jennifer Gardner and  urlLink Michael Vartan's  break up. Never Been Kissed, hello, hot.  I am bound to NYC and NJ public transportation, they own me like a subway and bus riding bitch, unless I take a $50 cab ride home, but that is just ridiculous. So I guess all I can do is pray for my, Adam's and our friend's safety. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>