<Blog>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dunno. Sometimes I just think I'm doing too many things at once... But I'll give it a try for a few days...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Slaving away at university at a stupid programme to save some stuff to disk. Sucks.  And I wanna see football (soccer!?) instead. But there's still hours to go.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That keeper really saved us there. And Sweden takes the prize for the 2 nicest goals in the Euro championships so far...  In other news, I got an e-mail from the university of Oslo telling I've been accepted for the fall semester. Made me a bit speechless but very happy!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lo and behold,  this is sortof a test blog from my new gmail account. Very cool, now I'm just waiting for messages to drop in... 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fair enough. Sweden's game was better :)  I'm actually getting a football fever worked up here... that's all good in preparation of watching the Sweden-Denmark game at work in Copenhagen tomorrow.  And I downloaded a load of pic's from my digicam today. Now all I need is a bigger disk to put'em on the web.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      France beat England, and Sweden  really  beat Bulgaria. I like. Henke is a national hero, even though he's from Helsingborg.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I voted on in the EU elections thursday to get that done.  On friday I went to Oslo, and partied two nights in a row. That was nice, but the Airport train in Oslo broke down and I was a full two hours late. What a nightmare. I even considered setting the train on fire: then, at least, the fire brigade would've gotten us out.  The weekend was superb, though!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and that's good, because for now that means the end of the week (not for long though, because I will be working weekends soon).  It also means I get tp go to Oslo. That's very good. 2 parties lined up, but that's not the best part  :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and that gmail and SkypeOut would want  me  to test their stuff. Well, I'll just wait and see.  Got my login data from SEB in Denmark. Seems their system sucks...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7 hours at work, 3 hours of commute and another 3 hours in the computing lab. I'm toast, but not sure I can sleep. But I got 2 answers I'd been waiting for today: one from my brand-new danish bank and one from the Commission (see yesterday's blog). Still waiting for news from the university of Oslo, though.  I had some Knake (typical Lundian sausage) and a dirt cheap Danish beer for dinner. The sausage was the better part...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah yeah, I checked out the web site of the  urlLink Euro Ombudsman  today to see if the Commission needs to answer me regarding student involvement and Erasmus Mundus. Turns out they do!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argl. Getting up at six is no fun... but work was OK today, we got to play with a car. The other job sucks; I hate calling people when they haven't asked for it. And it's way past bedtime. But I got a nice press release today on  urlLink AFP  and I made some dough I never baked off: fresh buns tomorrow for breakfast. I also washed and the drying stand fills up my whole bathroom.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just booked a flight to Norway and back with  urlLink Sterling . Actually, I made a mistake and booked for the wrong day; however I realised this in time and they let me change the reservation at no extra charge. That's cool, and it ain't what  urlLink Volare  did that time I wanted to fly to Palermo but accidentally booked to Naples instead.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got up at six to ride the train to work in Copenhagen. Left at four - and presto! a call from that other job. And was at school until ten programming away at a stupid news server in C++
     

    
</post>


</Blog>