<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Friday afternoon I went up to Dorchester for a Grad Party.  It was a good time.  I knew quite a few people there, a lot of math majors showed up.  There was a cookout, some beer, and the Red Sox on TV.  Apparently my new drinking habits have gotten around.  This guy Mark walked in and said Sara, no drink?  I was then offered a beer, which I turned down to his suprise.  I don't know where he got this idea from.  {Oh yea, that one Wed. night.}  Anyway, I had a beer a little later, to which he smiled, and said "ummhmm, she's starting"  We watched quite a bit of the game, and then around 10:30 headed into downtown Boston for some dancing and fun.    This only reinforced what I already knew to be true: I am not the club kinda girl.  We took two cars to this other girls house, and then we piled into her Mom's van cause paying for parking is obviously cheaper in 1 car than 2.  Something you never have to think about when going drinking in Dartmouth.  We parked in a lot, and then walked around looking for a place to go, and getting lost in the process.  It seemed to me like we were walking around in circles.  We finally found this place, I don't remember the name of it, but it started with an A and the name was 4 letters long.  We paid the $5 cover charge.  {I know!  WTF?}  Only to find the place was not that cool, with no dancing, and many guys in there that were balding.  It took me forever to get a drink, but as soon as I got it I was informed that this place sucked, something I already knew, and everyone was ready to leave.  They told me to chug my drink, a screwdriver.  So I drank it really fast and we were outta there.    We found this other place Sissy K's or something like that.  We had to pay another $5 cover.  They had food and a bar on the first floor, but we headed up to the second floor where there was a DJ, dancing, and another bar.  We headed over to the bar and before I knew it I was pulled out onto the dance floor.  I was going to argue, being the non-dancer that I am, but I didn't.  This girl Anna and I started dancing while the others got drinks.  They soon joined us and we had a party going.  And yes, it is very much out of my character but I danced (for the whole time we were there too).  I was not a fan of the perfumed smoke that blasted into my face every once in a while.  But I was a fan of the drinks they had in test tubes.  A lady came around with a tray full; I asked the girl who drove to pick a color, she picked blue, so I had a blue one, very tasty.  So much in fact I had another later in the evening, this time it was orange.  The lights in the place were crazy and by the time we left I felt like I was going blind.  When we left, we headed back to the car, I was tired and a little tipsy.  On the way we came across some sprinklers which everyone tried to avoid so as not to get wet, except for me, I purposely ran through them on the lawn TO get wet.  We made it back to the car way easier than when we left the car, good thing we were with people from Boston cause I would have gotten sooo lost.  We ran into some 3 AM traffic but took a side street and made it back to Dorchester by 3:30.  I was soo tired and not wanting to drive home, so I crashed there on an AeroBed.  It was very comfy.  And I was out as soon as my head hit the pillow.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	We all piled into my Mom's van after graduation to go get some lunch.  I had planned on going to Fay Too's in Dartmouth, because it is a nice place, and not right on Route 6 so I figured it would not be crowded.  We got stuck in graduation traffic, and the whole ride to Fay Too's, the 3 children were whinning and complaining about when we were going to get there, how much longer it was going to take, and being hungry and thirsy.  The three children being the 13 year-old twins and my dad.  Yes, dad was the worst of the whinning children.  We got to Fay Too's and I was right, it was not packed at all, in fact it was closed.  With no backup plan in mind, we just kept on driving.    This pissed off the children even more.  They started naming everything they saw saying "we can eat there", or "look a McDonald's, why are we still driving?"  We drove into New Bedford, and I had an idea for a restaurant.  But where is it?  Hmmm, I had forgotten.  So, I called up Ryan and asked him where Antonio's was.  {Actually I asked him where Angelo's was, and he had no idea what I was referring to until I said, "you remember that place you, me, James, and Ed went to at the end of last summer in New Bedford?"  "ohhh Antonio's" he said.}  What a guy, he gave me directions, and off we went.  We found it, and had our lunch.  {I actually tried calamari.  Yucky.  I was right not wanting to eat it.}  I had BBQ chicken skewers, and everyone else had something with seafood.  I am the outlier.  I got some good props from my family for picking the restaurant, everyone loved their food.    After lunch, my dad, the big child, had a graving for chocolate ice cream, as he does probably every day.  So we had to go find him chocolate ice cream.  I knew a place, the Dairy Chief.  Then he started complaining about how long it would take to get there.  "it is gonna take us 3 hours to get there?"  I told him yes it is, and should probly just go to the Dairy Queen {which isn't a dairy queen anymore} on the lower cape, cause that would be closer.  We made it to the Dairy Chief and he got his ice cream.  We all did, except for my aunt.  It was at this point that my little brother announced that it would be really gross if there was meat flavored ice cream.  Then he and Jack started to brainstorm all the different meat flavored ice cream's they could think of.  Oye.    After ice cream we went back to UMD to drop everyone at their cars.  James and Heather decided they didn't want to ride back with dad so my mom said she would drive them back when she left in a couple hours.  Back to Fall River.  My mom got out some stuff to fix my wall and immediately James brings the stuff over to the hole, and starts to fix it.  It was as tho he was on auto pilot.  I said he is very handy, I should keep him.  Heather said he punches holes in the walls at home all the time so he is used to fixing them.  Alrighty then.  When the wall was fixed, the family headed home after saying goodbyes, and I headed out to see the movie Troy.  Kinda disappointing by the way.  And that ends graduation day for me.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	On Sunday the clouds were supposed to break only for scattered thunderstorms, and not the gorgeous bright sun that showed up just in time for the beggining ceremonies.  But I jump ahead.  The day started with me waking up at 7 after 4 hours of sleep next to my mom.  When the alarm went off, I turned it off and sat up.  I had waken my mom up and she said, "you don't have to get up now do you?"  I told her I was going to go to breakfast before graduation.  She replied "oh.  I thought we were staying over here so we could see you, but we haven't."  I answered "I thought you were staying here so you would not have to wake up early and drive for about 2 hours."  "No, we came to see you."  I told her that some people were going out for breakfast beforehand and I was going to join them, if that was cool.  She said it was and I got up and started getting ready.    After a shower I put on the dress that I got for graduation, it was so pretty, altho it did have a halter top, and it was cloudy, and cool outside.  I put on a sweatshirt for the time being, and brought a cardigan with me to wear over it for the ceremony.  My mom thought I should wear pants because it would be tooo cold with just the dress.  {AHA!  a time when the Mom is wrong.  This must go down in history books.}  I wore the dress anyway because all my other clothes are crappy, but I did bring nylons to make her happy.  I headed over to Angelo's in New Bedford for breakfast.  A nice little place we sat on some stools and ate a delicious breakfast.  After, we headed over to Ryan's house to put on our gowns and figure out how the hell to wear our hoody things.  Yes that's right, 2 CIS majors and a math major could not figure it out on our own.  Luckily Ryan's mom had put his together so we had a model to go by.  We were all spiffy looking, and so off to UMD we headed.    When I got there I met up with the other math majors who were drinking OJ and scarfing down donuts.  Then we were herded like sheep into lines complete with a name card.  We talked and joked until it was time to walk.  What a mess that was.  We started walking 2 abreast next to the English majors into the Amphitheater.  However, once we got inside, the line merged into 1 line, however we were in the middle of the English majors.  We stood there waiting for them to go by, and then were unsure where to go since m is nowhere near e.  The usher had no idea either and finally got sick of us standing there I think, he just sent us onward to some seats.  We sat down, sure we were out of order and were going to mess up the ceremony.  {But when it started and people were getting their degrees, we saw that it really didn't matter where we sat as long as we were somewhere in the college of arts and sciences, which we were.}   By the time we had sat down, the sky was blue, and it was hot.  I took off my sweater underneath my gown.  And was very glad I wore my dress and not the nylons.  I was all ready for graduation, sat next to 2 cool people, Christine, and Mike, and I had my camera, bubbles, and a deck of cards.  I barely listened to any of the ceremony.  I was talking and blowing bubbles, or listening to someone else talk.  It was a lot of fun.  I'm glad we were towards the end because after we walked across stage it was hard to sit there and just wait.  I did find my family tho, after a while and they started making goofy faces at me, so I made some right back.   I was quite exciting I must say.  After the ceremony, us math geeks decided to meet up to take pictures after we found our families.  I headed over to where my family was, because I knew if they tried to find me we would lose each other.  I found them, was met with roses, hugs, smiles, and lots of praise.  What a loving family, I am so lucky.  We took lots of pictures.  The family, the kids, me and my parents, my aunt, mom, and me.  My mom and me, my aunt and me, we just went nuts with the pictures.  It was nice.    After this, I told them I had to meet at the yellow tent for more pictures.  We took so many, all the math majors lined up and all of a sudden all these people jumped in front of us taking pictures, like 20 of them.  I said who are all these people.  Sing said he felt famous.  Then we had to take a ton more pictures, just the BA's, just the BS's, three people at a time, then 2 people at a time.  I swear I think every combination of picture was taken.  Jack acted as my personal photographer, very nice, props to him.  Finally enough is enough, only so many pics you can take, plus the twins were whinning about food, so I said it was time for me to go.  We said goodbyes, and off we went on the journey to find food...
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	From the current book I'm reading,  Hyperspace  by Theoretical Physicist Dr. Michio Kaku.  Just a mind blower I thought I would share because, well this is my site damn it and I want to.    According to this theory, before the Big Bang, our cosmos was actually a perfect ten-dimensional universe, a world where interdimensional travel was possible. However, this ten-dimensional universe "cracked" in two, creating two separate universes: a four- and a six- dimensional universe. The universe in which we live was born in that cosmic cataclysm. Our four-dimensional universe expanded explosively, while our twin six-dimensional universe contracted violently, until it shrank to almost infinitesimal size. This would explain the origin of the Big Bang. If correct, this theory demonstrates that the rapid expansion of the universe was just a rather minor aftershock of a much greater cataclysmic event, the cracking of space and time itself. The energy that drives the observed expansion of the universe is then found in the collapse of ten-dimensional space and time. According to this theory, the distant stars and galaxies are receding from us at astronomical speeds because of the original collapse of ten-dimensional space and time.   This theory predicts that our universe still has a dwarf twin, a companion universe that has curled up into a small six-dimensional ball that is too small to be observed.   For more, consult the book, it is very good, but some parts are difficult to read, and need to be reread.  Or, check out Kaku's site.  http://www.mkaku.org/    I will also probably post more on the subject since I find it fascinating.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	hey the quizzy thing worked.  That's awesome.  Makes me feel better.  It doesn't take much.  Just don't ask what kind of sex I would have if I was gay.  {Don't get the wrong idea, it was a quiz just like this one where you put in your name, and some other info including sexual preference, I was horsing around and put in gay.}    But yea, I am definetly more of a cuddler.  I love to cuddle.  It's a very special thing in my mind.  I think cuddling is underrated just like the sense of smell.  I think if people were polled, sense of smell would be least important if they graded 1 to 5.  But I think smell is an important one.  I personally smell all the time.   HAHAHAHAHA.   I mean I smell things a lot... on purpose... not that I myself smell... altho maybe I do and people are just being polite...  Ok, I am weird and I am rambling.    Must now go listen to some good music, oh yea and I still have to get that shower to prevent myself from smelling grungy.  And of course to be appealing to the opposite sex, I will wash my ears...
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	In my life, I have only really made 1 big mistake, altho it was a whopper, and who knows how long I will regret it.  I am quite pissed right now.  fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.  This sucks.  I wish I could go back in time.  fuck fuck fuck somemore.    All i wanted was stupid fucking cable...  going to take a shower.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Hmm, where does she find all these?  Personally, I think I am more of a cuddler, but here are my results.            urlLink   What Is Your Best Sexual Skill?        Name:&nbsp;        Age:&nbsp;        Sex:&nbsp;    Male  Female       Sexuality:&nbsp;    Straight  Gay  Bisexual       Flirting Skill Level -  70%                                                                            Kissing Skill Level -  61%                                                                            Cudding Skill Level -  6%                                                                            Sex Skill Level -  92%                                                                             Why They Love You &nbsp;    You are too good to be true.        Why They Hate You &nbsp;    You get tongue-tied when they ask you to talk dirty to them.              This   Quiz   by  urlLink  lady_wintermoon   - Taken 84406 Times.          New! Get  urlLink Free Horoscopes  from Kwiz.Biz 
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I saw Fahrenheit 9/11 this afternoon at the Dennis Playhouse with my mom, Jack, and Karl.  This was a very heavy movie.  I liked the movie a lot.  There were comedic parts, but overall it was quite sad.  I liked how respectful Michael Moore was when dealing with the event on 9/11, instead of showing the planes, the screen was black and we could only hear it.  I think every citizen of this country should see this movie.    The Dennis Playhouse had five showings of this movie today and for at least the 2, 4:30, and 7 showings, there were lines down the street and the theatre was packed.  At our showing, the 4:30, the entire theatre clapped at the end of the movie.  One piece of advice, you might need to bring some tissues.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Last night I went over to the Beachcomber to hear Roomful of Blues and entered a Bizarro Universe.  It must have been bizarro, because the happenings are just unexplainable.    Bizarro incident #1.  I am not able to drink this week, not until Tues. due to medication, my mom knows this, and yet when we got to the Beachcomber she offered to buy me a beer.  {Yes, I went out with my mom, for some of you this may be bizarre in its own right, but for me, it is normal.}  Anyway, I told her I couldn't because of the medication, and she said, "1 beer won't hurt."  In what kind of universe does a mother go against doctors wishes to buy a beer for her kid??  Must be a bizarro universe.    Bizarro incident #2.  While my mom offered to buy me a beer, and thought it would not hurt, I declined and got a water instead.  In what kind of universe does a 22 year old who likes beer, turn down a free beer for water??  Must be a bizarro universe.    Bizarro incident #3.  The keyboard player in the band hit on me.  In what kind of universe does the keyboard player of a band hit on me??  Must be a bizarro universe.    Following baseball logic, 3 strikes = you're out, 3 bizarro incidents = you're in a bizarro universe.    It was a fun night tho.  I danced, got beer spilled on my feet, and some butch lady with cowboy boots stepped on me, that kinda hurt.  There was also a bachelotte party there; they were having quite the good time.  I forgot how much fun the Beachcomber can be.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	The Bush administration and its right-wing allies are launching an all-out assault on Michael Moore and his new movie, attempting to discredit the film before it is even public. Last month, White House communications director Dan Bartlett said the movie is "so outrageously false, it's not even worth comment" 1 - a comment made despite the fact that the movie was not yet public and Bartlett had not seen the film. Now the smear campaign is focused on creating the public illusion that Moore lied about a secret Saudi flight that was permitted after 9/11 when most U.S. airspace was closed. But, according to one new report, the Tampa International Airport "confirmed that the flight did take place" -- despite three years of Bush administration denials.   Check out the Daily MisLead, a Daily Chronicle of Bush Administration Distortion (on my links) for the rest of the story.  Also check out Michael Moore's new movie in select theatres now, I have yet to see this movie, but plan to soon.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I had my graduation party on Saturday afternoon/evening.  It was a lot of fun.  My mom bbq'ed chicken, grilled burgers, and we made our own shish-ka-bobs.  My aunt and uncle came, a very nice suprise, but not the only nice suprise guest of the evening. :)  My dad also came, and hopefully he wasn't too much of his crazy self.  Some family friends came, and my most close friends were there, which made it awesome.  We drank some beer, talked, listen to my dad's "i almost got killed in {fill in the blank of any country you can think of}" stories, I had to introduce everyone about 8 times, it was fun.  After a bit some of us headed down to check out the beach.  It was low tide, not as fun, but it meant Heather could pick up oysters off the beach, break them open on a rock and eat them.  I was a little tispsy at this time, not too bad, but I had a buzz.  We walked along the beach for a while, and then began walking back to my house.    When we got there, I made strawberry daquiri's, followed by margarita's, {but the daquiri's were favorite} and we sat in the living room sharing stories.  It was quite the fun afternoon; I had a blast
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Friday night I went home to help my mom and get ready for Saturday.  I was met by a call from Leah as my mom and I were heading out to P-town for some dinner.  {I had a hummus sandwich, yum yum}  When I got back home, Leah and I decided to meet up at the Seadog.  Not my favorite place in the world {thats cause the food kinda sucks, appetizers are ok, and drinks are good.}  But I was not hungry, so the Seadog was fine enough for me.  I met her there and to my suprise, and excitement, it was Karaoke night.  I now had a mission: get Leah drunk and drag her up to do karaoke with me.    I have never done karaoke before, but I've wanted to try it and with a few drinks, I'm sure it would be easy to get me up there; especially if I had someone to sing with.  But Leah was not having any of it.  She gave me a stern "absolutely not" look.  The kind of look you get from your mom as a kid when you are about to jump on the bed.  I told her I would order Tequila shot, and was shot an even stronger "absolutely not" look.  She had sangria which was HUGE, and I had an Appletini.  We saw a ton of people we recognized from high school but never made it up to sing.  I failed my mission.  But I will not give up.  We ended the night having hot fudge sunday's and left when this awful guy got up to sing another sad, slow, bad song for the THIRD time.
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Ok, Ryan rocks, not only was he the ONLY one who answered my question, he got it right.  So he wins a prize, a beer on me.
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I was posed this problem and thought it was interesting enough for a post.  So here you go.  Try it, problems are soup for the mind.     The Ages of My Sons  "A mathematician and a philosopher were taking a walk and talking.  The mathematician asked about the philosopher's sons.  The philosopher told her "they are well, all three of my son's celebrate their birthday this very day.  Can you tell me how old each one is?"  The mathematician says "sure, but I will need some more information."    "Ok” says her friend, “here are some hints.”  The product of the ages of my 3 sons is 36.  “Ok”, says the mathematician “but I will still need some more information.”  “The sum of their ages is equal to the number of windows in that building.”  Says the philosopher pointing to a nearby structure.    The mathematician thinks.  Then she says, “Still, I need an additional hint to solve the problem.”    “My oldest son has blue eyes” says the philosopher.    The mathematician thinks, and after a moment says, “Oh, I have the answer.”   And then tells her friend.    Can you figure out the ages of the philosophers 3 sons?? 
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I woke up at 6:30, suprisingly rested and not at all tired.  {The previous morning I slept in till 8:30 and was exhausted all day.}  I should have gotten up earlier tho.  I dressed, got myself ready and headed over to Home Depot to see about buying some welding glass so I could look at the sun.  I have this thing about eyesight, I would like to keep it.  So off to Home Depot I went.  I asked if they had welding googles.  I was shown to the safety department which is not what I wanted.  So I asked someone else, and they led me to these huge helmet looking things.  Hmmm, I thought.   "Do you sell just the glass plates and not the whole helmet?"   He replied, "no."  And looked at me like I had two heads.  I didn't want a helmet, I am not actually going to weld.  And by chance I looked around the helmet and found just the glass plates.  Ahh, exactly what I wanted.  I found the right shade, #12, and headed out to pay.  $2.00 later I was in the parking lot looking at the sun and a small black dot that was Venus passing in front of the sun.  How marvalous.  It was almost over when I was looking but not completly.  What a crazy wonderful place this world is... 
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	From Space.com  Get ready for a stellar date with Venus When, where and how to watch Tuesday’s transit  Go to space.com to see a chart of the sun's disk which shows how the June 8 transit will unfold as seen from New York City. The black disks indicate Venus' position at various times during the transit. There is a FREE VIDEO  NASA  By Joe Rao Night Sky Columnist Updated: 2:47 p.m. ET June 04, 2004  Venus has just finished up an excellent appearance in the evening sky that began in November. Now the planet has disappeared into the twilight, but it will make a brief and dramatic return appearance Tuesday.  On that day, more than half the world will get to see an exceedingly rare event: Venus crossing the face of the sun at what astronomers call inferior conjunction. Observers located over parts of eastern, central and the far northern sections of North America will be able to observe at least the closing stages of this striking celestial phenomenon.  The entire transit, as it is called, will be an east-to-west passage taking just over 6 hours and 12 minutes.    Safe viewing methods By far the safest way to view the transit is to construct a "pinhole camera."  The transit should be watched only with an appropriate solar filter — a solar filter that is sold by a reputable outlet of astronomical equipment. If your telescope comes with a filter that screws into the eyepiece, discard it immediately! Such filters have been known to crack under the intense heat of the sun’s magnified image.  Lastly, never look at the sun directly through your telescope, even through your smaller, finder scope. It is strongly advisable to cover the finder scope before the transit, so as to avoid looking through it accidentally.
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Sunday, June 6, My Mom and Jack picked up James and Heather, and the family and I met at McD's at the bridge and headed up to Boston to see the final day of the visiting Einstein Exhibit.  We took a detour to the Museum, aka, we got lost.  But we found it with a little help from Navigator Sara.  {Navigator is what my mom calls whoever sits in the front when we are going somewhere and are not sure how to get there.}  Into the Museum we went to find a huge line.  It went pretty fast, there were lots of people with strollers that take up a lot of room.  There was also a cute little girl who kept licking the entire railing while in line.  Her parents did nothing; it was kinda bad.  Anyway, we got tickets for the Exhibits and for the Mugar Omni Theatre's presentation of "Adrenaline Rush" the science of risk.  {This just encouraged my wanting to go sky diving even more, and discouraged any wanting my mom had.}    First up: the Einstein Exhibit.  Einstein was a brilliant thinker who reshaped our concepts of space and time, and a passionate humanitarian who used his celebrity to influence the politics of his era. Examining the theories, imagination, and persona of the 20th century's most influential scientist, this traveling exhibit Einstein presents a broad profile of the man and his achievements. Ever wonder what E=mc2 really implies about the physical universe?  There were interactive simulations and creative displays, which gave insights into the complexities of Einstein's theories about the nature of time, energy, gravity, and light.  It had handwritten scientific manuscripts, family photographs, Einstein's FBI file and report card, and other rare documents — many on display in the U.S. for the first time.   It was a good setup, they had experiments and letters he had written, and portions of his actual journals, quite neat.  On display was the actual letter he wrote Roosevelt that prompted the Manhattan Project.  There were also letters he had written to his wife and his cousin who later became his second wife.  Something I found to be particularly interesting was his relationship with women.  He had a daughter with his first wife out of wedlock; nothing is known about what happened to the daughter, but he later married the woman and she bore 2 sons.  After a rocky period, the wife, whose name I have forgotten, wanted a divorce, she felt science was Einstein's priority and his family came second.  She was also not fond of him having affairs, so she wanted a divorce.  Einstein tried to reconcile with his wife by writing a letter and giving her a list of things that she would have to do in order for him to remain married to her.  Some things on the list were:  science will be first, not her, and she would have to deal with that.  He wanted her to make him 3 meals a day, every day.  She was not to expect any kind of intimacy from him.  And she was expected to accept him having affairs.  It went over just as you or I might expect and they were soon divorced.  I spent about 2 1/2 hours in the exhibit, my family had to drag me out cause everyone was hungry and the twins were whining for food.  The family had finished looking at the exhibit about an hour before and was waiting for me.  At the end, there was a TV setup with physicists talking about superstring theory and taking over where Einstein left off with his Unified Theory.  I really wanted to watch the video, but outta time.  We ate, and then watched the Omni movie.  It was dizzying.  I did not throw up, go me!  But I did have to close my eyes a few times.  Plus when we got there, we were just about last getting in, so we had to sit in the front.    I am on a real science kick now.  I wanted to stop at a bookstore and get a bunch of books on the topic, especially Brian Greene's book, but there was not really time to stop, so I will begin with "Hyperspace" by Kaku.    After the museum we drove into Cambridge looking for ice cream.  We found a Baskin Robbins and a parking space and while walking there we saw an Au Bon Pain.  After debating on the sidewalk for about 5 minutes, we decided to get both, ice cream and croissants.  And after having our treats of the day, for the body and mind, we headed home. 
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	For those of you who don't know what Thedsday is... James and I were discussing how having a holiday on Monday throws off the feeling of the rest of the week.  {Not that there is anything wrong with a holiday Monday, they rock.}  For the rest of the week, the days seem mixed up and I have a hard time keeping track.  James and I were trying to make sense of the rest of the week.   Tuesday is definetly Monday and of course Friday is Friday.  But what about Wed. and Thurs.?  My feeling was that we skip Tues. all together and Wed. is Wed. and Thurs. is Thurs.  James brought up the good point that with only 4 days, there is no middle, therefor no hump day aka Wed.  The middle is now Wed. and Thurs.  James thought there was a Tues. and it was Wed.  And instead of skipping a day, Wed. and Thurs. combine into Thedsday.  So we have Mon., Tues., Thedsday, and Friday.  No wonder the week is confusing.  Thank God its Friday today, and a payday to boot.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	After work on Wednesday, played some bball, went home, showered and made myself some awful scrambled eggs which I threw out and replaced with Fruit Loops, a hearty dinner for sure.  After I headed back to Dartmouth for some ice cream at Dockside, and then off to the Immigrant.  It was kinda slow at first, the band was still getting ready.  I ordered myself a screwdriver {my drink of choice as of late} and sat down at a table with Ryan and Lisa.  The band started playing and they were awesome.  I had a couple beers thoughout the night while chatting, listening to great music and having a terrific time.  When we left at about 1:30, it was questioned if I could drive home or not.  I was ok to drive, something I do not take lightly is drinking and driving, if I am not ok, I don't drive.  This prompted me to think about how to tell when Sara is drunk.  So here I have the top 10 signs Sara is Suze.         10.  Mosquitos start biting me and are getting a buzz.    9.  I hurt myself without knowing it.  8.  The guy with the huge nose from "Piano" starts to look hot.   7.  Words are definetly slurred.    6.  I can focus better with one eye closed.  5.  Sara has 2 drinks in her hand.  4.  One of those drinks is still in the blender.  3.  I laugh at just about anything.  2.  I walk into things.  1.  I spend more time on the floor than I do standing up.    
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I don't remember as much of this dream as I did of the Bob Dylan dream.  But what I do remember is quite odd.  I dreamed this last night.  This time Bob Dylan was not my dad; he was not even in the dream.   Instead, the part of my dad was played by Dennis Quaid.  Yeah, odd.  My mom says we just watched something recently with him in it but I don't remember what we saw that he was in.  Anyhoo, he did not get mad at me like Bob Dylan did, instead we waltzed.  I don't even know how to waltz, but in the dream we Waltzed and it was beautiful.  That is the most vivid moment of the dream I have.  Also in the dream was Jay, yes, he came back to the shock of me, as well as Ryan and someone else, I think Eric W. but I am not totally sure.  Anyway I don't remember what else happened.  Or where we were.  Somewhere with a ballroom and yes there was music, and yes it was in color.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Now that I have cable, I've been taking advantage as much as I can.  It has caused me to be late to work, and to stay up till all hours.  It's great.  Anyway, my TV has a timer on it, so I have that as my alarm clock in the morning.  I set it to VH1 for 8 am.  For the past 8 weekdays I have woken up to  Maroon 5's  "She Will Be Loved".  I don't know what's up with VH1, they never seem to rotate their videos, maybe this was always the case, I don't know.    However, I am now a little obsessed with the song and video.  It's like I have to see it in the morning now.  But it does wake me right up, I open my eyes and turn to the TV so I can watch the video, and I sing.  It’s nice to wake up and start singing.  It’s a pretty cool video, and I love the song, however I think I may be biased because the song has been consistently in my head right at that time before I wake up, so I am in the process of waking up.  It’s that transition state in between sleep and awake and I think my mind is vulnerable then.  So I don’t know if I really like the song because I like it, or because my mind is in a vulnerable state.  Hmmm, maybe this makes no sense.    Yes, it makes no sense.    I’m going to stop now.  It’s sleepy time soon.    And I look forward to waking up singing to “She Will Be Loved”. 
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I saw  The Bourne Supremacy  last night.  I thought it was thrilling.  I loved  The Bourne Identity  and Matt Damon is excellent in both movies, as well as a hottie.  The theatre was packed, it was of course Tuesday at the Dartmouth mall (4 bucks for a show and free popcorn).  We were there slighly early, and got decent seats together.  I am not going to say to much, only that I was happy to see that Marie was the same actress as the first movie, German born Franka Potente.  In fact most of the original cast was back along with some new additions which spiced things up.  We still encounter Jason Bourne struggling with who he was in the past.  More flashbacks are present, as well as espionage and a terrific car chase.  If you loved the first movie you will surely love this movie as well.  It is action packed, and the plot requires your attention, so don't see it when you're sleepy.  Overall, 2 thumbs up from me, and I hope there is a third.    
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	This story came out last week, I didn't post it because I had other posts and was lazy, but I find it intriguing, so here it is.    Wed Jul 21, 4:17 PM ET 	 By SHAWN POGATCHNIK, Associated Press Writer   DUBLIN, Ireland - Famed astrophysicist Stephen Hawking said Wednesday that black holes, the mysterious massive vortexes formed from collapsed stars, do not destroy everything they consume and instead can fire out matter and energy "in a mangled form."   Hawking's radical new thinking, presented in a paper to the 17th International Conference on General Relativity and Gravitation in Dublin, capped his three-decade struggle to explain an elemental paradox in scientific thinking: How can black holes destroy all record of consumed matter and energy, as Hawking long believed, when subatomic theory says such elements must survive in some form?   Hawking's answer is that the black holes hold their contents for eons but themselves eventually deteriorate and die. As the black hole disintegrates, they send their transformed contents back out into the infinite universal horizons from which they came.   Previously, Hawking, 62, had held out the possibility that disappearing matter travels into a new parallel universe within the black hole — the very stuff of most visionary science fiction.   "There is no baby universe branching off, as I once thought. The information remains firmly in our universe," Hawking said in a speech to about 800 physicists and other scientists from 50 countries.   "I'm sorry to disappoint science fiction fans, but if information is preserved, there is no possibility of using black holes to travel to other universes," he said.   "If you jump into a black hole, your mass energy will be returned to our universe, but in a mangled form, which contains the information about what you were like, but in an unrecognizable state," he said with a smile, sparking laughter from the audience.   Hawking added, "It is great to solve a problem that has been troubling me for nearly 30 years, even though the answer is less exciting than the alternative I suggested."   In a humorous aside, Hawking settled a 7-year-old bet made with Caltech astrophysicist John Preskill, who insisted in 1997 that matter consumed by black holes couldn't be destroyed. He presented Preskill a favored reference work "Total Baseball, The Ultimate Baseball Encyclopedia" after having it specially flown over from the United States.   "I had great difficulty in finding one over here, so I offered him an encyclopedia of cricket as an alternative," Hawking said, "but John wouldn't be persuaded of the superiority of cricket."   Later, Preskill said he was very pleased to have won the bet, but added: "I'll be honest, I didn't understand the talk." Like other scientists there, he said he looked forward to reading the detailed paper that Hawking is expected to publish next month.   Hawking pioneered the understanding of black holes — the matter-consuming vortexes created when stars collapse — in the mid-1970s. He has previously insisted that the holes emit radiation but never cough up any trace of matter consumed, a view that conflicts with subatomic theory and its view that matter can never be completely destroyed.   Hawking, a mathematics professor at Cambridge University, shot to international fame with his best-selling book "A Brief History of Time," which sought to explain to a general audience the most complex aspects of how the universe works.   Despite being virtually paralyzed and forced to rely on a wheelchair with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis since his mid-20s, Hawking travels the world on speaking engagements. He communicates by using a hand-held device to select words on his wheelchair's computer screen, then sending them to a speech synthesizer.   The slow process of constructing answers meant that, in the press conference that followed his paper, Hawking was able to answer only two questions in a half-hour. The final questioner asked him what problem he intended to tackle next, now that he had solved the paradox of the black hole.   "I don't know," Hawking quickly replied, bringing the house down with laughter.   For more  Hawking mania  check out his site, www.hawking.org.uk   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I was so siked about going to the beach on Sunday.  The tide was perfect for boogie boarding, and there was a breeze, which added to the roughness in the water.  The waves were fantastic on Saturday, however it was cloudy and kind of cold, especially to be swimming in the Atlantic.  Ok, basically I was a wuss and didn't go in the water.  Which was disappointing when I woke up Sunday to find more clouds and cool weather.  Leah called me to hang out and at this point I still hadn't made the decision to not go to the beach.  However, it became more and more obvious that it was not a beach day as the morning went on.    What to do, what to do.  Ohh, I know, go to P-town.  Ryan decided to come down and hang out for the day, so he, Leah, Dana, and I headed out to P-town for lunch and hanging out.  My mom hooked us up with a free pass for an unlimited number of people to climb Pilgrim Monument.   {In case you didn't know, the Pilgrim's landed in P-town first, and then went to Plymouth.  It is quite a fight; I mean debate, between the two towns.}   I drove us out to P-town, and Dana told us we could park on his uncle's land which is awesome, cause I really didn't want to pay for parking, and they have recently made all the free spots, sticker only parking.  We parked on the land and headed for Commercial Street, the center for P-town.  I had wanted to eat at Mojo's cause I could get food cheaper, and I love their food, one moment please...  {mmmmm steak burrito, mmmmmm humus sandwich, mmmmmm french fries...}  Ok, I'm back.  Instead I was outvoted and we went over to Subway, which had a line out the door, and only 1 person working!  It was craziness, 1 person to make the sandwiches AND ring everyone up.  They need to take some lessons from Dartmouth and learn the sandwich making assembly line.  After a good 25 minutes of waiting, we had our sandwiches, and headed over to the pier to sit.    After lunch, we walked around looking in the shops.  We found some very cool T-shirts, ones with Bush quotes that were hilarious, others with funny sayings like "1 tequila, 2 tequila, 3 tequila, floor" or "Ever ride a fat boy?"  It was quite funny.  I also saw the greatest hat.  I fell in love with this hat; it was a Red Sox hat that was the most perfect shade of green.  It rules, I didn't buy it cause it was $20 but I have my eyes open for it.    In another store we say these zodiac magnets that had various qualities listed according to your sign.  Apparently Ryan is desired by all {women and men}, Leah is sexy as hell, and I am needy, overly-imaginative, moody, and it basically said I was lucky if I could get through the day without anyone throwing dirt at me.  Seriously, there were no good qualities on this magnet, every one was bad.  It made me angry.  But then I reasoned that maybe the guy or lady that wrote these had an ex who was a cancer and fucked them up.  That made me feel a little better.  But still, no good qualities?  I like to think I have at least 1...   We didn't see too many men dressed as women, altho we did see a fat clown.  And we didn't climb the tower, and we didn't go upstairs in Shop Therapy to the XXX Adult Only, have your ID ready section {a lot of old people did tho}, but I think we had a good time anyway.  I know I did.    After P-town, we went home, and hung at the house for a bit, but I wanted to show Ryan the beach, so I convinced everyone to drive over to the beach, we checked out LeCounts, and then Newcomb's, with a drive past Long pond and Wellfleet Center where the delinquents as usual were gathered on the front lawn of the town hall.  We swung by the pier, and then back home to watch the sox and eat food.    It was a good day, not a beach day, but awesome nonetheless.     P.S.  Monday I bought flip-flops for $1.25!   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Friday night we went to the Comber,  urlLink The Beachcomber  for a "Creole party".  The band there was,  urlLink Buckwheat Zydeco  they started at 10:40 and we went "down to the Bayou" a lot.  But before the band we were watching the Red Sox game, it was quite intense.  I'm sure you know the outcome and if you don't I don't wanna talk about it.  In the 8th inning, we decided that if the Red Sox lose, we would do Tequila shots.   {Course if the Sox won, we were also going to do Tequila shots.}   After we found out Tequila shots were 5 bucks, I KNOW!!!, we decided 1 was enough, well Karl had 2.    Then the band started.  They rocked the house.  The best instrument ever: the washing board.  That guy played it like there was no tomorrow.  He was awesome.  The funniest part of the evening tho, was the young woman who offered me her large pink stuffed penis toy.  That's right; she had a stuffed toy, like a teddy bear, only in the shape of a penis.  I politely declined.  And she stuck it under her arm.  She and her 2 friends were quite drunk.  That place must make a killing.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	So we had a cinnamon challenge at work Thursday.  You might ask what a cinnamon challenge is.  Well, for the past 2 weeks we have had challenges at work, {each week being more challenging than the last} and this week was no exception.  The challenge: eat a tablespoon of cinnamon all at once.  It does not seem hard but once you try it you find that eating 34 times the amount of cinnamon recommended for 4 servings of chili cannot be done.  Why?  Because the cinnamon makes a fast exit out of your body after 1.2 seconds.  This means it comes out your mouth and nose.  The competitors were Derek, James, Ryan and I.  {I could not be outdone by the men.}  We all spit up a cinnamon cloud and were coughing hysterically.  We rushed for the water and spit brown.  Our eyes turned red and bloodshot, and our noses ran.  And when we blew our noses, cinnamon chunks came out too.  In fact for 3 hours after the challenge, I was still blowing cinnamon chunks out of my nose.    While I was the weakest competitor, I was the only one who lost their lunch, looking back now, I am glad I did it.  Although I took over 12 hours for me to be glad I did it.  I had a burning in my throat for the rest of Thursday.  Derek had sniffed some in, and his nose was burning.  Friday morning on the way to my dentist appointment, I stopped at one of my favorite places, The Common Ground, for a banana smoothie.  I have these before, they are very delicious and very banana-y, however, I could only taste the cinnamon.  I think trying this challenge has heightened my taste of cinnamon, I am not surprised.  I have, however, concluded that we are all idiots at work.  This challenge was just stupid, please do not try it.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I learned a very valuable lesson last night.    No more triple sec for Sara.    It fucks her up royally.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I wonder how many people have a list of things they want to do before they die?  It seems pretty common, I bet a lot of people have one; whether it's in their head or written down.  I recently found this site online entitled   urlLink "390 Things to Do Before You Die"  and it is the top 10 in 39 cities.  While it makes it easily accessible, all the cities are in the US, it is also rather conceited to think that everything one should experience before death exists in the US.  The list is mostly restaurants, parks, and historic places, {for those with quite a bit of dough I might add} while some might be included on my list, activities, and books would also be included.  Here are this site's top 10 in the US:  1.  Wrigley Field- Chicago, Ill.  Sip an Old Style and cheer on the Cubbies from the lively bleacher seats of this historic stadium.  2.  Golden Gate Bridge - San Francisco, Calif. Walk across the bridge at sunrise; just don't forget your comfortable shoes for the two-mile trek.  3.  Mardi Gras - New Orleans, La. Witness the revelry: Ride a Mardi Gras float on Fat Tuesday.  4.  Willie Nelson's 4th of July Picnic - Austin, Texas Celebrate the U.S. of A. singing along to "Whiskey River" with Willie and 30,000 of his closest friends.  5.  Tournament of Roses Rose Parade - Pasadena, Calif. Camp out on Colorado Boulevard on New Year's Eve and wake up to the sounds of a marching band.  6.  Empire State Building - New York, NY Meet the love of your life at midnight atop New York's most romantic skyscraper, a la "An Affair to Remember" and "Sleepless in Seattle."  7.  Pat's King of Steaks - Philadelphia, Pa. On a Saturday night at 2am, wait in line for a cheese steak at the birthplace of Philly's signature sandwich.  8.  Pike Place Market - Seattle, Wash. Grab a latte at the flagship Starbucks and watch the beloved public market open for the day.  9.  Indianapolis Motor Speedway - Indianapolis, Ind. Walk 16th Street the night before the Indianapolis 500--it's Mardi Gras, a bachelor party and an insane asylum rolled into one.   10.  Wayne Newton - Las Vegas, Nev. After a 12-hour gambling binge at the Stardust, join a cult-like crowd of fans to hear the croonings of Mr. Las Vegas.   None of these would have been on my list, but looking at it, I think I would include #3, #4, #7.  I've been the the Golden Gate, not walking across tho.  I've also been to the top of the Empire State Building.    This is a list that keeps on growing.  Some items on my "Things I Want to Do Before I Die" list are:  parachute, parasail, swim in the Indian Ocean, and the Gulf of Mexico, camp in Baja California, drive across the country, read all the books on my reading list, see the Louve, snorkel in the caribbean, see the Eagles in concert, write a book, build a telescope, have a drink in the Viper room, travel {there are so many places I want to travel too, too many to list right now.}  I could go on and on.    Let's just say I better not die anytime soon.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Happy 35th anniversary to the astronauts of Apollo 11, Neil Armstrong, Buzz Aldrin and Michael Collins, and to NASA.  Thirty-five years ago these 3 astronauts landed on the moon and the day went down in history as the day "men from the planet Earth first set foot upon the moon."    To read more about the mission check  urlLink this  out   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	For some, this might just be another ordinary day. But for me, the ides of July are special, it is the day of my birth.&nbsp; It was really cool, I got a suprise phone call at 12:15am on July 15th, my first happy birthday wishes.&nbsp; I went to bed around 1 and woke up @ 7:30 because the cable people were coming between 8 and 11.&nbsp; I hoped they would come early and get it finished with and sure enough, the guy came at 8:15 and was finished at 8:25.&nbsp; Sara has cable!!&nbsp; It's awesome.&nbsp; I watched Roseanne and then The Golden Girls.&nbsp; I decided to dress up for my birthday, so I wore my black halter dress with pink flowers on it and a blue 3/4 sleeve shirt.&nbsp; I had a Hawaiian&nbsp;Lay in my hair, and dangly earrings.&nbsp; To make the ensamble complete, I wanted to get some new flip flops.&nbsp; So I headed over to TJ Maxx and found some very cute flip flops for $4!&nbsp; They are as close to going bare foot as one can get.&nbsp; My feet love them.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  And so over to work I went.&nbsp; I know I'm a dork, going to work on my birthday when I don't have to, but&nbsp;after you read about my work day, you'll understand.&nbsp; I went in around noon, and worked for a bit.&nbsp; On Thursday's we have a pizza party, I mean meeting.&nbsp; I went down to the meeting to find cupcakes with lit candles in them for my b-day, it was so sweet.&nbsp; I blew out the candles and we began eating pizza.&nbsp; After the pizza and some talking, it was time for this week's challenge.&nbsp; How many&nbsp;sour gummy fish can you eat in 60 seconds.&nbsp; Now these fish are&nbsp;large, they're not like the dinky little swedish fish, these are the Great White's of the gummy fish family.&nbsp; The only rule was you must put the fish into your mouth whole.&nbsp; We got set up, and then Sharon added another rule, after the 60 seconds, you must follow the gummy fish with a shot of Campari.&nbsp; Campari is a very bitter Italian liquor.&nbsp; And so the challenge began, one by one we shoved gummy fish into our mouths chewing with a rapid fire pace and then had to bear the shot of Campari.&nbsp; The faces that were made while drinking the Campari&nbsp;was hilarious.&nbsp; Sharon was the winner with 5 gummy fish.&nbsp; I had 1.5, it was pretty sad.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  After the challenge we sat around talking and trying to get rid of the "taste of death" (as Derek called it) that the Campari left.&nbsp; After a bit, someone decided that we should go see Anchorman RIGHT NOW.&nbsp; I was in the bathroom but when I came out everyone was running around the office getting ready because it was 4:40 and the movie started at 4:45 in New Bedford.&nbsp; And so James, Ryan, Derek, Jake and I piled into cars and raced off to New Bedford to see the movie.&nbsp; We got there at 4:55, not bad at all and we all ran into the theatre.&nbsp; James bought my ticket since it was my b-day, how very nice of him.&nbsp; Thanks James!&nbsp; Anchorman is sooo funny.&nbsp; I had already seen it, but&nbsp;I think it's funnier the second time.&nbsp; Brick is awesome.&nbsp; After the movie we went back to the office to get our belongings, and say hi to Ed.&nbsp; It was about 6:30; we then parted ways after the greatest work day.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Ryan and I went back to Ryan's house to decide&nbsp;where to get food.&nbsp; I&nbsp;called my friends Amanda and Mark to see if they wanted to get food, they did, so over to Smokey Bones we went.&nbsp; My aim was to get drunk and have fun.&nbsp; I started off with a beer.&nbsp; Mark then decided we should all try shots of&nbsp;WooWoo's.&nbsp; Having never heard of them, I was game.&nbsp; So we&nbsp;all took shots of woowoo's.&nbsp;&nbsp;The shot was large, and they are kinda like red-headed sluts.&nbsp; When the shots came I ordered a Long Island Iced Tea so I would have something to wash it down with.&nbsp; Halfway through that super giggly Sara made an appearance, aka Suze.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  After dinner Amanda and Mark headed home and Ryan and I went over to Bridge Street for more drinking and fun.&nbsp; I had a couple more beers there.&nbsp; I tasted Blueberry beer, it was good for a sip, but I would not want a whole one on&nbsp;my own.&nbsp; You know you're drunk when you go to the restroom and have to use the side of the stall to hold your head up.&nbsp; Shortly after that we left; it was about 1:30.&nbsp; We debated whether or not I was able to drive home, we reached my car,&nbsp;and as I was getting out of his car to get into mine, I feel out of his car onto the pavement and lay there laughing and looking at his hub caps.&nbsp; This was the concluding moment that I could not drive;&nbsp; not the perpetual giggling nor the scrambled sentences nor the stumbled walking.    &nbsp;   It was quite possibly the best birthday&nbsp;ever.     
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Monday night Jet rocked the Strand in Providence. I'd never been there before, the previous location or this one. I was very impressed. There were at least 2 bars, 2 that I saw, and they had little tables set up with stools and a small bar like counter with stools that faced the stage right behind the sound table, and pretty close to the stage as well. When we got there, there was a line down the street and around the corner. First thought: damn, should have gotten here earlier. But when we got inside, it was pretty empty. Ryan grabbed a spot at the counter by the sound table, and I grabbed stools. It was a perfect spot. We could see what the sound people were doing, we had a great view of the stage, and seats. The Everyone's came on first, they were ok. The next group Sloan, was better but I wished they had done some covers.   Then finally Jet came on. Right before they did I went to the restroom and on the way out and back to my seat, I accidentally got myself in between 2 large drunk guys who were just about to duke it out. I immediately removed myself from that situation and went back to my seat. From there we could see the playlist, very nice. I was especially looking forward to "Look What You've Done", "Get What You Need", and "Get Me Outta Here." All were on the set list {it was pretty much just the album and the Spiderman 2 song.} Each of those were great, but I think my favorites were "Look What You've Done", "Move On", and "Cold Hard Bitch." The lead singer was on crutches, but that didn't stop him from climbing on an amp and playing guitar. I was impressed.&nbsp;  Oh, before the show, while we were waiting for it to start, I got a free poster while standing in line, and I bought a t-shirt once inside, it's kick ass.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	While it's kinda stupid, I did the magic birthday zodiac game, not very magic at all, pick your birth month, and the animal that corresponds to the day of your birth and there you go.  Here's what mine said.    Not only are you attractive and popular, you’re considerate and easygoing!  Plus you make friends very easily.  You’re cool, smart and aware of yourself.    http://new.feelgoodpages.com/funpages/view.cfm/4802   Here is another quiz.  The Magical Name Acronym Generator.  {Also not so magic.}  Apparently I'm a refined kinda kinky      S     Silly       A     Altruistic       R     Revolutionary       A     Astounding       &nbsp;      K     Kinky       A     Arty       T     Tempting       H     Handy       R     Refined       Y     Yum       N     Noisy       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I was a total beach bum this weekend, and loved it.  Saturday, it was beautiful Round Hill beach that occupied my time.  I divided my beach morning by swimming, reading my new issue of Discover, laying in sun, walking, and playing frizbee.  It was great.   Sunday I headed over to Swift's Beach down the street from Amanda's house.  She spoils me.  I got there and she and Mark were cooking hot dogs and corn on the grill.  We then watched some poker championship, then walked down to the beach and lay in the sun and swam in the water.  When we got back, Amanda and I went to the liquor store, got some orange dream and went back to her house where Mark was cooking cheeseburgers on the grill.  We ate macaroni salad, cheeseburgers, and green salad.  Yuum, yum.  Afterward Amanda and I watched a weird movie and looked at Glamour magazine.    Weekends like this need to be more frequent
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	So I have an alter-ego, {always wanted an alter-ego, as well as an arch-enemy, but those are easier to get.}  She is 20, lives in WV, and has a baby girl.  She has the same name as me, and her blog is also absolutsara.  I am very intrigued.    Here is a quote from my alter-ego: I guess people think just because I'm band geek Sara I can't have sex.. ohhhh shizzle....   She is very white ghetto.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Apparently Wellfleet sucks this year with fireworks.  They stopped showing the fourth show, because of clouds, alright, understandable.  But when it was time for the makeup show, a small fire happened near the fireworks, and they all exploded on the ground.  So no more fireworks in Wellfleet this year.   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Here's some advice from personal experience this morning.  Don't go to the grocery store when you're in a funky mood, absolutely starving, and only have 6 dollars.    You will end up buying organic yogurt, taboule salad, and vegetarian sushi, and charging it to your credit card.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I was feelin kinda blah and sad yesterday, {stupid girl feelings} and really didn't want to go home, but alas it's inevitable.  I went home made some tomato soup, got a bubble bath, and then planned on hanging out watching movies.  But I was siked when Eric called me to hang out.  I don't see him much so it was a suprise.  I said, yes, let's go drinking.  He picked me up and we debated where to go, after a bit of driving around we decided on 99.  Good 'ole 99.  We got drinks and just sat and chilled out.  I didn't get trashed like I wanted to, but it was a good time; and just what I needed.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Today has all the making of a serious day. You are overly sensitive now and your feelings are weighing heavy on your mind. In spite of this, however, there is cause for optimism. If you are willing to move past your own self-created restrictions, there is a chance to do something meaningful. Serious consideration is fine but be ready to take that chance. Impulsive action can get you out of your rut.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	CANCER (June 21-July 22)  The emphasis these days is on some form of your public life or career competing with your private life, the life inside the shell of your home or consciousness or circle of friends. Quite honestly, it's your smaller world that is more interesting, and more worthy of attention. Though you'll need to sort out the characters: the married woman; the other woman; the adventurer; the father figure. Everyone is in greater harmony than you may think, and if all the lines of communication are left open or deliberately opened, somehow it turns out to be a great month for both great sex and emotional bonding. 
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	This will be short but has been bothering me.   Sometimes I wonder what the fuck is wrong with the judicial system in this country??  Here is a perfect example, a person has 7 counts of assault and battery, {the assault and battery being against this person's young children.}   The result?    3 years probation, and a $50. fine.  WTF? 
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Sunday was absolutely gorgeous.  I woke up, hung in the house for a bit, went down to the bay to swim, lay on the beach in the sun, evening out my burn, and came home and sat outside reading, and eating cheese and crakers with a Sam Adams.  It was great.  Then we ate, and headed off to the fireworks.  This time, they were in P-town.  We left a little early to get the seats we wanted, sitting on a concrete wall that connects the 2 wharfs with our legs hanging over the side and the fireworks directly ahead shooting over the harbor.  We parked on route 6 took our usual Fourth walk thru the cemetary, and were able to get the seats we wanted.  Jack and Karl left sweatshirts to save their places and then went to walk around.  Best conversation:    Me:  You guys should act gay while you walk around. Jack:  Yeah! Mom:  Oh god, people I know will see you and call me up saying, "I didn't know about your son." Karl:  We should find some of your mom's friends and act all huggy. Me:  Yeah, at least you would not get hit on Karl:  No, but we might get asked for a three-way. Me:  Ewww.  They left, no idea if they acted "huggy".  My mom then left me to go get us some iced coffee's, and I guarded our seats.  When she returned, I went over to get us some fried dough.  Mmmmm, fried dough.  I waited in line for what felt like a bazillion minutes.  Finally got the fried dough, and went back to our seats.    The fireworks started soon after, and they were fantastic.  Right in front of us, and boats nearby were lit up.  It was a terrific show that lasted about a half hour.  My favorite were the orange fireworks and the ones that looked like Sideshow Bob's hair.  It was the best show of the weekend.    P-town was sooo crowded.  They closed the main street, commercial street, and people were packed in the streets, up and down.  There was obvious drinking, people acting stupid, plus you could tell from the faces they made after they drank their "water".  As we were leaving, these 5 guys were in the street wearing only small towels around their waists, and exclaimed "Make your holiday better with some penis."  I just started cracking up.  {They were advertising their show, "Naked Boys Singing" by the way; there was a reason for their almost nakedness.}  Driving home was also nuts, tons of traffic, a drunk pair of speed racers, they worried me a bit, but we made it home safe and sound after a wonderful fourth.  Hope everyone had a terrific fourth as well, and got to see some fireworks!
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Orleans had their firework show on Saturday night off Rock Harbor.  Figuring it would be super super crowded, my mom and I went over to First Encounter Beach in Eastham, after a stop at Ben & Jerry's, to find that also crowded.  We had to park on the road and we never made it to the actual beach, we stopped along the road because we could see and the show was about to start.  We were quite far away, and there were bugs, but the fireworks were awesome.  It was very different from the directly over your head show in Wellfleet, and it was a bit far, but still a good show nontheless!  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I love fireworks, absolutely love em.  So of course I love the fourth, it's one of my favorite holidays.  What's not to love?  BBQ's, parades, festivities, fireworks, family, summer, and most people have an upbeat attitude about our nation, and the freedoms I am greatful for.  So fortunetly for me, Wellfleet had a fireworks show on Friday, Orleans has one on Saturday, and P-town has one on Sun.    Wellfleet Fireworks.   These are always the best in my mind.  First of all they are shot off from the end of Indian Neck, so we are able to just take a walk on the beach down to the fireworks.  On the way, we always run into people we know, and our party gets larger.  We sit as close as we can, a.k.a. we keep going till the fire chief says "stop".  We set up blankets and/or chairs, and just lay on the beach and the fireworks are directly overhead.  I mean directly.  Last night there was a point where the fireworks seemed like they would land on us.  We were far enough away so they would not, but they had that illusion.    Last night however, some fog began to set in and along with the smoke that accompanies the fireworks, it was getting harder to see.  At 9:30, after 15 minutes of fireworks, they stopped.  We knew this could not be the end because Wellfleet always has a huge finale.  We waited, 10 minutes later we turned to our blanket neighbors, the fire chief, and asked what was up.  Apparently it was too foggy and they were waiting for the firework smoke to clear before making a decision about whether or not to continue.  The final decision was not to continue, it was quite foggy, and apparently people watching from the other side of the bay could not see anything.  So it was the best decision, altho that meant a postponement of the fireworks.  The date remains unknown.  I predict sometime in Aug.    But the fireworks we did see, just fantastic!  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Last night was opening night for Spiderman 2, and oh yes, I had tickets.  I saw the 9:55 showing in the Seekonk theatre, have not not gotten lost getting there yet.  We wanted to get there early, after dinner, {a terrific fancy place in Warren RI called the Nat Porter Inn, the food was delicious and it had a fantastic atmosphere} but we got there just on time.  We had to wait in the huge line with 1 person selling tickets, even though I had already bought tics online.  I thought the theatre was going to be packed and we would have to sit in the very front or somewhere.  The ideal seats were already picked out in our minds; the front row of the second section where the most feet room is, and where there is a wall to put your feet on.  Not expecting to sit there, we walked into the theatre to find 5 seats on the isle in prime real estate!  Yes!!    It really was not crowded, not at all like I expected.  The previews were already playing, and were almost over when we sat down.  The movie was quite enjoyable.  I have not read Spiderman comics, so I had no idea of the plot going into the movie; but I was impressed.  I liked the villian of the second movie more than the Green Goblen, he just seemed more evil, and the whole premise for his evilness added to him being the favorite.  I was very glad for Spiderman in the end, he got what he wanted, the girl.  It took a while for things to finally turn up Spidey.  I was also extremely glad to find all the original characters return.  It's just the same when you have a sequel with a different actor playing a character; even if it's only a minor part.    All in all, it was an awesome night.  As was expected.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	It was party at the Dell time last night.  One of my co-workers was having a party, and all were invited, including a lot of random people he didn't even know.  I met Ryan and Mary-Kate at the club, and we headed over to the Dell for some drinking.  Derek had a keg, but it was gone by 11:30.  He was pretty trashed when we got there.  We had to catch up.  We got some keg beer and drank downstairs while talking to Derek and his girlfriend, who is such an awesome girl by the way, we love her.  Soon after we smartened up and drank next to the keg, that way we could refill easily.  It was at this point we decided James should be here, and Ryan called him.  He was a bit tipsy, as was Derek who was telling him what to say.    After we went back downstairs to watch beer pong.  After beer pong, we went out to play whiffle ball.  Yes, drunk whiffle ball.  But the best part was this kid, ed  {I called him ed, derek called him the prez, who knows what his name really is}  who was 17 and he was sooo trashed.  It was his first time getting drunk, and you could soo tell he was out of it.  He was our outfielder for a while, till he wondered away.  During the game Ryan, trying to do some sort of fancy windup for his pitch, spilled beer on himself.  After whiffle ball, the games continued inside with flip cup.  I like this game.  At first our team was not doing so well, ed was on it and I blame him, but when he left we were almost unstoppable.  At this point things were kinda confusing.  I'm sure Derek remembers nothing, it will be fun to fill him in.  I remember him on a bed with 3 girls, and sure enough, I took a picture with my phone.  By this time flip cup had stopped and we were just sitting around talking and trying to sober up.  About an hour later Ryan and I left and I dropped him at his car at the CCNB and went home and just crashed on my bed.  It was about 4.    
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I am Category IV - The Musketeer.       Category IV - The Musketeer     You have a small, highly edited social group, and you like it that way.    urlLink   What Type of Social Entity are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	Last night it was off to Pawtucket for the only reason one would go to Pawtucket, to see the Paw Sox.  I've never been to a PawSox game so I was quite excited, plus it was free hat night to boot!  Rock on.  Ryan, Dulcina, and Ryan's friends Erik and Jenn, and I went to the game.  I was thrilled to see Brian Daubauch aka Brian "Cheech" Daubauch, which brings me to the title of this post.  For some reason all but 2 of the Paw Sox players looked Hispanic when their faces were shown on the big screen.  Daubauch looked the most Hispanic, therefore is the leader of the Pawtucket HisSox and aptly named Brian "Cheech" Daubauch.  The Sox didn't win, even though they played a really good game early on.  In the top of the 8th the Clippers went ahead, they tied it on a balk in the 7th.  The Clippers are the affiliate of the New York Yankees.    It was a fun night though.  We had park food, beers, made dirty jokes, made fun of people, and just enjoyed the overall feeling of summertime in New England at a ballpark.  There is nothing like it.  
    	 

    	
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
	I'm extremely tired, so this post will just be a preview of the awesome weekend I had.  Awesome is the only thing that can describe this weekend.  A friend had a party on Friday night, so Friday after work I headed to CT.  Betsy sure knows how to throw a party.  Here is an overview: hot tub till 5am, drinking (see below for the list of drinks that I can remember), drunk strip asshole with ridiculous rules (good thing it was drunk, no one noticed I kept putting on more shirts and earrings counted as an item of clothing.  Needless to say, there was no nakedness), drunk swimming, good food, good music, getting 3 hours of sleep, lots of visiting and chatting and awesome people.    Saturday the fun continued, I woke up at 8 after 3 hours of sleep and soon headed home.  I was home for a whole 20 minutes before going to Boston.  We took the T in to Fenway and got a free Fenway tour where we touched the green monster that Johnny Damon runs into.  After that we headed to Newbury street and I got my green red sox hat for $11, and a fedora for $13.  We walked more on Newbury St. and visited CW.  Then we went over to The Wrap for a great lunch.  Then over to the Hatch Shell for free great music at the last dispatch show where I sweat like 8 pounds, like for real, it was sooo hot, and I was sooo gross.  After 3 hours of music, we left for home.  Once in Fall River I had a d'Angelo's #9 that totally hit the spot, and the best shower I've had in my life (I was soooo sweaty, sticky, and dirty), and to top it off some sleep.  Friday/Sat. morning drinks 2 Coors lights 2 Mudslides 2 Alabama Slamma's 1 Gin and tonic minus the tonic plus vodka 1 shot of Jolly Rancher 1 shot of vodka 1 something good that was white 2 Screwdrivers 
    	 

    	
</post>


</Blog>