<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > International > Middle East > From the Editors: The Times and Iraq   In an unusual editorial, The New York Times says it made mistakes when it reported on weapons of mass destruction in Iraq. The paper found that, in the months before the war, reporters and editors relied too heavily on Iraqi defectors and U.S. government officials eager to promote a war.   -NPR's Steve Inskeep and Tom Rosentiel, director of the Project for Excellence in Journalism at the Pew Center.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ESPN.com - TENNIS/FRENCH04 - Agassi upset by qualifier at French Open   My man goes down.  Could it be for the final time at the French Open?  Say it isn't so.  I'm disappointed that I still haven't managed to make it out to a Grand Slam tournament.  Maybe we'll make it out to Flushing Meadows, New York for the US Open at the end of the Year.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BBC NEWS | World | Americas | Bush defends his vision for Iraq   "[the President has] lowered expectations, troops are not coming home... dark days lie ahead... The president is in a jam, and he realizes it,"  -Bob Woodward, Author of "Plan of Attack" (interview with Larry King after the Monday evening address.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Air America Radio   What happened in this negotiated settlement?  I'm suffering some serious withdrawal.  Streaming over the internet just doesn't cut it for me.  I used to listen to Liz, Rachel, Chuck D, Al and even Randi in the car while crisscrossing the Chicagoland area.  Satellite radio is a commitment I'm not willing to make at this point--besides that's what corporate America and the FCC would like us all to do, pay for radio!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Musee de Louvre&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Send your message of peace at this monument in the shadows of the Eiffel Tower.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Eiffel Tower pokes into the fog.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    La Tour Eiffel et ma cherie&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Place de la Bastille, (Paris, France)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    It's me. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The love of my life. I took this picture after the two of us had dinner at The Tug restaurant.  It's sunset on the coast in Swakopmund, Namibia in February of 2004.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My gradeschool teacher in 4th and 5th grades used to buzz the office via the intercom saying, "Control central, control central, this is BLAH BLAH BLAH, come in control central."  The office staff never quite figured out how to respond.  It makes me laugh thinking about it even today.  (She's the same teacher that made me play Oberon, King of the Fairies in a fifth grade performance of "A Midsummer Night's Dream--I just wanted to be a stage hand.)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BBC NEWS | World | South Asia | MSF suspends work in Afghanistan   I'm really proud of the work that Lauren is doing for MSF in Angola, but I can't help but worry about her safety, especially with Bush making friends for Americans and aid workers all over the globe.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BBC NEWS | World | Americas | CIA chief George Tenet quits   This is the man that said that the case against Saddam Hussein with respect to WMD was a "slam-dunk."  You'll have plenty of time to spend with your family, George, because your career in Intelligence is OVER.  Lament over your mistakes and prepare notes for your memoirs--sure to be a bestseller.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>