<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm 17, and I don't drive.  How sad is that.  My younger sister is going to get her restricted on Wednesday.  On June 10th I'll have to go get my permit renewed for the second time.  It's really depressing, but I'm not ready to drive.  My dad thinks something is wrong with me.  He thinks I'm scared, but I'm not scared of driving.  However, I just realized recently the truth in what he said.  I'm not scared of driving, but I'm so scared of growing up.  I don't feel old enough or ready to grow up.  Growing up means responsibly and making choices about my life that I'm not ready to make.  Driving for me is a major step in my life that means I'm one more step to independence.  Every year on my birthday I think I'll magically feel grown up.  It has yet to happen.  So yes dad I'm scared, but I'm scared of growing up, not driving.  Those are my depressing thoughts of the day.  I'm also afraid of what a idiot I'll look like going to get my permit renewed for the second time.  I just need to grow up whether I want to or not, but it's so hard. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to a cast party last night.  There were all adults and me with my two friends.  I must say we were getting pretty bored until the adults started drinking.  Drunk people are really funny.  Well Andrew, Austin, and I were outside sitting by the pool.  Austin decided he was gonna start hitting this huge spider that was in the pool with the car keys.  He wasn't expecting it to latch on to the keys so Austin started flinging the keys to get the spider off. Well, in the process he dropped the keys in the deep end of the pool.  We were able to get the keys to the shallow end by hitting it with a pole and then I volunteered to try to grab it with my toes and got soaked in the process.  It was a lot of fun.  Well that's about it for now cause I don't feel like writing everything else that happened.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            urlLink What Classic Movie Are You?    urlLink personality tests by similarminds.com  
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had the weirdest dream last night.    I started off at school in the lunch room with veronica, but we were in the dark.  Our friends had ditched us so we tried to find somewhere else to sit.  After that everything got screwed up.  I was running down a hall trying to get away from someone.  I was looking for one of my friends (no one I know).  I found her in a costume room, and she stared to show me all of the things she had made.  I tried to get her to be quiet so this person wouldn't find me.  All of a sudden the person I was running from jumped out in front of my  hiding place.  We started fighting each other with giant clever looking things.  I ended up stabbing her with a sword (I have no idea how to I got the sword).  So my friend and I were gonna try to get away, but then just as we were about to run out of the room this other person showed up.  This person was either a robot that was supposed to look like the person chasing me, the twin, or a clone.  Well the person called for help because we'd be found.  My friend and I had just enough time to get through a door and run down a few flights of stairs.  I was getting really scared cause I could hear the people behind us.  I looked down the stairs and saw a doctors office kinda thing where they do evil experiments on people.    Then I woke up. It was all very aliasish.  If anyone wants to take a stab at what the dream might mean I'd love to hear it.  My version is I'm running away from someone because I'm scared (duh), and I try to get away but they'll always show up trying to catch me. That's about all that I have so far so...   Moving on, I went to see The Day After Tomorrow last night.  Very good movie by the way.  I really want to study meteorology or something like that in college, but that won't happen sadly.  I gave Andrew his birthday present last night.  I got him fuzzy dice for his car he just got and gift cards to eat and see a movie.  That's why we went to the movie because he could actually afford to go do something.  The one bad thing about the movie was that I really felt like I was a part of it.  I haven't decided if it was because the movie was just that could or because it was just that cold.  That's about it except I went by Poor Richards to see about an intership, and it's looking good for me.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gah people drive me crazy.  One day I'm just go freak out on someone.  I can understand complaining about a teacher if you actually try in the class, but it's really hard.  Yet there are those people who do nothing then they can't understand why they don't pass the class.  Open your eyes people.  Who would ever believe that I would defend the devil teacher to anyone, but I did it.  Well, I feel better now.  On a another note, my day was extremely boring.  I woke up, looked at the computer screen for awhile, and then I watched tv.  The exciting life of Laura.  I wouldn't trade it for the world.  I've gotta learn to drive. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to see Shrek 2 again.  I went last night with Veronica and Ryan.  Then Veronica came over here to spend the night.  It was fun for awhile then my sister made us play Scene It until 2 in the morning (that's late for us).  Then we were gonna take weird pictures of us being stupid, but that didn't work out too well because we started watching Young Frankenstein.  Then we stopped so I could come over here and tell everyone what we did because I didn't have anything else to write about.  Oh, we watch Win a Date with Tad Hamilton.  It wasn't nearly as bad as I thought it'd be.  I actually liked it (I can't believe I just admitted that).  If we end up taking stupid pictures of ourselves, I might put them on here.  I need to get out of this house.  I hope it rains (random moment go me!).  I want to go outside and do something weird, but there's nothing to do.  You just can't plan to do something stupid, you know.  I can't believe it's summer and no one is online.  It's not like they have lives.  Wait, that's just me that doesn't have a life.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Praise the Lord I made an 86 on my English IV Honors exam.  Of course, there probably was a ten point "margin of error."  I finished the class with an 85.  I didn't even have to hide my report card from my mom this time.  Not that I ever would but...  Well I'm headin' outside to play cards with Emily because I know ya'll really care.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It amazes me how random (modnar) I can be until I start talking to myself.  Thinking of things to say is really hard for me.  I guess it would be easier if I was good at writing.    I went to see Shrek 2 today.  Very good movie.  Although I did not like the plug for Justin Timberlake on there.  That's just wrong.  I'm having a tough time deciding if I like the first movie or the sequel more.  They're both good, but I think I'm gonna say I like the original.  Originals are always better (with a few exceptions).  I also saw Mean Girls recently.  It was ok.  I've seen better, but a lot of it was true.  One day I'm gonna write a script.  I've already started on one actually.  It doesn't have a title yet, but it's a parody on romantic comedies.  If any of this sounds familiar it's because my friend Veronica and I are working on it together.  She's already posted our favorite lines from it.  We'll be famous one day.  Maybe not for this script, but we'll be famous and loved by all.  I'm about to break into song.  Just a little hint, cover your ears.  This is all Veronica's fault.  She made me this cd (i'm still waiting on another one that I will get one day.  Won't I Veronica!!!!=) Mrs. Gilstrap smiley!!!)  So long, farewell, auf Wiedersehen, good night I hate to go and leave this pretty sight 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, I'm Laura, but you already know that don't you, Veronica.  I direct this towards Veronica because I know she's the only person, other than myself, who would actually read this and admit it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The past week has been pretty uneventful.  I went to Maury's to watch movies with him and David.  Then he came over and we played Scene It.  Our team lost.  Oh yeah Emily's driving now.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had a fairly busy week.  I took Dan's workshops in the morning, and I had to work at Sherri's workshop at night.  Wednesday Danny and I were in charge because Sherri ditched us.  Those are some hyper little kids.  Dan told me to play a lot of games to get them halfway calmed down.  It was amazing how calm they were compared to the other two days when Sherri wasn't there.  Today she left early, so I got to be in charge again.  The youngest kid is named Brady, and he's incredibly hyper (go figure), but he semi-listens to me.  He came and gave me a hug before he left.  Last night I went to see Saved with my mom and sister.  It was pretty good.  And today we took my dad out for an early father's day lunch.  That was my life this week.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I went to Dan's workshop.  I was really bad.  Actually I don't know if it's possible to be bad at doing nothing challenging.  It rained a lot today.  Gah, it was wonderful.  I worked at the camp today too.  There are about 15 little kids.  Lucky me most of them are hyper little boys that won't listen to me when Sherri's not there.  I also had my first James practice today. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remembered what I forgot...what was I saying...huh I forget (for Lyncoln).  Ok moving on, I got the mother and other stuff in James...lucky me.  Tomorrow I start Dan's workshops so I'll have to see him all the time.  Have I mentioned any of this? I probably have but don't remember because it's late.  My mom was going to take me and Emily to see Saved in Greenville, but we didn't make it in time.  We went to see The Stepford Wives instead.  It's so good.  I laughed, I cried, and I laughed some more.  Actually I didn't cry, but I did laugh a lot.  I'd see it again.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I actually had things to do this week.  Thursday I babysat kinda.  I went swimming with a little girl from the theatre workshop and then played with her for a few hours.  I was there a total of three hours and her grandmother was there so I didn't really have to babysit.  I got $20 for playing for three hours. So of course I couldn't have that money just laying around the house so I went shopping yesterday.  I got the coolest dress.  It looks like I just walked out of an Austin Powers movie.  Friday was the last day of the theatre workshop.  I could never imagine backstage being more hectic than it was that night.  Lucky me I was working back there with all the little kids.  After that I went to Applebees with theatre people for a going away party for someone.  It was surprisingly fun.  Saturday I didn't really do anything except Lyncoln's birthday party which was fun.  We went glow bowling.  Someone thought Riggins was someone's dad.  What I don't get is why these two guys would come up to a dad and ask about me and Stevie.  Of course the guy in the red hat seemed more interested in Stevie than the other one was interested in me.  In fact I didn't even know he was until Riggins told me the guy asked how old I was in stuff.  He never actually talked to me which was fine because I don't picture bowling as a place to find a great guy.  I also found out the truth about some of the people from school I saw there.  I learned that Brett smoked (doesn't surprise me) and so does caraway (does surprise me).  Maybe I'm just sheltered but stuff like that just ruins the impressions of people I originally have.  I think that's all I've done but for some reason I think I'm forgetting something.  Oh well chances are it wasn't anything important.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             I am  a Gauntlet Adventurer .   I strive to improve my living conditions by hoarding gold, food, and sometimes keys and potions. I love adventure, fighting, and particularly winning - especially when there's a prize at stake. I occasionally get lost inside buildings and can't find the exit. I need food badly.  What Video Game Character Are You?     
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are Schroeder!    urlLink   Which Peanuts Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my permit renewed...  again   today.  Go me!!!  I also went to see Raising Helen with Lyncoln.  It was ok.  I really wanna go see The Notebook and Saved.  That was my day.  Oh, this morning I worked.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I auditioned for James and the Giant Peach tonight.  I think I did really bad.  The only part I really have a chance of getting is the mother and I won't take that part.  I said I'd only do the narrator or a bug because I'm not giving up to go see Maury and David for a half a page part.  Oh well there is a bright side to probably  not getting in it and that's getting to see Maury and David.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had another really weird dream last night.  I don't remember a lot of it.  What I do remember is that it started off in the lunchroom again.  And then I ended up somewhere else, but I don't know where.  This time some guy was chasing me.  He had on a white mask so I couldn't even see facial expressions (they're the ones we used in drama, Veronica).  This guy was trying to hurt me, too.  This time we caught him though but then he got away and was gonna come after me while I was sleeping.  I was really scared but no one was willing to stay with me that night and help protect me.  That's all I remember.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My life is so boring.  I always do the same things.  Even when I go hang out with friends we do the same stuff.  It's not exactly an eventful place here.  The only things to do here are either to hang out in front of wal-mart and smoke.  I personally wouldn't consider that fun.  The other choice is to go to applebees and then a movie.  Even when we go eat I always get the same thing.  One day when I drive, Veronica and I are going to go to the "big city" and walk around downtown.  She also mentioned we should all go to Barnes and Noble or something which I think would be fun.  Any suggestions of things to do in a small town that's rather boring.  I want to go ice skating or something.  Something would be along the lines of going to the "big city." I mean when I go hang out with Maury all we do is go eat, go to a movie, or go to a play.  I've gotta find something new to do.  Have I mentioned that yet?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw the new Harry Potter movie with morning with two of my friends.  It was kinda a disappointment.  I liked the first two more, but it wasn't a total waste.  Today has just been an awful day.  I didn't feel good this morning but I made myself go to the movie anyway.  Then I remembered I have the SAT tomorrow which I'm dreading.  Last but not least, Maury is going up north for a week which means I have nothing to do pretty much.  I saw his play last night and it was...uh...well it wasn't the best I've seen.  The camp is going ok.  It's really early in the morning.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink      urlLink Which Princess Bride Character are You?  this quiz was made by  urlLink mysti   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Furnulum pani nolo. "I don't want a toaster." Generally, things (like this quiz) tend to tick you off.  You have contemplated doing grievous bodily harm to door-to-door salesmen.     urlLink   Which Weird Latin Phrase Are You?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     this madness is almost over I promise
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're GI Joe with the Kung Fu Grip!!  You're strong, tough, and know how to kick some ass. Don't forget though, no matter how manly you think you are, you're still just a doll. God Bless America.     urlLink   What childhood toy from the 80s are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     I'm just a little quiz happy today.  Don't worry it's just a phase, and it'll pass.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        wheeler..dang such a cool kid    urlLink   Who are you in Captain Planet?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        I really don't wanna know.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                         Introverted (I) 62.5% Extroverted (E) 37.5%  Imaginative (N) 59.46% Realistic (S) 40.54%  Emotional (F) 60.53% Intellectual (T) 39.47%  Organized (J) 52.78% Easygoing (P) 47.22%  
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You think you meet the one decent guy in the world and then you're totally deceived. Not only do I find out there's nothing between us. Atleast on his side there isn't. I realize he's a guy and thinks like one sadly. However I NEVER thought he'd consider acting on it, which makes me lose all respect for him and certain other person. At this point I'm so freakin' pissed off I'll tell them both what I think of them. I'd go into more details but I seriously doubt you wanna know. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They say everyone has a purpose in life.&nbsp; I think I've finally found mine whether I like it or not.&nbsp; I'm really good at pissing people off or blowing things out of proportion, which only causes more people to pissed off at me.&nbsp; I don't know how I came about this talent.&nbsp; However, through this so called talent I possess I've also learned that being extremely immature is not anymore annoying than being too mature.&nbsp; I'm not quite sure how all of this ties in together, but I'll figure it out one day.&nbsp; I just thought I'd make a list of how I go about completing my purpose.&nbsp;&nbsp; I really do picture it as a purpose because people can't go through their lives never being mad so I kind of give them the opportunity to get pissed off you could say.&nbsp; Back to my list:  1.&nbsp; Always being serious and getting mad when people don't take things as seriously as I do  2.&nbsp; I'm very judgmental  3.&nbsp; Being possessive  4.&nbsp; Blowing things out of proportion  5.&nbsp; I complain quite a bit  6.&nbsp; Jealousy   There is no one that can say these things aren't true because even if they don't annoy you you realize they're there.&nbsp; There are more but we'll just leave it at this for now.&nbsp; One day I'll make a list of positive things but those aren't as much fun.   On a happier note I went to hang out with Maddie and DAnny earlier this week.&nbsp; I wasn't  too  serious then, but I could still use some improvement.        
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And the table turns. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up this morning (yes that's right during the morning hours) and I went to the theatre to work on the set.&nbsp; I did something productive (I thought those of you who know me could use a good laugh.)&nbsp;I really did work today though.&nbsp; It's true I left early and didn't stay the whole time, but hey baby steps.&nbsp; Other than that my day&nbsp; has been very uneventful.&nbsp; I came home and slept, which means I missed going to the play (oh darn.) I'm so incredibly bored.&nbsp; There really isn't anyone online to talk to or anything on tv to watch.&nbsp; Poor poor me.   While I'm here I think I'll make a list of the top ten things I hate.  1. jeans that don't have back pockets  ~not only do they look stupid but back pockets can come in handy  2. stupid/immature people  ~i've always been too mature for my age  3. school  ~I shouldn't have to explain this one  4. reality tv  ~reality? I think not  5. cheese  ~never acquired the taste for it  6.The olsen twins  ~lets try for some more separate dramatic roles shall we  7. shirts with necklines cut off  ~trying to cut some corners when it comes to fabric people?  8. people who think they know everything when in fact they don't have a clue  ~I know plenty of them  9. ugg boots and mini skirts  ~Charlie  10.&nbsp; people who try to steal my friends  ~I'm very possessive        
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think&nbsp;I shall add a picture from my prom to my profile because I can.&nbsp; The power!!!&nbsp;Sorry it's late.&nbsp; Actually I'm not sorry I mean hey it's my blog I can be stupid.&nbsp; The picture will be replaced when I find a good one.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're addicted to.....  Nothing!&nbsp;Your addicted to nothing at all? Well..... ok I guess thats a good thing but come on just think of the possibilities!   urlLink  What are you addicted to? (pics!)    brought to you by   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I finally got my AP results.&nbsp; I'm happy to say I passed both of my classes.&nbsp; However I went from a 5 in AP language on my practice exam to a 3 on my real one.&nbsp; I also only got a 3 in psychology.&nbsp; But hey on the bright side I did pass.   I had a lot of fun last night.&nbsp; I stayed up until three, which is actually the latest I've stayed up all summer.&nbsp; Weird.&nbsp; Moving on now, I got bored last night.&nbsp; I was looking up the meaning of names because I can, and then I'd put my name back together from the meanings so my whole name means laurel (tree) by a lively running water.&nbsp; I had some time on my hands because after that I did almost all my friends if I happened to know their full name.&nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Star Wars!   urlLink  What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)    brought to you by   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.   urlLink  What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?    brought to you by   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dyed my hair today.&nbsp; It's a darker brown with reddish highlights.&nbsp; It looks ok I guess.&nbsp; Even if I hated it, it would wash out in a few weeks. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Next time I should probably think about everything I wanna write before I write it instead of doing this stupid five minute later deal.&nbsp; Ok moving on.&nbsp; I hate computers.&nbsp; I wouldn't as much if I knew what I was doing but I don't.&nbsp; I want to scan some pictures and put them on here but I can't seem to manage doing it.&nbsp; I can do it if it's on a disk but no scanning it is just to hard for me.&nbsp; I get as far as scanning it and then it won't work.&nbsp; Anyway, these pictures are really good and for me to say that then they can't be half bad.&nbsp; I got some headshots taken for drama last October and the person taking them need character shots for something so I got to wear this awesome dress and pose and stuff.&nbsp; It's fun now looking back on it.&nbsp; Maybe one day I'll be able to put the pictures on here.&nbsp; Doubt it but ya never know. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does anyone else feel like they were born in the wrong time? I'd love to have lived in the 50s or before.&nbsp; I live in the past and yes it's sad.&nbsp; And no I don't have anyone to tell me how I should live for today and all that crap because I really don't care.&nbsp; I want guys to open doors for me, and here's a thought pay for me on dates.&nbsp; There would be home comings and soda shops.&nbsp; Not to mention there'd be awesome clothes.&nbsp; Clothes that look good and still have material.&nbsp; That's a concept people don't really understand today.&nbsp; Plus my kinda music was back then.&nbsp; I could go to concerts when they were young and not ugly.&nbsp; It's not as interesting seeing like reunion concerts with a bunch of old people pretending they're young.&nbsp; Chivalry wasn't dead then.&nbsp; People might have&nbsp; even said please and thank you then too.&nbsp; Veronica can agree with me on this one that most everyone in our school never knew the meanings of those words.&nbsp; I realize I'm grouping all things together here.&nbsp; I know everything in the past weren't good, and I know not all things suck right now.&nbsp; However, I still don't care.&nbsp; Too bad none of this will ever happen but hey a girl can dream can't she?       
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Beach  The beach was ok.&nbsp; I didn't meet anyone, but that's nothing new.&nbsp; We had a lot of bad luck with restaurants though.&nbsp; The first night we ate out they forgot to put us on the board so no one came to take our order and my uncle found mold in his sour cream.&nbsp; The second time we ate out we had to wait for our food for 1 1/2 hours, and when we got it it was cold.&nbsp; The place wasn't crowded at all though and people around us were getting fed up so they left.&nbsp; When we went into beaufort we ate at a place called clawsons and it was really good.&nbsp; Halfway through my refill of tea I looked down and saw a dead fly on top of the ice.&nbsp; Luckily I was using a straw.&nbsp; The last time we went out it wasn't really a bad thing it was just funny.&nbsp; We had a two hour limit to eat and leave because we were going on a ghost walk.&nbsp; We told the waiter and he said he'd do his best but couldn't make any promises.&nbsp; Well I looked in the menu and it said "This is a leisurely restaurant, so sit back and relax.&nbsp; We're not in a hurry so why should you be." We ended up having plenty of time to eat.&nbsp; After we ate we went on a ghost walk.&nbsp; Now tell me if it's possible for anyone to take ghost stories seriously from a girl named Charlie that wore a mini shirt and boots.&nbsp; She was so ditzy.&nbsp; Everyone was fed up with her, so the ghost walk sucked cause no one could even halfway take it seriously.&nbsp; That was the beach.  &nbsp;  Theatre  Veronica and I decided to go see Mitch and Dan in a play they're in, but it started to pour when we got there so it was cancelled.&nbsp; We saw Mitch's car with the trunk open so we thought he might be over there.&nbsp; He wasn't.&nbsp; That was the play.  &nbsp;  Walmart  After the play we went to walmart.&nbsp;&nbsp; That is a fun place when you act stupid and relive your childhood, which is exactly what we did.&nbsp; We were gonna get iron on things to make shirts.&nbsp; Thanks to Emily&nbsp;we came up with two good ideas that were "I'm a different kind of popular.&nbsp; I'm not" (that's so me and veronica because we rule) and then on the back of a shirt we were gonna put "quit following me."&nbsp;They were&nbsp;more&nbsp;funny at the time.&nbsp; We went to look at the shoes and I got the coolest orange ones.&nbsp; I also&nbsp;bought some buttons cause they said cool stuff.&nbsp;&nbsp;Toys are fun at walmart too.&nbsp; Especially&nbsp;the dancing Elmo.&nbsp; Anyway that was a brief description of my day.  &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back!!!&nbsp;I'll write more later, but I've just spent 8 hours in the car so I'm a little tired.   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Farewell dear friends, until a later time.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ballet shoes- beautiful, graceful, and creative, you enjoy dancing writing and music.  You are often very poetic and sometimes dramatic.  Even if dancing isn't your thing, you are still very creative. You keep to yourself aside from a few close friends that you can relate to. You find your own ways to express yourself and don't have a need to br surrounded by tons of people. A small group of friends is fine. [please vote! thank you! :)]     urlLink   What Kind of Shoe Are You?(new and updated results!!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     How awesome.  Go me! Lyncoln aren't you proud? 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from the lake with my dad(father daughter bonding stuff I guess.) We had fun.  We were gonna climb up Chimney Rock mountain but they close before we got over that way.  We did take a scenic boat ride.  That was a lot fun.  We learned a lot about the history of the lake and that region, which is really cool for me cause I love hearing about that stuff.  My dad said we can look into renting a lake house for next summer instead of going to the beach.  When we get back from the beach he may take me white water rafting.  I can't wait!!! The boat tour was really cool though because of our tour guide he's really funny.  One day I'm gonna own one of those houses.  Some interesting facts about the place: The lake scene of Dirty Dancing was filmed there, the lake scene from 28 days was filmed there, there were also some other movies but I don't remember them(go figure.)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do guys have to be so confusing.  It annoys me so much(go figure.) Why can't they ever say what they mean or feel? For example, I have this friend who shall remain anonymous and this guy liked her but didn't tell her this until months after the fact.  Not to mention he tells her right before he's leaving.  I know I'm a hypocrite cause I do the same stuff.  Except I usually don't tell the guys at all I like them after the fact.  Also, maybe it's just me, which it probably is but I can never tell when a guy is being sincere.  Well most guys I can but the guys that are really close to me and I know they love me, but o who am I kidding this doesn't even make sense to me so I give up.  Well I went to the fourth or should I say third of July thing this morning to do my monologue.  I went back tonight to listen to some music and watch the fireworks with my dad and some friends.  It was fun.  Maybe tomorrow I can get people together to go see fireworks in Greenville.  Wow, the big city.  Hanson's gonna be there yipee ay oh ki yay(I just butchered that.) As you can tell I'm so excited *rolls eyes*.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you know my family is out of town except for me and my dad.  Well in a week my mom, Emily, and Daniel will leave from where they are to head up to the beach, and my dad and I will meet them there.  Well today at lunch my dad said he was in the mood to buy a new car, which is weird because he's all about saving money for us to go to college and stuff.  He said he wanted a new car for him or to buy a new van with more room for my mom.  Then he said if it's did cost too much money we could rent a van or something that he'd probably never buy.  We'd drive it up to the beach and surprise my mom.  The reason the van wouldn't work as well is because she has our van with her and wouldn't believe we'd buy another without trading hers in.  If they rented Hummers and it didn't cost too much for gas my dad said we'd have gotten that to drive up there.  He also said that when my mom asked whose it was he'd just tell us he bought it for me.  Which would never happen because I don't drive.  I think tonight after the car places close we're gonna go look at vans and stuff.  My dad just doesn't like people looking over his shoulder and calling him up to ask if he's made a decision.  This way if we go tonight and see something we like we can go back when the place is open.  I'd also like to let Veronica know that I'm so happy for her.  Jealous but happy.  Oh, and at least you have people comment even if you don't really know them.  I have you and Danny.  So if anyone is bored enough to read this please comment on it.  I won't beg, but pretty please.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes I realize it's been like a minute since my last post.  I remembered something though so I thought I'd come post it before I forget it.  My mom has an interview with the Easley Progress right now.  Veronica can agree with this statement.  The Easley Progress could really use my mom.  I mean this paper has the most typos of any paper around here.  They also want her for a design thing as well as a copyeditor.  Hope all goes well for her.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really glad that my mom, sister, and Daniel are going on a mission trip to rebuild houses.  They're doing something great for other people for a week.  They leave today, so they're already packed and stuff.  I took a shower this morning and went to find a hairdryer.  Now you all should know we have two hairdryers in this house because only three people use them.  Two of the people are going on the trip, which leaves one of them (me) at home.  Can someone please tell me why they have to take two hairdryers on their trip? Especially when a ton of other girls will be in the cabin and will probably be nice enough to share theirs if need be.  I mean I use one styling product thing and it's the hairdyer.  This may seem trivial but to me this is a big deal.  I mean what if my dad and I want to go somewhere nice while they're gone.  Will I be able to dry my hair? No.  And the rest of the family is going to rebuild houses, and they won't be going anywhere nice.  Is this God's way of punishing me for not going on this trip? I didn't think so.  Well other than that I've had a every uneventful week.  I'd tell you what I did, but I don't remember.  I do remember that I had my senior pictures taken.  Ah the joys of being a senior.  Emily and my mom better be glad senior pictures aren't this week coming up because if so I wouldn't have a hairdryer.  I don't consider that the biggest deal in the world, but my mom would because "it's my senior year." I also skipped a theatre thing this morning because none of my friends were going.  Hanging out with middle schoolers from 8-12 in the morning isn't exactly my idea of fun.  That's all for now.  When I remember what else I did this week I'll fill you in because I know you're dying to know.  Go ahead and laugh.  I would.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to go see 1957 Diva Heaven at Centre Stage. I knew one guy in it cause he'd done a play that I kind of helped with and he knows my mom through that. Well the play was 8 people and a band up there singing a ton of songs and they did a lot of audience interaction. They'd come and sit on people's laps and sing to them. One guy, Rick came up and sang to me. Later Will, the guy mom knows, came up and talked to my mom for a bit. Next thing I know later on they're bringing people on stage to dance (I don't dance). They tried to get me up there and ended up getting my mom up there and they tried to get me up there one more time so like an idiot I went. First of all I wasn't wearing dancing shoes which was a problem. They told me to get into it more and then asked me if I could do the swim so I did that cause it's easy. Then everyone was going back to their seats and they made me stay up there, so they could all sing to me. When I was leaving Rick said I looked so terrified. I was embarrassed but I'm really glad I went up there cause I did have fun looking like an idiot. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The first day of school for my senior year! Such memories (that I'll soon forget). The newspaper said it's the earliest first day of school that school officials remember. Well duh. Doesn't that mean we probably shouldn't have gone back yet? And yes Mitch I realize you don't start college yet so I don't need to hear about.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got a joy, joy, joy, joy down in my heart. Where? Down in my heart! I've got a joy, joy, joy, joy down in my heart, down in my heart to stay.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got home from the theatre and my dad told me he taped a TV show that I might find interesting. It's about a guy named Preston Brooks, and he's an ancestor of mine. He was in congress and is famous for caning a Senator in the chambers. Preston Brooks was mad because the Senator insulted his uncle who was also a Senator. His uncle was from SC. Brooks waited for an apology but when he didn't receive one so he found the Senator in his chambers and caned him. The man never fully recovered. Brooks was dismissed from the Senate, and when he came home to SC he received a hero's welcome. They held parades for him, and some people sent him canes. However the northern states weren't too happy. I just thought it was interesting that I had an ancestor on TV. They interviewed a family member we don't know who still owns the cane. I really want to get in touch with him because I think it'd be interesting.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>