<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey, If I really do end up going to Stagg next August, will I still be allowed to write here?   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Freedom!! remember these words of advice: Live hard Play hard ROCK HARD  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last day! Good luck on finals, everyone (I sound like a chick...).  Bowling afterwards. Well, for me.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      im never ever ever posting here again! *sniff* uh YEAH mean. MEAN.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Me and my big ass mouth always get me in trouble. I was just messin around, sorry.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      lol when i made this user name i was like, "save the wales!...wait...that doesnt...look...right..." but i got it now though. i was gonna make "save the gofers" but yeah. obviously, i didnt.  the other day in the car my friends mom was calling her friend saying, "we are at bob's at the marina. that's bob. B-O-B." and me and my friend hecka started laughing so now i like to spell obvious words.  Bye!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This place is empty, we need members!!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There ya go buddy.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ang, when you get a chance, do me a favor and put me back up to Admin status. I...was clicking a whole bunch of stuff...for fun... and I unclicked my Admin thing... yeah.  Shit. Finals.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah, those rules are fine with me. The only thing I hate is when people feel the need to use this as there personal billboard. Don't advertise something unless you really fell that we'll like it.     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh yeah, one last rule:  I will ban any little fucker who decides it is a good idea to bring up anything concerning my middle name.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes, I joined this damn thing, wheres the Punch and Pie?   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here we go.  Alright, basically, do whatever you want. There are only a couple things I ask (oh shit, I sound like a teacher):  1) Don't over use AIM slang. I understand that LOL may seem necessary at times, but try to use it sparingly. None of that 12/f/your room lolololololz!!!one!!!!1!!!!111!!!!one!!!! crap. We don't need that.  2) Don't fuck with the blog settings unless we agree on it. If it is something minor, go ahead. But doing something like changing the entire template should be something we decide on as a group. Other shit, I don't really care about.  3) No inviting non-Saint Mary's students to become members. This is for SM kids only. However, if you want to invite a Saint Mary's kid, go ahead.  I can't really think of anything else. If you have anything to add, by all means, go ahead.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And we have our first recruit.  I'll go over the rules in a sec.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I bet this fails.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Wankers,  Okay, K(r)is(t)ina asked me a question on the tag board, but I am going to make a new post because:  1) Nobody else is posting. 2) I have nothing to do right now. 3)   So, anyways, I have been able to post on my blog and shit because I just spent Saturday and most of Sunday in Los Angelos at my aunt Susan's place, and they have a computer. My aunt in San Diego, who I have been staying with for the majority of the time, has no internet connection (yes yes, I know, what the fuck?). Right now I am at my friend's house. I am  not  back in Stockton yet. I fly to Texas this Wednesday, and don't get back to Stockton until July 6. I know those of you with working memories realize I have told you the stuff in this post many times before.   Any ways, I am having as much fun as can be expected. I am gonna watch  Club Dread  in a little while, which looks good. Last night, we saw  Dodgeball , which was really funny. I already saw  The Stepford Wives  and  The Chronicles of Riddick , and I rented  Along Came Polly  and  50 Firs --  Okay, I should save this for my personal blog, so I'm gonna end this before I revert back to 'noob' mode. Um, anyways, I hope your summers are going alright. I have (some) pictures from my little trippy-thingy, so yeah.  That post was horrible.  P.S. I wasn't calling anyone a cupcake when I titled this post. Pet names are for fags, and the line is from  Invader Zim .  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Everybody, Hi. I'm leaving for a while. I will be back on July 6. My personal blog should be updated at least a few times during the course of my absence here at SM Kids. Feel free to invite new people while I am gone (as long as they are from Saint Mary's). I am giving you all admin status (at least until I return), so that if something needs to be fixed or you want to invite someone, you can. If I happen to die over my vacation, please put a whoopee cushion under my coffin, so when they lower me down it sounds like...   Any ways, enjoy your time without my constant badgering and sexual innuendo. Love, Pierce I mean fuck you.  P.S. w00t.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Welcome, Molly and Erica.  Well, Erica can't log in really...  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I have added in a tag-board on here. If you guys don't like it, you can either edit it or remove it. Whatever.  I'm not going to make the rules on this one, since this blog doesn't just belong to me.  Also, here is some information:  Tag-Board.com username thing: SMKids Password: I will tell you each personally.  I also set up an email account at Yahoo.com to use as the universal SM Kids blog email address (if you have to sign up for something, like Tag-Boards, this is the email you sign up with if it is going on this blog). The email address is: SMHSKids@yahoo.com (SMKids was taken...) Password: Same as above.  Mmmyep.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Haha, I was right (see first post). At least it spawned a few personal blogs that give me something to read.  The only reason I leave this crap up is in hopes that once school starts, someone will post something...  Wishfull thinking, perhaps.  [too lazy to link image]
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      School starts for us sophmores on the 18th. Fuck.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A: english B: pe C: religion D: math E: history F: bio G: spanish 2  Everyone that can be honors, is honors except for history.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Post your schedules under comments (this way we don't have to go to fifteen different blogs to get our schedules out there).  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoo!  I'm back!  Wait....argh! Vacation! Is! Slipping! Away! Nooooo!  Woof.  
       
    
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Memorial Day, a time for video games, and bar-b-ques. I had a few friends over and we played hella games. Halo, Timesplitters 2, Mario Kart for Gamecube, and SSBM. Yeah, thats about it, damn my life sucks.   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, this summer has been really boring so far, but it is four kajillion( yes, thats a number, you asses) times better then school. My "plans" dont start until next weekend. On Saturday, Im going swimming with Kristina, Lexie, and possibly aaron, so that should be fun. And the day after that, Im goin to that APC show, so yeah. I really need to get my lazy ass over to UOP to see when summer polo starts. The last thing I need is to get out of shape this summer( I' already out of shape, but more out of shape then I am now)  I have been playing  Knight of the Old Republic  lately. I like it because of the fact that you can decide whether you're evil or not. Its a star wars game, which makes me feel really nerdy(everytime I play the game, I can't help but think of the one time I was in Barnes and Noble, and saw the flier for people who really wanted to 'live' in the Star Wars universe) but besides from that, I really like the game.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             Wow, you'd think the last day of school would be fun right? wrong. I lost my phone, now I have to meet some dude I barely know so I can get the piece of shit back. Fuck.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today was my last real day of finals. Tommorow all I have is PE, so haha bitches.  I take back the remark about my parents being cool. My owners are actually the biggest pair of fucktards I've ever met. They took away my phone, bastards.....   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've enabled comments, this means you can comment on stuff. Yeah. There are some rules however, no AIM slang ( you can use lol, if you must) and no telling me where you saw my mother. Thats her business, not mine.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is my Blog!!! TA-DA  So this week has been finals. Nothing real hard so far, but tommorow is going to be a bitch and a half. I've got English, and Science, my two worse classes. So, mall tommorow, correctemundo? I'll propably go.   Sometimes I think me and my dad might be the same age. Today, in the car, he said to me "hey, you wanna go to an APC show this summer?" I was shocked. So when I got home, I went on the internet, and ordered the tickets.(87 fuckin dollars!!) So on June 6 Im gonna be in San Jose jammin to the tunes of Billy, Jeordie, James, Josh, and Maynard. Sometimes my parents can be so sick.  Been playing KOTOR lately, and if you're not a nerd you dont know what that means. So, I wont talk about it anymore. More to come later.     (BTW, thats Jeordie White aka Twiggy Ramirez of Marilyn Manson, he is now the Bassist for APC, sweet shit) 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jenn, you are really cool. I was gonna put this in the tagboard, but that gets erased eventually, and I wanted this to stay. You rule in English, and as soon as you get your Victorias Secret stuff, you have to model it for me.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          So, I went to San Jose Sunday night and saw APC, lemme tell you that was the greatest experience of my life, there were a few things that bothered me, but over all, I had one of the greatest times of my life. I even called one of my friends to let her hear my favorite song, and she isnt even a fan of APC. The concert was at a fairly small stadium ( the San Jose State University Basketball Stadium) so that means there was less people to annoy me. A problem I had was that there were people in the pit acting like assholes, I was in the pit myself and had to constantly listen to people bitch at Maynard because he wasn't showing his face. Come on people, you know that he never shows his face, what makes you think he'll do it this time? Another thing is that while moshing, I jacked up my shoulder really good, but thanks to modern medication I dont really feel it that much. I bought a t-shirt, and it cost me 35 dollars. How uncool. I mean the price, not the shirt. Sorry, I'm still kinda hopped up on pain meds.  Umm been doing nothing but sleeping, swimming, and hanging with my friends. Oh yeah, and doing some O skeet skeeing(dont ask)   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Today was very pleasant. I had to wake up at 9 to go to practice at 9:15. Practice was fun considering I shared a lane with James, Jordan, and JP. After that I chilled at the club for most of the day. Then I went and hung out at the Fetsch's house.   After that, I had to go to my cousins graduation party. I dont like my family. I REALLY don't like the white side of my family. Damn crackers (just because I dont like the white side of my family does not mean I dislike all white people. Some of you crackers are really cool.)  DUDE!!! APC, tommorow, San Jose, FUCK YEAH!!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was....interesting. My little brother graduated from school, so I had to go to his promotion. Lets just say I would rather spend a day with Mrs. Best then be there. I fell asleep like 5 times. Then we went to Garlic Brothers for lunch, where my mom just bitched about everything. Do I really have to spend three more years with these people?  After that, I was looking forward to an afternoon of Xbox, and naps. But no, my aunt calls and said she bought tickets for me, and my brother, and my cousins to see Harry Potter. I didnt want to do that, but hey according to my dad, I should hang out with my family, because they're all I got, or some bull. Anyways, I show up at the movie theater and see people dressed as Harry Potter. Now, come on I understand liking things, but I never dress up as Master Chief everytime I play Halo. But wait, it gets worse. As if having to go and see this movie was enough torture, I had people behind me who were like complaining because things didnt go exactly as they went in the book. Alright typing this vented some of my anger, I'm a little better now.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Had my first summer league practice today. The new coach seems like a no non-sense guy, I respect that. It was cool seeing all my fellow swimmers, after our non-summer break. I hope Katie swims this season.  So I rented a ninja game, its called Tenchu: Return of Darkness . It sells itself as a ninja-stealth game, but there idea of stealth is "run through a level killing everyone that you can, and pray to god that you dont get caught" but its fun. There are kills a la  Manhunt . Sneak up behind the soon to be meatbag, hit the attack button, WAAM, that monkeys gone to heaven. The story is weird, your some assasin, who kills people, but only bad people. Oh yeah, and apparently in medieval Japan, the people had a good 10 gallons of blood in them. But I like it so I reccomend you try it.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That theres a tag board*points to the right* its like a hyrbid, ungodly mix of forums, and IM. If anyone is familiar with Pierce, and his rules, mine are the same. For the love of God, no smiles. I'd go into the code and erase that part if only I knew how. Use internet slang, if you must. Pierce already did with his 1337 tagger crap. Have a nice day.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, some of you really would miss me if I went to Stagg, huh? Well, if thats the case, I will TRY to go to SM when August rollls around. I'm not promising anything, though.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck, I hate my parents. They made me go to the mall today with them because they dont "feel they can trust me by myself" This happened after a series of events, which I will list 1. I got in a fight with my mom and cussed her out. 2. After my fight with my owners, I snuck out and got caught 3. I called my older brother, and told him I was gonna run away with him, and my mom heard me.  So yeah, I cant do much now without parental supervision, and I have to go to Stagg next August, maybe.  FUCK   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      email me at swimmerang@yahoo.com  Konichiwa, Bitches   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have no idea why I refuse to update this, and I also have no idea why some people continue to badger me about it, my buddyprofile should have been some indication that I dont update things.  Today was boring, I didnt do much except watch  Edward Scissorhands , (I'll share my thoughts later) and play  KOTOR . I really need to find the funds to get a new game. I'm really looking forward to  Spider Man 2 , I like the fact that game designers are deciding to use actual cities in there games, I know  The Getaway  did it, but its based in London, so who wants to play it? I'm gonna thoroughly enjoy swinging over the Hudson river, and seeing the mob dump a body in the river.  As for eddie scissorhands, I have seen it a few hundred times, and it is by far my favorite Tim Burton movie. I kept getting the thought that it was like a modern day Frankenstein deal, and Ive never thought of it like that. Wynona Ryder is also really hot in this movie. I also like how they did that 50's-esque crap. Yeah its a great movie.      
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More craziness online.  Person 1:hi Me:hi Me:asl? Person 1: age, male or female? Me: Does it really matter? Me: I just want to play yu gi oh Person 1: yes Me:Well up until 3 months ago I was a male Me:but now I'm a female Me: and I'm 62, but that doesnt matter can I summon my Magical Barricade card? Person 1: brb Me:I AM THE GOD OF THE EGYPTIAN CARDS!! Me: feel my wrath Person 1 signed off at 11:13:13 PM  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My life is semi complete, as I completed my Tool collection today, well I completed the CD collection. (they released a DVD called 'Salival' whoever buys it for me will get candy)  The CD's include:  OPIATE     UNDERTOW     AENIMA     LATERALUS     Don't you just feel tingly all over now?     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I tottally ripped this off from pierce, but random people are so fun to mess with. This was my first one, and its not really funny, but it is kinda historic, so I figured I'd post it.  Me:asl? Person 1: ima guy Me: I dont care Me: asl Person 1: 15 m ny Person 1: u Me: u want the one you'll like, or the truth? Person 1: truth Me:48/m/FL Person 1 signed off at 4:55:55 pm 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, now that swimming is over, me and a couple of friends have starting playing water polo to waste time. I forgot how much I liked the sport.(last time I played was in October) We played 2 on 2 yesterday, and I was guarding Jordan, who is a senior at Stagg and is already on Varsity. So, a tad bit into the game, he decides I was playing to rough, so he pushes me underwater(which is an automatic foul) then he knees me in my face. I was pissed, so when he had the ball I fouled him,(by pushing him under)then I socked him twice in the face. haha, thats what that bitch deserves.  I saw Secret Window, and Unbreakable the other night. I've seen unbreakable before, and it is a really cool movie, though Samuel Jacksons character, Mr. Glass, creeps the fuck outta me.&nbsp;Haha,my favorite part of the movie is when Mr. Glass is in the comic place, and the clerk sees him back there and shouts "You better not be jacking off to the japanese comics, I swear to God"  Now, Secret Window was a cool movie. Stephen King is my favorite writer, and Johnny Depp is one of my favorite actors(he was the bomb in Edward Scissorhands, fo shizzle) I cant really talk about it without ruining some part, so see it.     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So, summer is winding down, and thoughts of school are appearing in our heads...... well not quite yet. So far, I have to get the cruise to Mexico done, the camping trip and the trek to water world( I get to swim in other peoples piss. Whoo.{Sorry Pierce, I stole your world})  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I look forward to camping extremely, I don't know if any of you private school kids have done it, but camping is really fun. You get to get raped by mosquitos, have bears threaten your life, and food supply, and ummm lets just say if you have to go, you have to dig a hole, so yeah really fun.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Pierce got me started on Morrowind again, its a great game, but it's just so friggin big that it intimidates me, and the fact that it is so open ended is kinda nice. I hate how bethesda made the guards invincible. Bastards.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, turns out that I do. Been hanging out mostly lately, not playing that many games, just chilling by a pool, I've gone to a few partys nothing big, and have had some summer flings, though Im thinking about going serious with some one soon. OK time to change the fuckin subject. UMMM yeah, nearly burnt my fuckin hand off on the fourth of July, but I had fun doing it. Yeah theres nothing much else to talk about so dont expect anymore posts from me til around August. Konichiwa Bitches   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahh cruises are indeed great things, the only thing that pisses me off is the fact that they are on the damn water. I got mildly seasick, so its ok, but it could have been worse.  Mexico was the shit, it kinda reminded me of Stockton south of Charter Way, dont know of you have ever been that far, but its like cool, and scary as fuck at the same time. Churro's kick so much ass.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kris, I'm sorry. I screwed up, I hope you can forgive me and I'll never do it again.    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I just got back from my cruise to Mexico. It was pretty fun, but I dont feel like talking about it right now, so maybe later, if you're lucky.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>