<Blog>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      SO this is my last day with internet connection for 5 WHOLE DAYS.  Good lord would it be a bit obsessive to bring Tate with me to an internet cafe??  It is 3:45 in the morning and I have just finished my exams for psychology and I think I did surprisingly well considering I have not studied the material in 8 weeks.  Now we must get back to packing.  Anyone want to lend us money for a house so I NEVER have to move again?  Come on I know I only have wealthy friends. SO I shall have plenty of new photos up since I will have nothing to do but take pictures OH and I guess unpack. Ciao all
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Tummy Time&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    YeeHaw Giddy UP Didge&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Monkeyface&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    In deep thought&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    In da hood&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Tuckered out&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A day at the beach&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Big Granma and LIttle Tate&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I have the right month now.  Emma you're right, life is too hectic to keep track of the months.  1 more packing day, and the stress builds. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well this has been a hectic week. I had two friends from Ottawa staying with us for a couple of days, Bills mom and aunt are in town, we're attempting to pack up for our move on Monday, and I have 2 exams to study for.  Tate is doing well.  We are now on a nighttime routine, and we seem to be getting 6 straight hours of sleep each night.  More after our move...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Go Sens Go&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Boys night in&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Handsome boy&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My little man&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    One month Old&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Tate and his New Suit&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Frog Man&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Smiley Boy&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Bath Time&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    BURP&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Puppies and Bones&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Beach Bum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    2 months&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Monkeys and Bananas&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Hangin' with the Didge&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    10 Weeks&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    4 weeks&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Blue and Green should never be seen....&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Close up&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    First time with shoes&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    8 Weeks&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Taking a stroll&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Feets&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      WELL it's about time - we have contact we are finally hooked up.  Today has been an exhausting day mr tate has not stopped screaming all day long - we suspect he might be teething even though this is VERY early for that.  I ate a Big Mac yesterday - it had been 14 years since I ate beef - AND IT WAS GOOD.  Tate and I took a sign language course this week.  It helps babies become less frustrated as they have a way to communicate before they're verbally able.  They also say babies who learn sign language have a higher IQ by 10-12 points and learn language easier and sooner.  Next week we start our sing and play class - since I can't remember ANY nursery rhymes I usually make up the words BUT they usually involve some farm animal running around with no head.  Tate had his two month check up and he now weighs 12lb 12oz and is quickly growing out of his clothing.  Now if only I could shrink back into my clothing!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello All Well it has come down to me sitting in an internet cafe checking my emails.  But babe is not with me I left him in the very capable hands of daddy. Our move went well - of course it is taking forever to unpack, cause SOMEBODY doesn't seem to want to nap EVER. Our internet is still not hooked up OBVIOUSLY I've been told Thursday but I believe no one. I also very successfully finished my schooling and I ended up with a B+ and a B-.  I will have new photos once I am up and running again. Take care all
     
    
</post>



</Blog>