<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No one's gonna bother with this blog... like ever...  Anyways, I was bored just now and since a friend told me to, I'm posting.  If u've read my main blog, u'd no, cleaning, like all other chores, is now up to me... I'll have to get up tommorow and vacuum. To make it fun, I play to do a little pretending while vacuuming.  I'm brain-sucking alien from the planet Vacuumius. I've come to Earth and with earthly vacuums as my weapons, I'm gonna suck the brains out of those puny bugs in the carpet. Hahahahaha.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Grin . Welcome! I made this role-playing blog cause I was bored and I hope this grants me some fun :). Anyways, role-playing by urself is no fun, so come join me :). In return, I'll share some of the fun, ok? Hehe.  Let's c, this will be a loose role-play kinda thing so that'll be a bit of tolerance for role-switching and out-of-role-ness. Just don't do it too much, kk?  Oh of course... Since only blog members can post, u'll need to be a blog member to role-play :).  Anyways, here's my first role:  Hello, I'm Criff. I'm a mage-in-training. Well, technically not a mage cause I can't really cast any spells... But, c, I got this kool sword. It's got these kool rune carvings. My teacher says it's created by his ancester, Alchemist Bran, with the aid of the Runesmith Raken. This sword means a lot to me. It's the key to make my dream come true. My dream... it's like this. There's a city, one that u might've heard of. It's called Druwyn. It's a place where the most powerful magic users gather. In fact, there's a rule for entering Druwyn: Only those who are either born in Druwyn or highly talented in the use of magic may enter. I want to go there. Because... because my father's there. He's a powerful archmage and I want to measure up to him. This has always been my goal. I was set offtrack, however, when the New Rune Academy rejected me. They said that I couldn't use magic at all. I was soon back on track, however, when I set out to seek a mage who could teach me to use magic one way or another. That's how I came to my teacher and this sword. But not before someone whom I had grown close to died. I'll never forget Belth. He was a friend and a mentor to me. Nevertheless, I have to go forward towards my dream, with this sword in hand. What exactly does it do u ask? Maybe u'll c if u c me fight...
     
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This week is gonna be hell, but then look at the bright side, 9 more days of school left.  June 2: English written exam June 4: English ISU June 8: Drama exam June 16: English exam June 18: Business exam June 25: Report cards June 27: My 16th birthday  I feel kinda weird now, because i'm sitting here waiting for Alex to call, i'm turning into one of those girls whose life is based on someone else, it's sorta a good feeling, i mean, i really like him.  but on the other hand it's not, because i love the sense of independence that i use to have, i miss it, but i like how things are like now, i wouldn't trade it for the world.    I should be doing my career studies homework, but i can't concentrate, and for the first time listening to jay chow doesn't help anymore.  i'm sitting here talking to mike about the one thing that i wish i didn't take, but it's not helping.  School is acutally getting fun, it's probably because i get to see Alex, but i'm actually enjoying the classes now, well, it's about time, i would say.  My lip is getting better, i should thank someone for that.  *wink* Today's weather was good, only if it was a little warmer, or i had a jacket or something, i love the sizzling rain, but i got a lot of goosebumps.  i'm waiting for baseball to come on, yes, i'm a toronto blue jays fan, but it's not on until 10, 20 minutes away.    apparently, i need to get my act together, i'm getting a 74 in business, and according to my parents that's not good enough, not even near good enough, in this house, 80 is passing, and if you don't want any lectures, about 90 is what's expected.  But hey, i'm not that smart, and my mom knows taht, i think she's just lecture me a bit, that's all, hopefully.  now, Alex called, got to go.  my priorities are straight, i think. 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finally decided to have a blog... maybe because i have nothing better to do at this very moment.   i think the fact that all four of us got blogs are so that we can stay in touch with each others' daily life.  I'm sitting here, seem to be waiting for something, don't really know what, don't really care either.  I sometimes don't understand why people let some of the things get to them, they all seem upset, angry... sometimes i think it's not what's really happening, just what they think is happening, it's all a matter of reception.  now i sound like someone who has no problems, but trust me i do, we all do, but the point is not let the problems lead to other problems, the trick is how to solve it, scream, swearing are all just temporary methods people use, but the real problems still remains, i know i'm making it sound too easy, but the fact is that it's not that hard if you just jump out of the box.    i should be a phsycologist ( if i learn how to spell it first), it hurts me to see people struggling.   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well well well, it's finally my birthday! i finally made it to 16!  i'm getting my G1 driver's lisence next week, then i can start driving, so exciting.  thank your for all the phone calls, emails, hugs to all the people who remembered my birthday.  i'm waiting for my mom to get home from work, and pick up alex to go to my dinner party tonight at the emporer's buffet.  i wish all my church friends can be there tonight, but unfortunately, they can't.  the church retreat is the this weekend, and i wish that they had fun.  i can't decide waht to wear tonight, i have this really nice top that i bought on wednesday, but i have nothing to go with it.  oh, screw this.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today i watched the Last Samurai for the 5 millionth time, and guess what? for the first time i was emotionally touched, two tears rolled down my cheeks during the final battle.  i think the first few times that i watched it, i didn't even feel anything, it was just like, " oh, whole bunch people died... booo hooo", that's probably becasue there were people around when i was watching it.  today, i just saw it by myself, and i actually cried.  when boys were young, when they fall, most parents say "be a big boy, don't cry."  so these people grow up not knowing how to deal with these unpositive feelings.  who do these people grow up to be? when they have a bad day at work, or things just don't work out, how do they deal with these violent feelings?  they beat up their spouses and children.   It's okay to cry, as long as you know why. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have a business exam tomorrow, so here i am to review some of the business issues.  Why is the interest rate so low?  in the 80s, the interest rate was around 18%, which means for every 100 hundred dollars that you put in the bank, you have 18 dollars by the end of the year, and the 18 dollars will continue to make money for you the next year.  so for those folks who decided to lock their money away at 18%, by now would have doubled their money 4 times. and for those who decide to take a mortgage at 18% and locked it there, they could have bought 2 more houses by the time they finish paying their mortgage.  the interest rate is created to balance the economy, when the economy is in depression, the interst rate is also low.  when the economy is in depression, people lose their jobs, and therefore stop spending unneccesary money and start saving, this cause other industries to lay off worker, and this eventually lead to few people working.  this is when the government lower the interest rate, so people would save all the money in the bank, spend it instead.  the interest has been the lowest in history for quite a while now, it is consistant at 0.25%, which means for every 100 dollar you have in the bank, you make a quarter by the end of year.  but the interest rate is about to go up, the canadian economy is now looking better.  if the interest rate is going up on savings, it is also going to go up on loans, so mortgage rate is also going to rise, if anyone is looking to get a mortgage, this is the best time to do it.  what are some better ways to save money rather than the bank? stock, they are riskier but have a better interest rate.  also bonds, they are not as riskier and they still have a good rate.  buy a house when you have the money, you can buy a house, and wait for the value of it to go up, normally you can sell it for 10% more than you bought it for.  did you know it is more expensive to live in Beijing than in Toronto?  a one bedroom apartment would cost 1.5 million yuans, even if you converted it, it is still very pricy.  so for those of you whose parents have some savings, i highly suggest that you buy a property in china, for those people who bought a house in year 2000, they can sell it for double the money.  especially with the olympic that's coming up in 2008, the real estate will double if not triple in the next 4 years. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i just finished my english exam today, it was easy and it was multiple choice.  i studies all the terms and all the definitions that we need to know, and how many were tested on the exams? None!  something i actually studied for wasn't on the exam, and waht kind of questions did we have? really basic ones.  we had 2 hours to do the exam, it had 25 questions and you pick the best answer out of four given choices.  i finished the exam after 40 minutes, sat there for like half an hour.  we all had to bring our dictionaries, and did we actually use them? no.    tomorrow would be my trip to Cayuga, it'll be 2 hours there and back.  fun fun fun.  and night, Rev. Mets and Mrs. Mets had invited me and lin to dinner, fun fun fun.  i have one more exam which i'll study for on Friday morning, and then write the exam in the afternoon, that way i'll remember more.  procrastination has it's own ways.  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Cinderella!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You are a child's kiss.  Completely sweet and innocent and pure. You mean no harm and only love in your sweet kisses.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      A GAME-BOY. Youre like a tomboy without the love of sports. Reality sucks, but as long as you have your electronics you feel you can cope. Time goes unnoticed when youre locked in your room hooked up to your Nintendo, rocking to your favourite collection of guitar-driven albums.  Your virtues: Intelligence, sense-of-humour, individuality.  Your flaws: Inability to cope with real life, action-freak spirit, reclusive nature.     urlLink   What kind of girl are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      you are the "you suck, and that's sad" happy bunny. your truthful, but can be a bit brutal.     urlLink   which happy bunny are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       My inner child is sixteen years old!    Life's not fair! It's never been fair, but while adults might just accept that, I know something's gotta change. And it's gonna change, just as soon as I become an adult and get some power of my own.    urlLink   How Old is Your Inner Child?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Your Heart is Red    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Aphrodite/Eros    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're GI Joe with the Kung Fu Grip!!  You're strong, tough, and know how to kick some ass. Don't forget though, no matter how manly you think you are, you're still just a doll. God Bless America.     urlLink   What childhood toy from the 80s are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      dependent    urlLink   Which Personality Disorder Do You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      hand holding - you like to be in constant physical contact with your special someone but you don't want to take things too quickly.    urlLink   What Sign of Affection Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You have a free soul! As all the souls go, yours is the most free-spirited and adventurous. You like camping, hiking, or interaction with other people. Your a social butterfly, but not because of your style, but because of your willingness to communicate with everyone. You probably have close friends who can rely on you because you always seem to know whats going on in the world. You love music and are free-spirited and someone fun to be around. A born leader and great explorer-dont ever change-the world needs more people like you.    urlLink   What Kind of SOUL do you posses? (For Girls only) Incredible Anime Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Mermaid: Mermaids, similar to Centaurs, have a torso of a human and the body of a fish. You are curious yet reserved in your actions.  You like to have fun but never at the expense of others and you never roughouse.  You love water and the creature in it and feel it is your job to make sure they stay safe.    urlLink   What Mythological Creature Are You (Many Results and Beautiful Pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're Element is Light. You are friendly, happy, social, bubbly, and can brighten up any one's day. You are very kind and a real people person because you have several friends (or atleast should). You're cheery nature makes you lovable and your stunning looks are sweet and stand out.     urlLink   What's Your Element(girls)? (PICTURES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You are a Siren. More adventurous than all with a voice like no other you sit on warm rocks and sing to the moon and sea. Yet sometimes shipwrecks find you and raving men want you. You are a bottle of talent and power. What the unknown is you seek to find, and a lover. You have the moon and stars as freinds. There are a very few of you, what a rare find.    urlLink   What kind of mermaid are you? (Gorgeous Pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Congrats! Your a Pure Angel! Angels, as far as most of them go, are all compatabile creatures, but Pure ones simply are symbols of God. Pure Angels always appear when a child is born, when a rainbow is seen, or when someone shares their first kiss. They never grow old, an can appear in the shape of a naked woman with white, bold wings. Pure angels are the carriers of god, and show their love to everyone in the world.    urlLink   What Kind of ANGEL are you? (For Girls only) This Quiz has amazingly Beautiful Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're a lollipop!! You're known for your coolness, for you are a trend setter. You're a natural leader, and are good under pressure.  People often seek you out for advice, for you have great insight.     urlLink   Which kind of candy are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Fun. You Truly Desire Fun. Your always willing and ready to play a game, whatever it may be. But be careful, you cn tend to get a little too competitive.   PLEASE RATE     urlLink   What Do You Truly Desire? *PICS*     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You belong in the world of balance, where everything has two sides and everything is not always what it appears on the outside. Of course, if you have a sense of humor, you may find employment as a sarcastic comedian. If not, enjoy the choices that are presented to you through life, they will always have two sides to them,one which leads you to the light, and the other which entrenches you in darkness. Walk on with hope, my friend.    urlLink   Where do you belong?(ANIME IMAGES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yep yep, alex came over to my house today after the tutorials, which were completely a waste of time.  i was nervous.  thank god taht i cleaned the house yesterday after all the movies that i watched.  i think he actually liked my house.    he was here since like 10 30, and we watch a movie,  Roxanne  ( Steve Martin), it was just a blast.  and then i made spaghetti, which were delicious, and i think alex enjoyed my cooking.  if you call that cooking.  and then we just talked, my parents were home, they wanted to meet alex and see what he's like.  my parents like him, i know how strict chinses parents are about dating, but i think my mom's pretty cool about this whole thing.    tomorrow, i'll be over at alex's house to study for our english exam. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       sunday morning, 10 o'clock.  showered, still in pajamas.  feeling a little like a hang over, not really awake yet awake. home alone.  suppose to take the day to cram for exam, but feels too ... crammed already.  i think i'll go eat an ice cream bar... okay, now what am i gonna do.  i think i'll just watch a movie, something romantic and cheesey, i still have to finish  How to Deal , i think Mandy Moore can actually act, i just watched  Chasing Liberty , again.  i started  How to Deal  last night, but never really got into it, so i'll just give it another shot.   *time passed*  i didn't just watch one movie, i watch four,  How to Deal  ( Mandy Moore, Allison Janney),  Notting Hill  (Julia Roberts, Hugh Grant),  Two Weeks Notice  ( Sandra Bullock, Hugh Grant),  Kate & Leopold  ( Meg Ryan, Hugh Jackman).  and now it's almost dinner time, and all i had all day is ice cream, i declare today Romance Movie Day.  i think my mom's pissed at me for not eating, but it's not that i don't want to eat, but i'm not really hungry.  i tidied my room, and ironed some clothes, and now i feel a little better.  exams are coming up, and i can't believe i'm not nervous, well, i'm usually not nervous, but i'm not even concerned, i guess i'm pretty confident, just hope that i'm not over confident.  i think the weather is really good for the pass few days, it's not like we actually even notice the weather, all we do all day is studing or trying to study, we are all too busy to even notice the nature's wonder.  i check the weather every morning, for what? it's not like i actually stay outside long enough to care.  i think we should all take a break sometimes, like today.   just slow down our pace and look around, we might just appreciate all the things that we took for granted. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hatred   Do you ever tink before you speak? Detroying every aspect of me Acting like you know who I really am Telling me who i should and shouldn't be  You are hypocritical, undeniable Sadistic mess up I want to let this go Leave me alone and shut up  You really screwed me over What did I ever do to you? you have messed you my lines I want to get over this, don't you?  You're a real work of art Too good to be true Ironically, you are I always thought there was nothing you couldn't do  Too bad you couldn't loveme Too bad you couldn't feel the same way Too bad you lead me on Then pushed me away  Now i'm all alone Sitting here with my broken heart You stole it from me And ripped it apart  When I finally move on You come crawling back Telling me he's not worth it While he has everything you lack                         -- Gagan Bath    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Dahling, if you luv me, would you please please smile?"  that is a book title, it's a good book, it's short, double spaced, large printed, and it deals with a lot of things that i think teenagers should be aware of.  things like peer pressure, drugs, sex, family issues.  i'm bored.  i haven't had homework for a while now, and i'm not use to it.   i have been working a lot, and i'm getting my paycheck soon, it's nice to make your own money and spend it in any way you want to. it gives you a sense of freedom.  i was just wondering how i'm gonna spend this summer besides summer school, i think i'll just work more, i wouldn't mind more cash.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Let me tell you somethings i love.  i love bridges, they are so cool. standing on them or underneath them, and do whatever.  it's really calm and quiet and soothing.  i also love the woods, it's like you are attached to nature once again.  i love the free time i have to spend on the bridge and the woods, i love the people i'm with.  i love writing on my blog and play math circus and listen to Punjabi music in the background.  i love the weather, i'm hot, sweating, hey, i don't mind an early august.  i love the new harry potter movie, especially when you have read the book, then you can acctually understand the movie, but overall it's a good movie.  there's one more day of school left, and i just love it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       since i know you are gonna read this, so here it is. apologies for those who read the last comments, sorry for the rudeness for those who should die. you want to konw the reason(s) why i hate you... the list is sooo long i don't know where to start, but as a whole, i just hate you.  hey, i gonna hate someone, it to be you than anyone else. and if you think my blog is childish, do us both some good and don't come. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i just realized that a third of canandian girls are not happy with who they are, there seem to be a global standard of waht a woman should be, and if you are, then sucks to be you, becuase you just stupid and ugly.  half the adolences girls are not comfortable with the phrase " i happy to be me", and it seems like all the time, girls are told that they are fat, they are ugly, but the truth is it's all an act.  some poeple have told me that i'm fat, but the truth is that she was just jealous and had other better to do.  and in the same situation, i have told someone that she was fat, and it was because i was jealous and bitter.  i know most people who read my blog are guys, and you guys don't usually realize the pressure of being a girl.  i'm very good at ignoring what others say about me, cause i honestly don't care, after the b!tch xuan, i think i can take anything, bring it on.  i think i just want to say that looks aren't everything, i know people tell you this all the time, but it is not.  i have learned taht super hot looking guys aren't worth a penny when come down to what's important, and i think this goes out to the guys too, a blonde, big boobs girl may not be what you are looking for.  I'm happy with who I am, atleast ... so far.    Are you? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today was as short.  well, maybe not.  alex wasn't here.  in english, we had the first part of our exam, although i finished on time, but the quality of my essay was definitely questionable.  that's when i realized taht alex wasn't here.    my last class was cancelled.  i came home at about 12 30, and called alex.  he forgot he had an exam  after lunch, me and stew went shopping at square 1, didn't buy anything since i didn't see anything i really wanted.  came home, and did this.  life is a bore, and so is this, and if you actually read this whole thing, i suggest that you do something useful with your time.  today, the reality of everyone leaving me finally hit me.  i just realized that high school is half way over, and the fun is half way over, and i think it's the fun that's keeping me in school.  manpreet isn't coming back next year, and there's many people who might move as well.  it's just that everyone is going there seprate ways, and i think i'm just a little depressed by it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm acctually falling in love with school. all the fun stuff we get to do in all my class.  in business, we are playing jepordy, and in drama, we just practice for our exam, which is turning out to be a blast, in english, we continue to watch movies, now we are watch moulin rouge, and in career studies, we just sit there and chat.  i'm really hally that there's only 8 days left of school, but i think i'm acctually a little unsettled, i think i'm gonna miss it.    i love school, everyone gets together, we get to meet different people and make differnet friends.    i know that this sounds really corny, but i find it fascinating that we get to learn something different each day, not just academic stuff, but now everyone gets along, how people react differently and why.    i think high school is one of the last places where in our lives that we get to see so many people with different purpose, interest, background, future co-existing in one school.  i think that high school is suppose to be the highest point of our life where we can have a lot of fun with little sense of resposiblities.    upon the arriving of our exams, i think everyone more or less will be under stress, i just want to point out the fact that you should still go out and have fun once in a while, clear your mind from studies acctually help you study better. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         "Your presence in my life brings wonderful smiles and loving thoughts within my heart."    i think i'm in love, i think for the firs time in my life that i'm in love with someone. i know i haven't been updating lately, or even reading anyone's blog.  that's because i have been so busy lately.  first of all, i'm taking summer school, so that just takes all the times that i have during the week to do homework.  secondly, this saturday i'll be taking my driver's lisence test, and on sunday i tutor fandi on the clarinet.  my mom just came in with the photos taken from my birthday, ick.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A Love That Lasts Forever by Shane  I sit here today with thoughts of you and I,  the aching feeling inside that I just can't seem to hide. When two people have shared as much as you and I have, when they've opened up their hearts, shared their dreams, thoughts, and fears.  We have come to know each other well enough to know if sadness is hiding behind a smile or if happiness is glowing from the others eyes. We have shared so many laughs,  and we know when each others pain at times has triggered some tears.  We have come to believe in one another and are always sincere to the other,  we have trusted one another with the truth that lies within our hearts. Our true love has yet to be seen with the eyes,  but it's felt with our hearts, we have gained trust, understanding, secrets, loyalty, and sharing ones deepest passions.  This love is rarely found in life, but when it's found it has a profound impact on one's well being, strength and character.  A true love does not need elaborate gifts or spectacular events in order to be valuable or valued.  True love needs what I have to give to you now. I want to give you my undying loyalty, unmatched understanding, unsurpassed trust, and the deepest of enless soulful sharing and love that I have for you.  I love you with all that I am and all that I will be for the rest of my life.....  http://library.lovingyou.com/poetry/201/201084.shtml 
    
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in a good mood today. Nothing too depressing happened today and I got no hw, except studying for 2 unit tests coming up. No complaints today :).  Awww, that's boring... nothing to talk about... Anyways, ... nothing to say...  Oh, I'm so mellow that I can't get mad... Anyways, I might make this a member's only blog so that no one will be able to post comments anymore. I no there's a lot of good-intentioned people out there, but the recent comment by HiddenAssassin(deleted already) is completely unacceptable. It was complete, unconstructive, pure insulting, flaming. I will not tolerate anymore or this. Since I can't do much about it as long as this blog is public, it may not remain that way long. I do wish, however, that everyone continues to visit my blog, even if u cannot comment.  I'm terribly sorry for the stupid actions of the lesser humans among us, who, I'm sure will go to hell.  Thank you for ur attentiona and I understand if u never come to my blog again, but don't hate me. Hate HiddenAssassin(MSN me for his real name). He's ruined a good thing so take him up for it.  I can't be bothered with this too much. I can only handle this much insult and still be mellow, so I'll just go revel in my mellowieness. Cya.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sigh ... I opened Pandora's Box and publicly advertised my blog using my MSN name... Now, I can't close it. I'm glad that people now has a gateway into my mind but I also regret letting in the people who just don't understand. And I mean u, creature. Everything u've said has been a judgement on the way I've chosen to live and the way I've chosen to write. Frankly, I don't care what u think. This blog is about me for a reason. I made it to be about me. Now, if u have a problem with that, stfu and go to hell.  As for M, thanx. That means alot to me... And I'm sry about calling u smug... and cute... I'm just paraphrasing what the chinese parents say... U no, dimples and all... I can imagine getting my ass kicked,  shudders . Anyways, I hope L and H reads it too.  Really though, I'm sick of it. I've heard it at school so I don't wanna hear it here. What I should do and what I shouldn't do, what I've done wrong and what I've done right. Get this into ur head: That is not what this blog is about. I'm tired of getting judged. I made this blog to feel relief from my anxieties and to be comforted, not to be bombarded by judements made by people who have a problem with how I live. From now on, negative comments better be constructive criticism in my eyes, or I'll flame ur ass out of here. That's right, this is where I have power.  Now, I want to note something about that "most important thing in life" thing I wrote a couple of days ago. I just want to make sure that no one confuses that as synonymous towards the "meaning of life". The meaning of life is something for each and every one of us to discover for themselves. That journey to discover it is what we call life. Therefore, the most important thing in life is to enjoy that "journey" and not regret it afterwards. IOW, be happy.  Sometimes, I do wish that I can control my own happiness, which is impossible since I'm not even sure what'll make me happy. All my fantasies have been about revenge and death is always involved in it. I've never even tried to imagine myself happy. I wish I could just be more optimistist once in a while.  Anyways, I got tons of hw, so I'm off, cya.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Again, I'd like to prompt people to leave comments. They can be any type of comment. Whether u can relate to the post or not; whether if u agree to the post or not; anything. Be warned though, if u disagree with something I've said and comment about it, expect a rebuttal from me. I'm like that.  Anyways, I've realized that my posts aren't very conventional. Usually, blogs take the form of a diary or journal, telling of the day's events and the person's reflections about them. In the case of my blog, however, I try to be as vague as possible on what happens to me. Instead, I focus on thoughts that derived from these events and build on them to create questions, hypotheses, theories, and philosophies. This is prolly because recapping the events of the day won't help me nearly as much as the analysing of my thoughts. That's just something I've realized...  Anyways, just felt like noting this, but Poetry.com wants me to write a poem and biography for their Internation Who's Who in Poetry. Now, I never sighed up for this... I'm even sure if I'm obligated to do it. It just might be written in the fine print somewhere when I entered my previous poetry entries... What a bother...  Also, I passed up a chance to go to my church friend's house. This kinda surpriced me as it sorta contradicts the topic I was gonna talk about today. U c, seeing my church friends on the weekends r usually the highlight of my week since school is always such crap. I've always taken comfort in these friends. Their very prescence has helped me though my period of depression during first semester. I've molded this in this statement: I find strength from without, instead of from within. I don't even no if strength is accurate. I might be more like  stability . Just being in the same room as them, listening to their conversations(I'm the quiet one), makes me super mellow. I forget all my worries. It's similar to playing video games and watching anime, both of which mellows me out temporarily, but much more effective. Without these friends of mine, I doubt video games and anime would be enough to keep me from attempting something irraversible... ie, suicide or a mad machine gun sweep of my school.  But me deciding not to go today... Why? I'm not regreting that decision, but why did I make it? Is it because I'm mellow enough from seeing them yesterday? Or too mellow from seeing them yesterday? Or perhaps I feel too tired or even too inadequate to face them? I think I'm growing distant from them. I practically talk to them on MSN everyday about gaming or anime matters, but the serious talks... they don't come to me for those anymore. It's cause I've been burying myself in computer games recently. They come to me, and I tell them to go away. If it was me, I'd be discouraged from talking to someone if they told me to go away everytime I tried to start a conversation.  One of them said something about this the other day. He said, although I was the oldest(when one of them isn't present), I'm perhaps the most immature and cared more about computer games than them. I no I'm immature. I am that way. It's sad, but I can't bring myself to do anything about it. It saddens me to no how dependent I am on others. I can't even ride the bus by myself...  I do care about them though, as much as they care about me. Even though the love is always there in our little group of friends, the relationships I have with each of them is quite different. Let's call them M, L, and H. M is a smug cute little boy(only in the eyes of adults) who is three months younger than. L is a big gangsta-like guy who looks exactly like the kind of person who lives as troubled a life he does who is six months younger than me. H is a super-liberal girl who seems like Lori from Gilmore Girls, except with an invisible shroud of mystery around her emotions who is five moths older than me. Let's see, I talk to M daily, usually about anime and video games. Now however, I'm begining to take him for granted and sometimes unintentially talk crually to him. L is being emgrossed in his personal troubles, and I'm not privy to it because I'm too busy playing computer games. H, the rest of us almost never c anymore; we're begining to doubt we no who she is anymore... The point is, I'm growing distant from all of my church friends, the ones who I can't live without.  Will the day come when they become strangers? I can imagine that day and I no I'll be crying. I don't want that day to come. So, if ur reading this, M, L, and/or H, I need u, even if I say I don't, I really NEED u. Please, stay by me no matter what, and I'll try to do the same. God nos I'll hate myself if I don't...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, everyone, just got back from church... Did pretty much nothing except eat slushies and talk to friends... Anyways, I just want to say that I really appreciate this blog thing cause it helps me write out and develop these theories about y I'm unhappy and how I can be happy. My only regret is that I forget some of these theories before I can write them down.  Anyways, today, I wanna tell about my self-hatred state. I hate myself for the same reasons someone else might hate me. Character defects maybe, possibly for just being plain wierd. But the most dominant reason is that I hurt other people. In my search to find my happiness, I hurt countless others, however unintentionally. That can prolly be attributed to my stupidity. When something seems right or cool to do at a certain time, I do it. And it ends up hurting someone. This has happened everywhere from gym to bonding time I spend with my friends. The worst thing is how the people I care about the most r the ones who get hurt the most. Many of them still carry the physical or emotional scars today. I think about the actions I did, the things I said afterwards and realize how stupid I was. And it was all done because I wanted to be happy...  One of my friends said today, that happiness is the most important thing in life. I agree because without happiness, nothing else matters much. But this important question struck me, who's happiness is more important? Ur own or someone else's? If they're equally important, then what happens if u can only be happy at the expence of someone else's happiness? What should u do? And what if u took away someone else's happiness? Does that make u responsible for that person's happiness, in addition to ur own? Who's to make these decisions? Deciding who gets to be happy and who gets to be unhappy is like deciding who lives and who dies. No one is qualified to make that choise. I certainly am not.  So what now? Do I feel guilty about striving for my happiness while unknowningly stepping on others' happiness? Do I continue to hate myself? I don't no. But then, I don't no much. Sometimes, like right now, I wish someone who had all the right answers would just tell me what to do. But the most knoledgeble is always the quiet one. In fact the all-knowing one is the most silent one. He nevers tells me anything. I've asked Him every question I've asked here in my blog and so far, I haven't got an answer.  I swear I feel tired whenever I write in this blog. I'm gonna go now. Cya.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm out of energy. I can barely keep my eyes open. Not that I really want to since there's nothing nice to c. Nothing nice to do, nothing nice to listen to, nothing... Well I have plenty of things to do, but they're not "nice". I can do research about Paul Bernardo, maybe find an ad to do my spoof ad assignment on. But... I don't wanna. As boring sitting here doing nothing is, there r worse things. Namely, hw. Sigh, I'm too tired to say anything or think anything or remember anything now... I'm gonna leave today like this... no interesting new topic, no mind-bogling afterthought, just a mental image of my very tired self: an Oriental kid, looks to be around 15, male, sitting with his ass sliding off a black ergonomic chair. His hair is all over his face and he is too tired to brush it away. His eyes r open only a slit, as if he's too tired to open them but too scared to close them. He's wearing a small black t-shirt with grey and white stripes along the sleaves. He's wearing black worn out Khakis with at least one hole in it, at the knee. His socked feet r under the desk in a rest position. His fingers and hands seem to be the only animated part of him, dashing back and forth across a dirty keyboard. In fact, from afar, the kid looks quite dead. He turns to look out the window and sees u... He screams... U scream... U run down the street, screaming in a frantic state. Because of ur current lack of focus, u run into a lamp post and hit ur head hard. U fall... And c the Oriental kid's face as u fall unconscious...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would like to thank D.J.Max for his comment and yes, comments r more than welcomed. To c his comment, check under the "So, tired..." post on Wednesday, May 26, 2004. I would like to say, however, that this blog is as serious as it gets. What I write here is, in truth, for my personal benefit. It's like a reality TV series, where the prize is better self understanding.  Now, Max, u seem like a smart person and ur depiction of how someone like me may end up living is, by all means very plausible. I even respect ur decision in not living the way I've chosen to live. Except, I've never made this choice. And I can't change the way I am. At least, not without help. How can I choose the other road if I don't no how far back was the last fork? Unfortunately, ur comments recognized many of the things that r "wrong" in the way I think and live but does nothing to help me change.  As for whether I want to change, I don't no. The one dominant thing in me seems to be a transandant laziness. Not just the kind of laziness that makes me not do hw simply because I don't want to go get my backpack from downstairs. It's the kind of laziness that shapes my personality and attitude toward an easy lifestyle. However, this laziness of mine contracts my yearning for greatness. One side will eventually win out but I just can't be bothered to make a decision right now.  The desperate question is this: When I do choose a path, will it be too late to go down it? Time and the world won't wait for me as I let my desires decide for me my fate. I'll graduate high school and go to post-secondary. I'll grow up. The further u go down a road, the harder it is to turn back. If it so happens that by the time I arrive at a decision, it seems incredibly difficult to turn around, will I just go alone the same path as before?  All this make it seem that it's all so urgent. I'm a procrastinator. I leave stuff off for tommorow. It's a bad habit but in a case like this, is it so wrong? I don't no what career path I'm going to take. I don't no what kind of car or house or anything I want. These r life-long decisions. I've been told this too many times by too many people. Now, is the decision on how to live my life the same? Or is it so important that it is made now that it will shape the rest of my life?  I simply don't care. I don't no what to do. I don't want to make the decision. I'll prolly do the same thing I do with everything else--Leave it for tommorow. Who nos when tommorow will actually come?
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was gonna post a follow-up to yesterday's blog at school... It didn't work out and I'm too tired to do it now. The basic gist of it was gonna be how my parents don't understand me. And how we forget our fights fast but it stays at the back of our minds fueling our anger when we fight again.  Anyways, too much happens at school everyday for me to bother to much with what happens at home. Yup, it's almost all school. The way I feel everyday. This lack of a desire to really  live . School does terrible things to me. Maybe I do these things to myself, I don't no. Maybe I should settle for a 90% on a major assignment when my friends got 95%'s and 100%'s. Maybe I should settle for hitting the ball just once when I made countless errors. Maybe if I just settled, I wouldn't feel so bad. Ya, I blame it on school. I don't think I can last long if I blamed myself. I strive to be the best yet deep down, I don't believe I can achieve it. Maybe if I did, I would actually  try  try. But it doesn't work that way. I don't feel that much hate anymore. I simply can't. Now it's the sadness, despair, and simple shame. Y do I suk so much at everything? Y can't I be the best at  something ? Just one thing. That's all I ask for. I don't have to be a Jack of All Trades, just not a Jack of No Trades.  So... What am I? I can't maintain a 90 average. I've tried but I no it's not possible. I can't do well enough in math to beat all the competition. I don't even have the guts to enter math contests. And gym. I hate my classmates. They fuel that fire that may one day consume me. I no it and they no it. That one day, I would just explode and either turn suicidal or homicidal. And even the pride I take in writing. The truth is simply that I'm not that good. I've done peer editing and there's way better formal writers in my very school. Even my fiction is weak. I have no bond with my characters. Whatever happens to them, I  feel  nothing. None of that forlorn feeling that u feel when ur favourite character in an anime series or RPG dies. I'm no one special. In fact, with so little specialty that I'm not even good enough to be normal.  Nowadays, I only have 3 states. Self-pity, self-hatred, and oblivious bliss. The last of which can be so simply attained through video games and anime that I've gotten addicted to it. This is what one might call a routine of self-destruction. When anyone least suspect it, I'll prolly just dissappear. Maybe turn up a few days later down river or something.  Sure, I have my life ahead of me, but what's the point. I've got very little satisfaction from my life so far. Who's to say that I'll get more from the rest of my life? It's times like this that I wonder if I should just kill myself.  Then more questions arise. What  if  I kill myself? Who will care? What will my only true friends from church think? What about my friendly classmates? My less than friendly classmates? My parents? Will they hate me for being stupid and killing myself? Will they blame themselves and live with the burden for the rest of their lives? I can't answer these questions. And I doubt I can ask them. After all, there's few of them would even consider the possibility of me killing myself as long as I'm alive.  This is the way it'll stay. These thoughts will run through my mind again and again until the end. The end of my life or the end of my current state of mind. Who nos... Well, I'm done ranting... Cya
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back, and u guessed it, I'm alive. After I went DDR downstairs, my dad came and just sat beside my dance pad. It annoyed me. I wanted to be alone. I guess feelings like that don't flow easily to parents. Anyways, I told him to go away, repeatedly. Then he got mad and got a broom stick to scare me. I new I couldn't fight him so I left for a walk in the cold. On my way out, he said that if I left, he'd lock the door and not let me back in. I didn't even hesitate, I had a key in my pocket. I distanced myself from my house. As I walked, I thought and talked to God. I realized what scared me so much about my parents. I didn't no if their love for me was like God's, totally and absolutely unconditional, or if they would abandon me as soon as they got news that I failed to get into the university of their choise. The more I thought about it, the more I believed it was the latter. It was cold and since I was wearing a t-shirt, I turned to go home earlier than I would've. Nevertheless, I dreaded going home. All I could imagine were my parents going on about how stupid it was to just walk out like that. On my way back, however, my mom found me. I didn't even c her since I was looking at the ground. She brought my sweatshirt and jacket. So... maybe she really loves me after all. I don't no. And there hasn't been a lecture, at least, not yet. I've been avoiding my dad since I came in so I haven't talked to him yet. And I haven't talked to my mom either.  So, what now? What else is gonna happen? Will we resolve our problems and be one big happy family? What will happen tommorow? And ya, I was crying. I was crying when I walked around outside and I'm crying now. I don't care about image. Think of me as a sissy who cries a lot if u want. I don't care. I'm just so sick and tired about not noing if it'll get better or worse. I g2g again. Cya tommorow.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ARG! This is so friggin stupid. My parents r so annoying. My dad screams for no reason. My mom sits beside and and stares at me funny. I'm gonna go crazy. Can't they just leave me alone?! I hate my life! ARGGGGGG! And y do I have to play ahead!? Do I care what I'm gonna do the coming summer? I don't think I do! But they think that I should! I hate this, hate this, hate this! And u no what? This isn't as satisfying as I thought it'd be. Maybe it's cause I'm refraining from swearing too much... Still I think I'm calm now... No suicidal or homicidal urges anymore... *deep breath... Yup, I'm fine. Sry for this meaningless post about my stupid meaningless life! I'm gonna take my agitation out on DDR, just so my mom would stop staring at what I'm typing...  Anyhow, cya all... Have a nice life in case this is my last post and I kill myself soon...
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heh, I've done it. I've created my own blog. I'm now one of them. Or should I say one of  you ? Anyways, life's crap as usual. Well it's better than sometimes. And it's definately better than the lives of some people I no... Ai ya, I can hear my parents sing... *shivers Life's not fair... I ramble a lot don't I? I've said so much yet I've said nothing at all. Let's start over.  I'm a 15-year-old Chinese Canadian with longish hair. Longish as in longer than any normal guy is ever supposed to have but shorter than that of the guys in Media Garden. I suk at pretty much everything. In fact, I'm failing Gym class... And I'm still in a state of shame after losing at air hockey to a girl... It's one of the delimmas in my life. I'm not good enough at anything to be clearly defined as anything.  I do, however, have a passion for writing. It's sad cause nothing I write ever gets published. Except what I just wrote, and that, and that, and that... Right, so maybe my stuff do get published. Some of my poems got published at Poetry.com and then they started scamming me for money... Nevertheless, Criff is the main character of my current major project. Well, my first major project anyway. I've got about 5k words into the story so far. Basically, it's this fantasy story involving magic and stuff. I'm really too lazy to give a basic description... But if u want one or want to c what I got so far, don't be afraid to ask me through e-mail. Sigh, I'm so bored that I've resorted to this... I still can't belive it.  Well, I supposed I need some love right now. But I doubt I can get any without giving first. So here it is, I LOVE YOU! Now love me back or I'll hunt u down and make u give my love back. That's it for now. Cya.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Retreat was fun... Well, not as much fun as really really interesting and rewarding. I suppose it wasn't like last year (to which I didn't go, because no one told me about it), which I imagine was more fun than rewarding. Beside the point, anyways, I'm exhausted, mentally, physically, and perhaps spiritually.  I'm tired physically because I stayed up late listening to the guest pastor, Rev. Tony Costa and because I played badminton. I'm mentally tired because I learned a lot, thought a lot, and had little time to sleep and recover. I'm spiritually tired because..., well, who nos.  Tony Costa is a really interesting man. Like I no he's visited our church before but I was never there... Anyways, during the first Message, I was pretty much analysing him, like I do with all public speakers. He's confident and definately nos what he was talking about. By the end of the worship service, or third Message, I admired him not only as a speaker, a man of knowlege, and a man of faith, but a human being as well. He's a man who does, thinks, and believes what he does so fiersely, passionatly, and absolutely that I can hardly comprehend. He's the type of Christian that would've been killed a long time ago if this was J.C.'s time.  Anyways, I've come to a personal revelation. I've been aware of this for sometime but it hasn't been this clear in my mind before retreat. For awhile, I've analyzed, from an objective point of view, Christianity. I've come to the conclusion that Christianity is the best explained, if not only, logical belief. Similarly, I've concluded that a Christian lifestyle, from a completely non-spiritual view, would be, at worst, neutral to my current life. My final conclusion: I've nothing to lose.  I've known this for a long time. But I never really put my real concern into a conherent thought before. I want to be genuinely Christian, but I can't. I've prayed and prayed for the Holy Spirit to touch me but it hasn't. And God nos, only the Holy Spirit can bring me to truly accept Christ in my heart. It's like the devil has me captive and just won't let me let go... My solution for now is this: strive to live a Godly life and to keep praying. That and ask for others to pray for me too...  I'm really a sinful person. I haven't really even tried to live up to God's standards. Maybe this is y I haven't recieved the Spirit. That will change. It has to.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just came back from weeding and mowing the lawn... Housework's a million times harder when u own a house and a lawn that comes with it... My hands are dyed permanently green and my foot's bleeding from pushing a lawn mower while wearing sneakers with no socks...  Sigh... Sometimes I just wonder, if Chinese food is so hard to cook and taking care of the lawn is so tedious, y do we bother? Sure we're born Chinese but that doesn't mean we can't eat other food and I don't c anything wrong with having a plastic lawn... Oh well...  Anyways, even though it's summer and i don't have anything to do, the simple day-by-day life is actually pretty interesting. Like today, (if u don't like sick stuff, skip to last paragraph) my ass bled... I've had this pimple on my ass for like two weeks and it's annoying when I sit on it. So anyways, I was scratching it and when I retracted my hand from my pants, there were like red stuff on it. I even tasted it to make sure it wasn't ketchup... Well, it sure isn't everyday that u can say "My ass is bleeding." =D.  Now... I gotta go cook :'(. Grr, I wonder if I'll survive the summer...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back after soooo long... Ya, after camping (friday and saturday) I didn't bother to update. Shows my laziness, huh.  Anyways, since last time, there's only one thing new and important. I've taken up a new summer endeaver. I'm gonna be a household slave for the ENTIRE summer :). It's like this: My mom wants me to do something during the summer, like something meaningful. Her list of choises were: Get a job, take swimming lessons, go to China, volunteer at library, volunteer at old-folk's home, and doing all household chores for the summer. Since I'm sociophobic, I can only choose to stay home and be a slave. Btw, all household chores mean EVERYTHING, from cooking dinner to cleaning the washrooms... And believe me, it's not easy... Chinese food is crazy... The simplest ones take an hour; U'll c me running across the kitchen, battering the eggs, picking the beans, cutting the melon-like thingies, frying the leafy vegetables, boiling the soup... eek, just thinking about it haunts me.  But being a slave gives me some power as well... Being able to prepare food means I'll be in the position to sneak in some poison. And being able to clean means I'll be in the position to install hidden cameras... The slave will be the master.  Grins evilly .  Anyways, I just saw AFI's 100 years, 100 songs. It's this list of 100 songs from 100 years of american film, voted in by a bunch of important filmography people... Guess what the number one song was...  Somewhere over the rainbow Way up high, There's a land that I heard of Once in a lullaby.  Somewhere over the rainbow Skies are blue, And the dreams that you dare to dream Really do come true.  Someday I'll wish upon a star And wake up where the clouds are far Behind me. Where troubles melt like lemon drops Away above the chimney tops That's where you'll find me.  Somewhere over the rainbow Bluebirds fly. Birds fly over the rainbow. Why then, oh why can't I?  If happy little bluebirds fly Beyond the rainbow Why, oh why can't I?  I doubt many of us would recognize that. After all, it was in 1939's  Wizard of Oz , "Somewhere Over the Rainbow".  I spent 3 hours watching the show... Listening and watching songs and scenes from almost 100 movies... It's inspired me to want to visit/revisit some of these classics. Right now, I have a tramendous urge to go download the Sound of Music and Westside Story. Maybe I will... hmm...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey hey. All my exams r done :). Actually they were done on tuesday but I just didn't update my blog... Anyways, life's gooooood... and boooooring... Yuck. What I do all day and all night is play computer and video games... Boredom all the way. :(. And none of my friends want to play with me :(. It's so  sad  :(.  So, anyones. I have a  temperory solution  :). I made a new blog. It's a  role-playing blog . I dunno what exactly I'm gonna do with it yet. But prolly it's gonna be where everyone makes up a role and plays it. I'll prolly make it loose role-play, i.e. peeps r allowed to change roles, small out-of-role moments allowed, etc. We'll c how that works out. Anyways, stay tuned :).  Btw, u can access the role-playing blog at http://rphaven.blogspot.com
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I could swear i poseted yesterday... Oh well.... Anyways... Exams coming up... well, actually tommorow... And I havent' crammed yet.... I'm so screwed... Oh well... Sloth has dug its claws into me, and there's little I can do... I don't even feel like posting... Nothing to say, nothing to express, when I don't have school, I have no feelings. No negative feelings anyway. Computer games make me feel neutral and friends make me feel.... warm and fuzzy inside?! WTF is this?! Wait, nvm...  And this leads me to believe that this is what summer will likely to be... totally, completely, and absolutely meaningless and empty. So much so that I will likely come out of it in such a vulnerable state that my first semester depression period is likely to repeat... WAHH! I don't want that to happen...  Y didn't plan out my summer properly :(. I have no job, no summer school, no vulenteer program planned.... no computer camp, no army training camp,no CS LAN parties.... no internet caf package, no computer upgrades, no VB projects, or that of any kind... no new endeavers, no plans of any kind, and definately nothing interesting... I can c myself for the whole summer right now... In front of a computer screen, going to the washroom once in awhile to cry about sucking at online games so much, then giong to bed for a few hours nap, before getting up for the rest of the NIGHT to keep playing with people who live in China and are enjoying their DAY. Pathetic... I no.  But what can I do... I can't shake myself loose of Sloth... she is evil and she clings... her fingers around my throat, her nails dug into my heart... she clings to me life, she does. Gluttony's got me too... colourful food, tasty food, wonderful food... food aplenty, eat to me heart's content, beyond what me body needs or wants... If he had to, he'd taken me from the stomach, or maybe the kidneys or the liver... I got my dealings with the others too... Pride's in my veins and I damn can't shake him off, afterall, I'll boast till I go hypovolemic. You can c Greed in my eyes. He darts here and there, telling me to take what I can. As for what I can't..., he leaves it to Envy, bet u'd be able to c me complexion turn to a sinner's green... And Lust... she stays in my pants, no? I do hope she does, cause jail's an unpleasant place... That and that she clips her nails... If u no what I mean. Now, if someone tries to take me from me earthly pleasures and earthly sins, Wrath be upon 'em... Me Warth ain't something to recconed with. He be raw and he be vicious, and he plays dirty too...  Now... Do u have an idea what I have to deal with? I take upon my daily sins like another takes up his daily bread. I got not guilt, either. They say the seven deadly sins trips those who seek spirititual salvation and takes 'em up on the route of spiritual damnation... Like I give a damn. Humans cannot exist without earthly pleasures and earthly sins, and I certaingly cannot exist without them. But noooooo, society tells us to feel guilty. Let me tell u, let Guilt be the eighth deadly sin. He'll be among friends.  I refuse to conform, but does that mean I'm rebelling? Really though, who the  orange juice  gives a  peanut butter and jelly sandwich ?!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ewww, there's stupid people visting my site, so i'll just post a post here.  first of all, mike, you can't let  your website die, you just can't.  there's nothing wrong with spending a lot of time on your site, since hey, it is your site.  is there really anything wrong with name calling for those who really deserve it? i mean, i could be creative about it too, let see... nah, i think i'll keep this site PG 13.  why do i have to give her a reason? i mean it's not like she gave me a reason? i don't owe her anything? do i? maybe i do,like a few more insults. but hey, why waste my time?  okay, i'm done bitching, what's up with everyone? updates plz
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just went a whole weekend without blogging, soo.... Those people who say I spend too much time on this, in ur face!  Anyways, I'm short on time so I'm gonna keep this short.  Let's c... I've gotten kinda bored of this blog thingie already... I guess it happens to the best of us, right? I'm prolly gonna spend less and less energy on each consecutive post and eventually stop... I no it's sad, I'll definitely miss my blog. It's just that..., I have more important stuff to do... Like I'd rather DO stuff instead of rambling on like a madman about things that really don't matter. Especially since posting REALLY takes up energy...  The way I look at it, the blog's gonna die sooner or later... I would like to keep it alive as long as possible though... However, I don't think I can do it by myself, so I'd like to ask my three team members to occasionally post here in my blog.  That's it for today. Btw, commenting's back to registered users.... I don't think HiddenAssassin will ever bother to come to my blog again... so... Anyways, if u MUST no something about my weekend.... M, L, and I skipped Sunday school again... Oh, and I went to the Toronto Zoo on saturday. Did u no pythons lays eggs while boas give live births? Never new that...  Hmm, today's lesson is: If u can't be something, be anti-something. Note: Like in my longer posts, my lesson here is most likely to cause u to crash and burn if u heed it... so, don't, OK?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Normally I'd post more but I'm all "thought" out from commenting on my friends' blogs... No more thought energy left...  Anyways, I got nothing to say at the moment anyway. It's the same old damned procrastination that's gonna one day kill me...  Ah, I'm bored down to the level of M's blog... I would copy and paste my comments but I'm too lazy to do that too...  So anyways, let's c how'd I do when I have nothing in mind to talk about. Hmmm.... Well, I've noticed that commenting others is a LOT easier than writting my own piece. It seems that the creation of a topic is something difficult and something to be considered a skill.  It's times like these, that u wonder about how creativity is useful in our lives. Certainly, we don't need it to stay alive. All we have to do is the do the same thing we do everyday like drones. But we do need it to  live . After all,  living  means going through our lives without acting like drones. It's creativity that introduced all the variance in our lives. Even the great minds that we admire would be nothing without creativity.  Then u come to this... Creativity is the source of all excitement in life, but in turn varience and excitement cause us pain. Sometimes, we think that living like drones wouldn't be as bad as living in pain. That is when we begin to doubt creativity. If I was never creative enough to up with the idea of putting a gun to a teacher's head in my comic assignment, I would've never got in trouble. The same trouble that helped fuel my depression during first semester.  But then, u can argue human nature. Human nature is to survive and advance and it is willing to use creativity as a tool to do that. None of us r above human nature and we can't do anything about it.  I prolly shouldn't think that way... If I justified all my actions with human nature, I just might do something terrible... Cya and I'm off to bed.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Um... I'm alive... U might think I'm dead cause I didn't post yesterday, but I'm alive... I AM! Look, if I was dead, would I be posting this?!  Huh? U're not arguing? That's wierd... Anyways, my blog is officially Member's Only for comments. I might change it back if enough people message me or e-mail me about it on MSN...  I finished my math unit test yesterday and my civics unit test today :). Now, there won't be anymore math hw so I just have to review till the exam... Aww, I don't remember ANYTHING about analyctic geometry and trig... I got a lotta work ahead of me... I'll just study the last day :). As for civics... stupid summative project thingie and final in-class exam r still left... DAMN IT!  As for my other two classes... I'm more or less failing 'em. Gym is one of those things I have no chance of even getting an 80 on... If u saw me doing beep test, u'd prolly think I have asthma or something. Which I don't. And English...  I WAS getting 90's in English until recently... Well, yesterday... I got back 3 assigments... The marks were 65, 67, and 75... Sigh, I'm a efing idiot... Along with my gym mark, that means I'll barely get a low 80's average... Which is BAD. No, not bad, just HORRIBLE. I'll just die! I need at least a mid 80's. Prefferably high 80's or low 90's. Wah! I felt like dying after english class...  Oh well. I swear, even though it's time to study like mad, I've actually amped up my video gaming... I'm just terrible, aren't I? I got myself into this situtation and I'm too lazy to even try to get out of it...  Oh, and I realized soemthing. I dunno whether this means that I can't blame people for hurting me anymore but I've realized that I bring the best and worst out of people. My meek, pathetic, unassertive personality with no trace of self-confidence seems to invoke specific feelings from those around me. They will automatically do one of two things unconsciously. Either A, Take absolute control of me and push me around. The people that get these feelings will make fun of and sometimes physically abuse me. They will force me do things to help them, which is in my nature to do. On the other hand, B, Take pity on me and help me as one would take on a project of taking care of a stray dog. The people that get these feelings are, although rare, absolutely crucial to my survival. They will seemingly help me selflessly but is likely to expact something back from me, which I am over-willing to give.  U c, my very existance influence the way people treat me... So, does that mean I can't blame them? Who nos... I gotta take a shower, cya.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, I'm posting again. Didn't think I'd post so soon, did ya? Well, I'm bored and working in Fairyland so... Anyways, since the last post, there's pretty much only one thing new.  I met a really interesting person on Fairyland. Her name's Shannon and she lives in Washinton State. I can really open up to her and I find her so interesting that I want to read her like a book. Does that sound strange? Anyways, if I really wanted to, I can go on and on telling u what I no about her. But, I won't. =D.  It's so strange sometimes, how a total stranger can become such an important person in ur life in an instant. I really enjoy talking to her. More so than perhaps even my closest friends(that doesn't mean I don't love u anymore... u no what I mean). Maybe it's because she's a total stranger. If I had to open up to someone who nos me, I'd have to get them to unlearn what they already think they no about me first. But to Shannon, I can start whereever I want.  I never really went to those online chatrooms, but I wonder if I would've had a similar experience if I did. I don't think so though. It's o so difficult to find someone who'll accept u as u r. I've always struggled with that. That's y I thank God for Shannon.  Anyways, almost all my Cotton Yarns are Cloths now. So, cya next time. (Bows and exits)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, everyone, I'm back. I no I haven't posted for quite awhile and I'm sorry about that... But hey, there haven't been comments for my posts for way longer than so y should I feel guilty?  In any case, all I've been doing these days r housework, playing FL, SCII, DDRMAX, watching anime, etc. U no, usual boring summer stuff. Oh ya, I got Soul Calibur II and Unreal Tournament for PS2. Both are oldies by now, but who cares... =D  Yes, there is something interesting today. Yet another revelation. I was pretty upset for awhile... Anyways, I'm just really tired of trying my best and not being good enough. I mean, I spend 45 minutes washing the dishes to the best of my ability only to be yelled at for making a mess. They don't even give me a chance to clean it up... Can't they c that I'm doing the best I can? And that the only thing yelling will do is plant a seed in me that will sprout and make me a just-as-bad parent? Can't they c that?  It's just like gym class. Even the teacher said I tried my best and still gave me a 78. A seventy-eight... U no what that's like?! Admitting I tried my best and then giving me a 78 is like giving someone a Christmas bonus and then firing him. It's the cruelest thing possible. U no what they teach in the early years of school... It's better to aim higher and miss than to aim low and achieve. Well that is total bs. The real world isn't a comforting place that u can survive in just by trying ur best. It's harsh and cruel. There's no conselation prize for trying ur best and failing, just the harsh reality that constantly remind u that u failed. Well, screw this world, I hate it. There's no sin in hating the world, since it's so evil, right?  That felt good. =D. I miss blogging... Anyways, cya soon. And for my sake, someone please post a comment...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>