<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Canada a plague called Red Death appears and starts to kill people in a small Town. No one knows what is happening. The Red Death kills people in a disgusting manner, Red Death shows its mask to its victims before flying through them and infects them with the virus, when the victim gets infected he/she will die in 30 minutes, when the victim dies all of their blood comes from the nose, eyes, ears and mouth. As the towns population keeps shrinking, Prince Prospero, who isn’t afraid of Red Death, rounds up the 1000 strongest warriors in the land and takes them into the castle. In the castle Prince Prospero brought anything that you could imagine like, wine, entertainment and lots of food. As all of this is happening Red Death keeps killing at will, and after a while he finds that he has killed everyone in town. Red Death floats around town until he finds a sewer, so he goes down there and keeps following it until he gets to a ‘Y’ in the path…. On the right hand side he hears nothing but on the left he hears a party going on, so he took the left path.  In the castle they have no Idea what is going on in the town. They also have no idea that Red Death is with in a stones throw of them and could take them all out at once. As the party goes on into the night the sound gets smaller and Prince Prospero goes up on stage and tells everyone that there will be a Masked Ball on the next night, as Prince Prospero says this Red Death gives an evil smirk. As the party continues Red Death slips through the drain, he is unnoticed and he travels to the shadowy corner and waits there all night. When morning came Red Death was still in the corner and everyone else was a sleep except the bar tender, who walks over to Red Death and ask “shouldn’t you be getting ready for the Masked Ball?” and Red Death Replies “ I am, do you want to see my mask?” “su….” Mid sentence Red Death pulls down his hood, shows his mask to the bar tender and leaps through him infecting him with the virus, when the bar tender turns around he sees nothing except a empty courtyard. Later on that day Lt. Jeff goes and inspects the courtyard and sees the bar tender dead behind the bar, Lt. Jeff runs to Prince Prospero and knocks on his door and yells “RED DEATH IS BACK” as he says that Prince Prospero opens the door and looks at him shocked and surprised. Even later that day Prince Prospero and Lt. Jeff are in the royal quarters thinking about what they can do… after a while they think that it is just a fake and go on with their plans for the Masked Ball. That Night: “Hey you want to dance?” asks Red Death, “only If I can see your mask?’ replied the lady “sure” after she replies Red Death pulls down his hood and shows her his mask and then leaps through her and infects her with Red Death. Red Death is contagious so everyone that she touches will be infected with the virus.  In the morning Lt. Jeff wakes up in the courtyard and finds a whole pile of dead bodies and starts to count them, after he is finished he runs to Prince Prospero’s room and tells him the body count, the body count is 789. “I’m certain that Red Death is hear” says Prospero “well dah”.  Later that night Red Death is sitting in the corner waiting for someone to arrive but no one came because they were to scared to come out, so Red Death took it into his own matters and went into every room and killed everybody in each room until he got to Prospero’s room and thought about it but flew in there anyway and infected Prospero with the virus and then decided to fly away. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       At Primary school there wasn’t a lot of bullies but there was one kid named Jake. Many people were scared of him but I wasn’t, ‘cause I was his mate. Jake was very tall, he was quite big, he had big shoulders, he was also very proud (like a pit bull) and funny. He was one of my mates and one day we were playing a game and a couple of kids came up and asked if they could play. We didn’t like these kids much. So we said ‘no’. So then they decided to start teasing us. We didn’t really appreciate it. So Jake decided to dish some back at them. He teased them about not having a lot of friends, and teased them about not being very good at sports. After lunch Graham (who Jake was teasing) told a teacher and there was a lot of talk about Jake and detentions and stuff.  After that incident Jake continued too bully people but got in a lot of trouble.  The End!!!    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As the head line says ‘Planet-X down under’ is coming and its ready to rock and roll. Planet-X is possibly the biggest bike/roller skate/motorbike/skateboard comps ever!!! Many pros will be coming such as Tony Hawk, Bam Margera, Bucky Lasek, Mat Hoffman and ‘The godfather’ himself Mike Metzger.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2 Days ago Josh Young arrived at Hawaii from a personal plane from Australia. He arrived with Aaron Ziino who was a Champion/Pro in the Jet Ski tournament. Both men have won loads of major titles in their sport. Only one week ago Josh Young (who likes to be called Jay, but we will call Josh for this article) won he Billabong Tournament at  Bells Beach in Australia. Because he won this tournament he got $500,000 prize money and a sponsorship from Billabong. Aaron who arrived with him has won many a title in Jet Skiing, they have both come here to compete in tourneys for their respective sports.  Josh was wearing Billabong Board shorts woth green and gold flowers on them and a Billabong shirt. Aaron was wearing a Yamaha Shirt and a pair of Billabong board shorts.  Josh’s tournament was in the huge Hawaii waves called Jaws. The Tournament is to see how long someone can ride one of these monster waves. Aaron’s tourney is a litle dif then Josh’s, Aaron has to do time trials, insane jumps and a drag race!!! Its goning to be an awesome couple of tournaments. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday the 15th of December saw the coming of all my Graduating class at La Trobe University Union Hall. All 56 students came in great clothes, I went in jeans and a nice shirt. The night started with a couple of dances and the first lot of speeches, I was in the first group to speak. After the first group came another lot of dancing. After all that dancing there was another lot of speeches. After those speaches we done some more doncing, then more speaches, and then some more dancing. After the last lot of dancing we got our rewards and sang our songs. After that we had the opportunitie to do some free dancing to some tunes.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      April the 14th was the night of the 2004 T.V Logie Awards©. At 8:30 Network 9 showed the ‘Red Carpet Arrivals’ at the Crown Casino, all the big stars were there including: Rove McManus, Delta Goodrem and Mel Brooks. After the ‘Red Carpet Arrivals’ the live telecast began.  The show started with a bang, with Shannon Noll and Guy Sebastian singing their number 1 hits, ‘Drive’ and ‘All I Need is you’.  The first award was presented by Megan Gale, I cant remember who won but they were very excited. Some of the special presenters were Steve Irwin, Delta Goodrem, Paul Hogan and Mel Brooks. Network Ten had a great night at the Logies picking up ‘Best Light Entertainment/Comedy show’ and the ‘Big Daddy’ the Gold Logie for ‘Most Popular T.V Personality’ and many more. Network Nine also had a good night winning ‘Best Drama’, ‘Best Sport Show’ and many more.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It as really late and I started to fall asleep, when I finally fell asleep I had a dream, in this dream all I saw was a big cool mirror. I asked this mirror, “Who is the...WOW, I have huge spine like forearms and about 6 legs, anyway who is the coolest Praying Mantis of them all?” just before the mirror replied I started to hear lots of yelling and footsteps. When I looked up I saw a huge door open, and a lot of kids, around about 23.  When they started to come in I was looking around for an exit, I saw one, It was a door on the other side of the room, so just as the kids started to walk in I bolted to the door, dodging feet like a deadest champion, plus, all these big ugly kids started to try and catch me, they were jumping on the ground, making fools out of them selves. I got to the door I saw the door open, and I saw a huge person walk out, then I ran through the door just as it closed, it snipped my back leg and almost took it off.  I looked around the room and I saw that it didn’t have any kind of exit apart from the on I came in. I squeezed through the tight space between the door and the floor. When I got out no one knew I was there, so I ran along the wall and jumped up onto the tables, as I jumped for a table to another table, I felt a large sweetie hand grab me. The large hand took me to the big person at the front of the room, when he almost got there I heard a loud screech, the persons hand started to bleed over me, I must have bit him, but I cant remember, I looked at me forearms and there was blood everywhere. The person dropped me and started to cry. The large person at the front of the room picked me up and through me out the window.  &nbsp;  After she through me out I woke up, and that is the story of my great escape!!!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>