<Blog>


<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Choi Sum fresh from my Dad's garden&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My work day so far... I have shown the work that I did the night before to my neighboring colleague Petra, began to do some work on some graphical results I generated the day before I am distracted by the idea of writing a blog.   In the corner of the office, we have Mark P replacing most of the components in of the laser printer and thinking it would be cheaper to buy a brand new printer.    Sitting quietly is Mark E doing some seriously evil looking maths equation.  Ant turns up a few minutes later (around about 10.30 am) with the comment "You must all love coming in early for work!"  Ant hangs around for a few minutes before rushing off to a meeting announcing "Right, I am off to save the world..."  Juan arrives next with a loaf of bread and a tin opener.  He has just been to Hamburg and has brought the office back a present of a party sized tin of German sausages, salami and meat paste.  He sits down and tells his cohorts in supervision about yesterdays encounter with the supervisor that the two Marks missed as they went home early.  The rest of the office filters in eventually and as they discuss how they are going to heat up the sausages with what we have to hand,  I slip on my headphones to drown out the noise of the office... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can see the world around me as a soap.  At any one time there are various things happening - no single day is the same.  There is always something happening and I have my trusty PDA with which I can write my thoughts for the day to be uploaded to my blog when I have time.  I work in an office mainly with a group of men.  We are all doing PhDs in biomedical engineering with a few other students thrown in.  At its fullest capacity and the time of speaking, we have 15 people in the office, but only 14 desks - go figure.  How shall I describe my working environment?   Let me begin by describing the people that I work with:  Ant has an accent that you can instantly identify with Newcastle.  He is our resident Geordie with a heart of gold and often regales us with his adventures with his 1980 blue Mini.   D is our whiz kid boy from India, and in his short time since arriving in the UK, he has developed a taste for R&B music, clubbing and chillin'.  Juan is our man with a cosmopolitan background.  Spanish by birth brought up in Belgium and studied at university in the UK.  He speaks six languages as well as lots of computer programming languages.  He is highly intelligent and currently working on the philosophy of 'Social Punishment'.  Mark E joined our office at the same time as Juan and he is a friendly chap working on something to do with treadmills.  If we are not careful, we might be put on it...  Mark P has a research project based around the filtration of sperm for IVF - seriously - no joke!    Paul joins us from Canada for a year.  He is doing a Masters here, and working on a similar project to myself.    He is fun loving and out going and has the biggest grin and has a penchant for playing Star Wars Galaxies (a virtual world playing game).  Petra is from Brunei, and he is a quiet chap who sits closest to me.  His work often takes him away from our office and into the electronics labs where he is developing some pretty nifty hardware.  Robin has long hair and likes heavy metal - totally hands on practical guy who can make almost anything mechanical.  Talks about PICs and Star Wars Galaxies a lot to Paul.  In the sidelines we have various other students:  Pak is loosely based in our office and shares a desk with Simon.  He works with a company on a teaching scheme and we get to see him some times in the evenings when he checks his emails.  Simon is the guy who runs our university formula student team.  We rarely see him as he is often found down in the workshop building the new team car.  There are also four civil engineers in the room but they make barely a ripple, as they work quietly away completing their write-ups, like I should be doing.  So I guess this brings the introductions back to me.  And I am not going to say what I am like, but you might be able to gather from what I write a little bit about what I am like.  What I do, now that is another thing.  I am working on developing a medical instrument that might instill fear into men who reach a certain age, but that is more to do with the taboo of talking about the subject than the actual procedure being performed and I will leave it at that at the moment as I spend enough of my day thinking about the subject than to write more about it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Orchids Timmy Gave Me&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, Robin and Paul decided to join the gym.  That makes it almost the whole office that goes to the gym or does sport.  Only Juan left, and when Robin suggested that he go too, Juan replied "Sport is bad for the tabacco mate."  Now Robin is looking at the number of calories in a MacDonalds meal - and this is the guy who scoffed at me and Mark P when we used to discuss fitness and dieting last year.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This lunchtime I took Juan, Sandra and Tim to Wing Yip - a huge chinese supermarket to buy noodles.  In the shop there is row upon row of oriental produce.  Imagine a whole aisle devoted to the many types of noodles available including the Noodle King Cup Noodles - by far the most superior of noodles in a cup (in my opinon).  An hour later, laden with noodles we returned to the office to eat.  I had great fun showing my Spanish friends the joys of eating chinese cup noodles.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday morning, I get into the office and am greeted by three people and the noise of two broken lights flickering away.  Silence in this office is a rare commodity during the hours of 11 to 4 (when the rest of the office are present).  More often than not, the sound of fourteen people working is quite noisy, but for now, there are only four of us in the office.  Ting working hard writing up her thesis, Mark P writing a paper and Mark E working on MatLab, headphones on.  Right, I have work to do, and time to make the most of the silence before the hoards arrive.  Back to work, with my head phones on to cut out the noise of the lights click click clicking... as they flicker away - note to self, email estates to get the lights fixed.  ... Later, peace is shattered by the arrival of Ant singing 'We have the right to fight and to PARTY!'  Juan has arrived, and makes arrangements with me to take him noodle shopping.  The boys are discussing when to go to the pub with comments about being hungry - very hungry.  As Ant turns on James Browne and Sex Machine, we know that Friday morning has come to an end and welcome chaos for the end of the week.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are days when I wonder what is the point of doing a PhD.&nbsp; Once upon a time, I thought I would like to own a cake shop and that would be my lot in life (ok, I was about six years old at the time).&nbsp; The I thought I found that I liked taking things apart, so I thought a career as an engineer might be right for me (that was decided by the time I was fourteen).&nbsp; So far, I have progressed my career so far as to doing all the school exams to qualify entry to an engineering course at university, and then when that ended, I kind of fell into doing research.&nbsp; Now my three years are almost up, I am pondering my options.&nbsp; What do I want from life?&nbsp; Perhaps all I want is to be happy - but isn't that what every one wants?&nbsp; Happiness&nbsp;does not mean&nbsp;being rich (nor does it mean being poor) but somewhere in between.&nbsp;&nbsp; It means being happy with&nbsp;your friends and family&nbsp;and most of all to be happy about yourself, about how you live your life.&nbsp; My, I am being rather philosophical tonight.&nbsp; The last week has been a difficult week with insommnia and my mind in turmoil.&nbsp; I just need to turn the corner in my mind about what I want to do else I will drive everyone around me mad.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today has been a somewhat eventful day. Following on discovering a betrayal of trust from the day before, today was a day for fact finding. Rage and anger and tears will only get me so far - and sometimes nowhere, but once the raw emotion had subsided, rational discussions of options were possible. Never underestimate the power of those who love you to help you with your resolve. Work was trying today, but it was a day that I had to get through, saddened by the news that one of my collegues has decided to&nbsp;resign urlLink   as he will be very much missed, but also happiness that he has decided that he has taken control of his destiny. I wish him well, where ever he decides will be the next turn on his journey.&nbsp; As for what I am to do, its a case of just carrying on for a little while longer.&nbsp; This is not a fight I know I can win, but&nbsp;it is not worth&nbsp;is losing my dignity over this.&nbsp;&nbsp; A little older, a little wiser and a little less naive I have become.&nbsp; The truth&nbsp;may eventually reveal itself by&nbsp;today's events with possibilty of further scrutiny.&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday morning are never quite what you expect them to be.&nbsp;&nbsp; Petra and Mark E are eating chocolate cake left over from Ant's birthday, D has gone back to India for a bit because of a family crisis.&nbsp; Juan said he was popping down to buy some food from the shop and asked if anyone wanted anything, to which Ant promptly replied, "£1000 would be nice, along with a Swedish blonde, a bronze statue of the pope and dolphin please."&nbsp; A few minutes Juan returned, but failed to get any of the requested items, suprise suprise. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Belated Birthday to Ant.&nbsp; It really was his birthday on the the 11th.&nbsp; Last night I went bought the cake and the a case of beer since there was no Trisha DVD in sight.&nbsp; After much deliberation - a phone call to Robin yielded little help in the matter, the call to D meant&nbsp;me leaving him a random voice mail message and a phone call to Juan confirmed that he might like beer, so I bought beer.&nbsp; Juan stashed the cake and beer for me and this morning, he set about sorting out phrasing some witty remarks to accompany the beer - which ended up as a phrase in Geordie about beer and women. At this moment, the beer has already been cracked open and has been poured onto breakfast cereal - go figure!  &nbsp;  Elsewhere in the office, Robin is all excited about his new mobile phone.&nbsp; It sings, it dances&nbsp;and it probably will do everything else you want it to do.&nbsp; Well not quite, but he seems pretty excited about the it - its a Nokia something.&nbsp; Me being a mobile phone philistine, haven't a clue (even thought I am Gadget Girl.&nbsp; I am happy with a phone if I can make and recieve calls, send a few texts and tells me the time - mind you, I do like Timmy's phone because its a smart phone and you can go on MSN, but then again, I would have difficulty typing on a phone pad, but I am better than before, because now I can actually use predictive texting - an alien concept for me until recently :)   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If Ant reads this blog before tomorrow (which I am sure he won't), he will realise that there is a belated birthday suprise for him tomorrow - that is if he makes it in tomorrow.  It was his birthday on Sunday, and being busy people as we are, we forgot.  Well to be honest, I have been rather busy of late and hadn't given it much thought.  I have been number crunching so much recently that all I seem to dream about are numbers floating in the air, and in binary too - that is too freaky!   Organising birthday suprises seems to be my second occupation in the office.  For some reason, I always end up buying the cake - and I hope I am not the person to buy my own birthday cake in September.  I guess we have a tradition of buying each of our colleagues cake, not the otherway around, like in other offices.  So, what do we get Ant for his birthday?  I have no idea, but D has kindly volunteered me to get that too... Am I a sucker or what?  Hmm, I wonder, do they sell a DVD of Trisha at Costco...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I decided to work from home.  It is degree congregation time so we have lots of lost souls wandering around the campus, parking is a nightmare and to cap it all, the office opposite ours is being renovated.  Renovation in the terms where they are knocking down walls and drilling from the hours of nine to five - which is not conducive to being able to work, even with my £30 headphones from Maplin.  maybe I should have taken them back.  But then again, maybe I am avoiding the office as there is too many people about - too many interactions with so little time.  I shall have to go back to the office a little later, as there are some experiments I want to carry out, but half a day without noise is better than a whole day of noise.  And then I will finish the day off by going to see Timmy after work and maybe if I am lucky, we can have a coffee together (though we tend to drink tea instead). 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was an exceptionally wet day.  After a couple of very hot and sunny days, the weather broke with torrential rain.  I was working late this evening - in the vain hope that I would get some more stuff done for the thesis.  Writing up Chapter Two this week.  Anyway, I was on my way home and stopped off at my big sister's shop to collect my little sister and we were walking to the car which is about 100 meters away when a car drove past and splashed us from head to toe with icky rain water, to the great amusement of the the guys who run the pizza shop we were walking past.  So much for carrying an umbrella - we still got wet.  Oh well, c'est la vie! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Spiciest Snacks In The World?  urlLink      urlLink http://bumbobeonfood.blogspot.com/2004/08/spiciest-snacks-in-world.html  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>