<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well let's see... after regretting how I acted on Saturday I got back online hoping to apologize.  That didn't work.  Lisa didn't get on again.  So I talked to Kevin and Jill for a bit.  Then I went to bed after staying up as late as possible.  I really hate how I acted.  It was deliberate and I was such a jerk.  Anyways Sunday morning was the usual deal at church.  I had to do children's church that day too.  Alissa LaCourse was baptized.  All through church Kevin and Kyle were trying to get me to come to the movies.  I didn't really know what I wanted to do.  I went home and I had lunch.  I sent Lisa an email telling her I was sorry for how I acted.  Then I told her I wanted to talk to her later and explain myself.  So I decided to go to the movie.  Better than wasting my time sitting around at home.  The movie was okay.  Afterwards we hung out at the mall for a bit.  Then we ate.  I got Jay fries and a drink since he didn't have any money.  Then Kyle and I took Kevin and went to my house so I could get my shoes and tell my parents we were playing basketball at Kyle's house.  We played for awhile then I had to take Kevin home and get milk.  When I got home I saw that Lisa had sent me an email and had been on a lot that day.  I talked for a bit then asked if I could call and explain myself.  She said yes and so we talked for awhile.  I think she understands how I feel and what I see etc but IDK.  So now I've told her mostly what is on my mind.  I don't know what to do now.  I just wish I could forget about everything.  I've decided that I am going to minimize my online time as much as possible now.  I don't think it helps me and I can be more productive this way.  I just want to be so busy that I don't have to worry about thinking.  I'll be busy enough this week, and hopefully I can stay that busy.  I'd go running a whole lot more except for my knee and my ankle.  I probably should just rest for a week but I don't want to do that.  I am kinda afraid that my knees are going to turn out like my dad's.  I really don't want that to happen.  But lately they have been feeling worse and worse.  I'm hoping it is just growing pains... wouldn't that be nice.  But yeah I am pretty afraid.  I can't wait to be done with living.  Why do we have to have such a long lifespan?  (Incase anyone is reading this I'm not suicidal, I just don't want to have to deal with everything.)  I'm so sick of feeling like this.  I just want to be happy, not being dragged around emotionally.  Oh well... off to work/chores/family gatherings... woohoo.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I did it... as usual.  I was just online not doing much of anything useful and Lisa got on.  I had made it clear in my away message I wouldn't be initiating any conversations.  So after about 10 minutes Lisa IMed me.  I gave her the lukewarm shoulder.  Then she asked about the "I'm confused but I'm still here for you" in my profile and I didn't want to talk about it.  So I told her that.  Then I ignored her for the most part then I left.  I don't know what I'm trying to do.  I don't want to hurt her but I do in a way.  I've tried to talk to her about how I feel but it didn't really matter.  So yeah I feel like an idiot and a jerk.  If she gets back on I'll apologize but I don't know if I want to get into how I feel yet.  On a lighter note I must agree that Stand Up by Skillet By VeggieTales is actually pretty good.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's a really good song but I almost wonder if it is having a negative impact on me.  I know who is singing the song and to whom it is being sung but still... I almost want to take it out of context.  Oh well... yes if you couldn't have guessed this Lisa thing is still driving me nuts.  She didn't come to YG last night (which was a blast BTW.)  She had said that she might not come if her foot was hurting her.  Oh well.  I find it interesting how she isn't online by noon I almost wonder if she went out to a friends house.  I know I shouldn't be thinking so negatively but I can't help it.  I really feel she is avoiding me.  She won't talk about it either.  Every time I try she has to go.  I'm deciding if I want to write a letter or not.  I don't want to pressure her but I also can't stand not knowing.  I just want to know what is going on in her life and she won't tell me.  Which would be okay if she made it clear that she didn't want to tell me but she hasn't.  I'm sick of talking about this.  YG last night was good.  Jillian came it was fun to talk to her in person.  We were waiting for her and for Kristin.  Jen was funny.  We were waiting for Kristin.  "Just 5 more minutes... and after that 5 more and after that 5 more until she gets here."  We waited for 10 minutes then we went to the mini-golf course and left Kristin a note on the church door.  We got there and about 5 minutes after we got there Kristin pulled in.  We played in 3 groups.  Frank and Elaine with Nate and Jeff in one group.  Renee, Steph, Allison, Jillian, and Lydia in another.  Then Kyle, Kevin, Myself, Jen and Kristin in the last group.  It was fun.  I saw Dave Bernhardt but I didn't get to talk to him.  It was also pretty windy.  Being the genius I am I wore shorts and a light polyester shirt.  So I was a little on the chilled side.  Jen was our Martin for the night.  She managed to get a 5 on almost every hole.  She would just smack the ball as hard as she could.  We went back to the church and covered the cans for change donations.  I got them working on those and then I went upstairs to talk to Pat.  They got the sound system sounding beautiful now.  We can use the sidefills and the board runs much nicer.  Pat was showing me how to blast everything.  It was great... I can't wait to get in there sometime and get in trouble.  I have to put it to the test otherwise we won't know what it is capable of.  Then I went back downstairs and finished off some ice cream.  I also had an "accident" in which I sprayed the people behind me with the hose from the sink.  Kevin dumped his cup of water on my head after.  Renee gave the devo which was good.  Then back home and to my bed.  I found out that Allison and Jeff like dc Talk so I'm going to let them borrow my collection.  Then there was this morning.  I got up, went running (3 miles) in 21 minutes.  It wasn't a bad time but I should be able to do better.  I'm not telling anyone but my knees are killing me when I run.  I hope it is just them getting used to it but I don't know.  My dad is getting me a new little gadget he found while reading a magazine at therapy.  It is a watch with a GPS system built into it.  So it can tell you exact distances, your speed, you can set waypoints and it will help you keep pace.  It is a really cool thing.  So I should have it within 2 weeks.  Now I'm sitting here doing nothing but writing about my pathetic life.  But I just need to get these things off my chest before I explode.  Kyle asked me if I wanted to go to see Shrek 2 tomorrow.  IDK I know the only reason he wants me there is to say 1) he asked people and 2) so he can say Jeremy was there.  While I would like to see Shrek 2, we'll see.  I don't want to be there as someone's excuse.  It is Kyle, Kevin, Steph, and Jen so it is basically a double date.  Except they won't admit that and they want someone there to make it not a double date.  So thinking about it that way I don't think I'm going to go.  If they get enough people that it won't be me and one other person I might do it.  But if that other person is Lisa I don't know either.  Of course if she is avoiding me she won't want to go.  Then again she didn't like the first Shrek so she probably won't want to go to this one.  It looks like this Friday I'll be able to go to the Audio Adrenaline concert.  That is going to be a blast.  I am working Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday this week for Bobi doing AntiqueFest stuff.  No more priming walls or roofing roofs.  Well I'm gonna go code and hopefully not think about any of this.  Until the next time I need to think through things (probably tomorrow.)
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well let's see.  Today was okay.  I didn't really feel all that much Lisa-wise.  Which was very good.  I woke up, got online, talked with Kevin (he updated his site  urlLink Here .)  Then I fixed the weedwacker which took a good half-hour.  Grandpa showed up to pick it up then I went to brownick to mow.  The mower was totally screwed up.  So mi padre y yo fuimos a casa.  We loaded our mower into the truck (it didn't really fit so that was a fun ride.)  I mowed Brownick then went to Liverpool looking for Kyle.  Didn't see him there.  Drove over to his house didn't see him there either.  Drove by Wegmans saw his car there.  All totaled there were a lot of bodies from all my driving by.  I came home then I decided to kill myself... 9 miles!  I ran it in 69 minutes too.  Which for you humanities majors is 7:40 miles.  Then I came home and ate dinner (Fillet Mignon :-).)  Kyle dropped by before dinner.  I went over around 7 to help him fix up the yard.  Afterwards we played ping-pong for a bit.  Then I came home and I'm writing here.  Oh yeah I only have to do 55 pushups and then I have met my 1K goal for this week.  So now I'm talking to Jill and relaxing.  I really love talking to Jill.  For her age she is shockingly mature.  I really like it.  She is a really good friend.  But off to bed now!  Work tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      	Jskuros: Can anyone give me tips on getting someone to download a  netdevil trojan server from me so i can get into their system?  Lineman: Tell them it's an elite hacking tool. That appears to work  like a charm.  Jskuros: where do you recommend i try to get people to download it and  do you have anyones ip address and port that already have the server  that i can tamper with?  Lineman: I would try 127.0.0.1. I'd bet almost anything that they are  infected with the trojan. Probably some pathetic script kiddie.  Jskuros: sorry how would i do that - thanks for helping me  Lineman: If they hav a trojan, they probably left their system wide  open. Try logging in through your internet browser. Just enter this in  IE or wherever: \127.0.0.1\c$ If they left their system unsecured, you  will be able to access their hard drive with this.  Jskuros: That lamer is running windows!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My day was going great until Lisa got on.  I really hate saying this but lately she hasn't been herself and it is really hurting me.  I don't know what it is.  I mean I think I do but I'm not sure.  I really hate this and what is worse is Lisa doesn't see how it is hurting me.  After talking to her for 25 minutes tonight I just wanted to cry.  I feel like she doesn't want me in her life anymore or that everything she says to me is forced.  I almost want to nail her down and try explaining everything to her but IDK.  I'd rather know I'm hated or whatever than her pretending and me wondering.  Life aside from Lisa is good.  Jill should be at YG this Friday which would be great.  Lisa still doesn't know if she is coming to YG.  I'm undecided on that one.  IDK.  I found my new life's verse.  Proverbs 24:13a "Eat thou honey my son for it is good."  Who says God isn't a guy?  Well as down as I am sounding I am not all that depressed.  I am just confused and not liking how things are.  I ran 9 miles today and did 75 pushups already.  I've got to do more if I want to meet my goal of 1000.  I'm going to be so ripped soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well let's see what do I need to get off my chest.  Well its all related isn't it.  I'm feeling empty like I have nothing to live for.  I'm still getting used to my relationship with Lisa.  I really don't know what it is now.  I am so confused.  I wish I could just go sleep and wake up and things would be great.  Right now I kinda wish I had never met Lisa so I wouldn't have to deal with all this.  Not because I don't like her but because I do.  I just wish I could understand what is going through her mind right now.  I know she is a flirt, and I know she likes one of the guys who runs track at another school.  And lately I kinda feel like I am being dismissed.  Like right after she told me she thought we should change things she made it seem like she wanted to forget me.  I know I am probably paranoid but what can I say?  I am so tired of feeling like this.  I hate it.  After not talking to her since Tuesday I get to talk to her for about half an hour and I don't get a single thing out of her.  She said she might not come to YG because she hurt her feet.  While I understand that, I don't understand how she can go to school and still go to practice (which she said she was at today) but not come to YG.  Then tonight I get online and I say Hi, she says Hi.  She goes away for 3 minutes.  Comes back I get to say 3 sentences and then she says she has to leave.  So our total conversation was about 5 minutes.  I was looking forward to seeing her today but Steph's meet was cancelled.  So Kevin and I hung out.  I need to ask her sometime tomorrow if she knows where the meet on Thursday is.  I really don't know what kind of answer I'll get.  If I get the feeling that she doesn't want me there then I'll know I just need to forget everything.  I won't mention that I want to bring Kevin.  I really feel like crying right now.  I just hate how I feel.  I want things to be better but IDK when that will happen.  Thankfully I get to work all day tomorrow.  So I hopefully won't have to deal with how I feel till later that night if at all.  Kevin and I were going to go to Steph's meet today but it was rained out.  So instead I brought Kevin to my house and we played ping-pong for a bit.  Then I took him out to dinner.  We ate at Chili's.  The waitress there made us feel like little kids.  She kneeled down when she talked to us.  Aside from that the food was excellent.  But I get even more confused about my life when I talk to Kevin.  Cause he and Lisa talk a lot and she tells him how she feels, much the same way I tell Jill.  So he has these little interjections that make me wonder if he is teasing or if he knows what he is talking about.  But all this being miserable about my relationship or whatever it is with Lisa has left me feeling pretty depressed.  I don't think I realized how much she meant to me.  I mean it feels like I lost a kidney or some other vital organ... say a heart.  I almost feel like asking Lisa to level with me on everything but then again if what I think is right I don't really want to know.  Right now without knowing much of anything this is what I think.  And I could be totally wrong and IDK if I want to be wrong or if I want to be right.  I guess I feel that Lisa still likes me and that she didn't like where it was going.  That she doesn't want me to know that she still likes me because then it would cause me to act differently.  Like I said I don't know what I want right now.  I wish I could just disappear and come back in 5 years... maybe 10.... heck why come back at all.  I wish I knew what to do.  I know I haven't said it because I don't want to start something or cause something to happen that shouldn't but I know I still love her.  I don't know if she knows this but it is true.  Everything I said to her online and on the phone and wherever I meant.  I think she is very unique and I truly love her.  Altho I can say that I'm not the only one.  I really don't know what to do.  I don't want to date her (again) because it would probably end up killing everything this time... but I do want to be around her and be the one she looks to.  Oh well.  All this makes me feel pretty empty.  I almost feel purposeless.  Oh big long words I know but hey.  For the longest time my life was devoted to making Lisa happy.  I know I probably shouldn't have let it become like that but it is true.  Lisa was and IDK I guess still is the highlight of my day.  It is hard and not a whole lot of fun right now.  No one really knows how I feel.  I've been able to hide this from everyone.  I haven't even told Jill.  As far as everyone knows I'm happily single.  And don't let me get myself wrong... I know I need to be single right now, I know I need to be concentrating on things other than girls... (namely one) but I can't do it right now.  It is seriously no fun.  The only good thing about being so depressed or angry or IDK what I am is that I am getting to be a giant.  425 pushups since Friday.  At this rate I should have done about 1000 by YG this Friday.  Fun isn't it.  I'm also running more and I'm getting in better shape all around.  Pretty soon I'm going to be unstoppable.  The only bad thing about being in good shape and being muscular is that unfortunately most of the time the other sex is attracted to it.  Allissa who came to YG a total of 3 times maybe and who've I've talked to online very little lately talked to me yesterday.  She told me she had a crush on me and it was pretty evident that she still does.  I just don't want to deal with relationships anymore.  I wish I could just stop thinking about Lisa and I.  I want to be the old me.  The one who didn't care about who liked him.  Was that ever me?  IDK.  I don't know what I want.  I want to be happy I guess.  But that might mean giving things up that I care a lot for.  Life... grand isn't it?  Well I'm off to do a couple hundred pushups or so.  I think I am going to aim for 1200 pushups by Friday.  Which means that I need to get cracking.  Only 4 days left.  With 775 pushups to go I need to do about 200 a night.  Maybe I'll pop my shoulders out of their joints and be able to not think... wouldn't that be nice.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      let's see... Sunday morning I got up and sent that journal entry off to Lisa.  I think I explained how I felt clearly enough that she understands... or at least I hope so.  I'm really having a hard time with this.  I agree that it isn't the right timing for us to be dating, that I'd rather have her as a friend, that I think we did the right thing... but I am really struggling with it.  I'm so used to having one good female friend to talk to and tell them everything on my mind.  So while I still want that and I would love for it to be Lisa it kinda hinders her.  I don't think she realizes how she acts with all her guy friends affects her other guy friends.  I want her to have good guy friends but I wouldn't mind if she kinda held back a little or whatever.  She really does a number on my emotions when she mentions how she owes some guys kisses etc.  I don't want to feel that way but I can't help it.  Another thing that has been driving me nuts is that I can't stop thinking about her.  I feel like I am back where I was before I told her I liked her.  All I can do is think about her and day dream.  It is really hard to not feel empty or whatever when she isn't around.  Like I talked to her on Tuesday and she had a meet last night and I had bible study so I didn't get to talk to her.  She has a meet in Camden today and I probably won't be able to talk to her tonight either.  Then tomorrow she is leaving for Rochester with Courtney for a dance competition.  So she won't be at YG or online.  She will be there for Saturday and most of Sunday.  So it will be about what 5 days?  I know it sounds sad and pathetic and hopeless but that is me.  I know dating her right now isn't what I should be doing but I still love her.  Speaking of that I made the unfortunate mistake of getting onto an AOL account and reading her profile.  She told me once that she wished I could see it because it was how she really felt.  Well I read it and well... the thing that stuck in my mind was "I can't wait until I make you mine" and things kinda like that.  Which I'm wondering if she still feels that way or if she just hasn't gotten around to changing them yet... IDK.  I really don't like dealing with all this uncertainty.  I almost wish I hadn't gotten involved with Lisa not because I don't like her but because this has seriously hurt my relationship with her.  It isn't anything she'll ever know but it is still something that is bouncing around in my head.  Let's see about the rest of my week.  Sunday was uneventful... aside from talking to Lisa for about 5 hours.  Monday I went to Bobi's and helped her there.  That night I talked to Lisa for awhile.  I really am glad that I have a friend like Jill.  Sometimes it feels like Jill is the only person I can talk to.  It is great to have Jill to talk to and bounce how I am feeling off.  Tuesday I went to Ron and Bobi's too.  I mowed and then helped at their rental house.  Tuesday I also talked to Lisa and Jill.  Renee was on too so I talked for a bit but she was kinda preoccupied.  Wednesday was okay.  I didn't do much.  Then there was today.  I dropped the Knicks off at the airport.  Then I got online.  And I'm writing this and I'm harassing Kevin.  I don't think I've laughed this much in a long time.  It feels really good.  We're picking armies, I managed to get Lisa, Jen, Renee, Alex, and Nate.  Kevin has been begging me for Lisa or Jen.  He isn't getting either.  Time to go tho.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well let's see.  I guess I am gonna write my life's story in here.  Well up until 6 days ago my life consisted of thinking of Lisa.  We "broke up" on Sunday and so this week has been a roller coaster ride emotionally.  I knew it needed to happen but I wasn't planning on doing it right away.  I wanted to wait until she was out of school and done with track etc.  So when we talked on the phone for awhile and then I asked her what she wanted to talk about.  She said that she felt that she didn't know me and didn't really know what she felt.  So I kinda figured that she wanted to change something.  So she was the one who said it but it was quite relieving.  I had told God that if anyone was going to end it, it was going to have to be Lisa.  Well God listened and took care of it.  Afterwards I thought I was okay.  I cried a little then I got online and talked to her there for a bit.  That night was really hard.  I cried for about 3 hours and then I finally fell asleep.  Monday was tough, cause all I could do was think about how I felt.  I felt relieved and really sad at the same time.  For the past couple of months Lisa was all I could think about and everything I did was for her.  I knew I shouldn't be focusing on her so much or even at all.  So I had decided that I would take care of things but when was the question.  It could have hurt a whole lot more than it did, God was really looking out for me.  So Tuesday I went to Albany with Kevin.  We rode down and I ate like crazy.  We hung out for awhile during the rally.  I saw Josh and Caleb Stauter, Greg and Aidan Cleghorn, and Josh Siddall.  Caleb as usual was flirting with the girls, Josh as usual was debating with Greg and Aidan.  Greg had dislocated his arm earlier that week.  So he gets the klutz of the year award so far.  He broke someone's nose and gave himself a concussion at the same time in one of our earlier soccer games.  He was going for a header.  It was beautiful.  Then we had to go and hand out fliers.  So many good Mexican jokes since Kevin had to give one to Assemblyman Jose Rivera.  On the ride back I told Kevin what went on Sunday and he was kinda shocked.  Then I went to Steph's meet and saw Kyle there and hung out for a bit.  I was good and didn't just spill how I really felt.  So I came home afterwards.  By now I was doing better but at night and in the shower it still wasn't fun.  Wednesday I had two tests.  Spanish and Fundamentals of Computer Science, both at 10:30.  I woke up that morning and kinda forgot that I had to do 10 pages in my Spanish workbook that was due then.  So I flew to school and sat in my car doing the exercises.  Then I got out and realized that the tests were at 10:30.  I had been thinking they were at 10 so I had gotten there way too early.  So I relaxed and focused on the tests.  I had been doing my devos regularly and so I was thinking about Hosea.  It is so nice to know that even when I willingly walk away from what I should be doing, I'm still forgiven and welcomed back with arms open wide.  I went in and took my spanish test.  Then he didn't have my workbook graded yet so I ran over to the other side of the campus and took my Fundamentals of Computing final.  I had it finished in under 10 minutes.  I walked into the class late and there were 4 people in there.  When I left there were still 4 people in there.  I ran back over to Academic and grabbed my notebook.  Then I ran back across campus to my car and went home.  I hung out at home the rest of the day.  By now I am getting used to the idea of how my relationship with Lisa is gonna work.  Thursday was pretty boring.  I mowed Brownick's lawn in the morning then I was thinking about going to Phoenix to see those who were there... A.K.A Lisa.  But Kyle wasn't free so, and I didn't really know how I was going to handle myself.  I went to Wegmans to harass him.  I was good tho.  So I went with my mom to pick the van up from the garage.  Then I did pretty much nothing.  While I am thinking... I talked to Lisa on Wednesday and I made an idiot of myself.  I opened my mouth and inserted my foot as far as it could go.  Oh well she is still talking to me.  I couldn't have made that much of an idiot out of myself.  Friday was okay.  I crammed for my math test in the morning.  I either aced it or flunked it.  I cleaned my room and my bathroom and the whole basement.  Kyle and Kevin came and spent the night.  That was interesting.  Kevin told me how he thought Jen wanted to breakup with him.  Then Kyle showed up late as usual.  Then he found out about Lisa and I.  So Kyle and Kevin had a blast with that.  It was great to laugh but it got kinda old after about 3 hours of it.  We ate and watched Batman.  The original movie.  It was pretty corny, which made it even funnier.  It's amazing how logical they are.  Then there was today.  Earlier this morning we were goofing off.  Ethan got to play ping-pong with Kyle.  Even tho I had to move him and help him hit the ball he had a blast.  The smile and the hug and the thanks I got from him was awesome.  Then he went upstairs and bragged to my parents about how he beat Kyle.  I love my bro so much.  Then we went to the "carwash."  We decided not to do it after all so we went back to the church after eating at TacoBell.  We played soccer for about an hour and a half.  It was so much fun.  Of course I could do without all the blisters and the sprained ankle but hey it was worth it.  I loved playing against Lisa.  Her competitiveness is one of the things that I liked about her right from the start.  She was throwing her body around and bumping and thumping just as much as me.  Then she started getting cheap.  Grabbing me and trying to take me out.  I had fun teasing her about it.  I also got to talk to her a lot more than I have before at a YG.  She noticed it too.  So all in all it was a good YG.  Well now that I know what my week has been like, let's talk about what I think about it all.  The things that I've been thinking about a lot lately are Lisa... DUH, school, and where my life is going.  Let's start with the easier of the three.  I really have no idea what I am going to do with my life.  I want to be doing something useful and fun.  I told my mom that I had thought about enlisting in the military just to jump out of planes and run around.  I really don't want a deskjob.  I want to be doing something active.  So I am really questioning if I should be in computer science at all.  Then since I am questioning what I want to do with my life that kinda asks where I want to go to school.  I am going to get as much finished with my CS degree as possible but then IDK.  RIT might not be a possibility since the stupid GED requirements are out there.  So I might have to go out of state.  The other possibility is Word Of Life.  Hang out for a year.  Then decide what I want to do with my life.  Who knows, I know I don't.  Well I guess that leaves me with Lisa doesn't it.  Well I don't really know how I feel.  So let's start with the things I know for sure.  I love her as a sister.  I think she is an awesome friend that I am not willing to lose.  After that I really don't know.  I loved being able to talk to her today relatively pain free.  I guess this is what I want in the long run, but I don't know.  I am trying to tell myself everything will be okay.  But I can't see it and it is really annoying me.  I really hate a lot of the things that are running through my head.  I know I am going to have a hard time when she dates someone else.  I would like to think she won't but then I'd just be stupid.  I really don't like emotions sometimes.  I want to be a close friend but I don't know if I can do that easily, especially if she is dating someone else.  Something that has been bugging me is when she would say she loves me or whatever, is when did that change.  Like I know she would say it to Joe, and then tell me how she didn't mean it.  It has really made me rethink a lot of what I know about her.  The whole waiting forever for me deal etc.  I guess I am having a little trust issue.  When I told her I agreed that we needed to change things I think she took that as I didn't like her anymore.  If I didn't like her anymore then it would have been so easy to end it but it wasn't easy.  I don't know what I am going to do.  I really hate this sometimes, why couldn't I just disappear.  I want to be a good friend but it is going to be hard for me when she finds someone else she likes.  Oh well I'll cross that bridge when I come to it.  I need to go to bed and get some sleep before I start getting too depressed.  Maybe I'll finish the deck of cards tonight.  The one good thing about being stressed and having a hard time is that I get so much stronger.  I mean I've done over 400 pushups in 5 days.  My chest has visibly gotten larger and so have my arms.  It is kinda cool.  I'm gonna need to get a bigger bra soon.  I really hope I can stop thinking about all this because it is really cutting into my sleeping time.  I'm so tired but whenever I go to bed I can't fall asleep before 2AM.  Then I always wake up around 6AM and just lay there.  However today at YG was the first YG in a long time that I've been able to just relax and be me (or at least something much closer to resembling the real me.)
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well it's been awhile since I posted.  Part of it is cause I have been busy, too tired, oh yeah I broke my arm too... that might have something to do with it.  Lets see Saturday I broke it playing paintball.  I broke it while I was capturing the flag, I tripped on the way back and heard it pop.  But I did pick the flag back up and kept running to score.  I walked back holding my wrist, it hurt a little everyone said I was white like a sheet.  So I went to the ER.  I got to sit around for 3 hours while they got around to fixing me.  They decided just to splint my arm instead of setting it.  So I went home and went to church on Sunday.  I wasn't in that much pain which was good.  Monday I went to see the doctor.  He said he would need to sedate me to set it.  Tuesday morning I went in to the hospital to be knocked out and set.  That went well I woke up from my drugs by a wonderful nurse... not.  I recovered for a bit then I got dressed and went home.  I ate 2 subs for lunch.  Then I just hung out.  They put a giant cast on so I can't move my elbow.  It's a real pain.  Wednesday I wasn't allowed to drive till noon.  So I got to Bobi's around 12:30 or so.  I finished up some work for her and headed home around 5.  Thursday was a fun day.  I got up and over to Bobi's a little late cause I took a bath.  I organized all the tent markers and walked through the park to get an idea of where everything is.  Then I went to the mall.  I got a card for Lisa and her present, a card for my dad, and some batteries for my new mouse I've ordered.  Then home and dinner.  Then I got online, big mistake.  I talked to Lisa for awhile then she brought something up.  Then she wouldn't talk about it.  See below:    20:57:14 livingoutloud777: *hears Lisa mutter something about how much of a pain Guys are* 20:57:40 lisxc7234: its true. 20:57:48 lisxc7234: although i thought last night and it actually scared me. 20:57:50 lisxc7234: haha 20:58:08 livingoutloud777: You thought?  That scares me too :-P 20:59:17 lisxc7234: yeah it was weird.. 20:59:18 lisxc7234: Lol 20:59:24 lisxc7234: lets just say im looking for SLU 20:59:25 lisxc7234: haha 20:59:29 lisxc7234: forward* 20:59:40 livingoutloud777: LOL Why? To get away? 21:00:18 lisxc7234: yes and no 21:00:20 lisxc7234: hahaha 21:00:27 lisxc7234: im done telling you my secrest 21:00:29 lisxc7234: secrets 21:00:31 lisxc7234: haha 21:01:00 livingoutloud777: LOL Okay... I'll just assume what I want then :-P 21:01:53 lisxc7234: okay that works for me because you have no idea, and you dont have proof 21:02:19 livingoutloud777: LOL 21:02:47 livingoutloud777: Well why don't you want to tell me? 21:03:14 lisxc7234: lol because lol.. its not your business haha 21:03:15 lisxc7234: :-P 21:03:18 lisxc7234: idk 21:03:23 lisxc7234: i just dont really want to 21:03:39 livingoutloud777: :-P You're afraid 21:03:47 lisxc7234: no., 21:03:51 lisxc7234: thats not it.. 21:04:01 lisxc7234: it doesnt concern you either so yeah 21:05:06 livingoutloud777: Okay whatever you want 21:06:38 livingoutloud777: But Lisa if you want to learn how to not be so annoying don't bring those things up 21:07:14 lisxc7234: well i was just saying sorry 21:10:11 livingoutloud777: It's annoying when someone says "I have a secret but I'm not telling you", makes me feel like you don't trust me or something.  Just keep it in mind for later 21:11:22 lisxc7234: well its not that i dont trust you.. but i just thought how i wanted to have bf, but then realized what happened bewteen me and the joe at my school and how busy i was.. thats all its nothing important if that makes you feel anybetter, but sometimes i girl just wants a bf, to be able to comfort and cuddle with ehr thats all and i was in one of those moods last night 21:11:29 lisxc7234: im sorry i said anything to begin with 21:12:57 lisxc7234: i have to go ill ttyl lylab bye Lisa disconnected (21:13:01)   So I sent her an email that night.  Lisa,  	I didn't get to say what I wanted to before you got off.  You need to understand this.  I don't care what you do when it comes to a boyfriend.  I mean I care about how you are doing and how it is going but I don't care if you date etc.  And I know what you mean about wanting someone to comfort you etc.  So you don't need to apologize for feeling that way.  I want only to be a friend.  I would like to know what is going on in your life and talk to you about the guys in your life the way I do with Jillian or Jen or my cousin.  I mean if you don't want me to that is fine I am pretty good at ignoring things.  I just don't want you thinking I'm jealous or whatever, I'm really not.  It might be hard to believe or whatever but it is true.  And I really hope you don't think of me as an ex (or etc), cause that isn't how I think of you.  You are a good friend Lisa and I don't want something like this to change it.  I hope you have a good day tomorrow (probably today when you read this) and maybe I'll talk to you on the weekend.  Jeremy   Friday was fun, I didn't do much of anything at Bobi's.  I got online that night IMed Lisa and she just ignored me.  That was cool.  One more reason to be ticked.  Saturday we had this convo:   12:31:41 livingoutloud777: (Ignore me if you want and I'll get the hint :-P but since you don't have an away message up)   Hey 12:31:48 lisxc7234: hey 12:33:10 lisxc7234: I didnt once think you were going to get jealous i was hoping that you werent, but i didnt think it would bug you, i just like to keep somethings to myself. 12:34:40 livingoutloud777: Okay I understand that I just didn't know what you thought, then when you ignored me yesterday... :-P  IDK You sure have interesting ways of communicating :-P 12:36:10 lisxc7234: Well yesterday i was mad because my mother has really started to be getting at me, and its really making me mad. And idk i just thought that you didnt need toknow but you keep nagging at it.. and it made me mad.. because  most of the time im an independent person 12:37:52 livingoutloud777: Didn't need to know you and your mom were having troubles?  And how do I nag? :-P  I thought only females could do that JK!!  I really want to know why you feel I nag because if I can change it I will.  You just have to tell me :-P  I failed mind reading class 12:39:28 lisxc7234: yeah well i didnt, idk you just kept bugging me about it, and i dont like to be bugged about something it really makes me p.oed and my brother was like oh your 3 mintues over so i had no chance to see what you had said because he was standing over my shoulder and watching what i was typing 12:42:13 livingoutloud777: Okay so I think you are finally making some sense :-P  Just cause you bring it up doesn't mean you want to talk about it and I shouldn't talk about it unless you do? 12:42:42 lisxc7234: yes! 12:42:45 lisxc7234: lol:-P 12:43:22 livingoutloud777: *shakes head* Then what is the point in bringing it up in the first place? 12:43:33 lisxc7234: Because you wanted to know! 12:44:43 lisxc7234: anyways how are you? 12:45:08 livingoutloud777: Look I don't want to argue all these little points but you need a memory refresher 12:45:12 livingoutloud777: 20:52:09 lisxc7234: lol thats good, hows the house? any better? 20:52:33 livingoutloud777: Yeah it is quieter, but still kinda tense 20:53:36 livingoutloud777: How's your life? Alex and your dad doing better? 20:54:07 lisxc7234: idk,.. my mom was gotten, umm.. how can i say this.. 12:45:46 lisxc7234: im confused.. 12:45:55 lisxc7234: What was that supposed to be showing me? 12:47:53 livingoutloud777: 12:43:22 livingoutloud777: *shakes head* Then what is the point in bringing it up in the first place? 12:43:33 lisxc7234: Because you wanted to know!   I asked because you mentioned it in the first place.  It isn't like I came out of the blue and asked.  But really how am I to know what you want to talk about and what you don't? 12:48:17 lisxc7234: wait, i was tlaking about the boy stuff, 12:48:22 lisxc7234: i dont mind explaining that stuff 12:49:44 livingoutloud777: 12:36:10 lisxc7234: Well yesterday i was mad because my mother has really started to be getting at me, and its really making me mad. And idk i just thought that you didnt need toknow but you keep nagging at it.. and it made me mad.. because  most of the time im an independent person  It being boys or your mom? 12:50:29 lisxc7234: it was being the boys 12:52:37 lisxc7234: idk, i dont mind talking about whats going on with my family, it was just bugging me that you wanted toknow soo bad about what i was thinking about about the boys.. 12:54:31 livingoutloud777: LOL :-P Lisa had you made it clear that would be one thing, but you didn't. 12:54:58 lisxc7234: forget it, i dont want to tlak about it anymore, it was on thurs. for goodness sakes 12:55:43 livingoutloud777: Yeah well I want to get it worked out because I am sick of misunderstanding you and you misunderstanding me 12:56:13 lisxc7234: it was stupid to begin with...  12:56:55 livingoutloud777: Fine nvm 13:02:51 lisxc7234: i gtg ill ttyl lylab bye  13:03:00 livingoutloud777: Bye Lisa disconnected (13:03:20) 21:41:49 lisxc7234: hey you okay? or you dont have to talk if you dont wanna Lisa disconnected (22:01:08) Lisa connected (22:01:14) 22:02:31 lisxc7234: hey i hope you feel better.. sorry if it deals with me, Lisa disconnected (22:02:43)   I had an away message up the second time she imed me that said:   I'm sick of this.  Unless your name has a V, N or K (or all three) in it leave me alone  I don't know and I don't know if I care either   I was so ticked at her.  I still am not happy.  Church was good.  This afternoon and all today with Lisa:   12:59:32 livingoutloud777: I don't have long, no I don't hate you, I just don't know what I feel right now.  I'm tired of some things and well enough for now 13:00:02 lisxc7234: okay then 13:03:39 livingoutloud777: I'll explain it later maybe once I've eaten 13:03:45 lisxc7234: okay. Lisa went away (13:06:00) Away Message: "grabbing the strawberries..  bbs " (13:06:00) Lisa came back (13:07:33) 13:10:24 livingoutloud777: Lisa I'm not going to say I'm not a little mad but I do care and I don't hate you.  I do want you to come to Lake Ann because I think you'll have fun but it is up to you. 13:11:35 lisxc7234: Thats the thing i want to talk about it, but you have to leave so yeah 13:12:08 livingoutloud777: Well I am here for 10 minutes or more, I just don't want to gave to stop once I start 13:12:15 livingoutloud777: *have 13:12:24 lisxc7234: yeah thats what i figured 13:14:17 livingoutloud777: You don't have any plans for today aside from watching the race? 13:14:31 lisxc7234: thats it. 13:19:14 livingoutloud777: You going to be online for awhile during it? 13:19:25 lisxc7234: idk 13:19:31 lisxc7234: it depends i might go study 13:20:14 livingoutloud777: Well if you are on we can talk otherwise there can be later 13:20:23 lisxc7234: okay. 13:23:22 lisxc7234: so when are you leaving? 13:23:34 livingoutloud777: IDK whenever lunch is ready 13:23:44 lisxc7234: oh 13:24:47 livingoutloud777: Why? I'll leave now if you want :-P 13:24:55 lisxc7234: no i was just wondering 13:31:54 livingoutloud777: Kevin tell you why he was mad? 13:32:01 lisxc7234: no 13:32:22 lisxc7234: prolly because i said that i didnt want to go to lake ann.. because it feelslike every is mad, or upset with me  13:32:26 lisxc7234: but thats my guess 13:32:32 livingoutloud777: Nope :-P 13:32:42 lisxc7234: why? 13:32:44 lisxc7234: what/ 13:33:11 livingoutloud777: They are making a rule that guys and girls can't sit together on the bus :-P 13:33:23 lisxc7234: really? 13:33:29 livingoutloud777: 13:13:56 mxpxacoustic: i am SOO mad now 13:14:56 mxpxacoustic: hows Kyle? 13:15:06 livingoutloud777: I didn't tell him 13:15:36 mxpxacoustic: omg 13:15:37 livingoutloud777: BRB Doing the garbage 13:15:41 mxpxacoustic: he is gonna flip 13:33:39 livingoutloud777: Yeah I guess 13:34:21 lisxc7234: oh. 13:34:31 lisxc7234: well ill still end up sitting by myself so oh well 13:34:43 livingoutloud777: LOL So am I :-P 13:34:50 livingoutloud777: Wit da brothas 13:35:10 lisxc7234: lol well now either kevin or kyle will want to sit with you. 13:35:28 livingoutloud777: Over my dead body :-P 13:35:33 lisxc7234: why? 13:35:35 livingoutloud777: I'll explain later 13:35:43 livingoutloud777: Lunch time, ttyl lylas 13:35:52 lisxc7234: okay ttyl lylab bye 14:06:58 lisxc7234: MY JEFFY IS IN THE LEAD *IN HIGH VOICE* 14:07:01 lisxc7234: :-) 14:07:12 livingoutloud777: *rolls eyes* 14:07:14 livingoutloud777: :-P 14:07:21 lisxc7234: hey im happy:-) 14:07:30 lisxc7234: Lol i also ran 6 miles today  14:08:18 lisxc7234: dude he is wicked p***sed. his word too. not mine 14:08:44 livingoutloud777: LOL 14:09:12 livingoutloud777: Well what do you expect :-P 14:10:15 lisxc7234: lol idk i didnt think it was that important they will prolly be sleeping anyways! 14:10:45 livingoutloud777: Which is why they are making it like that 14:12:10 lisxc7234: right.. idk maybe im just weird 14:12:34 lisxc7234: kevin is really upset, and hes gunna make it worse by talking to kyle about it:-14:12:59 livingoutloud777: Well I'm not afraid, they can complain all they want 14:13:10 lisxc7234: well, they think that they are going to get a say in it 14:13:50 livingoutloud777: LOL They can keep thinking that 14:14:05 lisxc7234: lol 14:14:06 lisxc7234: anyways 14:15:20 livingoutloud777: My reason for not sitting with them is this.  They didn't want to sit with me before, they'd rather be with someone else.  Now that they can't have what they wanted I'm popular all sudden.  I think nor 14:15:26 livingoutloud777: *not 14:15:54 lisxc7234: lol yeah i mentioned that didnt i? 14:16:07 livingoutloud777: Yeah and you asked why I said no 14:16:10 lisxc7234: lol im lost, i should eat  14:16:12 lisxc7234: ohh. 14:16:20 lisxc7234: lol i know the feeling. 14:16:53 livingoutloud777: Know what feeling? 14:17:25 lisxc7234: from not being notcied.. then all of a sudden being popular. 14:17:31 livingoutloud777: LOL 14:18:01 lisxc7234: guess who, bet you can! 14:18:13 livingoutloud777: Zeph? 14:18:15 lisxc7234: yep 14:18:16 lisxc7234: brb Lisa went away (14:18:19) Away Message: "Dog." (14:18:20) Lisa came back (14:22:49) 14:22:52 lisxc7234: back 14:22:58 livingoutloud777: Okay 14:23:14 lisxc7234: which watch when we get there she will want to sit with me all of a sudden because she cant sit with kyle now. 14:23:21 lisxc7234: We leave at 6 on sunday right? 14:23:54 livingoutloud777: We are meeting at Beacon at 5 PM, then riding to Central in our van and getting on the bus there 14:24:15 lisxc7234: okay, so 5.. so i should leave my house at 4.30 14:24:17 lisxc7234: gottcha 14:24:18 lisxc7234: okay, 14:24:21 lisxc7234: anyways 14:25:14 livingoutloud777: You gonna be around for awhile? 14:25:21 lisxc7234: yeah i guess so 14:26:51 lisxc7234: why? 14:27:08 livingoutloud777: Well I think I am able to talk now 14:27:11 lisxc7234: okay. Lisa went away (14:27:22) Away Message: "brb food " (14:27:23) Lisa came back (14:28:54) 14:30:56 lisxc7234: back 14:31:20 livingoutloud777: Okay, you ready then? 14:31:43 lisxc7234: yeah i guess lol,  14:31:50 livingoutloud777: LOL 14:37:23 livingoutloud777: Okay Lisa I don't want you to take any of this the wrong way.  I really do care for you.  I'll admit I was pretty upset yesterday and last night.  I told myself I really didn't care anymore that losing you as a friend would be okay.  I was angry with you for several reasons.  So yeah I don't really enjoy this next part but I'm going to tell you what they are and you might feel I am attacking you but I'm not.  I've just kept on ignoring them for too long and I finally lost it.  But I do care and I'm not attacking you. 14:37:58 lisxc7234: ok 14:46:51 livingoutloud777: IDK I guess the biggest thing is how sometimes you refuse to accept responsibility for your actions.  Like you kept on saying how I was "nagging" you, but you wouldn't admit that you are the one who brought it up.  People have brought it up to me before, and I kinda saw where they were coming from but I didn't think it mattered enough then. 14:47:20 lisxc7234: like who else? 14:47:41 lisxc7234: cuz i know i brought it up, but if ibring something up doesnt nessary mean i want to tlak about it. 14:48:15 livingoutloud777: Yeah but you wouldn't just accept the fact that you brought it up. 14:48:36 lisxc7234: no i knew i brought it up 14:49:58 livingoutloud777: Well you wouldn't admit that yesterday 14:50:07 lisxc7234: but iknew that. 14:50:25 lisxc7234: okay thats settled.. but what else? 14:50:31 livingoutloud777: Well that leads me to the second thing which annoys me 14:54:55 lisxc7234: i warn you, if i say somethings i dont mean it, jeff gordons engine blew up:'( 14:59:48 livingoutloud777: I don't think I've ever gotten a real apology from you for anything.  If you can honestly tell me you don't think you've ever done/said something where you could have apologized then IDK.  You said that Steph treats you worse than all the rest of your friends, well lately I feel that the same goes for you.  I don't know how to explain it. 15:01:00 lisxc7234: okay, 15:01:08 lisxc7234: Well i can understand that, somewhat.  15:02:49 lisxc7234: Like i now i have changed from the end of the year. And idk i havent been able to go to yg, so it has like made me feel that i havent been there for you guys, but it also feels like i shouldnt because i cant make it, so idk it feels like i dont belong there sometimes. idk its just something i have picked up, sometimes it seems you have more fun without me. And there for idk i set myself up for somethings. 15:04:18 livingoutloud777: I'm not talking about that. 15:04:25 lisxc7234: okay. 15:05:01 livingoutloud777: I'm talking about how I get treated by others and how I get treated by you 15:05:14 lisxc7234: ok. 15:05:23 lisxc7234: so basically your saying that im not a good friend 15:06:41 livingoutloud777: I'm saying something has changed.  You were before we started dating.  Then things changed.  You definitely aren't the same person I met a year ago 15:06:53 lisxc7234: ok? 15:07:32 lisxc7234: so i have changed. 15:07:39 lisxc7234: i dont think im the only one who has. 15:07:45 lisxc7234: (not you( 15:10:54 livingoutloud777: But yes you had me pretty ticked.  If I get yelled at for asking questions about things you bring up and then I am expected to apologize I get pretty mad 15:11:07 lisxc7234: im sorry then 15:16:08 livingoutloud777: If you don't want to talk about something don't bring it up and don't stop me when we are at the end of a conversation to tell me you don't want to talk about it.  I've been dreading talking to you because there is never anything on your mind and when I ask about things I get yelled at 15:18:05 lisxc7234: Ok, first, when i tell you that i dont want to talk about something that usually means its on my mind. And just because i say that doesnt mean that i dont want to talk, but you seem like the same way, nothing is ever on your mind anymore either  15:19:06 lisxc7234: so basically im getting in trouble for telling you whats on my mind, when you want toknow, but then also because i dont want to talk about it. 15:22:18 livingoutloud777: Fine I won't ask, you can tell me what is.  You can initiate the ims, and you can carry the conversation.  I don't want to be accused of prying 15:22:41 lisxc7234: No, i dont want that i was just saying.  15:23:18 lisxc7234: Because it seems like im doing all the wrong so idk, see this is why i dont want to go to L.A. because im sure everyone else feels that way 15:23:34 lisxc7234: and it seems something has bugged you ever since i couldnt go to yg. 15:24:33 livingoutloud777: Well aside from the fact IDK if I could pick you out in a crowd or that I don't really think I know you nothing is bugging me 15:26:02 lisxc7234: Well, that wasnt my fault i wanted to go, my dad said that i have to rest. I Swear because i loved going to yg and seeing you guys, but you know what if everyone hates me then why bother? Why bother going to lake ann, and why just bother doing anything? Lisa went away (15:26:44) Away Message: "brb" (15:26:44) 15:26:54 livingoutloud777: IDK where you are getting where everyone hates you 15:26:58 lisxc7234: brb 15:27:11 livingoutloud777: If I hated you I wouldn't be talking to you right now 15:28:55 livingoutloud777: I care Lisa and so does everyone else Lisa came back (15:29:23) 15:29:34 livingoutloud777: If you don't want to go to Lake Ann I can't do anything aside from tell you that I would miss you 15:30:31 lisxc7234: well i want to, but idk. From what im getting at jen thinks im trying to steal kevin from her, umm thats just one. 15:30:50 lisxc7234: idk. what else is bugging you then? 15:31:22 livingoutloud777: I think I'm done for now 15:31:27 livingoutloud777: Oh wait :-P 15:36:31 livingoutloud777: IDK one of the big things is that I don't feel you trust me as much as you used to.  I mean yeah I can understand that and all but that is still something I feel.  You know more about me than pretty much anyone, I trust you with just about anything.  Yeah now I'm done 15:36:51 lisxc7234: Geeze im amazed im not dead 15:37:12 lisxc7234: Its not that i dont trust you, i think my biggest fear is hurting you if i "date" someone else, and i dont want that to happen. 15:38:51 livingoutloud777: Lisa i'm not at all worried about you dating someone else.  I half expected you'd be weeding thru applications by now.  Don't take this the wrong way but you're a flirt :-P 15:40:53 lisxc7234: No i know, but not as bad as some people. and i only really flirt with guys im interested in   All in all... I'm still not happy with her.  I really hope she is grabbed by God at Lake Ann and is shook really hard.  I really don't think I like her any more, in pretty much all senses of the word.  I don't know I wish my life would hurry up and end.  Kristin had this to say about Lisa.   14:46:50 dabnc2erk067: i have to admitt im glad that u saw the light with Lisa  14:46:56 livingoutloud777: LOL 14:46:56 dabnc2erk067: shes not good for u...  14:47:20 livingoutloud777: Why do you say that?  I'm curios cause several people have said that 14:47:24 dabnc2erk067: b/c  14:47:43 dabnc2erk067: shes not ur type, shes not good enough for u, and she needs God.  14:47:54 dabnc2erk067: shes not looking for the same things n a realtionship  14:48:00 dabnc2erk067: that u are  14:48:33 dabnc2erk067: she is one of the most ungodly ppl i kno Jeremy  14:48:52 livingoutloud777: How so? 14:48:59 dabnc2erk067: shes a cheater and a liar  14:49:15 dabnc2erk067: she want all of the guys to like her (selfish)  14:49:36 dabnc2erk067: she denies it...but shes most definitely after Kyle  14:49:43 dabnc2erk067: and Kevin  14:50:24 dabnc2erk067: ??  14:50:40 livingoutloud777: IDK Maybe :-P 14:50:48 livingoutloud777: I don't see her at school etc 14:51:18 dabnc2erk067: yea...well most of what she does is o/s of school  14:51:45 dabnc2erk067: i dunno...i just really think that u deserve better  14:52:10 dabnc2erk067: and maybe she'll be better later on. but right now she seriously needs paryer  14:52:18 dabnc2erk067: prayer*  14:52:20 livingoutloud777: I know that 14:52:33 livingoutloud777: I'm glad she is going to Lake Ann 14:52:51 livingoutloud777: And that I don't have to sit with her on the bus :-P 14:52:57 dabnc2erk067: lol  14:53:01 dabnc2erk067: y?  14:53:24 dabnc2erk067: here's an example if lisa's behavior...  14:53:56 dabnc2erk067: knowing that Kev and Jen like eachother she told him to sit with her on the bus...  14:54:10 dabnc2erk067: even if he didnt sit with jen, he would sit w. u or kyle  14:54:18 dabnc2erk067: i mean, what was she thinking?  14:54:52 livingoutloud777: Well :-P I've been over that with her and kev and jen 14:54:58 dabnc2erk067: good  14:55:20 dabnc2erk067: thats just really frunsteratinf to me  14:55:29 dabnc2erk067: ing*  14:55:40 dabnc2erk067: i cant spell  14:55:42 dabnc2erk067: lol  14:55:51 livingoutloud777: LOL NP 14:57:48 dabnc2erk067: sry to get in ur business by the way...i just care  14:57:51 dabnc2erk067: ya kno?    IDK maybe Kristin is jealous of her or hates her for some other reason but there has to be some truth in there.  Lisa after Kristin and I talked   19:03:10 lisxc7234: Whats on your mind? anything you want to tlak about? 19:03:53 livingoutloud777: IDK I've stopped telling people what is on my mind.  Too much of a pain 19:04:13 lisxc7234: ok? 19:04:50 livingoutloud777: That and people get angry when I tell them 19:05:31 lisxc7234: so tellme 19:05:34 lisxc7234: i wont get angry 19:05:50 livingoutloud777: I really doubt that 19:06:28 lisxc7234: okay? 19:06:30 lisxc7234: well try me. 19:08:26 livingoutloud777: IDK 19:08:53 lisxc7234: okay only if you want to then 19:09:35 livingoutloud777: Sorry I just don't feel like having another argument :-P  One a day is enough 19:09:48 lisxc7234: why would i argue with you? 19:10:07 livingoutloud777: /get mad 19:10:41 livingoutloud777: Because you wouldn't like what I've been thinking about 19:10:44 lisxc7234: ok? 19:13:25 livingoutloud777: Fine just to calm you down.  What I've heard people say concerning you and what your *dies laughing* "Love Life" is like.  Okay?  Now you know and I'm not all that keyed up about talking about it 19:14:07 lisxc7234: ok 19:14:15 lisxc7234: this seems interesting. 19:14:42 livingoutloud777: You don't need to tell me anything and I'd rather not tell you anything :-P 19:15:19 lisxc7234: Why are people talking about my love life? 19:15:39 livingoutloud777: They aren't 19:16:17 lisxc7234: ok? then what were you talking about? im confused 19:16:29 lisxc7234: what have you heard then? 19:18:44 livingoutloud777: Lisa I don't really want to talk about it, besides it is nothing that will make you happy 19:18:52 lisxc7234: okay.   I hate this.  Well I am gonna go complain somewhere else... I'll think about it tonight and comment on it tomorrow
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a roller coaster ride since Sunday.  IDK if I am coming or going.  I worked for Bobi on Monday.  Nothing really special happened.  Tuesday I worked at the shop, then I ran 3 miles in under 20 minutes in 95+ degrees.  Just cause I was dared that I wouldn't.  Wednesday I worked at Bobi's then played basketball for 2 hours with Kyle.  I felt awesome.  I could have kept on going.  We played 5 games and it was a 3-2 loss for me.  But every game was decided by 2 points.  So he really only won by 2 points total.  He had to keep taking breaks too.  I had so many nice blocks.  I had to sit through Bible study because Renee came.  That wasn't fun.  Then I did the garbage and etc.  I got online (which was a mistake) and Lisa was on.  I didn't IM her, she IMed me.  Then she expected me to be talkative.  Which was okay and I tried.  I asked her how her day went, etc.  But this is something I've noticed.  Ever since Lisa and I agreed we didn't want to be dating I've gotten to see a side of Lisa that she hid pretty well.  When she yelled at me for trying to help I was pretty astonished.  Not the fact that she let lose, but the fact that she didn't apologize later.  Then last night she got online and she didn't really have anything to talk about.  So I tried to give her things to talk about.  I asked her how her day was, I asked her if anything exciting happened, etc.  She didn't ask how my day was etc.  It is really annoying.  Maybe I'm wrong or over reacting but I don't think so.  I ask about her day and her life because I care.  So when she got angry at me for talking about Nikki, IDK I was angry/hurt.  If I didn't care about Nikki and what was happening to her I wouldn't have asked.  It is really annoying.  I've noticed it more and more lately.  I want to talk to her about it but then again I am afraid she will flip out.  She doesn't handle being criticized very well.  Sometimes she will accept all the blame for something (losing a track meet etc) and then other times she won't accept any of it.  I guess I feel like I'm undervalued, I really don't like the way she treats me.  Just because we aren't dating anymore or whatever doesn't mean I get to be the one who gets to deal with her when she is not in a good mood.  I know she doesn't treat Kevin the way she does me.  Oh well.  Tomorrow I am working at Brownick doing who knows what.  Then more coding at night.  Saturday is the massacre.  Should be fun.  Off to the wonderful land of PHP with no girls... especially moody ones.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really don't.  I am sick and tired of dealing with relationships.  I don't want to deal with Lisa, Kyle, Kevin, Steph, Renee, etc.  I just wish I could be alone.  I don't want to put up with all the problems caused by relationships.  I hate how I have to watch what I say and to who.  It is really stupid.  *angered groan*  I'm just too tired to deal with all this right now.  Maybe I'll write later when I can think.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I figured I would hurry up and write this so I can't have anything else to write about.  Since last night nothing has really happened.  After my parents told me about my mom.  I got to get out of Biblestudy.  Lisa and I talked.  Nothing really came of it.  I can wait.  I don't want anything rushed.  I want something that she thought through.  Today was fun.  I vacuumed Bobi's pool, painted some steps, mowed the lawn, etc.  Wasn't bad.  Now I'm going to be a nerd and implement PEAR's DB_DataObject into the church site.  Should be a good learning experience.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      aren't in yet.  We talked for an hour and a half without really mentioning the novel.  So no news is good news.  I know I feel better knowing I don't have anything left to tell her.  I should be able to sleep finally.  I didn't tell her how I've been affected physically with all this but I don't think she needs to know.  I got another bombshell tho.  Carrie is going to have a major surgery on her back again.  Then tonight my parents told me my mom is pregnant again but it looks like there are going to be some complications.  She might not be able to carry the child to term.  I don't think I can handle this right now.  So I'm trying to not think about any of it.  Today at Bobi's I licked 40 dollars worth of stamps.  Kevin hurt his shoulder and can't come to the concert.  So now Kyle doesn't seem like he wants to come.  IDK.  Life it's a blast... oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear Lisa, 	I'm sure you couldn't wait to get another novel... but unfortunately that's what it is going to take to explain myself properly (hopefully.)  I'm going to be looking through my logs from last night and trying to make sure I hit on everything you brought up.  So it may seem like I am jumping around pointlessly.  Before I start talking about anything I want you to read this letter over several times.  I know there is going to be a lot of information and I don't think it is humanly possible to take it all in at once.  So before you respond, please make sure you've read through it a couple times.  Also, I am in no way angry at you.  I know you can't hear the tone of my voice when I am writing but trust me, I am not angry at all.  	To the logs...  	My giving you the cold shoulder.  Hopefully I can explain this and make sense at the same time.  The reason I gave you the cold shoulder was because I was hurting and I let my emotions get the better of me.  Truthfully when I was doing it I was hoping that it would annoy you or hurt you.  I am sorry for that.  I regretted it right after I got off.  I shouldn't have treated you that way.  I was hurting because I felt that you didn't want me in your life anymore.  Right after we talked that Sunday and when you got back online is when I first got that impression.  I forget what you said but it was something like trying not to lose touch when you go to college.  Now I realize that isn't what you meant, but then it seemed like you couldn't wait to get away, and that you were already thinking about the future and I didn't factor into it.  Then when you weren't able to come to the last couple of YG's and to the movies, it just let things get worse in my mind.  I told you I'm paranoid, but in truth I'm a worrier.  I will worry about anything and everything.  Most of the time no one will know it but I do.  There were a few other things that gave my imagination ammunition.  One of them was when you wrote in your journal about how you were flirting with Ozzy.  I felt it was significant because you and I had been flirting before you and Joe broke up.  You told me once or twice that you broke up with Joe because "you weren't being true to yourself."  Whatever that means I took it as you liked me more than him.  So in my mind I figured you didn't want me around you anymore.  So yeah I probably let my imagination get hyperactive with all that.  Also I know you and Kevin have gotten close (which is good I think Kevin is a great guy) and I remember how that used to be me.  Now I understand that, you needed someone you could trust as a friend to bounce ideas off of.  And since I was something else to you, Kevin became a good friend.  But afterwards when we decided we only wanted to be friends I kinda got the impression from you that you didn't want me as a guy friend to talk to because you had Kevin.  So yes I let my imagination get going and that is my fault.  However I've asked for forgiveness for doing what I did and I mean it.  If you don't want to forgive me then maybe you aren't the person I thought you were.  	Okay so that didn't go as bad as it could have... now onto the next topic foremost on my mind...  	Last night you said you felt I was jealous of someone.  Well I guess you could say I am.  I'm jealous of our friendship.  You have no idea how much it means to me.  Like it or not you still know the most about me out of anyone.  I trust you pretty much unconditionally.  I respect you a lot and I don't want to lose you as a friend.  Lisa I really don't want anything other than friendship from you.  I know I've told you many times I want you to be happy with whoever.  I want you as a really good friend, someone who I can talk to and also help when you need it.  I told you I've lost a lot of my friends over time and I don't want to lose you, well here is one very good example.  Before I met you, Renee and I were good friends.  We could talk about anything and I trusted her.  When I told her I liked you things changed very quickly.  And I lost a very good friend when I don't think I really should have.  Now don't take this as me saying you caused it or whatever.  Because you didn't.  All those choices were mine and I accept full responsibility for those.  But what I am saying is I lost a close friend and I don't want to lose you as a close friend.  Aside from you (and Jill but that is kinda different since we don't see each other all the time) I don't have any female friends who I can talk to.  Jen and I were never really all that close.  Same with Allison.  Steph... well we'll save that for a later paragraph but I can't talk to her either.  Steph was a good friend and yes I feel I've lost her.  So no I don't want to lose you as well.  So yes I guess you can say I'm jealous.  I just want to have you as a good friend.  And I would appreciate it if you would let me know what's going on in your "love life", but I don't want you to tell me unless you are comfortable with it.  (Altho if I think you're dating a jerk I might have to tell you :-P)  I don't want to be jealous (in the bad sense) of anyone.  	Thinks.... naw we'll save Steph for later...  	As for me wanting you to come to YG.  Well it is true.  I want you at YG.  But no I don't want you to skip out on previous plans.  If I had a prior commitment I would miss YG too.  But yes I love seeing you there.  That is truthfully the only place I get to see you now.  I don't want you feel like I am pushing you to come or whatever.  But would you rather I not tell you when YG's are?  Would you rather I tell you not to come?  I tell you because yes I do want to see you there but I want you to do whatever you had originally planned.  But yes when you missed those several YG's I was sad and I wished you could have come.  So let me put this as clearly as I can.  I love seeing you at YG.  I wish you could be at all of them.  I understand you can't be.  I'm not angry at you about it.  I don't expect you to drop previous plans.  That is the best I can do.  	Time to talk about Steph...  	Kevin told me that you and him were talking about Kyle and Steph and how they were acting.  How different Steph acted around him, etc.  Well before Kevin told me he was talking with you about it.  I told him how I was glad I wasn't the only one who felt that way.  When he told me you felt that too I kinda was surprised.  You had told me not to talk to you about Kyle and Steph.  I really think you need to tell her how you feel tho.  Forget telling Kyle.  Like I said I was there when you and he were talking and he was talking to me about it.  He thinks you are over-reacting.  He wouldn't listen to me about it.  When you said he would side with Steph he looked at me with a look of disbelief.  Like how could she think that.  I told him I didn't think he could deal impartially because he would side with Steph I got a nasty look.  So I think without realizing it he has already sided with Steph.  Kevin told me what his plan was.  He said he was just going to ignore Steph and at the time I thought it sounded okay.  But I got to thinking.  I don't think we should ignore her without telling her how we feel first.  If she continues to act like that then I could see ignoring her.  I really think you should tell her how you feel.  But sometime when Kyle isn't around.  	Okay we're more than halfway!  	"lisxc7234: well jeremy how can i talk to someone who wont talk to me, and tell me what is on your mind>? huh?"  If that is about me giving you the cold shoulder then I think I've said enough already.  But if it isn't let me say all this.  I want to tell you what is going on in my life, and I want you to tell me what is going on in yours.  I want to be good friends.  Once you've read this letter, if you want I will tell you what is on my mind aside from all this.  I'd also like to hear about what is going on in your life.  Not just the "I ran so far, so fast, etc." and I'll make sure not to give the "My day was boring summary."  There are some really big things going on in my life which I'm pretty worried about.  I'm not really scared of them but at the same time I am terrified.  Then there are some pretty small things going on in my life which I'm worried about as well.  If you haven't figured out by now I'm a worrier, I worry over stupid things that I can't control.  I don't normally verbalize the littler worries because I don't think they are worth talking about, but if you truly want to hear them I would tell you.  But only if you really want to.  	I hope I've touched on everything important.  If I haven't or if I've brought something important up please let me know.  I want all this to be cleared up so I can be the halfway decent friend I was before.  I really care for you as a sister (unfortunately I've been treating you like one.)  	If you want to talk about this I ask that you don't do it online.  I would rather it be in an email (or a real letter) or in person (the phone/whatever.)  It is just too easy to get sidetracked and miss talking about something important.  But like I said at the top of this novel... please read the letter over several times.  Remember I wrote it because I wanted you to know how I felt and what has been going through my head.  I didn't write this when I was angry, so please don't think I meant any of this letter as quarrelsome or trying to provoke you.  Truthfully right now I feel tired and burdened.  So if there is a typo or something that doesn't make sense or whatever, take it in the positive sense.   			Hoping you'll let me be a brother (or bother same idea) 			because I love you like a sister,   				Jeremy
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      21:01:04 livingoutloud777: Good evening 21:01:33 lisxc7234: my dad said if you ever drove like that when im in the car im never riding with you again 21:01:33 lisxc7234: :-P 21:01:38 livingoutloud777: LOL 21:01:53 livingoutloud777: Well since you are never riding with me that won't be a problem now will it? 21:02:07 lisxc7234: okay fine then ill hold that to you. 21:02:49 livingoutloud777: Well it is my parents rule actually 21:02:54 lisxc7234: oh okay. 21:03:26 livingoutloud777: Sorry I didn't say hi I was kinda umm afraid :-P 21:03:46 lisxc7234: ? 21:03:47 lisxc7234: from? 21:04:09 livingoutloud777: You :-P If Kyle got a "Don't talk to me" I thought for sure I'd get a "go jump in the lake" 21:04:58 lisxc7234: lol no i havent talked to him in over a month. 21:05:04 lisxc7234: and steph was really making me mad. 21:05:10 livingoutloud777: I know 21:05:16 livingoutloud777: Kevin and I talked 21:05:25 livingoutloud777: I've been drafting her a leter 21:05:27 livingoutloud777: *letter 21:06:24 lisxc7234: honestly. i dont consider her a best friend let a lone a real friend. 21:06:32 lisxc7234: thats how far we have grown apart 21:06:39 livingoutloud777: Yeah I know :-P 21:07:05 livingoutloud777: I told Kevin it hurt to say it but I can honestly say "Steph who?" 21:07:56 lisxc7234: And to be even morew honest.. idk if i want to invite her to my party.. i was thinking  21:08:11 lisxc7234: but no guys that would screw it up because last time i had a party it was a diaster Lisa went away (21:09:11) Away Message: "My Life, My Fun Click It ~ http://premium.xanga.com/skin.asp?user=LisRunner52" (21:09:11) Lisa came back (21:09:12) Lisa went away (21:09:24) Away Message: "Goign to find my brother..  Leave one" (21:09:25) 21:09:28 livingoutloud777: Lisa speaking from experience (unfortunately) if you don't tell her how you feel things are going to get worse 21:09:28 lisxc7234: Goign to find my brother..  Leave one 21:14:42 livingoutloud777: And now that he is gone.  After the meet I went to Kyle's house.  We ate and played basketball.  Then I looked at their computer.  So I was there 'til 8:30.  So I know what you said to him.  I wish you would tell me how you feel.  I never wanted you to feel like I was trying to make you come and give up your commitments.  I just miss you at YG and I want you back there.  But I don't want you giving up prior plans (unless it is something like knitting class.) 21:17:25 livingoutloud777: I just want to be able to see you and talk to you and be your friend. Lisa came back (21:24:16) 21:25:04 lisxc7234: brb 21:25:05 lisxc7234: again 21:25:09 livingoutloud777: k Lisa went away (21:25:15) Away Message: "hes dead!" (21:25:15) Lisa came back (21:37:39) 21:38:13 lisxc7234: okay. 21:38:23 lisxc7234: first off.. jeremy you were mad at me because i couldnt make yg 21:38:31 livingoutloud777: No Lisa I wasn't 21:38:35 livingoutloud777: I was never mad at you 21:39:04 lisxc7234: yeah you were.. you were giving me the cold shoulder.. jeremy you had to be mad about something i did. 21:39:11 lisxc7234: otherwise you would have just talked to me about it 21:39:25 livingoutloud777: Lisa truthfully I was hurting 21:39:41 lisxc7234: from me not going to yg? 21:39:57 livingoutloud777: No 21:40:09 livingoutloud777: Well kinda 21:40:32 livingoutloud777: It was more because I felt like you were trying to IDK get rid of me. 21:40:54 lisxc7234: And why would i do that. 21:40:59 lisxc7234: You are assuming things. 21:41:03 livingoutloud777: I know 21:41:08 livingoutloud777: I told you I'm paranoid 21:41:09 lisxc7234: Jeremy what would you have said if i had told you that? 21:41:16 livingoutloud777: Told me what? 21:41:27 lisxc7234: what i told kyle 21:42:05 livingoutloud777: That I wasn't pushing you, that I miss seeing your smiling face at YG, and that I would like to see you there when you can 21:45:08 livingoutloud777: So when I was giving you the cold shoulder it was cause I was hurting.  And I really am sorry.  Yes it was mean and cruel of me and you didn't deserve it. 21:45:53 lisxc7234: Yeah 21:46:21 lisxc7234: well jeremy how can i talk to someone who wont talk to me, and tell me what is on your mind>? huh? 21:46:39 livingoutloud777: Well Lisa I called you and told you what was worrying me. 21:49:02 livingoutloud777: I have to get off but listen.  I am very sorry for acting how I did. I am asking for your forgiveness.  I don't want to lose you as a friend.  I've lost too many already.  I want to be there when you need me, and I'm pretty sure you'll be there for me even when I am a jerk. 21:49:42 livingoutloud777: And I do have somethings on my mind I would love to talk to you about 21:51:22 lisxc7234: Yeah but jeremy, i cant just drop everything and just go to yg, i make plans and im always the last one to know whats happening iwth yg.. i make plans because my true life doesnt just revolve around yg. and above almost all of my friends come running.. jeremy my life has been spinnning and yg is just something i have to cut back, we have had it for the last 5 weeks straight and i cant do that..  21:51:45 lisxc7234: Running is a big part because its what keeps me sane. 21:51:54 lisxc7234: And nikki was cutting her self again 21:51:57 livingoutloud777: I can't respond now I have to go but maybe later 21:52:00 lisxc7234: so that has been on my mind too. 21:52:06 lisxc7234: okay then 21:52:10 lisxc7234: ttyl lylab bye 21:52:21 livingoutloud777: But do you forgive me for being such a paranoid jerk? 21:52:38 lisxc7234: idk i haev to sleep. too many things going threw my head. 21:53:02 lisxc7234: but i dont like it when guys do that it annoys me, it feels like we are "dating" and your jealous of someone.. and i hate that feeling 21:53:11 livingoutloud777: Okay, I'll ttyl lylas 21:53:23 lisxc7234: bye bye 21:53:26 livingoutloud777: Lisa I'm not jealous 21:53:30 livingoutloud777: I'll explain it later 21:53:33 livingoutloud777: Goodnight 21:53:35 lisxc7234: okay fine. 21:53:37 lisxc7234: night 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>