<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      guess what?i went to the saloon today.and u know what?i got my hair cut.i dont think u want to see my new hair cut cuz its damn hideous.everytime i got my hair cut,i will always regret it later.and still,i got my hair cut.stupid isnt it?and i dont even know what am i crapping about.anyway,this morning,after so many months,i finally attend my taekwondo lesson at the pusat belia near wisma saberkas.since i cant come to the school training,my sir recommended me to come to the black belt training on sundays.so,i come  la. needless to say,he and nadia never take their time to mention about the name of the training which is  Physical Training. and you can guess how they train.its very torturing.seriously.my body ache all over right now.i even suck at my patterns.thats the price i have to pay for not coming for 5 months.well,i guess things like this happens all the time...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i rawk man...ehehe.last night i went to the fatcat festival to watch a few bands playing and let me tell you something.i was supposed to haf the time of my life but guess what? i didnt.i suddenly haf this headache and stomachache and ...lets just say my body ache all over.i met some cute guys though.and also a cute band member named jaynsen.he's damn cute but too bad  nya dayak. ---> kimak li bunyi .anyway,i ate many sugarbun stuff last night because that's the only  tempat makan  that i can find.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      arpisz.its been two days since i last saw him.he's damn cute.but, yalah   dont know when will i see him again.and also that nazel[najib+fizel]guy.i am so the really very want to see the both of them.my!for god sake, [ngegeh li] i never talk to them.and not even making eye contact.fcuk  la. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just knew that pyah the great  udang  also have this blogspot thing.what a coincidence --->  ngegeh li jak bunyi ayat ya  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay.cant believe this.i'm having an online diary.ehhe.actually,i did have A FEW online diaries but you know la,i dont really activate them.i think i have created at least 10 online diaries.i can also bet that i will give up using this blog within one week.we will see...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hurm.its been like dunno-how-long-but-i'm-sure-its-long time since i have my last say in here.well,there's a lot and i really mean it when i said A LOT happened.the UPs and the DOWNs.the HIGHs and the LOWs.to put things in one,right now i'm ok.kind of.i feel ok.actually i feel neutral.am not happy and not sad.haha.huehue.*sigh* 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i woke up way early this morning because of sumthing that my mother said..."wake up and call afina.she said sumthing about dewi's father passed away.".and i was up in no time. i called afina and at the same time shafiah called my hp.and yup.dewi noorain aka nonoi's father just passed away.i was all "OMIGOSH".and afina was all "take your bath and i'll pick you up.as we arrived,dewi and shafiah were waiting in front of the house. dewi cried the moment she saw us.she even cried harder when i hugged her.all i could say was."calm down,k?".i even cried cuz i really cant stand it when i see people crying.all of a sudden,everything seems to come to my mind.i was thinking about my frens,my family and relatives.and my life.when am i going to change and start to be a true muslim? the question lingers in my head.dewi was better than before,but she's still not in the mood.i felt so bad for her.hope her father's soul will rest in peace and his family to take this with open heart.amin. al-fatihah  for him and his family.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      know what? W-H-A-T-E-V-E-R ... who are you anyway?i dont even know you.so, fcuk off  la,ok?who do you think you are?call me up and tell me some shit.you should be ashame of yourself.lying around to get attention.hey,puhleese...i dont like liars,ok...and also  pretenders ...you can do that to some other chicks but not me,OK?i dont know why i even bother to write this?i mean ur a complete stranger.. and i dont even know you...unless you've come to ur senses,then maybe i will talk to you...otherwise,just dream that i will ever talk to you again...for the moment,please do not bother me,ok?i have loads other frens,[real frens,mind you]to talk to...so,just get ur FAKE ASS outta my way,ok?and have a nice FAKE life!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i've just read my previous entry and i realized that it was way boring and lame.it sucks actually.infact,everything about me sucks.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      spent almost the whole day at afina's.i helped afina to pack her things because she's going to sabah with dewi,erin and nora.and then,we dropped by at sarawak plaza because afina wanted to buy a super super low cut  urlLink jeans .and then we went to erin's  urlLink house .on the way,we met siti rabiah on a scooter.and dewi and afina was all "OMIGOD!!!".then,we went back to afina's  urlLink house  and decided to buy burger at a stall nearby.on the way back to afina's  urlLink house  from the burger stall,we met nurul liyana in a  urlLink car .at night,me and afina have a-kinda-therapy-session.we talked bout ways to move on.best aiee...ehhe.i was sort-of- psikiatri ---> sik tauk eja lam  english.we burnt 4 lavender scented  urlLink candles .we also wrote things in a paper and burnt it.its kinda fun.its good too, you know?i felt like relieved.you should try it at  home .ehehe.after that,afina called aone and she told him she forgived him and apologized for insulting him the night before.she told him she hoped they can be frens.the funny thing is,just now afina called me and told me that aone just called her and talk like usual.as if nothing's happened.he even asked afina what  urlLink time  she's sleeping because he wants to call her tonite.i mean,what's that?boys are hard to predict.what's his motive on doing that?he's giving afina hope la.i cant do anything because afina likes to talk to him.i just hope he's not into anything.much lurve.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      on sunday,May 31st,abang azuan sent afina an sms saying that their relationship is off. reason : both have different interests.i mean,that's so lame.and guess what?its a really perfect timing when he sent the sms.afina was at Tun Jugah.coincidently,i was there too,with my family.afina cried like hell that she could'nt eat.she hugged me in front of the lift and  jompot  who was also there,was all like "what's going on?what's going on?"  fuck her D-cup breasts la!  i walked afina to her car and she was still all crying.her brother thanked me and off i went to the food gallery.that night, she slept over at dn's house.mind you,aone still have the guts to talk to afina.i mean,give her some space first la.he was all i-am-so-sorry-its-just-that-we're-not-meant-to-be-together talk when he called me.i mean,convince afina la.not me.boys are hard to believe.they're too much.what exactly they want from us?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       TOMORROW   i am looking forward  for tomorrow  another day  a new beginning  a fresh start.   tomorrow  i will rise  and start  a whole new life.   i realize   that you   are just a simple human  who made a mistake  but unfortunately,  a stupid one.   but still  you are only human  a weak man  who does'nt have  the knowledge   to appreciate.   tomorrow will come  and i will be reborn.   so,tomorrow  i will rise  and start  a whole new life. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       AGAIN   i noticed   the way you look at me  full with hatred  and disgust  it is written clearly  all over your innocent face.   but still i believe  all the nonsense you told me  but still i smile  after all the lies you have made  but still i hold on to  the love you promised me.   part of me know  that someday  you will realize  that you are nothing  without me.   everytime   after you dissect my heart  there is always a part of me  giving you   another useless chance  even when i know  that you will just do it  again.   i will make sure  that someday  you will realize  that you are nothing  without me.    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hide.or not to hide.   in the darkness,i walk  struggling to find the right path  in the darkness,i cry  desperate to break free  i could not hide it  not anymore.   but no matter what i do  i still can't  i do not have the guts  to do such a thing  never in my life  never.   maybe you were right  what you said that night  i am just being me  ego to admit it  but you were wrong.   i am a coward  i was scared to death  to say it to you face  afraid of your answer  your impression of me  will forever changed.   in the darkness,i walk  struggling to find the right path  in the darkness,i cry  desperate to break free  but i have to hide it  even if it hurts.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       GIRLS RULE!!! TOP 30 THINGS TO KNOW ABOUT US!!!   1. Don't ever lie to us, we always find out.   2. We don't enjoy talking dirty to you as much as you enjoy listening.   3. Don't say you understand when you don't.   4. Girls are pretty, get over it.   5. You don't have PMS; don't act like you know what it's like.   6. Saying something sweet might get you off the hook; doing something sweet will always get you off the hook.   7. If you talk about having a big dick, we know you don't.   8. Size does matter.  9. We don't like it when you act like Mr. Big; we like it when you are Mr. Big.   10. A system in your car only impresses your homeboys.   11. No matter what you say, your ex girlfriend is a hoe.   12. It's good to be sensitive, sometimes.  13. If you did something wrong or even if you didn't, apologize.  14. Be spontaneous, dinner and a movie won't always cut it.   15. We are self-conscious by nature, we can't help it.   16. We are drama queens.   17. Fashion police do exist.  18. Don't ask us to give head; if you are nice you just might get it.   19. We absolutely do not care about monster trucks, paintball or anything else you and your friends talk about, like: how much you know about the eastside, video games, porn, computers, Star Wars, etc.,   20. Hugs and kisses must be given at all times.   21. We don't shave our legs every day, get over it.  22. Don't make bets about us, we always find out.   23. Shave-no matter how cool you think it looks, we hate it.   24. Even is you think it is cool to burp, fart, or emit other strange gases from your body, it's not.  25. Don't compare our breasts with Pamela Anderson's, hers are fake.   26. It is not cool to shoot snot rockets.   27. We are beautiful, but make-up helps a lot.  28. We will always think we are fat so humor us and tell us we aren't.   29. You can shoot hoops, score a goal, knock down big fat guys, and hit a little baseball with a stick so why the hell can't you piss in the toilet and not on it?  30. Most importantly we are always right-so don't forget it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       GOODBYE   goodbye.  a simple word  yet meaningful  a simple word  yet dreadful  to me.   so,just go   without saying it  would you?  infact,just go   without saying a thing  can you?.   it hurts  listening to you  saying goodbye  to me.   so,just leave  without a word  without looking back  without goodbye  just leave.   the light of my life  just slipped from my hands  i lose the battle  i lost  you.   so,just stand up  turn around and walk away  without saying   goodbye.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       www.girlfriend.com.au...   You're the one who's by my side,  when no one else is there.  You're the one I can always count on,  you always seem to care.   You help me through  the tough times,  and when I've lost all hope.  You cry with me at sad times,  and laugh at all my jokes.   You never seem to judge me  or ever put me down,  you put a smile on my face,  whenever you see a frown.   You're better than a brother,  you're more than just my boyfriend,  you have a special place in my heart,  that's why you’re my Best Friend.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ENOUGH   enough of these crap  turn around and face me  turn around and see me  look me in the eye  and tell me i am wrong.   wrong  such a word to use  such a word to say  even to me.   come on  turn around now  show me your face  show me your smile  show me YOU.   what are you afraid of?  afraid of me?  afraid of the truth?.   enough of these crap  turn around and face me  turn around and see me  look me in the eye  and tell me something.   i do not have enough time  to go on with all these crap  so just turn around   and take off your mask   to reveal  the person behind it.   enough of these crap  turn around now  and show me  you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       a poem i found but could'nt remember exactly where i found it    IF I KNEW    If I knew it would be the last time   That I'd see you fall asleep,   I would tuck you in more tightly   and pray to god, your soul to keep.    If I knew it would be the last time   that I see you walk out the door,   I would give you a hug and kiss   and call you back for one more.    If I knew it would be the last time   I'd hear your voice lifted up in praise,   I would video tape each action and word,   so I could play them back day after day.    If I knew it would be the last time,   I could spare an extra minute   to stop and say "I love you,"   instead of assuming you would KNOW I do.    If I knew it would be the last time   I would be there to share your day,   Well I'm sure you'll have so many more,   so I can let just this one slip away.    For surely there's always tomorrow   to make up for an oversight,   and we always get a second chance   to make everything just right.    There will always be another day   to say "I love you,"   And certainly there's another chance   to say our "Anything I can do?"    But just in case I might be wrong,   and today is all I get,   I'd like to say how much I love you   and I hope we never forget...............................    Tomorrow is not promised to anyone,   young or old alike,   And today may be the last chance   you get to hold your loved one tight.    So if you're waiting for tomorrow,   why not do it today?   For if tomorrow never comes,   you'll surely regret the day,    That you didn't take that extra time   for a smile, a hug, or a kiss   and you were too busy to grant someone,   what turned out to be their one last wish.    So hold your loved ones close today,   and whisper in their ear,   Tell them how much you love them   and that you'll always hold them dear    Take time to say "I'm sorry,"   "Please forgive me," "Thank you," or "It's okay."   And if tomorrow never comes,   you'll have no regrets about today.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       two poems from www.girlfriend.com.au     FRIENDSHIP   A friend is someone special   For you to always hold dear   A friend is always there   To share a laugh or a tear   If ever your in trouble   And don't know where to turn   A friend is always there   With advice for you to learn   Whenever you feel   That you just can not bear   You know you can count on   Your friend to be there   If you were to ever   Have a fight with your friend   There should never be a problem   That you both cannot mend   So always remember   No matter what year   A friend is someone special   You should always have near     I'll Be Your Friend Till The End   I got your back   You got mine   I'll help you out   Anytime.   To see you hurt   To see you cry,   Makes me weep   I wanna die.   And if you agree   To never fight,   It wouldn't matter   Who's wrong or right.   If a broken heart   Needs a mend,   I'll be right there   To the end.   If your cheeks are wet   From drops of tears,   Don't you worry,   Let go of your fears.   Hand in hand   Love is sent,   We'll be friends   Till the end...  ...everytime i read this poem,i'll definitely laugh to myself.i have one stupid friend who claimed he wrote this poem that he slept at 4 o'clock in the morning to finish it or so.and ironically,i believed him.until i came across the same thing at a website.  fcuk off  la cuz i hate him so much i have no pity to spit to his face. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       www.lovepoemsandquotes.com     Perfection In My Eyes     All I ever wanted was to be part of your heart,   And for us to be together, to never be apart.   No one else in the world can even compare,   You're perfect and so is this love that we share.   We have so much more than I ever thought we would,   I love you more than I ever thought I could.   I promise to give you all I have to give,   I'll do anything for you as long as I live.   In your eyes I see our present, our future and past,   By the way you look at me I know we will last.   I hope that one day you'll come to realize,   How perfect you are when seen through my eyes.   - Ashley Borden -  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       LURVE   Love is beyond all description.   Love is greater than what anyone can express,   greater than that which anyone can understand,   or experience, and yet..   It is always fully expressed,   by those who are the givers   whenever Love is given, and   It's nature is quite fully known,   by all who have feelings,   wherever It's presence is felt.   Love knows no absolute boundaries,   but all of the boundaries in life   were put there out of love,   to allow Soul's desires to find expression.   Love is the inspiration for all that is,   and yet it is far beyond any thing,   or any combination of things.   Love is greater than any thought,   idea, or conception of meaning,   yet it is the reason why we have thoughts,   and why meanings are sought.   Love is far greater than any feeling,   and yet our capacity to feel grows more out of love   than for any other reason.   Love is far beyond anything   which can be obtained by reaching,   or striving, and yet..   Love is the real motivation behind all efforts,   striving, or reaching beyond oneself,   and beyond ones limits.   Love is the ultimate goal of all searching,   and it is also our only reliable means   of obtaining that goal.   Love is the one key that can unlock all things.   It can reveal the deepest mystery.   It will soften the hardest hearts.   It brings you to the very Heart of Heaven.   It will reveal itself through the art of giving,   and the sharing of oneself.   For Love is a gift.   It is, in fact the one gift there is.   As, truly, all other gifts are a part   of this gift of giving.   Love is the basis for Life itself!   In fact, It is Life, and everything else   also arises out of Love.   Love is the very substance of Life,   and Love's expression is the purpose   for which all of reality came into being.   It is the one thing to which all life aspires,   because Love is what we have always been.   Love is so healing, and it feels so familiar,   because it is the true nature of your Self.   Soul has the same nature as Love.   It arises out of the giving of the One.   Soul is the Kindness of the One   Divine Self incarnate.   Life is the expression of Its   desire to show Love.   Ours is the fulfillment of Its   dreams of Love's expression.   This is the essence of Divine Love.   It is the One Self giving the gift of Itself to us,   so that we might share in the great expression of Love.   It is the one gift, that we can find   Love's meaning in our lives,   and the Life of the Divine in Our Self.   Giving, Kindness, and the expression of Love   bring us closer to the One,   and closer to our own true Self.   They make it possible to experience   the Love that Spirit has for us,   and they make it easier for us to accomplish   Life's sweet purpose.   All other things in life pale before Love,   for true fulfillment comes only   when Love is realized.   It is as great as a lightning stroke,   so bright, and powerful,   that it threatens to shatter the heavens.   But Love is as soft as a Flower too,   and often just as fragile.   So, though It has always been here,   It will only be sure to appear in Its own sweet time.       
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i pick this at a nice website.kinda true.    that's amore!the mystery of love is solved.   A. in terms we can all understand!   Crush, lust, admiration or respect. Love can mean different things to different people. The filial love you feel for members of your family is very different from the passionate, erotic (from Eros, the Greek god of love) feelings you have for your mate. You can love your friends, but that sort of platonic affection is very different from what you feel for your boyfriend.   Yet some people maintain that there is no difference in types of love and that all forms spring from the same human desire to connect with another being. While this may be true, how can you determine if what you feel is love and not just sexual attraction? And what if you happen to find someone you're in love with, but then you decide to ignore your feelings because the timing is off? Does true love only come around once, or can it happen many times in one's life? Is there really such a thing as love at first sight, or can you only truly fall in love with someone you've known for a long time?   What's the difference between a crush and true love?   Crushes usually occur when you first meet someone and feel a special connection. Most are based on sexual chemistry and are accompanied by a rapid heartbeat, sweaty palms and, for an unfortunate few, drooling. A crush has more to do with lust and infatuation than with enduring love. It could stem from both a physical and a mental attraction.   The main difference between crushes and love is that crushes often happen when there is little chance of forming a relationship. These types of crushes are a safe way to explore your feelings for someone who you may think is unattainable. But sometimes the strongest variety of crushes occurs when the person is not completely outside of one's reach. These can closely resemble love, and if your feelings don't fizzle after you've snagged the object of your crush, they can lead to love.   Can you fall in love with someone you don't know?   Yes, you can. But whether or not you can have a relationship is another matter. Usually this type of love involves a fantasy. The person who falls in love projects his or her feelings and ideas of happiness onto the love interest. And since a fantasy can often be as strong as any true-life situation, love in these types of scenarios is not out of the question. But be careful. Should you meet that person and they turn out to be very different from the way you imagined, don't get depressed. You opened your heart, and this takes bravery.   Can you be in love with someone who doesn't love you?   Unrequited love is very common and has been around since before Shakespeare's time. And while the 19th century poets may have made it sound romantic, the problem with this situation is that it can quickly turn into an obsession if you're not careful. Most people are programmed to want what they can't have (also known as 'the grass is greener on the other side' syndrome). By simply being denied someone's love, they can form feelings of attachment, which can turn into an obsession if left uncontrolled. Another problem with unrequited love is that it can quickly become more of a challenge than a real emotion. Being rejected can rob someone of his ego, and in turn, this person may try to prove that he is worthy of love. On the other hand, if you feel strongly attached to someone because you respect and admire who they are, you may actually be in love.   Is there such a thing as love at first sight?   Some people are true believers in this phenomenon. These are usually the ones whose love at first sight led to a happy and satisfying relationship. Others, who felt this connection only to be let down, believe that love at first sight is really just lust at first sight. Nonetheless, it does happen more than you think. If you spot a person across a crowded room and feel a rush of emotions, don't be so quick to dismiss your feelings. When someone falls in love at first sight, it's usually an indication that the love interest has evoked some pleasant memory from the past. Maybe they remind you of your parents, your first love, or even someone you used to love from afar. Many couples who have fallen in love at first sight have gone on to live happily ever after. You never know when Cupid's arrow will strike gold, so go with it and enjoy the ride.   Can you love someone much older or younger than you?   Often we cannot control whom we fall in love with. Provided you're both of legal age, there's no reason why love can't unite two people of very different ages. Whether or not your relationship can withstand the criticism of others is something time will tell. But if you're confident about your feelings, the opinions of others should not play a significant role in the relationship.   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       GUILTY   Guilt creeping   All over me   It is everywhere   Covering every inch   Every part   Of my bare body   Leaving nothing at all   Why must it be me?   Stuck in this situation   Have nowhere to go   No space to move   And even   to breathe.  ...this is what i feel most of the time.i feel guilty to god,to my parents,my best friends,...i can say i feel guilty to the whole world.i badly want to change...but somehow,i cant.help me,please!!!anyone?  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       www.lovepoemsandquotes.com     A FRIEND'S GREETING     I'd like to be the sort of friend that   you have been to me;   I'd like to be the help that   you've been always glad to be;   I'd like to mean as much to you   each minute of the day   As you have meant, old friend of mine,   to me along the way.   I'd like to do the big things and   the splendid things for you,   To brush the gray from out your skies   and leave them only blue;   I'd like to say the kindly things that   I so oft have heard,   And feel that I could rouse your soul   the way that mine you've stirred.   I'd like to give you back the joy   that you have given me,   Yet that were wishing you a need   I hope will never be;   I'd like to make you feel as rich as I,   who travel on   Undaunted in the darkest hours with you to   lean upon.   I'm wishing at this time that I   could but repay   A portion of the gladness that   you've strewn along my way;   And could I have one wish this year,   this only would it be:   I'd like to be the sort of friend   that you have been to me.   - Heather Haff -   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       www.lovepoemsandquotes.com    1.   Have you ever felt like you knew someone a long, long time ago?   Another place, another time, a friendship of the souls?   Two people who share a bond for reasons neither know,   A feeling that they were friends, a long, long time ago?   Did they stumble onto each other by pure circumstance,   Or was it fate and destiny that played a certain hand?   Two souls intertwined, they are worlds apart,   But the soul, it knows no difference, in matters of the heart.   Somehow they are drawn together, fate has brought them back,   Each living worlds apart, they journey separate paths.   When this life is over, and a new life begins,   Their souls will find each other, two souls that we call friends.   - Lia Fail -   2.   Standing by,   All the way.   Here to help you through your day.   Holding you up,   When you are weak,   Helping you find what it is you seek.   Catching your tears,   When you cry.   Pulling you through when the tide is high.   Absorbing your voice   When you talk.   Standing by when you learn to walk.   Just being there,   Through thick and thin,   All just to say, you are my friend.   - Brittani Kokko -   3.   Friendship is like the breeze,   You can't hold it,   Smell it,   Taste it,   Or know when it's coming,   But you can always feel it,   And you'll always know it's there,   It may come and then go,   But you can know it'll always be back.   - Terri Fanning -   4.   Friends will come and friends will go,   The seasons change and it will show,   I will age and so will you,   But our friendship stays, strong and true   - Anonymous - 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       an email my friend forward to me.sumthing good to ponder upon.    Have you ever wondered which hurts the most?   Saying something and wishing you hadn't? or   Saying nothing and wishing you had?   I guess the most important things are the hardest things to say.   Don't be afraid to tell someone you love them. If you do, they might break your heart...if you don't, you might break theirs.   Have u ever decided not 2 become a couple because you were so afraid of losing what you already had with that person?   Your heart decides whom it likes and whom it doesn't.   You can't tell your heart what to do.   It does it on its own....when you least suspect it, or even when you don't want it to.   Have you ever wanted to love someone with everything you had, but that other person was too afraid to let you?   Too many of us stay walled up because we are too afraid to care too much... for fear that the other person does not care as much, or even at all.   Have you ever denied your feelings for someone because your fear of rejection was too hard to handle?   We tell lies when we are afraid... afraid of what we   don't know, afraid of what others will think, afraid of what will be found out about us.   But every time we tell a lie, the thing we fear grows stronger.   Life is all about risks and it requires you to jump.   Don't be a person who has to look back and wonder what they would have done, or could have had.   * What would you do if every time you fell in love you had to say good-bye?   *What would you do if every time you wanted someone they would never be there?   *What would you do if your best friend died tomorrow and you never got to tell them how you felt?   (even if it is that you don't care anymore)   *What would you do if you loved someone more than ever and you couldn't have them?   *What would you do if you never got the chance to say I am friends with all of my family and they know I love them?*   People live, but people die. And I want to tell you that   you are a friend.   If you died tomorrow, you would be in my heart.   Would I be in yours?   If you care about me as much as I care about you, you will send this back   You might be best friends one year,   prettygood friends the next year,   don't talk that often the next,   and don't want to talk at all the year after that.   So, I just wanted to say,   even if I never talk to you again in my life,   you are special to me and   you have made a difference in my life,   I look up to you,   respect you, and   truly cherish you.   Send this to all your friends,   no matter how often you talk,   or how close you are,   and send it to the person who sent it to you.   Let old friends know you haven't forgotten them,   and tell new friends you never will.   Remember, everyone needs a friend,   someday you might feel like you have NO FRIENDS at all,   just remember this e-mail   and take comfort in knowing   somebody out there cares about you   and .. always will..    I LOVE YOU!!!!    Send this to all the friends that you have...all the friends that you've lost...and to all the friends you've lost touch with...just to let them know that you care...send this back to the person who sent it to you if you consider them a friend as well! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A poem i found while i was browsing at  www.lovepoemsandquotes.com     What You Are To Me     I am a rose, you are my thorns,   clutching to me, protecting me.   I am the sun, you are my rays,   helping me to shine and to be all that I can.   I am a lake, you are my water,   filling me with ideas, dreams, and hopes for the future.   I am a tree, you are my leaves,   sharing who and what I am   and becoming an important part of my life.   I am a heart, you are my beat,   beating rhythmically to my happiness,   my fear, my sadness, my excitement.   I am me and you are with me,   to share all that I am,   to share life, love, and happiness.   Always.   - Bernice Ellrick - 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Love is about understanding. so, here are  few 'secrets' of gurls that u might have to  know.   1. When a girl says she's sad, but she isn't  crying,it means she's crying in her heart.   2. When she ignores you after you've done  something wrong,it's best to give her some time  to cool down before touching her heart with an  apology.   3. A girl can't find anything to hate about the  guy she loves (which is why it is so hard for  her to 'get over him' after the relationship's  over.)   4. If a girl loves a guy, he will always be on  her mind every minute of the day, even though  she flirts with other guys.   5.When the guy she likes smiles and stares deep  into her eyes, she will melt.   6. A girl likes to hear compliments, but  usually is not sure how to react to them.   7. When a particular guy flirts with a girl  very often, a girl would start thinking the guy  likes her. So if you treat a girl just as a  friend,go easy on the smiles and stare 'okie?   8. If you don't like a girl who likes you,  break it to her gently.   9. If a girl starts avoiding you after you  reject her, leave her alone for a while. If you  still treat her as a friend, talk to her.   10. Girls enjoy talking about what they feel.  Music, poetry,drawings and writing are ways of  expressing themselves(which explains why most  girls like writing journals).   11. Never tell a girl that she is useless in  any way.   12. Being too serious can turn a girl off.   13. When the guy she likes calls her for the  first time, the girl may act uninterested during  the call. But as soon as the phone is back on  the hook, she will whoop with joy and  immediately  start telephoning her friends to spread the  news.   14. A smile means a lot to a girl.   15. If you like a girl, try making friends with  her first.Let her get to know you.   16. If a girl says she can't go out with you  because she has to study, leave.   17. But if she still calls you or expect a call  from you, stay.   18. Don't try to guess a girl's feelings. Ask  her.   19. Hearing the words "I love you" is a great  reassurance to a girl that she is beautiful.   20. After a girl falls in love with a guy,  she'll wonder why she never noticed him before.   21. If you need tips on how to flirt with a  girl,read romance stories.   22. When class pictures come out, a girl would  first look at the girl next to her crush before  actually looking  at herself.   23. A girl's ex-crush will always be in her  memory, but the guy she loves now stays in her  heart.   24. Girls love having fun!   25. A simple 'Hi' can brighten a girl's day.   26. A girl's best friends usually know best  what she is feeling and going through.   27. Girls hate it when a guy pays attention to  them just to get close to their 'prettier'  friend.   28. Love means devotion, caring and happiness  to a girl,in that order.   29. Some girls care about looks,  some care about brains, but ALL girls want a guy  who will love and care for them.   30. Girls want nothing more than to feel loved.   ------------------------------------------------ you can't make someone love you,             all you can do is to be someone  who can be loved, the rest is up to the person to realize that your worth or not ------------------------------------------------
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woohoo. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A song titled Slipped Away by Avril Lavigne.A perfect song to describe me right now.   I miss you,  miss you so bad  I don't forget you,  oh it's so sad  I hope you can hear me  I remember it clearly  The day you slipped away  Was the day  I found it won't be the same  OooohNah nah la la la nah nah  I didn't get around to kiss you  Goodbye on the hand  I wish that I could see you again  I know that I can't  Oooooh  I hope you can hear  cause I remember it clearly  The day you slipped away  Was the day I found it won't be the same  Ooooh  I had my wake up  Won't you wake up  I keep asking why  And I can't take it  It wasn't fake  It happened, you passed by  Now your gone, now your gone  There you go, there you go  Somewhere I can't bring you back  Now your gone, now your gone  There you go, there you go,  Somewhere your not coming back  The day you slipped away  Was the day i found it won't be the same noo..  They say you slipped away  Was the day that i found it won't be the same oooh...  Nah nah, nah nah nah, nah nah  I miss you...    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A long time ago, before the world was created and humans set foot on it for the first time, virtues and vices floated around and were bored, not knowing what to do.One day, all the vices and virtues were gathered together and were more bored than ever. Suddenly,Ingenious came up with an idea: Let's play hide and seek!All of them liked the idea and immediately Madness shouted: I want to count, I want to count! And since nobody was crazy enough to want to seek Madness, all the others agreed. Madness leaned against a tree and started to count: One,two, three...As Madness counted, the vices and virtues went hiding. Tenderness hung itself on the horn of the moon, Reason hid in a pile of garbage.Fondness curled up between the clouds and Passion went to the center of the earth. Lie said that it would hide under a stone, but hid at the bottom of the lake, whilst Avarice entered a sack that heended up breaking. And Madness continued to count:... seventy nine, eighty, eighty one... By this time, all the vices and virtues were already hidden - except Love. For undecided asLove is, he could not decide where to hide. And this should not surprise us, because we all know how difficult it is to hide Love.Madness: ...ninety five, ninety six, ninety seven... Just when Madness got to one hundred,Love jumped into a rose bush where he hid.And Madness turned around and shouted: I'm coming,I'm coming! As Madness turned around, Laziness was the first to be found, because Laziness had no energy to hide. Then he spotted Tenderness in the horn of the moon, Lie at the bottom of the lake and Passion at the center of the earth. One by one, Madness found them all - except Love.Madness was getting desperate, unable to find Love. Envious of Love, Envy whispered to Madness:You only need to find Love, and Love is hiding in the rose bush.Madness grabbed a wooden pitch fork and stabbed wildly at the rose bush. Madness stabbed and stabbed until a heartbreaking cry made him stop.Love appeared from the rose bush, covering his face with his hands. Between his fingers ran two trickles of blood from his eyes.Madness, so anxious to find Love, had stabbed out Love's eyes with a pitch fork. What have I done!What have I done! Madness shouted. I have left you blind! How can I repair it?And Love answered: You cannot repair my eyes. But if you want to do something for me, you can be my guide. And so it came about that from that day on,Love is blind and is always accompanied by Madness....There are some people who meet that somebody that they can never stop loving...there are some love that don't go away...but we should all be lucky to end up with that somebody who has a little of that insanity.Somebody who never lets go. Somebody who cherishes you forever. 
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it is. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>