<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haa..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Going for a night out this evening...hehe..kinda suit my mood today...haaa..anyway Zed's not been back for some days and i couldnt go out.well.. guess father's gonna come back like before 7?That's it.Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heyhey!well..simply wasted my time today..hogging on the phone,watched hours of tv and stuff like that.Actually heading for a chalet but have to take care of my limping brother.Dunno the host really well anyway..But maybe meeting Joycelyn there for a beach talk as she's quite crossed.hmm..seems like being single saves all those unnecessary everything.Wonder if jia is doing fine?Gosh..a simple thing can be so complex huh?Anyway i wanted to pocket alot of things recently.A bag,pair of bermudas,and do SOMETHING to my hair.seemingly a chronic girls-yearn-for illness hey?School's starting next month and i've been quite excited.Hell~if my brother did not drop out we will be schoolmates..wonder if there's this possibilty to bump into HW.Like..who knows?!Haa!reminds me of his van.  It's been like half a year since year start.i guess 04's gonna end faster than i prophocised.sigh...what to do.Time control us and we must work hard to control time.so life's bout slogging.and slogging.just for the munneh to make ends meet.whats the point man...unless you struck lottery or become somebody someday.Actually its just about LUCK.In years to come,once i built up my career,if possible in anyway,will migrate.To somewhere hecking carefree and munneh comes by eaily.Australlia maybe?I'll try flying back to Spore as and when i've time to visit my old friends.haa..im mad...but im not really jesting about..hmm..perharps a little bit too early to even speak of it.But thats wad hell loads of people told me(counting my fingers 1,2,3...sigh,whatever~) Guess i'll have to end here for a shower.-end-
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Accompanied Joycelyn to Toa Payoh for some physical test yesterday...arrived and was like whoa!trudged our way amongst a stunning scene of guys...small short big tall you name it..hordes of people..quite scary though..i was quite shut down and cranky as i woke up at 6 in the morning...and then have to wait for this Joycelyn under the scorching sun while she was being test on.i am ALONE sitting around some 2 hundreds enlisted NS guys?milling around the stadium...i thought Joycelyn would not make it through..but she got a silver!YAY!!!imagine having to jog six rounds of endurement round the stadium...i would lasped into a coma i tell you. -Applause!!-  Hate the tropical weather in Singapore.jus so sucky.at least Malaysia has got a Genting but Singapore..like what?!snow place in science centre?haa..its a nono to go out in the afternoon between 11-4pm coz its simply too sunny and desert-like,aint it?sigh...suddenly have this urge to eat sushi or some wanton dumplings..anyway i tink i will go grab something to fill myself for the afternoon..ciao!   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>