<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My son was thrown out of preschool on Monday.  It was awful - he attacked a teacher because she told him he couldn't plug something in and she took it away from him.  I felt so bad sitting across the desk from the Director as she told me about the events of the day.  After she took it away he jumped on her and hit her and kicked her.  He had been fine until naptime and then just snapped.  He was kicking and hitting other kids too.  They had to restrain him for 2 hours because they couldn't reach me since I was out running errands with my mom.  He's never had an episode like this before.    I guess I should go back and give some history on him...he's 5 years old.  He was diagnosed with ADHD when he was 4 and then by 4.5 years we knew he was bipolar just like me.  He is one of the sweetest, most loving children you will ever meet.  If he comes in contact with you he will always give you a hug upon leaving you.  People adore him, he just has that sort of happy-go-lucky personality that attracts people to him.  On top of that he has manners.  Only because I drill them into his head all day long - if they had subliminal tapes for them I'd have him listen to them too.  I despise rude children.  Anyway, back to the story...we went in and saw one of the pdocs (psychiatrists) that he sees on Wednesday since they had no cancellations on Tuesday.  They increased his Resperdal and we were going to slowly take him off of his paxil - even though it was a very low dose.    On Thursday morning he was so wired I didn't give it to him at all, just the Resperdal and then called the pdoc who increased his dose again.    Everything seemed all right until he wanted to play a computer game and my mom (Big Mama) told him he couldn't.  Well he came over and kicked me a good one in the leg.  She told him you don't do that to your mother so he did it to her too and tried to hit her.  We had to restrain him for a half-hour before he would calm down and stop screaming and trying to kick, hit and bit us.  It was horrible.  He was drenched in sweat and if you tried to talk to him he just screamed.  Then he climbed into my arms exhausted - seemingly unaware of what happened.  It had me in tears.  He did finally say he was sorry when prompted, but I really don't know if he was aware of what he was sorry for.  We have a month and a half to get this under control because kindergarten starts August 17, 2004 and I doubt they will put up with this sort of behavior or have the staff to.  I hate that he is like me.  I was so hoping that this would skip him like it did with my mom.  I received all of my lovely mental problems from my grandmother and her mother!  Thanks a lot!  I don't want him to endure all of the pain I went through as a child and as an adult too -- even now.  Too late to put him back now though (as my mom likes to say).  Well, exhaustion has set in and I must go to bed...more updates to follow.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a week we had!!  It was our first week at home together alone.  It was pretty awful overall.  I've never been home with him alone since he was 9 months old - when I went back to work and even then it was hard from what I can remember.  I recall he cried a lot, slept really well, ate really well and I was tired all the time.  It's not much different these days.  Since going off his paxil he's been more tearful and insecure.  Always questioning whether I love him.  I can understand this though because I've had to punish him a lot this week.  It hasn't been fun.  I think he's spent as much time in Time Out as he has out of Time Out.  Of course, I've always reassured him that I will always love him no matter what.  We went to the pdoc (psychiatrist) on Wednesday and made a 6 month plan.  We started him on a med called Trileptal which is an anticonvulsant that is used as a mood stabilizer.  I've actually been on it before and it did help me.  It's what Zack's pdoc calls the "son of Tegretol" which I was on for years - very helpful, but requires blood tests.  So he's just started on this and knowing how quickly we (he and I) seem to react to meds, we should know within a week if this is going to work for him or not.  I hope that it does because I know that he is even more frustrated and lost than I am.  Being only 5 he has no idea what is happening to him.  He's been throwing up again - Wednesday at my mom's house at dinner and tonight right after dinner too.  I've learned to give him his meds after he eats so he doesn't end up throwing them back up.  Poor thing.  Don't get me wrong though - he is very, very exasperating.  I feel like pulling my head off sometimes and shoving it up my own ass just for being so stupid as to think I might be able to have a child who wouldn't be bipolar. (A little guilt there.)  But this hitting thing he has needs to be controlled and controlled now!  I won't have him growing up hitting me - not considering his daddy is 6'6" and not a small man.  I'm thinking of going back to martial arts just to defend myself - and I'm not joking.  I practice a defensive only martial art called Aikido (and not the hollywood hyped up jujitsu version that Stephen Segal does either).  Anyway, he is very angry and he told me last night he was frustrated because his tummy hurt.  I think it's the stress.  I know mine is hurting because of stress over the entire situation.  My mom came over today and we went to one store - Zack was good for the first 1/2 hour and then he started running around, hiding, and left a pair of my mom's shoes in the middle of an aisle (that he insisted he carry).  I finally had to take him outside he was become so loud and volitile.  He hit me as I took him outside and I grabbed both of his arms - then when Mom came out he had calmed down and he looked like he wanted to take her hand to cross the street and he hit her too.  I'm sorry, but he got a spanking when we got to the truck - then he called me an asshole (oops - my fault there - that's something I say when I drive).  The whole way back home he kicked the back of the seat and screamed off and on.  Needless to say he went right to Time Out when we walked in the door.  Mom left and I was so pissed off I cleared his room out of all of his toys.  He spends so much time in there that it isn't punishment when he has all of his toys to play with.  So out they all went.  During the process a few of them went into the trash can too.  I was doing it so fast I ended up breaking a nail - right across the middle of my finger - hurts like hell too.  Now I will have to go get that fixed before it gets infected.  Gosh, what else???  That's all I can think of for now - I'm just worn out.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, after the second increased dose of Resperdal, we had a day without an anger episode - although he was still being a pill.  Pushing his limits to the max, not listening at all and trying my patience until I thought I might scream.  My mom felt about the same way, but since he was better than yesterday she was still goint to let him spend the night.  ...That was until the throwing up began.  First he didn't want to eat dinner - so we said fine, but you have to sit at the table - well he nearly refused to do that so I sent him to Time Out.  Well he was refusing to go until I started to get up then he took off.  A couple of seconds later we here "Mommy, I got sick in the bathroom."  Sure enough he puked trying to make it too the bathroom.  After that he seemed fine though and wanted to eat.  So we fed him - only to end up cleaning up more puke that extended from the kitchen to the bathroom.  Thank goodness for hardwood floors and not carpet!  Needless to say, the poor little guy went home with me last night and we sid we'd try for next weekend.  The incresed dose of Resperdal seems to be helping though, so that is a good sign - but they are going to take him off of it soon, (pdoc appt. is on Wed) so we'll see how that goes.  As of this morning, he's been pretty good - except for losing his breakfast.  Gave him some yogurt and peaches just a bit ago, so maybe he can hold that down.  He is full of energy, that's for sure.  Time to go and see what the little bugger is up to!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Three good days in a row!!!  I haven't been hit since Tuesday - yay - even if he is only 5 he hits pretty hard and only 1 Time Out yesterday and 1 today!  Hooray!! :)  Being with him 24/7 is tedious on me but it is nice in some ways too.  There are more hugs and kisses which is nice.  I get special kisses on the nose too - I think just because it sticks out there so far.  Boy I hope he doesn't get my nose - I'm not even sure where I got it from - no one else in the family has it!   Zack's frustration has rubbed off onto me today - I'm snapping like a turtle - I think it's time for some valium because I feel anxious!  That and some aspirin for this headache.    We did some lovely painting today, pictures will be up later on that.  Besides that we really didn't do much - it was a lazy day for us.  My fault because I'm grumpy.  Oh well, it's Friday!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, as the story goes, it's not always a shining success story right off the bat!  And it hasn't been around here either, but I think we are making a little progress and that is a good thing.  I don't ever expect it to be easy with Zack - as I don't expect it will ever be easy with me.  He will always have difficulties and will have to be more disciplined than his friends to keep up.  He will have to think harder to stay in control of his emotions or they will get the best of him.  He will need more coping skills (and so will I), more relaxation techniques, more diversion tactics than anyone.  Good thing that people with bipolar are typically very smart and creative - we need those things to stay alive.  Yesterday I was actually proud of us both.  We sat and talked through what could have been a fit of anger and a stay in Time Out for him and more lousy feelings for me.  I caught his rising mood before it escalated and starting talking to him (after I had to go after him, down the hall and find him hiding behind his bed at my Mom's house).  At first he wouldn't talk he just hit the floor and stared at the wall.  Then he started to talk but I couldn't hear him.  He said he didn't want me to look at him so I looked away and he sat up and started answering my questions.  He wasn't mad at me, Big Mama or himself or any of the stuffed animals (lol) - he was just mad.  I told him I understood this and asked if he knew how.  He didn't.  I didn't realize  until that moment that he didn't know what was wrong with him, what it was called, or that I had the same thing.  All he knew, since he had been diagnosed so young was that the medicine helped his brain work right and Mommy took medicine too.  So I sat and explained that we both had Bipolar.  It was a serious problem with our brains and we had to take medicine to help us think straight, but that we had to also work really hard at controlling our own thinking as well.  That just because we were angry didn't mean it was okay to hit someone or kick the wall - only our punching bag.  But, I think it helped him a lot to know that I was the same as him - like a switch going on.  A switch that I should have turned on months ago.  My mistake.  But it's corrected now and now we will talk about it a lot more.  He may not understand everything that is said - but I'd rather it be that way than not say enough and have him be left out in the dark again.  Today, well, today started off great but we hit a rough spot.  He became frustrated over the date.  We do a "Countdown to School" calendar because he is so excited about starting Kindergarten that he was making himself really upset about it.  Well, school had started one for him too so now we have two of them.  One has stickers (ours) and one has stamps (school's).  He stamped up until today on Friday by accident.  So this morning early we did a sticker for today but not a stamp for the other one.  After lunch he was looking at the calendars and mentioned we hadn't done them yet.  Well, it went back and forth of me trying to explain what happened and that I'd show him on the computer what day it was and he said no and hit me.    "5 minutes in Time Out."  "No!" Hits me again.  "10 minutes."  Back and forth until I finally stopped him at an hour and a half.  I took him to his room and he turned around and hit me again, threw his pjs at me and shut himself in the closet.  So we settled on 2 hours.  He then got his door closed - which he hates - and I was surprised it didn't start a riot.  No screaming, no crying, no nothing.  Odd.  Maybe, just maybe, his new medicine is starting to take affect.  I hope!  Anyway, he decided it would be naptime and asked for a hug.  I went in there and he gave me a hug and said he was sorry.  Then he had to go potty (which he does about 6 times when he's in Time Out! *g*) and came back into my office for another hug and kiss.  He hugged me for a long time.  I reminded him of our talk and how hard it was, to try to remember that and go think about it.  He said he would.  And he asked if he could keep his door open.  I told him yes if he could be quiet.  Well, this has been the quietest hour of Time Out so far.  2 calls to say "I love you" and one potty break.  I just gave him his 3PM Risperdal - let's hope the rest of the day goes good.  I could use a break from the hitting. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What are the symptoms of bipolar disorder in children?   Bipolar disorder involves marked changes in mood and energy. In most adults with the illness, persistent states of extreme elation or agitation accompanied by high energy are called mania. Persistent states of extreme sadness or irritability accompanied by low energy are called depression.    However, the illness looks different in children than it does in adults.  Children usually have an ongoing, continuous mood disturbance that is a mix of mania and depression. This rapid and severe cycling between moods produces chronic irritability and few clear periods of wellness between episodes.    SYMPTOMS MAY INCLUDE:    an expansive or irritable mood  depression  rapidly changing moods lasting a few hours to a few days  explosive, lengthy, and often destructive rages  separation anxiety  defiance of authority  hyperactivity, agitation, and distractibility  sleeping little or, alternatively, sleeping too much  bed wetting and night terrors  strong and frequent cravings, often for carbohydrates and sweets  excessive involvement in multiple projects and activities  impaired judgment, impulsivity, racing thoughts, and pressure to keep talking  dare-devil behaviors  inappropriate or precocious sexual behavior  delusions and hallucinations  grandiose belief in own abilities that defy the laws of logic (ability to fly, for example)    If your child behaves in these ways, don't assume that they are a bad child or that they have bipolar disorder...take them to a psychiatrist to be evaluated or at least to your family doctor.  Help is out there.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zack's behavior is still not acceptable. There is no way I could send him to school acting the way he does. His anger and frustration are still the biggest problems, or I should say his lack of control over them. His concentration level is about a zero too. Racing thoughts and lack of concentration are part of a manic episode. I just hope he comes down from this soon.   We went to the pdoc yesterday and thankfully we were able to increase his Trileptal - which is his new mood stabilizer. So far the low dose has helped some so the higher dose may produce the effect that we want - which is to bring him out of the manic state into a more stabile state.   Right now he is sitting in Time Out for not listening, slamming things down and hitting things (thankfully not me or the dog this time). But he knows better. So we are having a bit of a rough day. He is quite tearful as well. *sigh* It makes me want to curl up in a ball and weep myself - but I have to teach him that even though he is bipolar, he has to have some sort of coping skills. He knows when he gets frustrated that he is to hit his punching bag and that is it. He also knows about counting to ten and taking deep breaths - he just won't do it until I get to my breaking point - then he wants to comply - that shows me he can do it - he just won't. He also gets into a little habit of suddenly not being able to do what I ask him to do because he "doesn't know how." Things like getting dressed. He tells me he can't - he doesn't know how.   At this point I'm surprised I have any hair left!    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been 4 days since Zack had his new med increase and I have yet to see a difference.&nbsp; He is just so elated all the time - giggling at everything and at nothing at all, running through the house, not wanting to learn his lessons for the day.&nbsp; I even gave him the extra med the pdoc said I could give him.&nbsp; That calmed him down for about 2 hours, of which 1 hour was a nap.&nbsp; But he wakes up cranky after a nap so that isn't going to work - especially not for school.&nbsp; If he's like this tomorrow - the pdoc is getting a phone call from me.   
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's been almost a full week and Zack is still acting quite manic at times during the day so I'm afraid I'll be calling the doctor's office on Monday about doing something different.  Maybe another increase, maybe a different med - but it's only 2 more weeks until school starts!!  Zack did see his therapist for the first time on Thursday though and it went very well.  He calls him Dr. Mel and took to him right away.  Good choice to get a male therapist!!  Pat on the back for Mommy!  He talked to me about 1/2 the time and then did some things with Zack that I got to sit in on.  He also gave me several things to read and the title of a book to get.  I think it's going to work out well with Dr. Mel.  Zack had a pretty rough day today.  He was in Time Out a lot for not listening and we didn't get to go see Big Mama today because of it.  Maybe tomorrow.  Well, one exhausted Mommy is going to bed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, what a week we've had - both of us!&nbsp; Zack is still manic/hyper so I'm going to have to call his doctor tomorrow and see about doing something with his meds.&nbsp; His frustration level seems to be dropping a little - he gets frustrated less often and gets over it much quicker, but he is wound up tighter than a top!&nbsp; He cannot walk anywhere - he must RUN.&nbsp; So I take him outside and let him run thinking it will wear him out, but he still runs throught the house like he's jet propelled.&nbsp; Everything is a race with him...fast, fast, fast!!!&nbsp; He writes fast, eats fast, has to be the first to get his seatbelt buckled even.&nbsp; Everything is "I can beat you, Mommy."&nbsp; Ahhhhhh!&nbsp; I know little kids have a lot of energy but this is rediculous! &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>



</Blog>