<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok so i go to work today and this fucking girl that i work with who has already decided that we are going to have sex just comes from a funeral.  Acting all deperessed for no reason.   She barely knew the guy and she wants sypmathy.  Fuck dat.  So anyhow she is also like half naked.  She has a large chest and is pretty thin with a getto booty.  tight pants and like a shirt that looked like a tank top.  I look at her and was like "did u where that" she goes yeah but i wore a jacket.  TITS STILL HANGING OUT moron.  What the fuck was she thinking.  I rolled my eyes and she said "fuck off" and i tell her.  What were u trying to do see if you could wake the dead guy out of the casket by showing him ur cleavage.  Anyhow  SHe is lazy as shit at work.  I am thinking i shouldnt hvae sex with her.  She would probably be soo fucking lazy anyways.  Besides it would hurt her ego.  On anouther note Allison called me today.  GIRL I LIKE.  And was upset because she thinks she did bad on a test she took.  I really felt bad because she seems like a smart girl and she studied hard.  Anways. enough going to the beach. with roosh and kristen----mindgamesgirl.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is my first blog today so i should talk about who i am.  My name is Som Bahrami and i am a 24 year old male who nearly goes out every night of the week possible.  I have found the most important tool I have to pick up women is my love for drinking.  I have the balls to hit on whoever i want and say whatever i want.  Its fun however i dont remeber shit.  I have my friend roosh aka rocking hoarse fill in the gaps and tell me what happens.  So as you can see you are going to see some funny drunk stories over time.  BY the way I cant spell well.  So much for that University of Maryland degree.  FUCK TERPS
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright this is a good one.  Monday night I bought myself a pizza for dinner and come home to dine.  I have a slice and then run off to the gym.  I come back and its gone.  Turns out my brother thought my dad bought it (which my father never shops at jerrys only pizza hut) and ate the entire thing.  I let that one slide and said don't let it happen again.  Wensday I bought a pizza for my dad and I, and one for my dinner on Thursday night.  On wensday night I called my brother and told him, "Sean I am buying this pizza for my dinner tomorrow so don't go off eating it again this is my dinner".  I also told my father that the pizza would be my dinner for the next day.  Thursday afternoon I called  my brother and told him not to eat my dinner.  So anyhow I get off of work and come home.  WAIT!!!...My pizza isn't there.  I ask my father "have u seen my pizza?".  His response, "I don't know where it is".  I notice an empty pizza box with no fucking pizza!!!  I am furious at this point.  Called my brother and cussed him out. His first response "I didn't know it was ur pizza"...Bullshit!!!After telling him?..Then a few minutes pass and more cussing..."Dad told me I could eat it" .  That's right Mr, "I don't know where it is" said so.  I went off on both of them. I started to kick things off the floor and cussed both of them out.  They said I was being childish!! Well fuck them.  Anyhow I am right, its rude and disrespectful to do that shit
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I don't know if I wrote about this but I meet this hot older chick that's my aunts friend.  She is in her thirties and just got out of a divorce.  Anyhow I got her number and was supposed to call her yesterday but I called her to late and she was asleep.  I am very interested to see how that one pans out.  I talk to steph yesterday and she told me she would call me and let me know what's going on last night so we could hang out but she flaked and never called.  Rocking Horse and Chaco said that I should just blow her off for now which is what I am going to do since I am irritated with her.  Last night All of use went to Cosi,Then EYEBAR (which was dead) then Dragonfly.  This once cute girl who was with her fat friend were walking around and looking and I just shouted "hey ur looking for me aren't u, well look no further I am here".  Not expecting them to stop and actually talk; they actually did and I ended up talking to them both.  I was signaling for a wing to get rid of the tubby girl but to no avail it no one came. Finally Chaco got the fat one distracted and almost instantly the cute one moved closer and was being touchy which caught me off guard.  Anyhow I was going to close it by getting her number since tubby wanted to play hide the sausage with something but before I could someone called and Poof cute girl left to go to Spank.  Anyways!!! OH get this shit I haven't heard from Ms Allison.  What a Punk That pisses me off.  I have been getting flaked on a lot. In response to this I am switching up my game and not going to be as nice.  I am going to call my aunts friend who we shall call Convent Girl because she wants to join the convent.  And we will be celebrating rocking horse's birthday.  So latter Beash
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok let me reintroduces that I was feeling horrible on Sunday.  The nausea lasted the entire day.  Rather than staying home I went and spent time with an X cara.  Cara is a supersweet girl. Lots of fun and is very similar to me.  Why did it not work out between her and I you ask? To sum it all up; in case you didn't notice like all guys I have issues. Anyhow we went to Georgetown and basicly walked around.  I am her favorite "metrosexual"  Went to FCUK and then we ended up on the waterfront and saw Mahreen and Steve.  They are a really chill couple and we all just chilled and enjoyed the view.  I almost puked everything I got a slight whiff on booze.  We eventually went back to my car and for a quick spin. Really nice convertible day.  I saw her apartment which was really clean and organized. Then we called it a day.  It was interesting since even though I felt like shit physically I ended the day with a smile.  IT SOUNDS SOO GAY I KNOW.  As far as today.  Steph called to give me her new number. I am really irriated with her games so I am not going to call her back.  Well at least until I calm down.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright, just got off the phone with Rocking Hoarse. I got wasted once again last night and slept too late.  He is off to the wine tasting thing.  EWW no more booze.  I went over the edge again last night. OH as for AL and I going out today it doesn't seem likely.  I feel like she is going to flake RH called it out yesterday which is weird.  Oh well I don't feel so hot right now to do anything but recover. But it does bother me cause I was interested to see where things would go with her. She seemed pretty cool. Last night the terror twins were out.(my brother and I)  We started out at RH's where we meet Ron, cara and Rowena.  RH got everyone trashed.  I had this really cool drink which was green. Anyhow we did the metro party and they drove  to meet us. We knew they would not come to Vida VODKA BOY. So we get to Vida and we are trashed.  I hit on this ugly chick to warm up. She ignores me so as she is walking away I flick her off. She comes back and goes "don't ever flick me off" so I flick her off and Sean my brother heard and was like "u mean like this" so we are both in her face flicking her off.  It was funny she stormed off.  So I hit on some fat chicks and ran into the fam and crew. My aunt was with this older chick who just got out of this divorce. She is pretty cute but has major issues. "I WANT TO JOIN THE CONVENT"  WTF? Is that?  We drag them to eye bar. I drink more. I work harder on her. So she is opening up I get her number which I fucking lost.  Anyways she tried to say I was so young but she was still on me so that was bullshit. At one point she is like you are not going to be have sex with me if we date. I was like ok this is a bluff or a shit test if I ever heard one.  So I spit out "I want to get to know you better lets just go with the flow"  anyhow we obviously missed the metro so we went back in the car.  And I drove home.  And now too fucked to go to wine festival. Sorry RH. Well so now we are down to no prospects. Games Games Games. Everywhere!!! It gets annoying. If you like someone don't fuck with them.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright just got off work its about eight and i need a nap to get ready to party. Its raining as always and mother nature that fucking dirty skank cockblocker is going to try to ruin the night.  Well fuck you mother nature.   Ok thus far we got plans with  Alison this weekend finally!!! Both got busy scheudles.  She won mad points when she told me that she is going to be in the race for the cure thing in DC on saturday.  Shows she is a giving person.  As for SL fuck her i cant play her games she maybe cute but I am not doing shit till she calls.  OH i did today but didnt leave a message.  Anyhow as far as what i want alison is on the top of the list. She seems nice, hot, and ambitious.  Those are my top three qualities for a girl.  So tonight i dont know whats up but i will be drinking.  Saturday if alisons not to tired i told her to let me know if she wanted to go out. if not sat then def sunday.  I called her today because i figure that there is this wine festival on sunday.  So what better place to take a girl.  Lots of drunk people (hiding their inebriation), culture, and my crew of peeps.  She hasnt returned my call yet so we shall see.  I am interested to see if she will flake. It would def screw up my weekend and after the beach this past weekend i dont need anymore drama  mama. Ok fifteen minutes nap then i got to get ready peace beash
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok its time to post about the beach.  Went to the beach with KC and rocking hoarse.  We take my moms car since my car only seats two.  The moment we get to the beach the transmission dies. (car trouble the last beach vacation too)  Anyhow KC gets us a tow truck flirts with the tow truck driver and says that we need to be towed to a mechanic at the beach we were going to say.  She also begged the driver to let rocking hoarse to come along.  She said that he was her brother. Anyhow on the way rocking hoarse leaks out the secret. funny thouggh. I laughed as i squeezed him everytime her blurted something out.  Anyhow we finally get there and go to meet KC crew of girls.  Rocking hoarse and I are thinking awesome this is it.  Keep in mind i have been messin around with KC and sweat her friend SL. SL is 32 but looks like 19 soo hot.  Anyhow They basically diss her so we are these bars i am wasted at the puker barier and KC keeps going out to call her friends.  So anyhow to sum it up Rocking HOarse kicks the door open for her to sneak in and they get thrown out. She then leaves us to fuck her "friend"  So i am like great i just hooked up with her oh welll.  Rocking and I leave depresed and go sleep.  She comes back. We see her naked to sum things up (which was nice) but we go out again to meet up with the flakes.  I see SL and she is all friendly i am still irriated she hasnt called me back in like two weeks.  Anyhow she was up on me which made. KC mad.  OH one of the first things SL said was that KC got mad at her because we went out on a date. FUCK that KC JUST BONED SOME DUDE TWO HOURS AGO.  ANyhow we dance and KC grinds on rocking hoarse making him soo hard.  It was funny trying to make me jealous.  Nite ends with KC going to FUCK AGAIN!!! and SL spending the nite at GOOGle guys place. They probably fucked. He was playing nice guy.  Exit (the depressed som and roosh walk back to hotel)  On the way back Rocking Hoarse did an amazing job at getting information out of them.  Basically SL is a fucking player. Which i called her and confronted her about and she denied. FUCK YOU SL>   Anyhow she called today.  But so did allison.  Both are cute. Allison is my age which is a plus but i dont know she lives far.  We shall see.  Its down to two girls.  Both play fucking games. I am going to talk to Allison latter and see whats up for this weekend and SL is supposed to call me back to make plans.  Which i doubt fucking old flake. But she is soo fine.  And WORK SUCKS.  BUT as for who i want i think its Alison i want to take her out more to get to know her.  Both rocking hoarse and i agree that SL AND KC are COOKOOO
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok first of all rocking hoarse said not to use real names sooo I am going to use there initals.   Later i will post about the beach trip.  It was very educational  and the fucking car died!!!!  But friday night i am at RV's house and i get a phone call from AL it turns out she had her friend call.  They said they were going through the phone and calling everyone.  Bull shit.  Anyhow girls and there petty games cause she started to ask me questions and shit.  So anyhow this probably is a good sign since she probably was telling her friend about me.  But on the other hand She hasnt called since.   Girl def play games.  I learned this after my beach trip.  They are just like guys.  DOnt fucking think they are sweet or just to busy to call.  Seriously is anyhow that busy?  NO i think not.  So its BS and a part of the game.  Remember men are the agressors and women get to pick and choose.  Sucks doesnt it.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>