<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have recently discovered the coolness that is multiplayer gaming. In my particular case, it was in the form of Final Fantasy:Crystal Chronicles for the GameCube. Before this, I had always considered gaming to be, for me anyways, a solo past time. I wasn't into online gaming at all, and I tend to play games I like obsessively, so no one wanted to challenge me.  But FF:CC has changed my anti-social ways! I am ready to play with others! I might even try Worlds of Warcraft when it comes out! (I hope I'm not getting in over my head.)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was definitely one of those days. Everything exploded after lunch. I had a million things to do, and absolutely no time to do it in.  But you know what happened when I got home? I had an e-mail waiting for me from Michelle. She's an extremely kewl chick that I met through a Jay about a month and a half ago. It was her going away party on Tuesday night, as she was making the big move to Vancouver. Although I hadn't known her for very long, I felt that we really connected. I felt almost instantaneously comfortable around her, and could be a total goofball with her. Jay told me how upset she was the night before she left, just about leaving all her friends. So I sent her a note telling her basically what I just put here. I wanted to do something nice to make her day a little bit better.  I get fairly nervous saying stuff like that to people I haven't known forever (my core group of friends have all been together for at least six years), so it was a big step for me. It apparently worked, though, since she just sent me a very happy reply. It really brightened my day. I think I'm going to make an effort from now on to say something nice to at least one person a day. (I'm starting small, alright?)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, since I couldn't sleep when I went to bed, I started thinking about suicide. Not the actual act of committing suicide, but who I would write letters to and what I would say in them. Even just thinking about that, I started feeling guilty about all the people that I wouldn't write letters to. I mean, this would be my last chance to let someone know I didn't like them, or was indifferent to them in general, and I feel guilty? I really need to get over that.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it odd that I refuse to go to bed? I know if I go there, I'll just lie there and *think*, and that's not cool. I need to learn some trick on how to shut off my brain. So instead of doing the sensible thing and getting some sleep before getting up and going to hell, I mean work, tomorrow, I sit here on the computer, surfing the 'net.  I've been checking out some other blogs. It's weird. I'll read one, and if it intrigues me enough, I'll check out some of the archives. I'll always go to the earliest posts first, to see if they mention why they started their blogs. I almost need that insight into another world. I also get an intense curiosity to meet them in real life, just to see how different they are from the persona that they present in cyberspace. I don't think I'm too different from lots of my posts (I've had other sites, I'm not judging by the last three posts here), but I've read some of the e-mails I've sent, or logged conversations, and I'll hardly recognize myself. That's a scary feeling. Which one is real?
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And  urlLink THIS  is why I'm disgusted by society today. Don't get me wrong, I know there are tons of good people out there, and I've met lots of them, but every now and then, something like this happens that kind of shakes my entire faith in humanity.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever heard the song "Flake" by Jack Johnson? I can't get enough of it. I've seriously listened to it about six times already today. I'm a little obsessive, sometimes.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The past week has been very strange for me. I've been spending way more time by myself than I normally do. I tend to avoid being alone, since it gives me too much time to think, and I don't like what I discover. However, I have recently become friends with Sam, who is all about the analyzing. He comes up with some weird shit about me, but lots of it is also very true, and some stuff that I would barely admit to myself, so it was a little jarring to have a virtual stranger nail it on the head. I also spent about a day and a half locked in my basement, writing. It's been a long time since I've done that. I thought I had lost my creative spark. I tend to fantasize a lot, so I decided to start with just writing down my fantasies as they played out in my head. After a while, I would start to zone out and just let it flow. That was when I really discovered that I'm not nearly as different as I like to make myself out to be. I wonder how many people are like that?  But it has gotten to the point that my fear of rejection stops me from even taking a chance. I would like to fix it, but unfortunately, I don't know how. Any suggestions?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's something to be said for the anonymity of the Internet, isn't there? I can post my inner-most thoughts and feelings here, and never meet the people that read them. There will probably start to be strangers in the world that will know more about the real me than my personal friends. What is it about face-to-face interaction that makes me freeze up? Staring at this blank, non-descript font, I feel like I could write anything and be free.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally bought my first skateboard! Let's see how long it takes for me to hurt myself! :D
     
    
</post>


</Blog>