<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am back from my long weekend gotta work on some more web projects now.. So how did my weekend go well fri.. went to Cataract didnt end up camping cause orf all the rain.. but prbly still could of but didnt want to cause i was going to get up early and drive to Muncie to my brothers place.. so thats what i did i woke up about 7 am saturday monring lef the house about 8:20 and got to muncie about 11:30 first time driving to old muncie was kinda nice not to have my mom nagging me while i was driving. Usually when i drive im driving far with my mother lol..Chicago as an example.. I hate to drive.. I usually try to get out of it. Anyways got to muncie me and my bro hung out went to the mall cause I had to have a tye dye shirt and some black dockers alright well there goes 50 dollars flush lol maybe 25 in gas used going and coming back so there 75 total. We went to work about 3:00 clocked in at 4... and started working the bar i do think i am a might sexy bartend oh ya... lol... didnt even get to see Rupert... lol... worked till Midnight sheesh i am not used to all that like i used to lol.. my feet were killing me anyways made maybe a 100 dollars total so lets do some math professor 100 minus 75 equals 25 dollars was it worth it? well sure it was kinda nice to do something different and get some expereince its nice to know some things about how other jobs work and it was nice seeing my bro and helping him out.. So Sunday today came back home....&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Looks like i will be having a busy weekend this is my weekend schedule                                       Fri. going camping at Catiract Falls with some worthington friends...   Sat. driving to Anderson - to Hoosier Park (horse race track) my bro works there and he its the last day for the race season. and he needs a bar back.. so i will be helping him at the bar... so if your up in anderson come by... also Rupert from survivor will be there signing autographs and ect.   Sun.- If not to tired or still up north I will be attending Vincennes Redezvous . &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In today working on some online projects... lol good thing i decided to stick around home today its pretty nasty outside have had a cple tornado warnings..&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The Finished Product for the logo..is going to be used in a couple magazines and t-shirts&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    In Spring of 2004 in order to get a good concept and aspect for a logo I was looking for the the University Aviation Department took me up in the plane.  &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    sheesh look fields of corn ready to grow... imagine that in Indiana .... crazy&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Vincennes University... where I attend college.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Summer 2004   Nothing really goin on trying to get my site up and running.  While keeping social appearances. and working on projects. Sigh...i need a cple clones.. lol  Got a busy weekend ahead..  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Chris and his Girlfriend(Angela) at cataract falls... I dont know to either say aww ... or throw up&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Chris and Matt at the Sulfur Pit&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Chris - picture taken June 16th 2004 out behind Matt's house had a nice fire goin and thought this would be a cool picture.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Photoshoped the picture.. looks pretty cool i think&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Left to Right - Chris, Chad, and Matt - taken after swimming in the sulfur pit.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well Summer is going wish it was a little cooler though. Been doing alot of camping and hanging out. Drove this past week to a friend from colleges house he lives way out in the boodocks. Just been hanging with some of the crew in Worthington. Thats prbly what I will do most of the summer. That and work on some online jobs. Just hard to motivate myself sometimes. &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>