<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Have you ever had one of those moments when you opened your mouth to say something, and something else spilled forth?  It was a sentence, a statement, an oath that you couldn't belive exited your own mouth and sallied forth into the world, and after it was said it couldn't be taken back. Then once you heard it said you knew it to be true.  You knew deep down that this was part of your inner self leaping up to seize your tongue.  You could not deny it.  You could try, but the truth of it compelled you to admit it.  I've had a couple of those in my life.  I'll give you the first right now, it's by now means the best, but it is the first realization that I've ever experienced.  I'll begin with a little background.  I went to a small college, and I was on the schools very first collegiate swim team, I was the only Distance swimmer on the team, everyone else was a sprinter.  There were eight kids on the original team, seven guys and one girl, a majority came from the state where I went to school.  The long and the short of it was I was really annoyed by the girl,  we'll call her Sharon, I was convinced that I hated her, and my reaction to my friend starting to date her eventually cost me my friendship with him.  SO this went on for a while until she confronted me.  She said "Swimmercrazy, why do you hate me?" My response was immediate, I didn't even think about my answer. "I don't hate you, I don't hate anybody." And right after the words exited my mouth, I knew they were true.  I also knew that I was the one at fault.  I tried to repair the damage that had been done, but it was no use.  But I knew then that I didn't hate anyone, lest of all Sharon.  I've carried me with me to this day. It helped me know myself, but in the end it was a costly lesson.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So here it goes. I'm Joe the oldest boy and second oldest child in a family of 8.  Yes that's right eight kids.  And yes to your next question I am Irish Catholic.  I like guiness.  I like redheads (even though they're trouble).  I like blondes just because( does a man need an answer?) they're blonde.  I like politics and arguing, and people in general.  I havea  strange yet developed sense of humor that sometimes gets me into trouble.  Ah well.  On to the reason for this lovely blog (that is such a nasty sounding word by the way, it vaguely sounds like it should be a curse, like "I'm gonna blog you good", but maybe thats just me)  The reason, oh yes, is life.  Life is a journey blah blah blah, you hear that garbage every day.  But in it's essence the sentiment is true.  What life is really made up of is a series of vignettes, stroies and anecdotes that stick in our mind as if they were super glued.  We don't remember everything (Thank God) but we do remember what counts.  That my dear blogees (that term sounds slightly sexual by the way) is what it's all about.  Those collection of moments that stick in our brains and are suspended there as if they were trapped by some blessed flypaper.  That dear friends is what I will endeavor to jot down.  Stories of me, stroies of others, thoughts, dreams and realizations.  I could fill this blog about tripe like what I did that day, and what I ate for breakfast, but you don't care about that hogwash and I won't pretend that you do.......   So there! My intro is complete  Welcome to my world.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here I sit, my job is now a faded memory, I was/am a teteacher, but that is no more. Oppertunities have suddenly presented themselves to me, and they are good enough to disrupt my plans. Hmmmmm. Do you plan?  Do you scheme?  Do you try to run mental circles around your foes? Whats that?  You say that you don't have foes?   Then you are in more trouble than I thought. You have foes, surely not like Lex Luthor, but you have foes all the same.  If you still think not, look a little closer at your friends, then examine your aquaintences, your foes are there lurking. This is not paranoia. It's just something of which you need to be made aware. Still doubting? Okay... Think for a moment is there someone at work or school who just annoys you to no end?  And silently you've found yourself rooting for their eventual fall, whether it be a work or else where.  Well not everyone is silent, some people are acutally ou to get you, whether it be because of what you represent or what you have said in the past. People are petty. Not as a rule, but it's still something to watch out for. Life is not fair, and you should look out for times when others may try and trip you up. Just a word of advice.  I had to learn the hard way. I'll leave that story for another time though. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This will be a running monologue of insights, frustrations, and complaints.  Chime in whenever you want.  I remember one thing in particular from a very bad Johnny Depp movie called Don Juan Dimmarco, and it was this quote in a roundabout way:  "Every woman is a world unto herself.  Each woman is beautiful.  You must look for that beauty sometimes, but it is there.  Women love me because I can see that beauty, becasue I know they are beautiful and can tell them as such."  Or it was something like that.  Anyway, I've found this to be true.  Every woman is beautiful just l;ike every man is good in some way, all thats needed is the patience to see it.  It's very hard to do.  But once you get the hang of it, it'll be hard not to fall in love with every woman you meet, and expect the best out of the worst of guys. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I went to work somewhere new, and there are geese everywhere, crapping, honking, looking dumb.  They left a mess that one can only describe as prodigious and there was this sign that said "Please pick up your dog poop"  $50-$200 dollar fine.  And I'm like man thats daft.  I'll tell you what these geese made more mess than a great dan that had just eaten a pound of butter.  It was nasty.  And these people are gonna charge people for letting their dogs crap here?  Dumb dumb dumb.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      the summer the summer the summer it is a bearing down on me.&nbsp; the ex from last summer is working with me a again.&nbsp; And I find it hard to disconnect.&nbsp; She still needs me I can tell but she still doesn't want anything serious.&nbsp; so thats it for me.&nbsp; I've decided to cut her out of my life when she leaves agian in September.&nbsp; It's done.&nbsp; I'm done.&nbsp; It's shown me what I don't need.&nbsp; And what I don't want.&nbsp; So I have to thank her for that.&nbsp; but it's also kind of twisted me as well.&nbsp;   I'm at that point that being heartless is the only solution. I need to move on.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>