<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Nashville News is quite peculiar, sometimes they'll shock you by running a good news program, then other times, it's a bunch of liberal propoganda..... I personally enjoy much of Channel 2's news, except for the morning show, when Victoria Hansen was replaced, I wept for weeks..... She had a face and smile that could snap you out of the worst hangovers and make the news seem a little gentle, now you have the love fest in the mornings with the husband and wife duo, who are oh so happy, hey it's a good thing if that's your bag. Personally I think Heather Orne probably told Neil to get her on the air and quit making ' Come Hither and Ravish Me ' eyes with Victoria... Come on people you know there was some repressed sexual fustration between the two. And then poor Lilla Marigza ( however you spell that last name ) she must be a true sport.. She's always out in the worst weather and gets asked the dumbest questions ( For instance one time it was supposed to snow and ice so they sent her to the KY line..... they ask her ' Lilla is it cold where you are right now??? ' Keep in mind she was wearing a parka, steam was coming from every oxygen expelling orifice and ice/rain/snow mixture was coming down.... She should have said ' No, it feels like 80 out here, a mere 45 minutes from where it's freezing, in fact I don't even know why i'm wearing this parka, it's not like it's raining or sleeting or snowing anyways you f*cking jerk ! ' ) She needs to get some hazard pay, she's like the crocodile hunter minus the khaki clothes and alligators and australia and a zoo and a p*nis and a mullet def leppard would be proud of... So now that that point is shot to hell, let's move on.... Lilla you're a good woman!    I can stomach Channel fours morning show, except for the weather guy... the last thing I need to see before i go into work is a weather man who does poetry, i hate hippies anyways and the fact he said ' yes indeedly doodly ' once really makes me wanna donkey punch him in the sideburns. Oh and Ben Senger looks like my Boss, a true stiff in every since of the word, maybe Ben's a nice guy, but I already wanna throw burning feces in his eyes for resembling my boss.    Channel Fives morning show is boring. the only good thing is that cute little Kristin Preisol, she reminds me of a little angel ornament you can get from the flea market, and you don't have to put up with fat women wearing fanny packs and tweety bird shirts with sweatpants and ' Kool Cigarette ' Visors on.... And as long as I don't see the fetus boy that does the weather I'll be a o.k. .    I don't check out Channel 7 because it reminds me too much of the Ralph Emery show and Ralph came to my church once and farted in the row in front of me, that was a bad experience. I always liked the little buck toothed guy that replaced him too. Granted I was a kid back then, like 8, but my parents made me watch the show. And you wanna talk about pent up sexual fustrations.... That buck toothed guy and Karlen Evans had a lot of static electricity between them.... Leave your comments below and don't forget to vote in the Hottest TV Newswoman Poll................
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Click the link below to vote for the local TV Media Hottie that you think deserves the award. This will be a weekly poll and each winner will get a certificate that they can hang proudly from there news cubes.... If I left anyone off, don't worry we have more weeks and more people can be added. Personally I'd vote for Sara Walsh, but that's just me... I think John Dwyer from News 2 deserves an honorable mention, he at least spends 18.56 hours a day doing his hair and putting on his abundance of makeup. Also if Mark Howard whines a little bit more than usual during his sports segment on Channel 5 he may qualify as a chick.....      You'll have to copy and paste the address into your toolbar, but that doesn't take too much effort, unless you're a lazy@ss.                http://www.misterpoll.com/2026683752.html
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Hey what's up.... Welcome to the Nashville TV Media Blog... I'll do my best to add a little bit of comedy to the stiffs that pimp the news on local TV. I'll cover everything from the Embryo that does Channel 5's weather on the weekend to the Fashionably Retarded Cynthia Williams on Channel 4. I'll cover the idiotic ramblings of the too happy to be there weatherman on channel 4  to ' Johnny Too Cool For You ' Sports Guy on Channel 2. I'll also be doing polls and awards for the most insane and idiotic things out there on your tv. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>