<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So, enough of the introductions.  Let's begin.  This is my life.  These are my friends.  Let the great epic of my dilemmas begin.  Yesterday was Commmencement.  After deciding that I would not cry, I saw the miraculous Katie Bowen, my favorite senior, in the dreaded cap and gown and just about feel to pieces.  I don't think I'm an incredibly emotional person.  I think that if I decide to appear stoic, I can.  However, yesterday was an exception.  During the ceremony, my seniors and I sang together for the last time in our high school choir.  After the ceremony came another melancholy session with Bowen and a few other favorite seniors.  It blows my mind that she's now out of high school and I have another full year without her.  Next up, graduation parties.  I went with a group of five, which included Samantha Akers, Heath Hupke, Ben Johnson, and the ever-amazing Heidi Uridil.  The weather was gloomy - tornado and flash flood warnings all over.  Compartively bleak was the atmosphere amongst the group.  Sam (an incredibly emotional sophomore) was for some reason convinced that everyone in the car (and in the world) hated her.  Heidi (who often encounters Sam's insecurities) had completely lost patience with her.  I was short with Ben, though I admittedly had no reason to be.  For some reason it seems like Ben and I are constantly competing with each other.  The two of us disagree on everything, which is not actually a bad thing.  The difference of opinion that Ben and I share I think usually enriches our relationship.  I think it's good to spend some time with a person that is completely different from  you.  However, sometimes it's also incredibly annoying.  In the middle of all this, was the immaculate Heath Hupke, just wanting everyone to get along.  Heath's a good kid.  Things got better when we went back to Sam's house after attending numerous graduation parties.  We played a couple of board games, rented and watched the Halle Berry movie Gothika.  And that's high school for you.  You can spend any amount of time completely at each other's throats but at the end of the day, you all go home and have fun.  Doesn't make sense.  And, yeah, it's immature.  But maybe high school's really our last chance to be immature.  As always, the best part of today was Heidi Uridil.  It's days like today that I really, really am happy I have her.  In this Whirlwind that is high school, it's good to have someone that always supports you.  I'm an amateur at this whole 'relationship' thing, but I think it's coming along just fine.  More than fine, actually.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So, here I am: Seth Kaltwasser, documenting the first day of summer vacation.  Junior year is over.  It's been a long journey, but as of today, I have only one year of school left.  Senior year.  And that blows my mind.  Junior year certainly was a good one.  Very possibly the best ever.  It seems like just yesterday the year started and I was blown away to realize that I was officially an 'upperclassmen'.  As an 'upperclassmen', I finally got a chance to perform leading roles in the school's two theatre productions  (the musical "Anything Goes" and the play "It Runs in the Family").  Also, the Katie McCormack and I made All-State in Speech with our skit, "I'm Herbert".  Finally, show choir brought the greatest and least expected reward of all:  the incredible Heidi Uridil, a sophomore.  Seven weeks and five days ago I ended my extended age as a single guy (which lasted 5 years).  The almost two months that followed were quite possibly the best of my life.  That brings us to this week.  My last week with this year's seniors.  We'll see each other again, yes.  But the memories we made together this last year will never be equaled.  So, here I am, on the first day of summer.  In a couple of minutes I will leave to go pick up Heidi so that we can begin our weekend of attending graduation parties.  Tomorrow is Commencement where we officially close the book on last year.  What's on the horizon for this summer?  Hopefully, I'll be getting a job.  I have one more week of Heidi before letting her go spend three weeks at camp.  Add that to the three weeks I'll be spending on a family vacation and you have a consecutive six weeks that we'll be communicating only by phone.  It will be hard, but I have every intention of making this week last as long as possible.  Anyways, I have to be going.  Don't want to keep Heidi waiting.  Peace out.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I guess I just feel numb.  It's hard to see things change, but the idea of the transition is so bizzare that until it sinks in, I can't begin to cope.  It's hard to think that this was the last day for you.  That now you have to go and grow up and live in the 'real world' without us.  I'd love to look at you and know that you'd never have to grow up.  Not only must I face the fact that you're going to, I must realize that it's already begun.  These are the best years of our lives.  Catwalk Parties.  Stolemates. Invitationals.  Clowns in Target. Gas in milk jugs. Razzle Dazzles in the loft.  Madrigals, Javas, and a Big Orange Ride.  I guess it has to be.  I know that life goes on.  But Junior year has been great.  The last eight weeks have been the best of my life.  Seeing it go - seeing you go - and knowing there's nothing I can do about it.  How does that make me feel?  I guess I just feel numb.  You will be missed.  
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's been a rather uneventful week without Heidi.  Monday and the majority of Tuesday were spent doing more or less nothing.  I was bored out of my mind.  In all honesty, I do want Heidi to enjoy her time at camp.  But it's a little hard knowing that without her, I'm practically losing my mind...and without me, she's having a great time with friends at camp.  I do think she misses me, but she can handle it.  I need to learn how to handle not being around her.  Being in a relationship should not mean forgetting how to be independent.  But that's my own fault.  Tuesday I wrote her a letter and sent it.  Then, on the edge of losing my mind after spending two and a half days helping my mom clean the house and nothing else, I gave Keri Brecht a call to see what she was doing.  She and Billy Hahn (a junior) were announcing for the baseball game that night and she invited me to come hang out with them.  I did, and it was fun.  Then again, compared to the rest of my week, having my skull busted in by Governor Schwarzenegger would have seemed like a trip to Disneyworld. Anyways, our Bobcats KILLED Washington and the game ended within the first 5 innings.  So, Keri, some girl named Christy that I don't know, and I went back to Keri's house were we talked, looked at pictures, and watched "Young Frankenstien".  Good movie, that.  Very funny.  Anyways, moving on...  It's now Wednesday morning and I'm bored again.  So, I convince my mom to take me into Cedar Rapids.  While in town, I get a phone call from the mother of Katie Bowen.  Katie just got her wisdom teeth removed Tuesday morning and is still pretty weak.  She's been passing out and stuff.  Her parents have to work until about 9:30 tonight and they want someone to be home with her.  Kegan will be there in the early afternoon, but wanted to see if I could be there from about 4:30 till the parents get back.  And I think that sounds like a great idea.  Katie and I watch "EdTV"...wow, that movie sucked, a little Drew Carey, a little 'My Wife and Kids' and 'The Ultimate Love Test'.  During this last show I contemplate how I would seriously lose my mind if I went on that show and my Heidi Uridil spent three weeks away from me, in paradise, with one of her ex-boyfriends - especially if it was Josh Hennings.  I would kill something, for sure.  I'm not sure why Americans like watching people go through this on TV, but...well, I enjoyed myself immensely.  Heidi made Katie a frame with pictures of the two of them in it for Graduation.  I spent five hours at Katie's house tonight, and the majority of that time I was staring at the frame.  After four days of not seeing her, I think I almost forgot how beautiful Heidi Uridil really is.  I get home and my mom seems very excited.  She says something to the effect of -"So, Heidi called you?" -"Uhhh...no" I say Turns out Heidi called my house while I was at Katie's.  Mom told her where I was, explained why, and gave her the phone number.  Heidi said she would call there.  But she never did.  I assume it had something to do with the fact that last year she got in trouble for using her cell phone at camp.  I suppose she was going to call me at Katie's, but had to postpone the phone call due to counselors being around.  Or, maybe she was just afraid she would disturb Katie, since she wasn't feeling the best.  In any case, I'm surprised to see I'm not really that disappointed.  My mother seemed very disappointed (originally, she was excited because she knew how much I've been missing Heidi).  I, on the other hand, didn't care too much that I didn't get to talk to her.  It's not that I didn't want to, but I was just so happy to hear that she called.  Sure, I would have loved to have a conversation with her again, but just knowing that she's thinking of me and made an attempt to call is more than enough to keep me happy.  *sigh*...I miss her.  But I'm so glad that I'll have her when this is all over.  That Heidi Uridil's just about as perfect as they come. 
     

        
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So, my last night with Heidi was Saturday.  She is now gone to summer camp.  Heidi used to date this boy named Josh Hennings.  And, because of it, I hate his stinking guts.  Josh can be a real jerk.  He's also a pothead.  And an alcoholic.  That's fine.  You wanna be a pothead, jerk, and alcoholic, what do I care?  But the thing that drives me nuts about the kid is that every adult in the county wants their daughter to date him.  He's good-looking and, around parents, awfully polite.  My mom loves the kid.  Heidi's mom loves the kid.  But he's such a phony.  And it drives me nuts.  Luckily, Heidi knows he's a phony.  And hates him as well.  But that's not much consolation.  For some reason, I become infuriated anytime I'm around the guy.  Such was the case this morning at church.  Because Heidi is in the picture, it's weird being around the guy.  I guess one reason I hate him so much is that I feel like we're competing.  I guess since Josh used to date Heidi, and Josh has a way of looking perfect, I always feel like Heidi is comparing me to him.  And he's showing me up.  -- Before I go any further, let me tell you that that fear of mine, is completely all in my head.  Heidi is completely turned off by the "bad boy" thing.  She doesn't want a boy who drinks.  She doesn't want a boy who does drugs.  Lastly, she doesn't want a boy who's going to date her, then treat her like dirt because she won't put out.  And Josh is that boy.  Those are the very reasons they broke up in the first place. --  Anyways, so at church we didn't talk or anything, but there was a moment of eye contact.  Perhaps I'm being paranoid (very probable), but I'm convinced he wants Heidi back (also very probably, seeing as how Heidi is a dream come true).  So, I go to Sunday School after church (Josh doesn't go to Sunday School - told you he was a bad kid).  Then I get online.  Heidi's online.  She's doing some last minute packing before she leaves.  I tell Heidi about Josh (she knows how I feel about him).  She laughs at me and tells me that she likes that I hate him so much. Says she does, too.  Then she tells me that she just talked to him.  I'm crabby now.  Heidi says it was weird because they have barely spoken since they broke up, but about half an hour before I got online, Josh was online and he IMed her.  Heidi tells me that the last two years she went to camp, she told Josh to write her, and he never did.  But today, when he IMed her, he says he will this year.  Heidi says that's fine but there's no way she's writing him back.  And now it's clear.  Josh is making this a competition!  After the moment of eye contact, Josh skips Sunday School and while I am being a good kid learning about the book of Genesis - JOSH IS MAKING A MOVE ON MY GIRL!  Heidi laughs at my insecurity, but I'm convinced.  But you know what, Josh, that's fine.  Because Heidi hates you...I hope.  Heidi's not fooled by any of that "you're perfect" stuff.  She goes for the real guys.  The ones who participate in ....choir...and drama....yeah.  She's doesn't go for the cool...athletes.......  I hate Josh.  In other news, Katie Bowen found out today that her boyfriend of two years has just recently cheated on her.  (He's attending college six hours away.)  Also, he's been telling her that he's not drinking, and he has been.  Poor Katie.  She's in a tough spot.  Korey tells her that he was sorry and he loves her and he regrets it.  He tells her that he's not drinking as much as other people says he is.  Katie shouldn't trust him - this isn't the first time he's cheated on her.  But she wants to.  And she doesn't want to throw away the last two years if Korey really does regret it.  On the other hand, she's worried that some of her friends will thinks she's stupid if she doesn't leave him.  She doesn't want to leave him, but I think she knows she should.  High School is dramatic.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There are two cliques that I hang out with.  The first is the theatre people.  The second is the show choir people.  Now, these groups aren't completely separate.  Many theatre people participate in show choir and vis versa.  But when it comes to after school, and who hangs out with who, they become very distant.  Back in the days of my freshmen and sophomore years, I was very much a 'theatre' person.  But this last year, the 'theatre' group has become a bit too 'dramatic'. We DO get along.  More or less.  We were very good friends.  Hung out together all the time.  But, for some reason when it came to rehearsals this year, we were constantly at each other's throats.  I don't know why.  Stupid reasons, I'm sure.  But, you know, we just didn't work well together.  An innocent practice would turn into Katy and Ryan vs. Me, Keri, and McCormack vs. Curtis and Kyle and Veronica vs. Ben vs. Smiley and Billy.  In the end, we'd all pull together and turn out a fine show.  I mean, we were all talented.  Just, we could NOT cooperate.  And, it kinda broke us apart.  Now, we're all going our separate ways.  The seniors (Katy, Kyle, Curtis, Veronica, and Smiley) are graduating.  Keri's seen only at the Mini Mart where she works.  Fed, up with that group of kids, I discovered how nice, fun, and laid back the show choir people seemed to be.  Because of this, I became close with Heidi.  And now I dedicate most of my time to her.  God knows what the others are up to.    This isn't as dramatic as I'm making it sound (but, heck, I'm a theatre person, what do you expect??).  I mean, it's summer:  Keri isn't the only high schooler who spends all their summer time working.  I, too, should dedicate the majority of my time to Heidi.  I think that she should become priority.  It is, however, rather depressing to just watch the friendships dissolve.  The reason I'm bringing this up is because last night I attended Katy's graduation party.  And it was weird.  Keri was there.  Ryan was there.  Kyle was there.  And I felt like such an outcast.  I mean, it was obvious when I deserted the group.  We were all getting fed up with each other.  We weren't hanging out as much.  So, I took all the extra time I had and spent it with other friends.  Then, when wounds began to heal, the 'theatre kids' started hanging out again - they all went camping last weekend.  And I wasn't there.  I had already made plans with the 'schow choir kids'.  So, I show up at the party, and it was uncomfortable.  Keri was thrilled to see me.  Welcomed me back very nicely.  The others tried.  I don't want to make it sound like they weren't even attempting to welcome me.  But it was weird.  Heidi, of course, was never even mentioned.  After the party, Keri invited me back to her house.  We watched some videos from earlier in the year and reminisced. Talked a lot about the whole 'theatre kids' situation.  She's been feeling the same way I have.  As has McCormack.  As has Ben.  I'm rambling.  Sorry.  But it was really nice talking with Keri again.  She is a really good kid.  We've been friends since very early elementary school.  Heidi's gone for the next two weeks and I would really like it if we could hang out together during that time, but I'm also afraid we shouldn't.  Because when Heidi gets back, I'll want to spend my time with her again.  And I don't want Keri to think I was just using her company as a way to get out of the house when Heidi wasn't around.  And maybe, if she did think that, maybe she'd be justified in thinking it.  Like I said, I really like Keri, but if growing apart is inevitable, maybe I'm wrong in resurrecting our friendship, while knowing, all the while, that I would devote all my time to Heidi again when she comes back home.  On the other hand, maybe growing apart isn't inevitable.    And maybe I'm just incredibly dramatic.  Maybe this won't even be an issue in two months and things will be back to normal.  I just hate being stuck in between two 'cliques'.  Being very close to people on both sides - Show Choir: Bowen, Heidi / Theatre: Keri, McCormack - and not being able to spend time with both.  We'll see what happens.  There's no use in worrying about the future or regretting the past.  And maybe there is past to regret.  Maybe I was wrong in leaving the 'theatre kids' during the period of discomfort.  Maybe I was wrong in showing up at Katy's party.  Maybe I was wrong in going over to Keri's house last night.  But what does it matter?  Can't change any of it now.  I grew up with this girl named Becky Loy.  We've been friends since preschool.  She lives one house away from me.  We were best friends (incredibly close best friends) all through elementary and middle school.  And then when we reached high school, something happened.  I gues in high school, you become so busy with your extra-curricular stuff that you only have time to be friends with people involved in the same things you are.  And Becky isn't in theatre or show choir, so we've barely talked to each other for the last three years.  Yesterday night, when I was driving home from Keri's house, I saw her with her boyfriend on her porch.  And it made me sad.  I miss her, too.  But maybe growing apart is inevitable.  It's a fact of life.  And that's depressing.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Soon, I have to send my Heidi off to camp.  For the last few weeks I have been dreading summer for this very reason.  She leaves on Sunday.  She will then be away at camp for two weeks.  The very morning she gets back, I leave on a three-week long family vacation.  The day before I get back, she leaves for camp.  She will be there for at least one week, possibly two.  She only has four more days here.  But she won't be spending all that time with me.  Understandably, she has to spend time with her friends before leaving, too.  Tomorrow, she's spending the day with Derek, one of her best friends and ex-boyfriends.  Tomorrow night, her best friend Julie is spending the night with her.  They'll be spending that next day with each other and then Heidi has to babysit that night.  The next day (Friday), we are taking our siblings to the new Harry Potter movie.  Finally, we'll get to spend time together, but the kids will be there too.  Saturday, we're going out to another movie - this time alone - to celebrate our two month anniversary and to enjoy the last day we'll have together for a long while.  Being apart from her for at least six weeks will be hard.  But I'm not worried - er, I should say, I wasn't.  The reason I'm worried now is because Heidi's worried.  Today, I went over to her house, and it seemed that something might have been bothering her.  I then had to leave because she had to babysit for a neighbor.  When she got home, we talked on the phone.  And she tells me she's scared.  This worries me.  In my opinion, it will be hard, yes, but there's no reason to be scared.  If we both want this relationship to work, it will.  And it'll suck being apart for two months, at the end of the two months we'll be back together and everything will be ok.  That is, if we both want this relationship to work.  It would take a long explanation to really help you understand how I feel, and I don't want to ramble because even then I still probably can't make you understand.  The short story is this:  The fact that Heidi is being pessimistic scares me.  If she worries about it too much, she'll lose hope.  And that's the worst thing that could happen.  If, on the other hand, we both know everything will be fine, everything will be fine.  But Heidi doesn't know that.  And, if she's worried, how can I be so confident?  So, we get off the phone.  And I get online, hoping that my man Heath will be online because he knows us both well and could make me feel better.  But he's not online.  I just need to talk to someone and nobody is on to talk to.  So, here I am.  Writing in my blog.  After all, I guess that's what it's hear for.  The blog's hear to help me organize my thoughts.  And then the transcendent Katie Bowen gets online.  Katie has just spent basically the last year away from her boyfriend.  Her boyfriend, Korey, graduated from High School last year, and is now attending college six hours away.  They don't get to see each other much.  For this reason, Katie can completely relate to my present apprehension.  And she offers me some advice.  Korey gave her a stuffed animal.  When she misses him, or is worried about the strength of his feelings, she has the stuffed animal.  And it reminds her that their feelings are strong and that as soon as they're together again everything will be fine.  Katie suggests that I find something - anything - to give Heidi, so that any time she needs me while she's gone at camp or while I'm gone on vacation, she has that.  Not as a subsitute, but as consolation.  I think that sounds like a great idea.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      OK, so I realize that I've dedicated the last few days to nothing but whining about losing Heidi.&nbsp; And how she's stupid.   So, the last couple of days, when I went to write a new post, I was overwhelmed.&nbsp; I go through so many different emotions in one day, that it's getting to the point that I'd either need numerous posts per day, or one incredibly long, boring post to cover them all.   My solution?&nbsp; Not to write about any of them.   You get the picture.&nbsp; You understand.&nbsp; I haven't yet gotten over her.&nbsp; Now that my point is across, there is no need to further beat you over the head with the topic.&nbsp; I can't promise that I won't wake&nbsp;up tomorrow and need to complain about it again.&nbsp; But, as for tonight, I'm going to resist my temptation to grouse.&nbsp; Instead, I will tell you what I have done this week in addition to sitting around the house griping.    Day #1 - July 19, 2004 :&nbsp; The first day of my renewed bachelor-dom was probably the best.&nbsp; This day was pretty much covered in my previous post "The Day After (Emails, Phone Calls, and AIM)"&nbsp; It was the day of our "closure" emails and the infamous phone conversation with Tasha.&nbsp; Later, over AIM, Heidi and I got into a fight about the reasons she broke up with me.&nbsp; The fight ended when she told me that she had already stressed about this too much and could debate it no longer.&nbsp; Oh, right, and then I felt horrible, too.    Day #2 - July 20, 2004 :&nbsp; I still felt horrible about the previous night's fight.&nbsp; So, I called Heidi and left an apologetic voicemail.&nbsp; In the message, I told her that I missed her and hoped we could be friends, but that I needed a lot of time to sort out my thoughts and let things rest before talking with her again.&nbsp; Later, I got a call from Bowen saying that she wanted to go out.&nbsp; Ben joined us, too.&nbsp; Also, Ben and Tasha are really good friends, and even though Katie and Tasha don't know each other well, we invited Tasha to come with us.&nbsp; It was already late, so we just went to the restaurant where Katie works and ordered some Root Beers.&nbsp; It was nice.&nbsp; I've been on vacation, Ben's been busy working, and Katie's been busy helping out with her sister's wedding (her sister's getting married this Saturday), so we haven't had much time to see each other and it was good for me just to be able to talk with my friends again.&nbsp; Also, the evening was beneficial for me, because I realized that I had the support of many people.&nbsp; When Heidi broke up with me, she told me that she had discussed it with many of her friends.&nbsp; This made me feel like everyone knew it was not going to work out, and I was the only one left in the dark.&nbsp; However, tonight Bowen and Ben both stepped up, saying that they&nbsp;completely disapproved of the break-up and didn't know what Heidi was thinking.&nbsp; Also, Ben told me about how he had recently talked with some other people who strongly supported my relationship with Heidi.&nbsp; When I got home, I also had a brief discussion with my mom on the subject.&nbsp; It's really nice knowing that many people supported Heidi and I (when we were together) and now really feel that she's made a mistake.    Day #3 - July 21, 2004 :&nbsp; On the third day after the break up, I went shopping with Katy Kennon.&nbsp; Katy and I were best friends my freshmen and sophomore years, but lately she's become incredibly abrasive.&nbsp; She's just the sort that will always vehemently uphold her opinions and assumptions, even when she knows she's wrong.&nbsp; For this reason, I cannot stand being with her when she's in a large group.&nbsp; However, I don't mind being alone with her.&nbsp; So, I went shopping with her, mostly because she needed to buy a birthday present for her boyfriend (Ryan Morrison), but also because I needed out of the house.&nbsp; Then I got home.&nbsp; If the day before was a good day in terms of my emotions, this day was a bad day.&nbsp; After talking to Kegan Cliburn and Ashley Schmuecker (one of Heidi's best friends), I realized how easily Heidi is taking this break-up.&nbsp; And it really burned me up.&nbsp; But you can read all about that in the last post, "Just Another Boyfriend".    Day #4 - July 22, 2004 :&nbsp; Thursday was another beautiful example of Heidi's resilience.&nbsp; She spent the day at Adventureland with some of her girlfriends.&nbsp; Awesome.&nbsp; It's not that I don't want her to be happy and have fun.&nbsp; It's just that...well, I don't want her to be happy and have fun this soon after our break up.&nbsp; However, her trip proved beneficial for me.&nbsp; For the past couple of days, I had needed to return a video that my mom borrowed from Heidi's mom.&nbsp; After the break-up, this task became a dreaded one.&nbsp; My mom volunteered to do it for me, but I decided I had more dignity than to let my mom do the hard stuff.&nbsp; However, when Kegan told me that Heidi was gone for the day, I jumped at the oppurtunity and drove to her house.&nbsp; Her mom was home, and as I helped her carry in groceries, she told me how much she'd missed me, and I told her how much I'd missed her.&nbsp; She never really told me how she felt about Heidi's decision, but she did tell me that she thought it sucked that the relationship didn't work out.&nbsp; The main thing she stressed was that she didn't want me to stop hanging out at their house.&nbsp; I told her that I hoped to hang out with Heidi again after things cooled off.&nbsp; After about 5-10 minutes of conversation, I left the Uridil home.&nbsp; For the most part, I was happy with how it played out.&nbsp; However, it was hard being back in that house and talking with her mom.&nbsp; I love her family to death.&nbsp; And I'll miss spending all the time with them that I did.&nbsp; Later that night, Heidi tried to talk to me on AIM.&nbsp; She made many attempts at conversation, but I anwered mostly in one-word replies.&nbsp; Finally, she asked if I even wanted to talk, and I told her that I just didn't think I was ready.&nbsp; Which is true.&nbsp; And that night was proof.&nbsp; After talking to Heidi, I seemed to lose as much progress as I had made in the previous days.&nbsp; Even though the conversation was short and dull, being in her presence inspired in me a deep hatred for present circumstances.&nbsp; I was overwhelmed and spent the next hour (the midnight hour) walking around Keystone, sorting out my thoughts.&nbsp; And I realized that there was&nbsp;one question I couldn't answer.&nbsp;  What did I want?&nbsp;  Did I want Heidi and I to put the past behind us and become best friends?&nbsp; Did I want us to become bitter rivals?&nbsp; Did I want to try and win her back?&nbsp;  What did I want?&nbsp;  And then I realized that there is no answer.&nbsp; Because I don't want any of these things.&nbsp; The only thing I want is to take things back to how they were.&nbsp; To make sure that Heidi never broke up with me and things were great again.&nbsp; But that wasn't an option.&nbsp; Things can never be the way they were again.    Day #5 - Today, July 23, 2004 :&nbsp; Today, my brother Jared, his girlfriend Cambria, and my older sister Erin came home.&nbsp; My brother and Cambria are home (from Tulsa, where they live and attend college) to be at Katie Bowen's older sister's (Barbi's) wedding, which is tomorrow.&nbsp; Erin, then, came home to see them.&nbsp; Tonight, I also went with Keri, McCormack, Veronica, and our high school drama teacher, Mrs. Deerberg, to a local performance of  Big River,  a musical based on Mark Twain's  Huckleberry Finn.&nbsp;  It was pretty good.&nbsp; And a lot of fun.&nbsp; But, I'm exhausted.&nbsp; Heidi was supposed to be my date to the wedding tomorrow, but I think now I'm going to be Katie's.&nbsp; Ben will be at the wedding, too, which should be a lot of fun.   So, you're caught up.&nbsp; And I've got to call it a night.&nbsp; My eyes are fighting to stay open.&nbsp; I always proofread my posts before publishing them, but that's going to have to wait tonight.&nbsp; So, if you read this after I've published it, but before I've proofed it (which will be sometime tomorrow), I'm sorry.&nbsp; It probably made little to no sense.&nbsp; And you may have wasted a lot of time.   But thanks anyway.&nbsp; It's good to know someone's interested.   
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I went for a walk today.&nbsp; Had to sort out my thoughts.   It's hard to sort them out, though.&nbsp; Incredibly hard.&nbsp; Because my opinions change by the hour.   I go through such a range of emotions throughout my day -&nbsp; depression, frustration, disappointment - but the one that always seems to stick is anger.&nbsp; And I really am pissed.&nbsp; That she gave up so easily.&nbsp; That I seemingly gave up the last three and a half months of my life.&nbsp; And that she's already over me.   The latter is really the hardest part.&nbsp; It sucks knowing that - to me - she was 'my only girlfriend'.&nbsp; She was it.&nbsp; And it's hard getting over her.&nbsp; But - to her - I'm 'only her boyfriend'.&nbsp; I'm just one of many.&nbsp; I'm just the latest in her long list of ex-boyfriends.&nbsp; She's been through many relationships before, and mine's no different.&nbsp; She's been through many break-ups before, and this one's no harder.   When I say stuff like that to her, she gets mad and tells me that it's not true.&nbsp; That&nbsp;I wasn't just another "Josh" or "Beau".&nbsp; But that's such a load.&nbsp; I was.&nbsp; I'm just another boyfriend to her.&nbsp; Josh had his three months.&nbsp; Then I got my three months.&nbsp; Now, who's turn is it next?&nbsp; And, honestly, I give it 3 months.&nbsp; 4 months tops.&nbsp; She'll have another boyfriend.&nbsp; And she will have completely forgotten about me.   It frustrates me because I could foresee this going in.&nbsp; I told her who worried I was that I was just going to end up another "Josh".&nbsp; I asked her if our relationship felt any different.&nbsp; She assured me she that it felt much different.&nbsp; She must have just been telling me only what I wanted to here.  If our relationship meant anything to her, it wouldn't have been so easy for her to break up with me.&nbsp; And that's another thing!&nbsp; I hated how she broke up with me.&nbsp; I hated how we wait seven months to get to be together again, and then when we finally get back home and everything should be fine, she dumps me ( over the phone!)  for seemingly no reason.&nbsp; At least no reason that I can understand.  And&nbsp;I was the last person she talked to!&nbsp; She talked to her friends, she talked to her exes, apparently she talked to the  entire state of Iowa  except for me.&nbsp; By the time she talked to me  (again, over the phone)  she had already made up her mind that she was breaking up with me.&nbsp;  I should have been the first one she talked to!&nbsp;  We could have discussed our feelings, encouraged each other, and assured each other that things would get better soon.  But, no, I was the LAST person she talked to.  Also, I've realized that getting over her requires not only giving up talking to her, but breaking off communication with her friends, as well.  Tonight I talked with one of her best friends, Ashley Schmuecker.&nbsp; Why was this a bad idea?&nbsp; Because I realized how fine Heidi is doing without me.&nbsp; She's carrying on as if nothing ever happened.&nbsp; Ashley talked to me about how they spent the whole day at the mall, and when she told me about funny things that have happened to her recently, she usually ended them with "Heidi and I laughed about that for a long time afterward".  Outstanding.  I put so much time and effort into making this relationship work, and then nothing.&nbsp; She dismisses it like nothing ever happened.  Earlier, I called the last three and a half months a waste.&nbsp; And that's what it was.&nbsp; I know that sounds a little harsh, but it's true.&nbsp; I put so much time and effort into making this relationship work, and I get nothing out of it.&nbsp; The only thing that resulted from the last few months is that now Heidi gets to add me to her long list of ex-boyfriends.  Well, fine.&nbsp; Congratulations, Heidi.&nbsp; You can mark yourself down for one more.&nbsp;&nbsp;But don't ask me to be your puppet again.&nbsp; Because I'm  not &nbsp;volunteering.  ....(Hopefully I'm not challenged on that.&nbsp; I don't much have an appetite for crow.)    &nbsp; I just want to add one more thing.&nbsp; Just in case anyone is kind enough to devote five minutes of their day to reading my blog, I apologize for the last few posts.&nbsp; I know a lot of this is just stupid teenage drama.&nbsp; I also know that it will pass.&nbsp; But, until it does, this blog is my outlet.&nbsp; This is where I get it all out.&nbsp; I suppose posting it on the Internet in a blog is always better than yelling it in her face...and then living to regret it.  So, I'm sorry.&nbsp; But bear with me.&nbsp; Just like I keep telling myself, this too shall pass. 
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So, I woke up today and I guess the finality of it all just hit me.&nbsp; And it hurt.&nbsp; Like, I don't want you thinking that I spent the whole day bawling and listening to 80s romance on the radio.&nbsp; But, when I realized that things were never going to be as perfect as they were in the first 2 months, it did hit me hard.&nbsp; And, although I wasn't crying, I was awfully depressed. &nbsp; I decided that I was going to send Heidi an email entitled "Closure".&nbsp; I would just tell her my thoughts.&nbsp; The purpose of the email was to let Heidi know what I was feeling, but still not have to talk to her for a few weeks.&nbsp; Because I kind of feel like that's the best way to get over her.&nbsp; Of course, she gave me the "let's just be friends" speech, but, personally, I think that if we make an immediate transition to just being friends, I'll never get over her.&nbsp; I miss her, and I want to hang out again, but perhaps it's for the best if we don't. &nbsp; Anyways, so I spent a long time on this "closure" email, because I didn't want it to be me just being emotional.&nbsp; Since it was only the day after, I may not have had all the time I needed to sort out my thoughts.&nbsp; But, I wanted to get the email sent out ASAP, so I just took my time to make sure that none of it was over the top.&nbsp; Here are some&nbsp; excerpts... &nbsp;  "I guess I have a pessimistic&nbsp;side.&nbsp; A side that believes there are certain types of people.&nbsp; Certain classes of people.&nbsp; A side that believes in the idea that a person from one class could never fall in love with a person from another.&nbsp; However,&nbsp;if for only three and a half months, I changed my mind and I wasn't so pessimistic.&nbsp; And it was beautiful.&nbsp; And maybe during the last six weeks I knew in my heart that our relationship was only an illusion, and I knew that girls like you don't end up with boys like me.&nbsp; But I really tried to hold on, because I wanted so badly to prove that idea wrong.&nbsp; I guess in the end it wasn't your fault that this didn't work out, and it wasn't mine.&nbsp; It's just the way things are.&nbsp; I was never the man for you, and you were never the girl for me."    &nbsp;  "The bottom line is this.&nbsp; I'm frustrated and I'm disappointed and I'm sad.&nbsp; But I'm ok.&nbsp;&nbsp;I'm frustrated because I really think that we could have made this work and I really feel like we called this seven weeks ago.&nbsp; Seven weeks ago we talked about how we were afraid that this would happen.&nbsp; And now it is happening.&nbsp; And you're not fighting for it.&nbsp; So, I'm frustrated.&nbsp; And I'm disappointed&nbsp;because I spent the last seven weeks telling myself that if I stuck it out everything would be back to normal and perfect like it was before.&nbsp; And now I see that I'm wrong.&nbsp; Things will never again be how they were in the first two months.&nbsp; And that disappoints me.&nbsp; And I'm sad.&nbsp; I'm sad because I already miss you.&nbsp; And I don't want to see this happen.&nbsp; But now it's too late."    &nbsp;  "Anyways, I'm keeping you.&nbsp; Wish the family my best.&nbsp; And I really do hope that things remain good with you.&nbsp; Maybe I'll see you around sometime.  &nbsp;  - Seth"    &nbsp; Seeing as how those were only excerpts, you know it was a long email. &nbsp; So, then I tried to move on with my life.&nbsp; I made plans to go with Kegan Cliburn (one of my  best  guy friends...which isn't saying much, because I don't have  that  many guy friends) to a party, but then the party never happened.&nbsp; So, I made plans to go bowling with Keri Brecht, Katie McCormack, Billy Hahn, and some other people, but then decided I did not want to leave the house. &nbsp; So, I get back online and Heidi has replyed to my "closure" email.&nbsp; Here are some excerpts... &nbsp;  "Ok, first off&nbsp;I just wanted to tell you that you are an incredible writer and secondly&nbsp;I want you to know that you and&nbsp;I are not in different 'social classes' (if you will) and that&nbsp;I really do think that we were just too good of friends for it to have worked out."    &nbsp;  "You did everything right, Seth Kaltwasser, - you're funny, sweet and interested in the same stuff&nbsp;I am.&nbsp; I mean you were exactly what&nbsp;I was looking for- however&nbsp;I just felt like there was some element missing and I'm sorry if you think I'm giving up but&nbsp;I really don't think that is the case because the element has been missing the entire time we were together- and&nbsp;I just think that is due to the fact that we are just too alike- too good of friends. "    &nbsp;  "Im sure that this all happened because of the distance but on top of that -&nbsp;like&nbsp;I told you - I've changed so much and my intentions and desires for my high school life have changed too -&nbsp;I don't need this extra stress - because that is what it has turned into -&nbsp;due to nothing you've done; whether or not you agree doesn't really matter because that is how&nbsp;I felt and&nbsp;I don't think that that is fair to you, as previously stated."    &nbsp;  "So I'll give you your sweet time to be friends again because&nbsp;I love you to death - as a friend. and&nbsp;I know you think that's pathetic but&nbsp;I think that it is pathetic that you ended your 'closure' letter with maybe I'll see you around. It's actually somewhat ironic, that's how Josh ended his...    &nbsp;  - Heid"    &nbsp; This reply is unbelievably reminiscent of our relationship.&nbsp; Why do I say this?&nbsp; Because there are certain points where she drives me insane.&nbsp; Like when she says that our relationship turned into nothing but stress.&nbsp;  What?!&nbsp;  And how she implies that our relationship couldn't have worked out because we're "too perfect" for each other, or something. &nbsp; On the other hand, it's reminiscent of our relationship because there are certain points where I love her to death.&nbsp; Like how she starts off the crazy-serious email by telling me what I great writer I am (compliments always help).&nbsp; And, more so, how she ends by telling me that the ending to my email was the same as her ex-boyfriends. &nbsp; The email sends me into such a spectrum of different emotions that I have to call someone, but there are few people I would talk to about the whole thing.&nbsp; Katie Bowen, maybe, but she had to work.&nbsp; Kegan, maybe, but I don't know his cell number.&nbsp; Keri, maybe, but she's bowling.&nbsp; And then I remember how I saw Tasha's cell number on my desk a few days ago.&nbsp; And how I've been meaning to catch up with her. &nbsp; OK, this post is already long enough, so do I really want to go into the intense history of Tasha and myself?&nbsp; *deep breath*...here goes... &nbsp; Tasha is an ENORMOUS character in my childhood.&nbsp; She was my first crush.&nbsp; I fell madly in love with her the moment I saw her, in Kindergarten, and immediately decided that she was to be my girlfriend. &nbsp; We became best of friends, along with Keri Brecht, Becky Loy, and Keaton Albers.&nbsp; But, once we got into 3rd Grade, that kind of died off, because we weren't in&nbsp;the same&nbsp;class.&nbsp; And for some reason, if we didn't have the same teacher, we never were able to make time for each other. &nbsp; But that all changed, in 6th Grade, when we both got Mr. Krob.&nbsp; It was our final year of elementary - we ruled the school - and it remains to this day the best school year of my life.&nbsp; We  finally  became boyfriend/girlfriend.&nbsp; All of our friends were friends and everything was perfect.&nbsp; Until I broke up with her. &nbsp; I'm still confused as to why I broke up with her.&nbsp; It happened in the early summer between our 6th and 7th Grade years.&nbsp; I think this was because I was under the false assumption that when I went into Middle School, I would meet many new girls (this is true) and that I would easily find a new girlfriend (dead wrong). &nbsp; The next two years (Middle School) were devoted to Tasha trying to get me back.&nbsp; She asked me out numerous times a week, made beautiful speeches on how we were meant to be together, and even sent me some very rememorable love letters. &nbsp; But everything changed once we got into High School.&nbsp; My theory is that, when you reach High School, you become so busy with your extra-curricular activities that you only have time to become friends with those involved in the same things you are.&nbsp; And Tasha and I were not involved in the same activities.&nbsp; I was involved in the music and drama departments, show choir, choir, musicals, plays, and madrigals.&nbsp; Tasha was involved in...well...nothing. &nbsp; I take that back, she is involved in band.&nbsp; She plays the alto sax.&nbsp; But for the most part, Tasha became one of the "naughty girls".&nbsp; She pierces things I wouldn't want pierced.&nbsp; She hangs out with people who smoke anything they get their hands on.&nbsp; And, from what I hear, she's rather experienced in the bedroom, too. &nbsp; So, we don't talk much.&nbsp; The last time we really talked was two years ago between our freshmen and sophomore years.&nbsp; She had started dating a major asshole&nbsp;named Ralph, and I tried to talk her out of it.&nbsp; She didn't listen.&nbsp; We got in a major fight, one of those fights that you can remember vividly for years to come.&nbsp; She accused me of acting like her father, and I accused her of "disappointing me" and settling for an identity that insulted her potential. &nbsp; Saying that she had "disappointed me" stuck with both of us for a long time.&nbsp; It hurt her, and I learned to regret it. &nbsp; I've always been intrigued by Tasha.&nbsp; She's just has such an exciting personality.&nbsp; And, being an ENORMOUS part of my childhood and now becoming the girl with quite a nightlife, she's always been one of the foremost characters in the story of my life, whether or not we actually hung out.&nbsp; The romantic side of me thinks we'll end up married. &nbsp; It would just be quite a story, I think.&nbsp; I knew, on the first day of Kindergarten, that we were meant to be together.&nbsp; We then finally got together later in life, but I broke it off out of ignorance.&nbsp; Then, Tasha became part of Iowa's aphotic underworld, but we found ourselves in the other, and led each other to a new life.&nbsp; Dramatic, huh? &nbsp; Tasha knows me, probably, better than anyone.&nbsp; The long phone conversations we've had over the years have supplied each of us with a vast knowledge and love of the other.&nbsp; And last night, we had another one. &nbsp; We ended up talking very little of Heidi.&nbsp; We laughed about old times.&nbsp; And caught each other up on the new.&nbsp; She's single now.&nbsp; For the first time in a long time.&nbsp; She just broke up with Ralph last February.&nbsp; She then had what she called a "fling" with a guy named Dan, but he turned out just to be horny.&nbsp; I told her about vacation.&nbsp; And how I was now looking for a job.&nbsp; And about the break-up.&nbsp; And she was sympathetic. &nbsp; It was such a breath of fresh air talking to her again.&nbsp; I realized that I really do miss her a lot.&nbsp; I also realized that she really is a sweet girl.&nbsp; The girls she hangs out with aren't so sweet.&nbsp; And she does certain things that aren't so sweet.&nbsp; But, in heart, she's not one of those girls at all. &nbsp; I'm really not trying to turn this romantic again.&nbsp; I lots of times think, even when I was dating Heidi, that Tasha and I could very well end up together.&nbsp; It would be funny, wouldn't it?&nbsp; The gentle pastor's son, marrying the Punk Princess.&nbsp; But, again, I'm really not trying to turn this romantic.&nbsp; I just miss her.&nbsp; And if that's where this leads, so be it. &nbsp; Another thing I want to enforce is that I really wasn't  using  Tasha to make Heidi jealous.&nbsp; However, as long as this post is, it's not over yet.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Well... &nbsp; I&nbsp;was on AIM&nbsp;when Tasha returned my call (when I called her, she was at work).&nbsp; When she called my parent's cell phone, instead of getting offline, I put up an away message saying "On the phone...leave me one".&nbsp; And when Seth Kaltwasser, who has just recently been dumped by the hottest girl in high school, is suddenly spending 2 or more hours on the phone around midnight...people begin to wonder.&nbsp; And just the right people, too. &nbsp; Kegan was online.&nbsp; Chelsey Stoddard - one of Heidi's best friends - was online.&nbsp; And Heidi was online.&nbsp; And as soon as I got off the phone and came back to the computer, Kegan and Chelsey immediately IMed me. &nbsp; The conversations didn't go directly to the phone call.&nbsp; But you knew that's what they were getting at.&nbsp; They asked me questions that implied they wanted me to casually mention who I was talking to, without them having to ask me straight up.&nbsp; When they weren't successful, Heidi IMed me.&nbsp; She told me that she did not mean to pry, but wanted to know if it were Katie Bowen on the phone.&nbsp; I told her no.&nbsp; I really don't know why she was asking about Bowen.  Anyways, this post is getting too long.&nbsp; And for the next part, I would rather avoid detail. &nbsp; But Heidi and I fought again.&nbsp; About whether or not she was justified in breaking up with me.&nbsp; I think one thing that I learned from this conversation, is that I am not the only one hurting because of the break up.&nbsp;&nbsp;After much intense debate, Heidi told me that she was done, spent, and could no longer discuss it right now.&nbsp; She told me that she had done nothing but worry about it for days now and that she simply couldn't go on with the conversation.&nbsp; She got offline.&nbsp; And I felt awful. &nbsp; And I think I knew what I had to do.&nbsp; You see, I want to be best friends with Heidi, too, at some point, but I'm just not ready to be there now.&nbsp; And until I get there, I should really avoid Heidi. &nbsp; I don't like that solution, because I don't want to avoid Heidi.&nbsp; I miss hanging out with her already.&nbsp; But, until I can put all this behind me, I won't be able to hang around Heidi without bringing it up.&nbsp; And that's only going to hurt her. &nbsp; And I asked myself, why do I do it?&nbsp; Do I do it because I think I can get us back together?&nbsp; And the answer to that is no.&nbsp; I honestly don't think we'll ever get back together after all of this.&nbsp; And that pisses me off.&nbsp; I want things to be like they were before! &nbsp; But, if I don't do it because I think I can get us back together, why do I do it?&nbsp; Is it because I want to hurt her and make her feel bad?&nbsp; No.&nbsp; Honestly, no, I don't. &nbsp; So, why?!&nbsp; And I was finally able to answer that.&nbsp; It's because I miss her.&nbsp; And I want to talk to her.&nbsp; When I'm not around her, when I'm not talking to her, I only think about her.&nbsp; So, I try to talk to her, and - as I mentioned before - until I can put all this behind me, I won't be able to talk to Heidi without bringing it all up. &nbsp; So, that's the solution.&nbsp; If I want to save even a shred of my relationship with Heidi, I must leave her alone now.&nbsp; She doesn't want that either, she misses me.&nbsp; But I can't just be friends with her yet.&nbsp; And until I can, I'll just have to miss her. &nbsp; When I'm with Heidi, I know&nbsp;I want her.&nbsp;&nbsp;But I think about Tasha.&nbsp; And how I think nothing of Heidi when I'm with Tasha.&nbsp; So, maybe that's the answer.&nbsp; I should hang out with Tasha&nbsp;a lot this summer so that I can get over Heidi.&nbsp; And then I can start hanging out with&nbsp;Heidi again. &nbsp; But then what?&nbsp; Do I just dump Tasha? &nbsp; I really like Tasha.&nbsp; And I don't want just to use her to get over Heidi. &nbsp; All this High School drama is soo stupid.&nbsp; I know that.&nbsp; But, it also seems to be unavoidable. &nbsp; 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yesterday I promised to post the details.&nbsp; So, here goes. &nbsp; Yesterday, my family and I went to visit my older sister (Erin) and brother-in-law (Paul).&nbsp; Paul just recently got a job as principal of a parochial school and they just recently moved into a very nice house owned by the local church.&nbsp; So, we went there yesterday to see it.&nbsp; And them, too, I guess. &nbsp; I was eager to see the house and wanted to go to support my sister, but I really wished that I could just stay home and hang out with Heidi, seeing as how she had been home for two days now and I had yet to see her.&nbsp; I was going to invite Heidi to come with us, but turns out she had to go to a family barbecue or something. &nbsp; Now, as you can tell from two of my previous posts, the Heidi/Seth relationship was sort of on the rocks.&nbsp; But, every relationship has its 'off' days.&nbsp; Saturday was an 'off' day.&nbsp; Sunday, however, turned out to be an 'on' day.&nbsp; By the time I got home, I knew in my heart that all I had to do was to push through these final days of distance and things would be back to normal and fine.&nbsp; I had been reading some of the emails I saved and noticed that all of them sent before the distance showed a seemingly healthy and perfect relationship.&nbsp; This told me that the only problem in our relationship was the distance.&nbsp; And I was soo ready for things to go back to perfect. &nbsp; When I got home, I called Heidi, as promised, but she wasn't home.&nbsp; Instead she was with her friends (the bitches), who&nbsp;have always been against me and were presently convincing her that the distance was  not  our only problem.&nbsp; They were astonished when they heard of our relationship, because they couldn't believe Heidi would "settle" for a guy like me (someone from a sunstantially lower class).&nbsp; Since then, they've always assumed that it wouldn't work out and considered it their duty to convince Heidi that she was off her rocker, thus saving her disappointment and embarrasment.&nbsp; Again...what bitches. &nbsp; So, after the phone call, I watch a Shyamalan movie with my dad, which lasted a couple of hours.&nbsp; I then got on the Internet and found that Heidi had emailed me, saying that I was to call her as soon as I got the email and that there was something we needed to talk about. &nbsp; This meant one of two things.&nbsp; One, she was breaking up with me.&nbsp; Or, two, she had cheated on another guy.&nbsp; I prayed for the latter. &nbsp; And, of course, I was wrong. &nbsp; And I fought with her.&nbsp; She told me that she was completely surprised by this reaction.&nbsp; She was surprised that I was fighting with her.&nbsp; She said I was being mean because I called her a wimp.&nbsp; I wasn't being mean, I was being completely honest about how I felt.&nbsp; I felt that if she was giving in this easily, she was a wimp.&nbsp; Or, she just didn't care.&nbsp; But I told her that I sometimes felt the same feeling of despair.&nbsp; And that we should still try to get this back on track.&nbsp; If, once we start hanging out again, all of our problems go away, then we're golden.&nbsp; If, on the other hand, we find that they don't go away, then her friends were right, the distance was not our only problem, and we could call it quits. &nbsp; But it was obvious.&nbsp; Her mind was made up. &nbsp; If I were to discuss my full range of emotions, this post would take up a month of your time.&nbsp; So, lemme just sum it up into the three main emotions:&nbsp; frustration, disappointment, and sadness. &nbsp; Frustration because I truly believed that the distance was our only problem.&nbsp; That we had been through seven weeks of hell, and now that we were reaching the homestretch (now, of all times!), we give up without even testing to see if the distance was the problem. &nbsp; Disappointment because for the last seven weeks I had been telling myself that if I only hung on and dealt with the period of distance, everything would be back to normal and beautiful.&nbsp; However, I hung on and I dealt with it...and to no avail.&nbsp; It was over. &nbsp; And sadness for that very reason.&nbsp; It was over.&nbsp; Things would never again be as perfect as they were in the first two months.&nbsp; And I already missed her. &nbsp; But, the big shocker, was that I was alright.&nbsp; I knew that I wanted to handle this like a man.&nbsp; I'm usually incredibly emotional, but I really just wanted to get through this break-up as easily as possible and leave it all behind me.&nbsp; After the 30-minute phone conversation, I sat down in my bathroom with my head in my hands and I cried for about five minutes.&nbsp; But then I was done.&nbsp; I came out and didn't cry again. &nbsp; The hardest part of the break-up, I've found, is telling people about it.&nbsp; When I told my mom, she cried.&nbsp; When I told Erin, she gave me a beautiful and touching speech about how high school girls are stupid and Heidi was the one who lost.&nbsp; I like my older sister.&nbsp; When I told my dad, he felt horrible and believed that the reason I was&nbsp;going through this&nbsp;was because he took me on a three week vacation. &nbsp; But that wasn't the reason, Dad.&nbsp; It's Heidi's fault.&nbsp; She gave up. &nbsp; Now, after having 24 hours to think about everything, the number one emotion I am experiencing right now is anger.&nbsp; I'm pissed at Heidi.&nbsp; I feel that if she could so easily and abruptly end our relationship, it never meant much to her to begin with. &nbsp; So, hell with it.&nbsp; What's past is past.&nbsp; I'm moving on. 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Heidi and I broke up today. &nbsp; Surprise, huh? &nbsp; I'm alright, though.&nbsp; I'm disappointed....and frustrated....and sad.&nbsp; But I'm ok.&nbsp; And it's almost as though a burden's been lifted. &nbsp; Details later.&nbsp; I'm too exhausted to talk about it now. 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just talked to Heidi on AIM.&nbsp; She just got back from babysitting.&nbsp; It's 1:38 in the morning.&nbsp; I told her I'd wait up for her so we could have a few minutes to talk before she went to bed.  &nbsp;  I guess I just feel like that's how it typically is with us.&nbsp; I'm the one doing the work.&nbsp; I'm the one making the effort.&nbsp; I'm the one who throws away his entire night, so that he's home if she wants to call him.&nbsp; I'm the one who stays online hours after he would have gone to sleep so that we can talk.&nbsp; She gets online and - without really saying much - talks to me for 15 minutes while she gets ready for bed and then, of course, leaves to go to sleep.&nbsp; It's her second day back and I still haven't seen her.&nbsp; I've barely talked to her.&nbsp; And I won't be able to see her tomorrow, either.  &nbsp;  I think it's right in a relationship for the guy to do most of the hard stuff.&nbsp; The guy needs to make the girl feel special.&nbsp; Let her know that she's important to him and that anytime she needs him, he's there for her.&nbsp; The guy needs to make sacrifices.&nbsp; But I still feel a little unappreciated and a little taken for granted.&nbsp; Holy crap, I sound like a girl.  &nbsp;  Whatever.  &nbsp;  One thing I noticed tonight is that when i talk to her, it's like nothing anymore.&nbsp; I don't feel anything.&nbsp; This distance thing has left me completely drained and exhausted so that now that we are together again, I'm too tired to care.  &nbsp;  Did I mention that she went out to a movie last night with her ex-boyfriend because I wasn't around?  &nbsp;  I do hope that things get better now that we're both home.&nbsp; But as for right now, it's just 'whatever'.  &nbsp;  I'm drained.&nbsp; I'm exhausted.&nbsp; And I'm going to bed.  &nbsp;  Good night.   
     

        
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm tired of it.&nbsp; Maybe I'm just insecure.&nbsp; Maybe I'm just whiny.&nbsp; But I'm sick of it.&nbsp; Am I paranoid when I think that she's done caring?  &nbsp;  But I just want out.&nbsp; I'm tired of expectations falling flat.&nbsp; I'm&nbsp;tired of getting excited over a new plan that&nbsp;will make&nbsp;her really happy only to find out that nothing I do could&nbsp;stir any emotion&nbsp;from her.  &nbsp;  Dating Heidi Uridil has become like dating a brick wall.  &nbsp;  I buy her gifts.&nbsp; Nothing.&nbsp; I&nbsp;compliment her.&nbsp; Nothing.&nbsp; I open up my heart and tell her things I could never tell anyone.&nbsp; Nothing.  &nbsp;  I'm sorry.&nbsp; Excuse me.&nbsp; Being away from my girlfriend for&nbsp;eight weeks was difficult for me.&nbsp; Maybe that makes me a manic depressive, but it's true.&nbsp; Believe it or not, it was actually hard for me.&nbsp; And yet, all the waiting and all the insecurity would be worth it if i got a response from her at the end of the day.&nbsp; If i felt that she appreciated me, or cared for me, or missed me.&nbsp; But I get nothing.&nbsp; Brick wall.&nbsp; And it's not worth it anymore.  &nbsp;  I know what you're thinking:&nbsp; Seth Kaltwasser actually gets a chance to date a girl like Heidi Uridil and he's going to dump her?!&nbsp; And that's just it.&nbsp; That's the worst part.&nbsp; No.&nbsp; He's not going to dump her.&nbsp; Because he's convinced himself that if he's miserable dating Heidi Uridil, he's not in his right mind.&nbsp; And if he is in his right mind, nothing will make him happy.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  For the last eight weeks, I have been trying to convince myself that she cares for me.&nbsp; But today is just too much.  &nbsp;  We simply aren't compatible.&nbsp; We knew that going in, but thought we could make it work.&nbsp; But we simply aren't meant for one another.&nbsp; She's not happy being with me because there are so many other boys - "sports guys", even! - that she could be dating.&nbsp; I'm not happy being with her because being with her is like being with a fucking brick wall.  &nbsp;  I'm a pretty private person, that's why I write my feelings in blogs or journals.&nbsp; And yet I told her things I could never tell anyone else.......and what do I get back?&nbsp; Nothing.&nbsp; Well, I take that back.&nbsp; I get laughed at.&nbsp; Come to think of it, the last thousand times I told her something that meant something to me, she laughed at me.&nbsp; Great.&nbsp;&nbsp;Perfect.  &nbsp;  Consolation?&nbsp; Not important.  Encouragement?&nbsp; Unnecessary.  A good laugh in the face?&nbsp; Ah, now there's the ticket.&nbsp; That'll make me feel better.  &nbsp;  Right, Heidi.&nbsp; Right.  &nbsp;  So, it's Saturday.&nbsp; I haven't seen the girl in a month.&nbsp; I haven't talked to her for a week.&nbsp; I wake up soooo ready for her first day back.&nbsp; I've even bought a dozen roses for her.&nbsp; But then what?&nbsp; I sit around the house for hours waiting for a call.&nbsp; Finally I get something.&nbsp; Not a call, though.&nbsp; No, that would be too personal.&nbsp; I get an email.&nbsp; Turns out she actually got home Friday afternoon.&nbsp; (And the first I hear from her is 3:30 p.m. Saturday.)&nbsp; And she's babysitting tonight.  &nbsp;  Later, she gets on IM.&nbsp; I decide that it's cool that she has to babysit, but I still miss her and wanna see her again.&nbsp; So, I tell her that.&nbsp; I tell her that I'm sick of phone calls and emails.&nbsp; I wanna see her.&nbsp; I ask if I can come over, even if for only five minutes, because I miss her.&nbsp; I'm 100% willing to drive 20 miles there and 20 miles back, so that I can see her for five stinking minutes.&nbsp; Silly, Seth.&nbsp; He thinks this is romantic.&nbsp; He thinks she'll like this.&nbsp; Instead, no, Heidi's tired.&nbsp; She's not really interested.  &nbsp;   We haven't seen each other for four fucking months and when we finally get the oppurtunity to meet up, she decides she'd rather sleep.     &nbsp;  Honestly, is this a relationship?  &nbsp;  And now what?&nbsp; Well, I could go to the baseball game and hang out with my friends - people that actually care about me - but instead I opt to stay home and complain in this stupid blog because there's a chance Heidi might call me tonight.&nbsp; Why the hell do I put so much effort into this?!?!  &nbsp;  You know, the problem isn't that she had to babysit tonight.&nbsp; The problem isn't that she's too exhausted from her week in Chicago to spend five minutes with me.&nbsp; The problem isn't even that she didn't contact me to tell me she was home until 24 hours after she arrived.  &nbsp;  No, the problem is just that she's the #1 priority in my life.&nbsp; And I wish that I was a top priority in her's.&nbsp; Hell, I'd even settle for the top ten.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  So, I go up to my room.&nbsp; And I sit.&nbsp; And I mope.&nbsp; And I blast the "RENT" soundtrack from my CD player.&nbsp; That's when I think of Tasha - have we talked about Tasha yet?&nbsp; My ex-girlfriend.&nbsp; On my desk, I see where i scribbled a note of her cell phone number.  &nbsp;  Tasha knows me better than almost anyone else.&nbsp; Tasha cares for me.&nbsp; I care for Tasha.&nbsp; I consider her one of my best friends.  &nbsp;  But she's my ex-girlfriend.&nbsp; And I know I shouldn't call her.&nbsp; But maybe I don't care.   
     

        
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Usually when I sit down at this computer to publish a post, there's something weighing heavily on my mind. Something that I need to write about. Or, at least something worth writing about. I'm not sure that's the case tonight. But I feel like posting. We'll see what comes out...  Three weeks from yesterday school starts. I was reminded of that last night by the cheerful and always hilarious Ashley Schmuecker. And I'm dreading it.  I don't have a job. I don't have plans every night. Actually, I spend at least 3 nights a week sitting at my computer. One would assume that I would be ready for some excitement in my life, but I'm not. I've embraced this sloth, I guess.  But, you know, there's more to it than that.  When I think back to three weeks ago, I realize that at the time I couldn't wait for school to start. But, of course, that shouldn't come as much of a prize. Why? Because my life then was 180 degrees opposite of what it is now. That's true. I remember when Heidi and I were together, it was hard for me to remember what it was like to be single. And, now that Heidi and I are separated, I can't imagine what it was like to have someone.  Three weeks ago, every other thought was about Heidi. Three weeks ago, I was not an individual, but part of a team. Three weeks ago, I even hung out with a different group of people than I do now. Three weeks ago, it seemed that everything in my life was as it should be, I had a place in this world, and a reason for living. Now, that's all different.  I'm wondering around aimlessly. I'm not sure who I am, who I want to be, or where I'm going. As of right now, I'm alive...and that's all I really know. It's not a bad existence, just kind of lonely.  I've adapted to it. Although, I spend maybe every other night with Brecht and McCormack, I spend my days alone. I don't ever talk to anyone anymore. And, I rarely see anybody other than the two I just mentioned. I've been invited to some parties and such, but if ever there's even a chance that Heidi could be there, I decline.  I haven't seen Heidi since before I left for vacation, which means it's going on two months. When I got back from vacation, she was so ready to cut me loose that she couldn't even wait to tell me in person. It was all done over the phone.  And I think that's one reason I don't want to go back to school.  I haven't seen Heidi for like 7 weeks, but sometime in the next 3, I will. If I don't see her at Registration, if I don't see her at Open House, if I don't see her at a friend's house or in town, I will see her when school starts. And I'm not ready for that.  I think going through a break up in the summer is a bad idea. If your girlfriend breaks up with you during school, you see her everyday. Although this might make it harder for you to get over her, at least you'll only have to do it once.  In my case, however, I may have to do it twice.  I have more or less gotten over Heidi in the last three weeks. I don't think about her as much. It's still painful when I allow myself to think of her, but I very rarely do. I can control it now. And that's good. I haven't completely forgotten everything, but I have forgiven and I have adapted to my new life. However, when school starts, and I see her every day again (I know I have at least two classes with her), I think it's going to hit me hard.  Because, the first time I got over her, it wasn't done right. The reality I adapted to was one where I never saw her. Now, if it was a year from now, and I was going for college, this would be no big deal. But it isn't a year from now. And in three weeks I will again have to adapt to a new reality. This time it's a reality where I see her everyday. And this reality will be much harder to adjust to than the first.  I hate this. I wish I was going to college. I wish last year was my senior year. Why? Because I don't want my senior year to be like this. I don't want to spend it getting over a girl. I don't want it to be that stupid and immature and painful. I just want it to be fun. And, hopefully, it will be, sooner or later. But probably later.  I won't lie. I think I'm being childish and immature about the whole situation. I will admit that. Not going to parties because Heidi might be there is childish. Wanting to make Heidi feel bad even though I know she did everything with the best of intentions and never wanted to hurt me is immature. But I really don't care. If being childish and immature is the only way I can get over her, so be it. I really don't care what the method is, as long as I can forget. Maybe that's the most immature thing of all.  So, who knows what the future holds? I sure don't.  What will senior year be like? Will Heidi and I get into large arguments and end up hating each other? Will we end up talking things over and become best of friends? Will it never even become an issue? I really don't know. And I really don't care. Just as long as I can get over her, I don't care if I'm her friend, or enemy, or just some forgotten piece of history.  What I do know is that in the last three weeks, I have become detached. Detached from people that I would normally speak to every day and detached from issues that are more of a factor in my life than I care to admit. However, when school starts, I can no longer live in my little bubble. I can't remain isolated from the world. I have to go out and make the most of everyday. I have to see people again that I don't want to see. I have to deal with things that I don't want to deal with. I have to put myself out there. And that's why I don't want school to start. The last time I ever really "put myself out there" was when I was with Heidi. When I dedicated everything to her and let her see exactly who I was. And it ended up getting shoved right back into my face.  It's easy living in this bubble. But it can hardly be considered 'living'.  So, what does the next month have in store for me? I don't know. But I pray things work out for the better. And I pray that I can learn to be every bit as happy without her, as I was with her. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ok, so I realize I haven't posted in over a week. And I apologize.  But, to me, this blog is an outlet. I use it to vent whatever I'm feeling at the moment. Therefore, I need to feel  something  in order for the inspiration to write to kick in. And I'm not feeling anything. I'm not mad about anything, I'm not sad about anything. Nothing's excited me. Nothing's confused me. Nothing. I'm just numb. The lack of things happening in my life has caused an emotional drought. I'm numb. Things aren't bad, but they're not particularly great, either. I feel like I'm just sitting still as life passes me by.  Heidi's tried talking to me a couple of times on AIM. I say "tried" because I refuse to be much of a conversationalist. It's not that I'm still mad, but I just don't want talking with Heidi to become the norm. I feel like the best way to get over her is just to make a clean break. Don't talk to her. Don't talk about her. Don't think about her. Don't reminisce. Before, when I was so used to talking with her, I missed her a lot. Now that I rarely talk to her, I don't miss her (as much) when I'm not. So, when she's talked to me, I do my best to be polite. And I do my best to silence my emotions. But I don't really try to improve the conversation. Very rarely do my replies consist of more than two words. It's not that I'm still mad. I just don't want to talk to her if it means risking all the progress I've made.  I have, however, started talking to this guy I met over the Internet. I know, that's dangerous. But I'm 99% sure this guy's no pedophile, murderer, or kidnapper. He's my age, lives in California, and likes a lot of the same stuff that I do. He's a really cool guy. And we're similar in so many ways I cannot even begin to list them. On the other hand, we're also very different. He lives in Beverly Hills. His family's loaded. He has a 4.6 GPA and plans to go to Stanford or Princeton. I, on the other hand, am just some middle-class kid from rural Iowa attending a high school whose entire student body is smaller than his graduating class. And because we are from completely opposite worlds, we sometimes struggle with conversation. But it's worth the struggle. Like I said, he's a really cool guy. And I don't mind staying up past midnight to talk to him.  But, that's about all the news from here. So, for my readers' sake as well as my own, I hope things get exciting soon. And they will. I know they will.  I know this because school starts in just a few weeks. And, when it does, I'll have to struggle to even find time to blog.  Junior year seemed to fly by.  But Senior year's gonna be over in a flash. Guess I better buckle my seat belt.  Maybe I should be enjoying my last few weeks of serenity instead of moaning about them.
     

        
</post>


</Blog>