<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Arrested Development   Every afternoon, around 5 pm or so,I find myself sitting atop the Daily Planet Globe watching mothers bustle home carrying paper bags and harried businessmen beat each other silly over a cab like a scene straight out of a Laurel and Hardy skit. sometimes, I bring a thermos of hot cocoa or some romance novel I’d picked up on impulse while waiting in line to pay for a box of Gentle Glide tampons. sometimes, I don’t bring anything but my thoughts. and believe me, they’re more than enough.  like the general stuff that the coffee shop crowd gab about on Saturday nights—You know, like the why-am-I-here musings and the I-should-be-doing-more litanies over a cup of some frothy caffeine concoction— just the usual things that hit you when you’re twenty-something and alone and you begin to question why you exist in the first place. I mean, when I really think about it, I’m almost useless because this is his town and sometimes I feel like a little kid who bugs her big brother while he’s doing his chores, so he assigns me some stupid task that’ll make me feel important when all he really wants is to get me out of his absolutely fabulous hair.  oh, yeah, that’s the thing, you know. I’m not his little sister. I’m not his cousin and I’m not a feminine version of him who had fled from an alternate universe and I’m certainly not some DNA replicant spliced from him and Wonder Woman. what’s wrong with “I just got tired of living on a moon just right next to where Krypton used to be, got in a spaceship, and zoomed for Earth”? well, okay, I guess that’s kind of boring, but that’s really how it was.  right around a quarter to six, of course, I snap out of my brood fest and duck behind the PLA to watch him walk out with her—she of the skinny legs and bouncy-bouncy hair—and with unerring accuracy, my blood boils on cue and I fume like the teapot who couldn’t shout “It’s me you should love, not her!” Don’t get me wrong. I’m not in love with him. but it’d be easier for the both of us if I were and he was.  it’s a shame, really, that crime doesn’t pick up till you’re sitting in the dark with a bowl of ice cream, all set and ready for MUST-SEE TV. it would keep me away from the Daily Planet, at least.  Christ, I need a hobby.   Ok... I had a shitty day at work today. Then again, work is always shitty. It's not that I hate my job, but... Ah, yes, I DO HATE MY JOB. The boss sucks. The clients suck. Worst of all, I don't even have a sound card on my computer. What kind of shit is that?  Anyway, I should really start on those two online final exams that I still have to take, but can't get myself to do it (I mean, today IS the last day to take the tests). I should totally go do that right now... Okay... right now...  The wedding is tomorrow.  le sigh . My dress still doesn't fit and I even skipped dinner last night.  By the way, the poem up there is mine. It may not be Nobel Laureat material, but I do not want to open a book of crappy poetry collection one day and find my poem printed there without credit to me. I would be extremely angry if that happened. I would not hesitate to sue your ass off, burn your house down, and skin your family alive. Stealing is bad.  That is all. Thank you. 
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ha ha, so I tricked my  urlLink long-suffering boyfriend  into taking my stats finals for me (I signed up for 3 online classes this year in my continuing quest to get a frickin' education). He's a sweetie, that one, and I'm an asshole for even thinking of asking him to do it, but I'm HORRIBLE with numbers. Can't even look at a row of them without hyperventilating. So HAH! There goes the stereotype of Asians being good at Math (I am, however, good at  urlLink tsismis  which is  urlLink Tagalog  for "gossip").  Anyway, I still have to do my Economics and Computer Information finals. I'm not sweating it, though. I started practicing  urlLink Hatha Yoga  this week and have been working on my breathing. I've been prone to hyperventilating whenever I get freaked out since I was a little kid (and sometimes break into hives), so I figured it's about time that I did something about that whole holy-shit-someone-hand-me-a-paperbag bit. I mean, it always scares the people around me when I do it and on one occasion, a woman even suggested that someone do CPR on me (mind you, I was breathing at the time).  So my cousin  Maja  is arriving from Washington D.C. tomorrow. My mother is picking her up from the airport. She's going to be staying with me and my boyfriend for the weekend. She's a nice girl... my mother loves her. I'd rather that it was her who stayed with us and not the cousin I have who is married with two kids (two very LOUD kids). I don't mind kids most of the time, but after prolonged exposure to them, I start to get itchy and this vein under my left eye goes spastic.  My mother and her  boyfriend  (that sounds wrong.  "boyfriend" . They're both almost in their fifties) are finally getting married this weekend after years of should-we-or-shouldn't-we. They were like  urlLink David and Maddie  . But yeah, I get to wear this lovely off-the-shoulder dress which is a size too small. I told my mother I needed a larger size but all she said was, "Lose weight, then. I refuse to acknowledge your flab." I'm not fat, by the way... it's just 5-8 lbs. of flesh I've yet to tone. I'm working on it, though... But hah! The wedding's in two days.  It's  Tim 's birthday on Sunday. I haven't gotten him a present because I don't have any money. I actually have no plans whatsoever for it. I'm a horrible girlfriend. I also haven't bought a wedding gift for my folks (but maybe I can just pick 'em up something when we go to the  urlLink Philippines  in 2 weeks). Monetary issues aside, however, I really don't have a frickin' clue what to get them. Besides, my mom would probably just say, "Ay,  naku , it's too much. Take it back" when I give it to her. Maybe my sisters bought them something really nice and I can just add my name to the card...   As for Tim, I can just be  really, really nice  to him that day.
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Even to this day, the very idea of meeting someone on the Internet is met with skepticism at best, but usually mockery. As everyone  knows , the Internet is where losers and psychopaths meet. It's definitely not a socially respectable place to find love. A church social, your school library, a friend's get-together, a set-up by a friend... these are the "acceptable" ways to meet a mate... but the Internet? What kind of loser pimps himself out to hundreds and thousands of strangers through his computer?  But is that really the case? Just how desperate do you have to be to turn to the Internet?  Consider the young singles of today's world; hard working and hard partying young adults mingling out in the world.  Cool and hip, drinking and laughing; where do they go for love?  Clubs, bars, and parties, of course - a wild mixing of alcohol and music to help loosen inhibitions and meet new "friends".  But what if you're awkward, socially inept, and your only connection to the world is through the Internet? What if even the very thought of going to a bar filled with  actual  people turns your bowels into ice and your knees shaking like James Bond shakes his martinis?  Are these two worlds, in fact, mutually exclusive? I mean, you can meet someone online and invite that person out for a drink or something outside the Internet, can't you? You can also meet someone in a bar, want to stay in contact with that person, so what's the harm in exchanging email addresses?  The reality is that the Internet is simply a means of communication, better enabling and empowering people to stay in touch.  It is a tool like any other, and it is not any more sad or desperate than going to a bar to find love.  Desperation is a feeling that you have to find love in order to satisfy your own sense of self worth. You can't avoid desperation by staying away from the Internet. It's in the air you breathe! Bars are full of desperate people who avoid the Internet, just as the Internet is full of desperate people scared of bars.  Meeting someone on the Internet is the same as meeting them in a bar.   Think about it.  Sure, there's that sense of anonymity, but isn't that what makes you pick up a guy in the first place? It's exciting because you know nothing about him, yet you want him to go home with you. It's kind of like that on the Internet. Let's say that you enter a chatroom and encounter a witty, funny individual who just strikes a chord deep within you, and instantly, you know you want to get to know that person. Even though you don't even know what this person looks like, you're instantly attracted to him (the reverse is true for bars). You trade some IMs, agree to meet for coffee, and then when you finally see this paragon of virtue, you think to yourself, "Holy crap, it's the Creature from the Black Lagoon," when you were actually expecting the Creature of the  urlLink Blue Lagoon .  Bars, on the other hand, are dimly lit. When you're in a bar, you drink a lot. You dress in  way that's deceptive in comparison to  how you normally dress. You even find yourself lying when you flirt, poised to keep them interested.  Worst of all, you're spending money that would be better spent on clothes or even video games!  In all, it's a painful experience unless you're drinking with friends or singing karaoke! But let's just say that you meet that special someone... you're a little drunk... a little giddy, so you go home with him. The next day, you make up next to a guy who looks more like Clint Howard than Billy Crudup, and to top it all off, he's a complete tool!  But let's break it down a bit. Whether you meet someone in a bar or online, the following ALL apply: - You don't know whether the person you just met is a boy or a girl - You're not sure how old they REALLY are - You're not sure if they're as attractive as you think they are - You don't know whether or not they're actually married - They could be lying about their job or education - They don't know where you live unless you tell them  So don't sweat it, go find love in bars, Internet sites, coffee-shops, bookstores, whatever!  Face it, you're desperate! Looking for love in a bar is already sad, so you might as well extend this to the Internet as well. Why should you limit your desperation to one medium?  You'll be pleasantly surprised to find that there are millions and millions of other sad people dying to meet you! I mean, a bar only offers a few good looking people at a time, so quit wasting time that could be better spent fornicating and go sign up for the  urlLink Onion Personals !    (Editor's note: By the way, the author and I met at a bookstore. And also, we don't fornicate. We are waiting till after the wedding. We sleep in separate rooms. Seriously.)  
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I've been working on my manuscript for about six months now and haven't always been consistent on my production schedule, but have worked enough to have reached chapter six. I'd write a few pages here and there whenever the mood struck me, but lately, not so much. I thought starting this blog would help to get the juices flowin', but so far... well, let's just say I'm stalled.  This always happens, you see. I'd start on a story idea and even with an outline, I just stop a quarter of the way through, and don't start up again unless it's a new story. I can't seem to finish ONE story. It's very annoying and I've tried everything to fix it. I've read self-help books and once, even got a girl at a party to hypnotize me to become more focused about my writing. The result? Well, let's just say that she was a little drunk at the time and must have messed up some of her suggestions. All I know was that one moment, she was saying, "You are getting very sleepy," and the next thing I knew, it was two days later. I thought I'd pull a  urlLink Peter Gibbons  and become extremely carefree, but that didn't happen, either. I think I'm more neurotic than ever.  Maybe this trip to the Philippines will help. I'll bring a notebook, slip into a hammock, and jot a couple of things down... the rainy season should help. I heard rain's good for inspiring would-be authors to write.   If not, there's always whiskey.
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently saw a movie called  urlLink Dragon Fighter  on the  urlLink Sci-Fi  Channel. It was about a bunch of scientists working in an underground lab somewhere on a remote island who manage to clone a dragon. The dragon, of course, escapes and they were almost  quite literally  toast when a courageous, break-all-the-rules helicopter pilot steps in, and saves a whole bunch of them. It was awful. The storyline was ludicrous, the dialogue was painful to listen to, and the actors were C-list at best. Heading the cast was your stereotypical action hero: brash, quick-witted, and handsome with a devil-may-care smile and the appropriate wind-blown hair. The actor who took the role has done it before in a dozen other movies that are just as low-budget and predictably atrocious. He has since played: a  urlLink military specialist  considered by his peers to be a  loose cannon  (aren't they all?), but honorable, and brave, a  urlLink thief  who's out to steal corporate secrets only to answer a true hero's call when the building catches fire and there are people trapped on the top floor, an  urlLink ex cop  with revenge in his heart and an Uzi in his hands, a charming  urlLink police detective  who has ensnared the hearts of all the women in his department, a  urlLink park ranger , a conflicted  urlLink bank robber , and a beleaguered  urlLink athlete  who's had enough of the way he and his team mates are treated, so he leads a revolt. The man has 45 films and TV shows on his resume, and he has played the hero in about 90% of them!  Well, okay... except that movie where he played  urlLink Scott Peterson . What was he thinking? Of course, he looked eerily like the real  urlLink Scott Peterson , so really, they couldn't have picked a better actor to play him... but...  urlLink Superman ? That just seems wrong. The man who brutally... oops... allegedly  urlLink murdered  his beautiful wife and unborn son is played by the same man who once donned the briefs & cape of The Last Son of Krypton?  Who am I talking about? Why,  urlLink Dean Cain , of course. From 1993 to 1997, he played Clark Kent on ABC's  urlLink Lois and Clark: The New Adventures of Superman , but before that, we knew him as Rick,  urlLink Brenda's  Paris fling and the man who stole her from  urlLink Dylan McKay . Seriously, what happened to him? He had what seemed like a good career path before him back then. He could have been as big as  urlLink George Clooney , but instead he's more like  urlLink  Julianna Margulies . I mean, at least  urlLink David Caruso  has his own hit  urlLink TV show . It's not like he's ugly like Caruso... he's got the dark, brooding good-looks befitting of an A-list action star, plus he's got some acting  urlLink skills , unlike some  urlLink no talent ass clown  who's still getting work ( mainstream  work, at that). Come on... don't tell me he's no better than  urlLink Richard Grieco  or  urlLink John Stamos . I mean, at least he's still working, unlike his former  urlLink costar  who was recently seen peddling batteries for Radio Shack.     Oh, Dean Cain, we hardly knew ye. Maybe you can salvage your career by playing a bad guy on the new  urlLink Superman  movie, if it ever comes out. After all, it's going directed by that  urlLink assnugget  who helmed the  urlLink train-wreck  that brought us back  urlLink Demi Moore  (who really should go back to whatever cryogenic chamber in Idaho from where she crawled out). I mean, how much worse could it be if you added your pleasant countenance to the cast? Or you could always stay away from those horrid Sci-Fi TV movies for a while and wait patiently till  urlLink Quentin Tarantino  resurrects your career.  By the way, there is a  urlLink TV show  on the WB right now about man who is sent from a crumbling planet so he could survive on  this  planet and eventually becomes our unlikely savior. If the  urlLink star  of that show doesn't get a better agent, he might find himself looking at a mirror one day and saying to himself, "Dear God, I've turned into Dean Cain". Tom Welling? I'm looking at you.
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Editor's Note: If the topic of female plumbing makes you feel uncomfortable, you should turn away now. Seriously. This is your last and only warning.   What the doctor said: "We found some abnormal cells on your cervix." What I heard: "You've got cancer and baby, you gonna die." She didn't have to say the C-word. In my mind, I was already picking out the wig I was going to wear when my hair fell out due to chemo. In my mind, I was already bracing myself for the moment the doctor would say, "The drugs just aren't working and there isn't anything else we can do. I'm sorry." In my mind, I was already yelling at the sky, shaking my fists, and yelling, "What did I ever do to You? Why can't I stay? Why are You taking me away?" When the doctor said "abnormal," the word itself began to bounce against my eardrums like a ball to a wall, and for a half a minute, my breath was trapped within my chest. The vein under my left eye began to throb and I could feel my heart pounding in my throat.  Abnormal.    It had been a routine  urlLink pap , the same one my mother has forced me to get since I was 16. It had always come back normal. For the past seven years, the doctor has done the same thing: wrote me a prescription for birth control pills, said a few words about sexually transmitted diseases, patted me on the head, and sent me on my merry way. Normal. You see, that's me... Normal. Mundane. Average. Ordinary. Now's not the time to get special. I could totally deal with boring. I could totally deal with being that girl who always escapes notice because she's as common as they come. I like being nondescript. Now's not the time to get special.  I'm only 25 years old.  I'm not ready to die. Tim hasn't even taken me to  urlLink England  to meet his best friend  urlLink Chris . And he had promised to take me. We're supposed to go next year.  I don't want to die.   I had a  urlLink colposcopy  last week. Doesn't the word itself drag a finger of dread down your spine? Colposcopy. It's actually as awful as it sounds. First, you put your legs up in stirrups, then the doctor slides in the speculum, and pours a vinegar solution on the  area of concern . With the help of a microscope, she studies the colors. If the cells stay pink, you're in the clear. If they turn white, however, well... it's not a good thing. She then takes a little gadget that looks like a tiny steel brush and scrapes at your cervical walls. Afterwards, she sends the tissue to the lab and in about a week, you'll have your results. Today, I received my results. The doctor says that the cells indicate a very high risk for the C-word. What we need to do next, she adds, is a little procedure called a   urlLink cone biopsy  . I read up about it at lunch today and lost my appetite then, so I'm not going to explain it here now. If you want to know more about it, you can follow the link.   By the way, both my mother and Tim promised to go with me and hold my hand during the procedure. It would be a little weird having my mom on one side and my boyfriend on the other, but I need all the moral support I can get. I know I'm just being a drama queen, but how would you like it if you went for a routine checkup and your doctor found a lump in your boob or told you that your balls hang funny? You'd freak out, right? So I think I should be entitled to some major wiggins. I usually bust out humor as a defense mechanism right about now, but you know what?  I'm too scared to be funny!   But yeah, time to change the subject before I start throwing up again. Let's now continue the saga of  urlLink my sister and her boyfriend . Last night, lil sis got to talkin' and spilled the beans on what happens when ZH gets a little drunk. Apparently, the poor boy can't handle his liquor, so after consuming a half bottle of tequila the other night, he went berserker on her. He began to throw around glasses and plates, and even managed to smash the cute little salt & pepper shakers that he gave her last Christmas. He began to yell  urlLink obscenities  and called her names. He told her it was all her fault that he was all messed up and that if he stayed with her any longer, he would go crazy and end up strangling her. He even managed to throw in a punch. It took the strength of my 250 lbs, 6'5 Dad to restrain him, while my other little sister sat on his legs so he would stop kicking around. The boy threw up until about 3 am in the morning, while my Dad glared at him and my sister vowed revenge. She told him as he began to fall asleep on the toilet that he was going to pay for the bruise on her arm and that she was going to make his life a living hell for the whole summer. All's well that ends well, then. Ain't love grand?  Also, my mom found a baby rat on the street. She thought it was cute and had wanted to put it in a little box with some cotton balls 'cause it looked "cold". She was about to get what she needed for a make-shift nest when the phone rang, which ultimately distracted her from the mission at hand. She talked to my aunt for a while, then hung up because she remembered that she had to go to the store for milk. She got into her car, reversed on the driveway, and heard a distinctive  pop . She immediately got out of the car and peeked at the tires to see what she had hit. If you think she squished the baby rat she had been about to rescue, give yourself a point.  Good one, Mom!  Thankfully, the little bugger died instantly, so my mom didn't have to watch it struggle to shed its mortal coil. Unfortunately, my 2 year old  urlLink niece  saw the whole thing and I think she's traumatized for life. We're talking industrial-strength therapy.  By the way, I'm leaving for the  urlLink Old Country  with Tim and my family on Monday and won't be back till the 21st. I probably won't be able to update my blog daily since my grandfather has a shitty internet connection. When I come back, I promise I'll have many stories to tell and the pictures to prove it.  And that's all I got.
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Editor's Note: This author would like her readers to know that she does not mean to offend her friend Maria or her judgment. Maria, in fact, is well-loved by this author and her partner in crime, Tim. The editor would also like you to know that when he's editing this author's work, he doesn't do a very good job because he's sleeping with her.    urlLink Maria , we REALLY have to watch  urlLink The West Side Story  the next time you come over.   Maria . . . The most beautiful sound I ever heard: Maria, Maria, Maria, Maria . . . All the beautiful sounds of the world in a single word . . Maria, Maria, Maria, Maria . . . Maria! I've just met a girl named Maria, And suddenly that name Will never be the same To me.   So last night, for Tim's birthday, we all went to a sushi place in  urlLink Pacific Beach . The food, as always, was excellent, though the service was kind of shitty (honestly, how many times can you ask for water and STILL be ignored?) The calamari salad with spinach was to die-for!   Okay, first thing's first... Tyler, you big dork! You're not supposed to put chopsticks in your hair! Honestly, we can't take you anywhere.  On with the show!   We had a blast. Aubz and Andy were there and we haven't seen those two in a while. Looking good, Aubz! We've been planning a home-cooked meal for all y'all for months now. Is it ever going to happen? :) Kamal! K-dawg! The Special K! Always good to see ya! Maria... Maria... Maria... I just met a girl named Maria... and that creepy guy who followed you to dinner.    Alright, I don't know the dude from Adam or Mike or whoever, but all I can say is... I don't like him. Have you ever met someone who's never been intentionally mean to you, but for some reason, that person just makes your skin crawl? Yeah, well, it's this guy. For anonymity's sake, let's call him Creepnasty. We met Creepnasty at a party and he had approached me in the kitchen as I was making a snack plate for Tim. He asked me if I were enrolled in the same program as some of the other girls at the party (these nasty, skanky stripper girls... I have nothing against strippers... but those girls should really only be taking off their clothes in the privacy of their own homes... preferably in a locked bathroom) and I knew he was just making conversation, but there was something about him that just totally struck me as... well, creepy (plus he was short, bald, greasy, and I think he was even wearing a gold chain around his neck). He was giving off these scary stalker vibes and seemed like the type to call you fifty times a day even though you had already told him you weren't interested. He actually looked a bit like a  urlLink date-rapist . I stammered a lame  see-ya-wouldn't-wanna-be-ya  to get away from him and made a bee-line for where Tim was sitting with Aubrey. I told them about Creepnasty in the kitchen and we all had a good laugh. Little did we know that the little turd had also been hitting on the lovely Maria.  I was sitting with Tim and Aubrey when Maria came up to us and asked Tim to pretend to be her boyfriend because she thought Creepnasty had designs on her delectable self. Maria introduced Tim to Creepnasty, hoping that the slimeball would think Tim was her man, but Creepnasty completely ignored him. He gave him a little look that said, "why you gotta be cock-blockin', man?", then proceeded to talk to Maria as though Tim weren't even standing there (my guy is a little hard to ignore, by the way. He's 6'3, while Maria is 5'10 and Creepnasty is... like... I don't know... 5'4, 4'11... who really cares). He began to spout some bullshit about Ralph Nader--who Maria thinks is a Libertarian, but Tim says he's not--which already means Creepnasty is an idiot... wait, who cares... he's a tool. I mean, we tell people all the time that we voted for Nader in 2000, but really, it's all in good fun. Did people actually,  sincerely  vote for Nader? I mean, really? I mean, not just 'cause it's funny or something? 'Cause Creepnasty says he did. For real. NO joke. Seriously. Shut up, stop looking at me like that. I'm not lying. Shut up. NO, you shut up. Anyway, for some reason that I still cannot understand, the lovely Maria STILL gave him her phone number, telling us that she thought he was funny. Sure, funny  urlLink like a little Asian child with a blank expression on his face sitting outside on a mechanical helicopter that shakes when you put quarters in it . Funny like the mental retardation that  urlLink Cartman  faked, so he could join the Special Olympics. The unlikely pair went to dinner a week later, but by then, Maria's odd fascination with him had already faded, and she began to dodge him. In fact, Maria had already MOVED on to this adorably shy young man that we thought would be perfect for her.  Which was WHY I'm totally at a loss as to why she brought Creepnasty with her to dinner last night. The guy doesn't like Tim, first of all--he always glares at my poor boyfriend when he thinks Maria isn't looking--and while we were eating, he made it a point to ignore the rest of us and just focused on Maria (which wasn't too horrible in itself, but he put his beefy arm around her shoulder that just about screamed "this is my girl, so you fuckers just back off"). And then he smirked--SMIRKED--at me when I spilled my Miso soup on my lap. Sure, the bowl of soup actually slipped out of my hands, spilled all over my pants so it looked like I pissed myself... and sure, I screamed like a girl 'cause that shit was hot... and fine, the entire restaurant thought I was a complete moron and began to point and laugh at me, but that FUCKER did NOT have to SMIRK AT ME! And then Maria paid for his dinner! Tim thinks the guy just gave her cash later and I think the world of Maria, so I refuse to believe that she actually paid for his meal. Afterwards, we all headed for the bar, where everybody--Kamal was first in line--proceeded to buy Tim drinks. Except Creepnasty, of course, 'cause he sucks.  When we finally cornered Maria later on that night, we asked her what the hell she was thinking and she just shrugged with a sheepish smile on her face and said, "Oh, I know. But what was I supposed to say?". She added that she'll tell us all about it soon. I'm assuming that when Creepnasty called and asked where she was going, she told him she was going to a dinner party for Tim and the slimeball had invited himself. Maria, SWEETIE, it's okay to say no. It's okay to say, "Listen, fucker, you're creepy and my friends hate you. Get away from me." If that doesn't work, you could always get a restraining order on him. I mean, otherwise, the next time you see him, he might slip something into your drink, which would make your legs get numb, then you'll pass out, and when you wake up, you'll find yourself inside a box with  urlLink NO LEGS OR ARMS !   Anyway, Tim and I said our goodbyes and headed for home. Utterly exhausted from the  urlLink wedding and my relatives , we watched a little TV, then fell asleep on the couch. With the exception of Creepnasty, we had a good day. A really good day. Ask Tim.  Heh.  We slept in till noon, visited my folks for a birthday barbecue, then met our friends later on for an excellent Japanese meal. Aubrey had even brought a delicious-looking chocolate vanilla cake which everyone just enjoyed with gusto. Thanks,  urlLink Aubrey ! You're the best!  I still haven't brought Tim a present, but I will one of these days. I swear it. No, really. No joke. Shut up, I haven't spent all my money on Ebay. Shut up,  urlLink Kaye !   Oh, and by the way, it's always a pleasure seeing you: Maria, Aubrey, Andy, Kamal, Lisa, Tom, Joe, and Cheng Fay (I'm sorry if I horribly misspelled your name)! Let's get together again soon!   
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm tired, I have a headache, and just found out that my teammates for the final group project for my Stats class gave me a bad feedback. What bitches. They said I helped out, but only with "minimal contribution". Dicks. Okay, I guess I could have done more, but... fine, I have no excuse. I'm still getting an A in the class, though.   On to happier things!  The wedding went unbelievably well. My mother looked beautiful in her dress, while I barely managed to fit into my own dress. At least it fit, though, so that was a relief. The ceremony was beautiful and I found myself getting  verr-klempt  on a few occasions. The funny part was when my little cousin barfed all over the front pew just as my step-dad was saying "I do." It wasn't because he was grossly jaded about love anything at such a frighteningly young age, but because he was sick. The poor little guy. Good thing I didn't slip on his vomit on my way back down the aisle.  The reception was also quite nice. The food was excellent. Tim and I danced and danced, even though the STUPID DJ wouldn't play any of the songs I had requested. Stupid idiot. He was this arrogant little prick named  Preston  who had a  superstar  complex, but looked freakishly like Barney, the empathy demon from the 2nd season of  urlLink Angel . When I asked if he could play my mother's favorite song "Just to be Close to You" by the Commodores, he just looked at me with his slimy-ass attitude and said, "Who is your mother?" I had to restrain myself from beating him over the head with my shoe and settled with replying haughtily, "She's the bride and the one who's going to be signing your paycheck." What a tool! He was probably just bitter because he ended up doing weddings and bar mitzvahs when all he's ever wanted to do was become the underground rave scene's answer to  Madonna . Reptilian prick.  My sister also managed to get into a fight with her boyfriend of a few years. He had wanted to hang out with "the boys" after the reception, but my sweet, sweet sister wouldn't let him... WOULDN'T  LET  HIM. That's right, it's a bizaarro world just like the 19th century, only it's the women who have the men on a tight leash. If you knew my sister's boyfriend, you'd be pissed off, too. He is the nicest, sweetest boy in the world and treats my sister as though she is the Queen of the Nile or something, but dear sis treats him like... well,  dog poop . My sister can be a bit of an  asshole . Imagine crying to your mother on  her  wedding day and expecting her to pay attention only to your pain when she's got tons of guests to attend to. My sister, the misery vampire.  Anyway,  urlLink remember  how I didn't get a present for Tim at all because I have very little money? Well, I should at least have gotten him a card or something. God, I can be such an  urlLink asshole  sometimes. Maybe I could have made him an arts & crafts card or washed his car. I could have done something, no matter how small... anything's better than nothing. I am the  urlLink worst girlfriend  ever. I'm taking him out to sushi tonight, but I know that's not enough. I have to do something special for him.  Maybe I can strip down to my skivvies and shake my groove thang to "Poison" by  Bel Biv Devoe . Or maybe I should just wash his car. Where's the car wax?  
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, Tim and I went shopping for clothes to bring to the Philippines. We went to  urlLink Ross  and I was lucky enough to find these really cute halter tops for $5.99 each. Only they're kind of thin and I'd have to wear a strapless bra and I really hate those things. Afterwards, we went to hang out with our friends Stacia and Philippe. Philippe was cranky because he has a cold, but other than that, we had fun with Stacia just catching up on things. Stacia is really good at talking and listening. She's the kind of person with whom you can shoot the shit for hours. We were supposed to go to my parents' house, so my folks could finally meet Stacia and Philippe, but those two have a baby (Stacia and Philippe, not my parents) and let's just say that I never knew how much time it took to prepare a baby for a night out (not that I don't love the little tyke, mind you. He's a doll).  Stacia and I talked about the possibility of me and Tim having children. I told her that it wasn't in the immediate future. I brought it up to Tim later and we decided that since I can't even manage to feed our fish twice a day, it's probably not a good idea for us to be bringing a child into the world any time soon. Also, the thought about having children within one or two years from now just gives me the willies. Can't do it. Ask me again in ten years.  Today, we're going to buy some travel toiletries and possible gifts for my grandfather. Tim thinks we should get him a region-free DVD player, so he could play whatever DVD he wanted, but I don't know if you can just pick that up from  urlLink Target  or something. I mean, are those things even legal?  We leave for the Philippines tomorrow. We bought a glaring red suitcase, so no one could possibly mistake it for theirs on the conveyor belt at the luggage pick-up. Our stop-over is  urlLink South Korea . I've never had Korean food. Is it any good?  
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tim and I spent two glorious days at the White Rock Beach Resort in Subic Bay. A nice little storm came along and I was worried all night that our roof would fly away. Thankfully, it didn't.  Anyway, Tim is frustrated that I eat too much. He's concerned about my blood sugar. My dad is a diabetic and the last time I went to the doctor, the good man informed me that I am hypoglycemic. I told Tim he should trade me in for a better, newer model. He said he'd rather nag me about my diet than find someone else. Awww...  I'm hungry.  
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm sitting in this dank Internet cafe a block away from my Lolo's house and I'm thinking to myself, "This is a really good set-up they've got here." I mean, there are tons of people in this city who don't have computers or an internet connection, so they must be making bank.   Tim seems to be enjoying himself, except he's got a ton of mosquito bites. My aunties think he's absolutely precious and that I'm lucky that he deemed me worthy for a partner, while my uncles think he's a hell of a guy... a man's man. Even my Lolo (who doesn't like anybody) thinks he's a catch. Why doesn't anybody think that  I'M  the catch for Tim?   Tim reminds me everday that he's the lucky one.   Anyway, I have this disgusting looking bump on the back of my leg. I'm convinced that some unknown species of a bug has laid an egg in it and an  urlLink alien  will burst out of it. Everyone tells me it's a flea bite. I don't know what's more disturbing. The city is hot, muggy, and a little stinky. Still, Tim and I are having a blast.  By the way, since Tim and I are not married, my Lolo has insisted that he and I sleep in separate rooms. Tim sleeps in one room, while I sleep on the couch where my Lolo (who prefers sleeping in the living room for some reason I have yet to understand) can keep an eye on me. While I'm sleeping, he keeps a hand on my ankle, just so he is sure that I don't sneak out to see Tim. My Lolo is a funny guy. He even wakes up and watches me when I get up in the middle of the night to go to the bathroom. This over-protection is cute and all, but I miss Tim.  Anyway, we will be flying back next Monday. I think I'm already missing this place.  More to come when I return...  
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't been able to sleep in the past couple of days. I'm starting to feel like Trevor Reznik from  urlLink The Machinist . I hope I don't start seeing weird shit in my bathroom mirror or I'm really going to lose it.  I haven't been going to work, either. I just don't have the energy. I've been watching Lifetime movies and napping. Listen, why is it that every Lifetime movie includes: a battered spouse, a dead cheerleader, a raped housewife, or a woman who was kidnapped as a child and about to reluctantly reunite with a dying biological mother who needs a kidney?  I need to get back into my regular sleep routine... stupid jet-lag.
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of these days I'll write a long entry about my trip to the Philippines, but let me get over my jet lag first, okay? To hold you over, feast your eyes on  urlLink this .  Anyway, I had a doctor's appointment early this morning today, so Tim and I woke up early (which sucked 'cause we didn't get to sleep until about 2 am, since we're still on Philippine time which was 6 PM). I called my doctor to let her know I was on my way only to learn that they had a computer glitch last week and I don't actually have an appointment. I ranted and raved and told them that I took a day off for the appointment and had spent about 50% of my vacation worrying about the stupid  urlLink procedure , so they had better find a way to slip me in. I must have sounded pretty frantic, so they moved some appointments aside and managed to find me a slot.   My mother, father, and Tim came along for support (my parents sat in the waiting room, while Tim went in with me until I kicked him out).  When I entered the examination room, the first thing that caught my eye was THIS BIG FUCKING NEEDLE. I'm not even exaggerating. That thing was gigantic and had a needle that was about half a foot long. Local anesthesia, my ass. That thing looked big enough to numb  urlLink King Kong ! I understood that it was absolutely necessary (since the procedure called  L oop  E lectrosurgical  E xcision  P rocedure involved the doctor cutting out a piece of my cervix like it's pizza), but I was still intimidated by it. Thankfully, it didn't hurt at all. Seriously, the nurse said I was going to feel a small pinch (like a bee sting, you know), but I didn't feel anything. Maybe it was because of this giant plastic speculum that they had jammed in there or that I was too worried about the upcoming procedure to even feel any pain, but I was fine. My knees shook like bowling pins after the injection (which was normal, I was told), but I was fine. I was cool like  urlLink B.B. , yo!  By the way, there was this vacuum cleaner thing on the floor that the nurse told me was necessary for the procedure. It wasn't a Dirt Devil. Tim told me he could yell out things like "You missed a spot!" to the doctor while she was working on me and this cemented my decision to kick him out as soon as the doctor came in.  Anyway, the doctor initially thought that she would have to do a cone biopsy, but she thought LEEP would do the trick just as well and it would only take about five minutes. After kicking Tim out, the doctor went to work. First, she looked at the area with this  urlLink microscope looking thing , then she said, "Alright, it'll be over before you know it". The nurse slapped on this sticky rubber mat on my leg, which she said was for grounding purposes (so I wouldn't get electrocuted), then turned on the little vacuum cleaner thing. While the doctor was working her mojo, I stared at the ceiling (which was seriously lacking in entertainment.  I could have totally used a  urlLink word search  up there!) and sang " urlLink Ninety-Nine Bottles of Beer on the Wall " (shut up, it's a classic!), while the doctor said things like "Almost finished!" and "Okay, now we just have to scrape a little on the sides!". I actually managed to tune her out after a while (but not the smell which kind of reminded me of barbecue... eww, I know... and the smoke coming out of MY VAGINA!). I was only on me 89th bottle of beer when she said in a chirpy voice, "All done!" I couldn't believe it. I asked her if she got all of it and she said, "Yup!"  She added that she would have to send the sample to pathology (there's a marginal chance that the cells are actually cancerous), but she said that since she managed to get rid of all of it, I probably wouldn't have anything to worry about.   I  urlLink worried  over nothing. I was ready to make out a will and shit.  The doctor patched me up and sent me on my way. My knees were a little shaky and Tim had to guide me as I walked, but all and all, I was as good as new. The doctor told me I had to take it easy for the rest of day (which meant bedrest... woo-hoo!), so Tim and I ordered pizza and watched the mini X-Files marathon on the Sci-fi channel.  Yay! I'm not going to die!  
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back... and now I'm going to bed.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I said I wasn't going to see  urlLink it  on opening night, but I did, okay? I plunked down the 21 bucks for it ($9.50 x 2 + $2 "service" charge. Whatever,  urlLink scalpers !). The lines were insane, but Tim and I managed to find good seats. Right to the side, with no one in front of us (no big heads or people standing up to go to the bathroom), but there was this bar where we could put up our legs. That was pretty sweet.  What can I say about the movie? Better than I expected. It's not only one of the best "comic book" movies ever, but one of the best movies I've seen all year. Of course, I've only seen  urlLink Van Helsing ,  urlLink Troy , and other such  urlLink forgettable  fare like that, so it's not like I have a  urlLink Casablanca  to compare it to. I'm just saying that if all we've got so far for Oscar contenders are Mel Gibson's S&M fest and Michael Moore's  urlLink sorry excuse  for a "documentary", Spidey better get a nod, too. I mean, it wasn't  urlLink Superman II  or anything, but it was pretty good.  By the way, there's this Japanese flick I got on  urlLink Ebay  (it's not available for sale in America, so I had to get it "imported") last year called  urlLink Ju-on  or  urlLink "grudge"  in English. Tim and I watched it together, but I have to say that I still don't have any idea as to what it's about. Why? Because I spent about 85% of the movie covering my eyes or hiding under the blanket. All I can remember is this pale little boy who doesn't say anything... just pops up right next to you and lets out this meow-like scream... which is, of course, just a precursor for an even creepier thing: his mother broken and bloody crawling down the stairs in a clear plastic bag with this  urlLink cold, dead look  in her eyes. Anyway, I've been meaning to see it again, just to see if it still has the same scare factor, but for some reason, I can't get myself to do it. It must be because from time to time, I still expect that little boy to pop up next to me and make that little meowing sound...   Listen, do yourself a favor and acquire the film somehow. There's Ju-on the TV movie and  urlLink Ju-on: The Grudge  which is the big-budget remake of that. Go get both. I don't know if they'll ever release those movies here in the US (I'm still waiting in vain for  urlLink Battle Royale ), but there's an American  urlLink remake  with fuckin'  urlLink Buffy  coming out either this year or next year, but I don't trust it. Sure, it's executive produced by  urlLink Sam Frickin' Raimi  and directed by the original  urlLink director , but fuck that! It's Buffy, for God's sake! The same woman who married this  urlLink numbnuts ! Besides, no matter how many times you assholes tell me the American version of the  urlLink Ring  was so much better the Japanese  urlLink "version" , I still won't believe you. Why? Because you assholes keep calling it a "version" like the Americans did it first. The Japanese made the original, morons! And don't you dare tell me that whatever the Americans remake is just an improvement on the original, because I'll always have  urlLink this  to bring up in defense (by the way, I know that it was  urlLink "originally"  done by Americans, then  urlLink remade  by the Brits, okay? I just don't think there was any point to stealing it back only to fuck it up in ways that the network that could keep this  urlLink show  going for 4 seasons, ever could. Are we still mad at the Brits about that  urlLink war  thing?).  Oh, and another thing, if some of you could just learn to read faster, you'd be able to enjoy subtitled  urlLink flicks  in their original glory, too!  And I'm done.
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Spiderman 2  comes out today. I wonder if I should shell out the bucks to see it right away or wait a couple of months. There's nothing I like better than an empty theater. Mainly because there's nothing else in the world that I can't stand more than a tubby, loud kid overflowing into my seat and shoving greasy popcorn into his gaping maw while I'm trying to enjoy my movie. Not to mention the screaming babies (Why do parents bring their infant children into movie theaters? How the heck would a senseless child enjoy something on screen when its mind is not even fully developed yet? Spend the twenty bucks and hire a babysitter, cheapo!), inconsiderate assholes yakking into their cell phones, people who discuss plot points and dialogue DURING THE MOVIE (What the hell is wrong with you assholes? That's what coffee shops are for! Visit one AFTER the movie!), and people who kick the back of your seat (I'm serious. The next dickhead who kicks my chair  dies . I'm not even joking. We're talking evisceration). This is also why I have a large collection of DVDs (last count: 510).  Maybe I'll just stay home tonight and watch 2 hours of  urlLink Law & Order  on TNT, then another 2 on NBC.  By the way, I saw the funniest book title at the bookstore the other day.  urlLink Michael Moore is a Big Fat Stupid White Man  by David Hardy and  urlLink Jason Clarke . Hah! Now that's gumption.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eh, I've got nuthin'.  I've gone back to work, though. Stupid job.   One of these days, I'll write again. Probably. Stupid jet lag. Still can't sleep.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay!  urlLink Dean Cain 's working  urlLink again ! This fall on CBS. I give it 3 episodes.  
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, remember how I've said  urlLink before  that my job sucks?    Ok... I had a shitty day at work today. Then again, work is always shitty. It's not that I hate my job, but... Ah, yes, I DO HATE MY JOB. The boss sucks. The clients suck. Worst of all, I don't even have a sound card on my computer. What kind of shit is that?   'Cause seriously it does. Anyway, I went on a job interview today and I don't think I did very well. The whole thing lasted about five minutes and the guy let me do all the talking (which is never a good sign). When he asked me why I wanted to leave my job now,  maybe I shouldn't have said, "Umm... 'cause it sucks ass." Well, okay, I didn't say that. And when he asked about my typical workday, I didn't say  urlLink this , either:    "Well, I generally come in at least fifteen minutes late, ah, I use the side door - that way Lumbergh can't see me, heh - after that I sorta space out for an hour...Yeah, I just stare at my desk, but it looks like I'm working. I do that for probably another hour after lunch too, I'd say in a given week I probably only do about fifteen minutes of real, actual, work."   Well, anyway, I have a couple of more leads lined up, so I'm not doing too badly. But the real reason I want to leave my job?  BECAUSE THE MEDICAL INSURANCE SUCKS!!  I'm not even joking. Those people are so  GODDAMNED  disorganized that my claims aren't even going through and the doctor's office keeps having to send me the bill. You know what I did this morning other than stare at the wall?  STAYED ON THE PHONE, ON HOLD, FOR FORTY FIVE MINUTES WITH MY GODDAMNED MEDICAL INSURANCE COMPANY TO TELL THEM THAT I WASN'T PAYING A GODDAMNED RED CENT, THAT'S WHAT!!     Ahem.  Okay... yeah... time to watch  urlLink Battle Royale . 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's with  urlLink Jason Lee  acting like a deranged monkey on crack on a commercial for  urlLink Tour de France 2004 ? And why does he look so nasty, greasy, and like he hasn't bathed in a year? Is it his punishment for starring in that craptastic Stephen King shitfest  urlLink Dreamcatcher ? Or is it for playing all those kind of amusing, but also kind of annoying second banana characters on those kind of funny, but vastly overrated  urlLink Kevin Smith  movies? And what's going to happen to him now that the world has realized that Kevin Smith really has  urlLink nothing else  going for him, but colorful, yet empty pop-culture references and a potty mouth? Will he be on his way out, too? If so, that's too bad. I kind of liked him as Brodie on  urlLink Mallrats .
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's supposed to be a parody of  urlLink Hardball with Chris Matthews  mixed with  urlLink Crossfire  on CNN. It's called  urlLink Crossballs  and it premieres tonight on Comedy Central at 7:30 pm with an encore showing at 11:30 pm. I caught the earlier show and thought it was cute and all, but didn't fall off the couch from laughing.   The show's premise is this: they provide a real topic for debate, present a panel with  urlLink  so-called experts  ... sounds good, right? Only the panel also includes  experts  who are not aware that the show is fake. The  so-called experts  that are showcased on the program are actually stand-up comedians. I've seen the trailers. The show is supposed to be funny. I even saw the one where one of the  experts  say, "The real problem nowadays is that people don't know how to drink  and  drive". No, really, it's funny (especially if the  expert  on the hot-seat was some obnoxious know-it-all blowhard who really deserved the very public humiliation). But I wasn't laughing tonight. Maybe it was the show's topic that rubbed me the wrong way.  Reality TV . I'm just thoroughly sick of it now. But that's topic enough for another blog.  P.S. On July 18th, there's going to be this  urlLink "documentary"  on  urlLink M. Night Shyamalan  on the Sci-Fi Channel. It's supposed to be a big deal because apparently, in the middle of the filming, the spooky director thought the network was getting  urlLink too personal  and refused to give any more interviews. Sci-fi promises to show us hapless viewers what this man is  really  like. What, are they gonna show us that the man turns into a big, whiny, diva-like  urlLink crybaby  when he doesn't get what he wants?  What-the-fuck-ever.  Smells like publicity to me.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to a barbecue party of a married couple we know. Is it automatic to hang out with married people or coupled people when you're part of a couple? I've noticed that when you've been dating someone for a while, you become more naturally inclined to hang out with people who aren't single. Why is that?  Afterwards, we went to my mom's house for some barbecued chicken (Phil's #1 recipe).  Then we headed over to Rancho Bernardo High School to see watch the fireworks because Cheng-Fay insisted on seeing a "real American fireworks show with real Americans". Her boyfriend, who is an American, said we could just stay home and watch fireworks on TV. Cheng-Fay did not agree.  Today, we brought Stacia a sandwich and hung out with her for a couple of hours, just shooting the shit. Her son, Riley, is starting to talk now. His vocabulary is expanding. It's frightening because right about this time last year, he was just an infant barely out of his mother's womb. Now he's jumping and running and laughing out loud just like a little boy.   Ah, kids. Not that I want any myself right now, but they're nice to think about. Unless you added dirty diapers, sticky hands, crying for no reason, and the whole lack of coherent speech thing. 'Cause  that's  scary.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tim and I went looking for a townhouse to buy today. I mean, not in the immediate future or anything, but something to think about when the lease on our apartment expires in a few months. Did we find anything we liked? You betcha. Can we afford it? Nope. We're better off buying a house in  urlLink Iowa . There's no way in hell we can ever afford San Diego real estate unless I manage to sell my novel.  And here it is, your random quote for the day:   "You son of a bitch. You moved the cemetery, but you left the bodies, didn't you? Didn't you? You left the bodies and you only moved the head stones. You only moved the head stones!" - urlLink Steve Freeling ,  urlLink Poltergeist  (1982) 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude... I got&nbsp;"terminated" and shit. I'm all upset and stuff in a not really sort of way.&nbsp; My boss said it's because I'm not "the best fit for the position" and that the "quality of [my] work has been steadily declining". DUDE, I CALL PEOPLE ON THE PHONE AND ASK HOW MANY FUCKING BATHROOMS THEY HAVE IN THE BUILDING! IT'S NOT LIKE I INVENT SHIT LIKE  urlLink TRIOXIN 245 ! This cruel bitch I called once even said to me, "You know, if you had a college education, you wouldn't be doing what you're doing." HEY, BITCH, SHUT UP! YOU'RE A FRICKIN' RECEPTIONIST WHO MAKES 9 BUCKS AN HOUR (not that I have anything against receptionist or anything. I quite like them. Especially the non-bitchy ones)!   Relatives (especially my mother): Don't worry, mom. I'm looking for a job right now as we speak.   Anyway, here's your random movie quote of the day:    "I've passed the point of no return. Do you know what that is, Beth? That's the point in a journey where it's more difficult to go back to the beginning. It's like when those astronauts got in trouble. I don't know, somebody messed up, and they had to get them back to Earth. But they had passed the point of no return. They were on the other side of the moon and were out of contact for like hours. Everybody waited to see if a bunch of dead guys in a can would pop out the other side. Well, that's me. I'm on the other side of the moon now and everybody is going to have to wait until I pop out."  - urlLink D-FENS ,  urlLink Falling Down (1993)  &nbsp; Ah, well, looks like I've got the time now to write the  urlLink Great American Novel .  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I want to see this movie called   urlLink Maria Full of Grace  quite badly. The only problem is, the closest theater playing it is in Santa Ana, which is like... an hour and a half away. No way I'm driving there, if I can just wait for the damned thing&nbsp;to be released&nbsp;on DVD.  &nbsp;  By the way, the movie is about a 17 year old Colombian girl who smuggles these heroin-filled pellets in exchange for a passage to the US. By swallowing them. Poor girl.&nbsp; It reminds me of this  urlLink episode  of Law &amp; Order where this Nigerian woman swallows these heroin-filled balloons and they pop inside her, so she dies... dude... that episode was heavy.  &nbsp;  Ok, now I'm gonna go watch that version of  urlLink Moll Flanders  with  urlLink Alex Kingston  from ER in it. This version is much more bawdy, fun, and just plain dirty. The  urlLink one  with  urlLink Robin Wright Penn  just bored me to pieces. Maybe it's because I can't imagine frickin'  urlLink Buttercup  as a 'ho. But that's just me.   Oh, and here it is, your random quote for the day:    "Ooooooooooooh, he is my absolute all-time favorite! Oh, paying money to have watermelon sprayed all over you? Oh, give me more of that. Oversized props mixed with undersized talent? Oooooh, put me in the front row. Excuse me, Mr. Shopkeeper? Can I trade in my volume of Annotated Shakespeare for a tape of  Melon Crazy ? Oh, please, may I? Ooooooooh!"  -  urlLink Tom Servo ,  urlLink Mystery Science Theater 3000  (1988) [On watermelon-smashing "comedian"  urlLink Gallagher ]   P.S. The "official" release of  urlLink Batman: Begins  is on  June 17, 2005 . I should acquire some sort of counter for this, but I don't want to be like those creepy geeks who counted the days till those  urlLink freakish twins  turned 18. I mean, don't get me wrong... I'll still be counting. You just won't see it on my blog. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Starting today, I'm going to put up a quote from a random movie (it could be daily, weekly, or monthly) that I think is pretty hilarious, silly, or profound (okay, I'm fucking with you on the last one). And so here it is, the 1st one:   "Yeah, he's a professor... OF BEING A DOG! OOOOOH, FACED! Scratch moded!"  -  urlLink Grim ,  urlLink Cabin Fever  (2002)  Classic! I spent the summers of my youth in Northern California, so that quote holds a sentimental value with me. When I was a kid, whenever I thought I had out-witted someone, I used to yell "FACED!" obnoxiously, while dragging a hand in front of my own face. I did it so much one summer that my mom warned me that if I did it one more time, she was going to kill me.  I tried it a couple of times on Tim tonight, but he didn't think it was as funny as I  still  think it is. Sucka.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why won't they write a song like this for  urlLink Christian Bale ?    "David Duchovny" by  urlLink Bree Sharp     It's Sunday night; I am curled up in my room The T.V. light fills my heart like a balloon  I hold it in as best I can  I know I'm just another fan  But I can't help feeling I could love this secret agent man  And I can't...   Wait any more for him to discover me  I got it bad for David Duchovny  David Duchovny, why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me?   My friends all tell me,  "Girl, you know it's just a show,"  But deep within his eyes  I see me wrapped up like a bow  Watching the sky for a sign  The FBI is on my mind  I'm waiting for the day  When my lucky stars align  In the form of...   David Duchovny floating above me  In the alien light of the spaceship of love, I need  David Duchovny hovering above me  American Heathcliff, brooding and comely David Duchovny, why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me?   So smooth and so smart  He's abducted my heart  And I'm falling apart  From the looks I receive  From those eyes I can't leave  And you may say I'm naive  But he told me to believe...   Ooooooooo....   My bags are packed, I am ready for my flight  Want to put an end to my daydream days and sleepless nights  Sitting like a mindless clone  Wishing he would tap my phone  Just to hear the breath of the man, the myth, the monotone  And I would say...   David Duchovny, why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me? Why won't you love me?  David Duchovny, why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me? Why won't you love me?  David Duchovny I want you to love me  To kiss and to hug me, debrief and debug me  David Duchovny I know you could love me  I'm sweet and I'm cuddly - I'm gonna kill Scully!  David Duchovny, why won't you love me?  Why won't you love me? Why won't you love me?   Yeah...   I'll be waiting...  In Nevada...    And if you don't know who  urlLink David Duchovny  is, I don't even want to talk to you.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like Yoga. No, I LOVE Yoga. It's soothing, relaxing... helps you breathe better... so last night, when Tim and I went to  urlLink Target , I decided to buy this Yoga video starring  urlLink Denise Austin . I should have known better, though, because the second I stuck the disc into my DVD player, I hated it. The woman is CRAZY. She doesn't take her time with the poses and talks CONSTANTLY. Here I am trying to enjoy my downward-facing dog and she's saying inane things like, "Ooh, I just love this stretch, don't you?" and "Yoga makes me feel so good!" and "Yay, Yoga!" And I'm all, "Shut up, Bitch! Jesus, what the hell is YOUR problem?"  Bottom line: I don't recommend it unless you're an experienced exerciser. Or on crystal meth.     A Yoga body in 21 days? Heh. Yeah, right. I'll stick with  urlLink Karen Voight .
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck 'em all if they can't take a joke.  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spent the day shopping with my mother. It was really... pleasant. Ever since I moved out, my mom and I really haven't spent a lot of time together, except on Sundays, but that's more for our weekly family barbecues (and we don't get the chance to chat, anyway). I've forgotten how well my mother can listen and offer advice that is almost always astoundingly appropriate for the situation. She's eerie that way. It's funny 'cause when I was growing up, I fought my mother at every opportunity and was convinced that she was only out to sabotage my life. How wrong I've been and was. My mother is always right... I may not like it most of the time, but she really is remarkable.  I have three job interviews lined up next week. If I don't find a job soon...  By the way, I checked my  urlLink Paypal  account this morning and no one else has given me money. I guess I really DO need a job.  Random Quote of the Day:  "Oh, it's no use. She's so beautiful and I'm... well, look at me!"  - urlLink Beast ,  urlLink Beauty and the Beast  (1991)
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just want to thank my good friends Stacia and Philippe for giving me money. They're fine, young, upstanding citizens and I don't think I've ever known better  urlLink people .  My readers: You too can get a spotlight on my blog, if you just give me money. It's easy. Just click that little Paypal logo to the side of my blog just underneath the archives and boom, you're a good Samaritan. Don't you want to feel good about yourself by helping out your less fortunate fellowman? Or you can have true altruistic reasons, whatever, I don't care.   But to Stacia and Philippe (the most selfless, generous people I've ever known)? You're better people than this poor black-hearted soul will ever be!      "It's people... Soylent green is made out of people! They're making our food out of people! Next thing they'll be breeding us like cattle for food. You've gotta tell them. You've gotta tell them!"  - urlLink Detective Robert Thorn ,  urlLink Soylent Green  (1973)
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had an interview with a temp agency. Sounded promising. Will let you know.   "You a low down dirty dog, that's what's wrong. Time for me to get away from you, and enter into Creation. And your dead body'd be just the welcome mat I need."  - urlLink Celie ,  urlLink The Color Purple  (1985)  It's the only Whoopi movie I like. Shut up.   
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to include a  urlLink Paypal    donation tag to this blog (it's on the side bar, above the counter). Umm... you don't have to give me a money, but maybe you, my reader,  can find it in your heart  to donate enough so that I may be able to afford a box of Ramen noodles which should last me about a month. Or fuck it, don't give me money. Whatever. I'm not a  urlLink money-grubbing whore . Okay, maybe sometimes.  Umm... your mom.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay... I think it went well. He talked about the company, the position, what my duties would be... then he asked if I had any questions. I asked him about his managerial style, the office atmosphere, and any possibilities of future lay-offs.   I actually sounded pretty good, like I was REALLY interested in the company!  Then he asked me about my best and worst character traits. I gave him the usual spiel about being determined to succeed, having the uncontrollable compulsion to help my co-workers, as well as the obsession with organization and efficient multi-tasking, and of course, the glowing excitement to go to work each day. And my worst traits? Worst. Question. Ever. What the hell was I supposed to say? That the "glowing excitement" fades after a couple of weeks only to be replaced by this animal urge to bash my co-workers' heads against the walls merely to alleviate boredom? That once I figure out a short-cut to do my work, I cease putting even the most minimal effort into it and do only a couple of hours of  actual  work, at most, inside a week? No, I don't think he would have wanted to hear that at all. HOW THE HELL WAS I SUPPOSED TO ANSWER THAT SHIT? Instead, I said, "Oh, I'm a bit of a perfectionist and a workaholic, I'm afraid. I don't stop working until my fingers are reduced to bloody stubs and even then, I have to be pried away from my desk by security." He seemed impressed. He also asked me if I liked bugs. Yep.  Bugs . Do I like bugs? Are you kidding? I love 'em!  Anyway, he told me to call him on Wednesday for a second interview. That's good, right?   "No, I'm only joking. I'm not really Brian. No, I'm not Brian. I was only - It was a joke. I'm only pulling your leg! It's a joke! I'm not him! I'm just having you on! Put me back! Bloody Romans! Can't take a joke!"  - urlLink  Eric Idle ,  urlLink Life of Brian  (1979)
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tim and I went  urlLink out  with some friends last night, but mostly it was an impromptu send-off for Maria, who is moving to Santa Ana on Saturday. Grossest thing happened to me. I ordered a cheeseburger, medium-well as I always order it, and I was half-way through the damned thing (tasted fine) when I looked at it (and I really shouldn't have) and saw that the fucker was still bleeding! Eww! No joke. I handed it to Tim to finish and he had no problems gobbling the thing up. Yuck. It was almost enough to turn me vegetarian.  Almost .    "With this money, I can get away from you! From you and your chickens and your pies and your kitchens and everything that smells of grease. I can get away from this shack with its cheap furniture. And this town and its dollar days, and its women that wear uniforms and its men that wear overalls."  - urlLink Veda Pierce Forrester ,  urlLink Mildred Pierce  (1945)   
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw  urlLink Bourne Supremacy . It's just as good as the  urlLink first one , maybe better because it doesn't have a lot of  urlLink Julia Stiles  (who almost ruined the first film for me.  Almost .). I wasn't too impressed with  urlLink Joan Allen , either, but oh... that  urlLink Matt Damon . When oh when did he get so hot? Oh, he's so cute and boyish, but at the same time, there's just something glittering in those chocolate-brown eyes of his that says "danger! danger!". Jesus, listen to me. I sound like  urlLink Blaine Edwards  and  urlLink Antoine Merryweather  from  urlLink Men on Film .  Delish ! Because of this movie, Matt Damon is now on my Top Five Male Celebrities to F*ck Before I Die. "Three snaps up in a Z-Formation!" Hopefully, this delightful little action gem will help Mattie-poo shed the stink of  urlLink Affleck  forever. You don't need him, Mattie-poo! You're the star now! Oh, schnap! You can maybe throw him a bone every once in a while, but just remember what happened to that poor, unfortunate  urlLink Kevin Smith  (who, like an asshat, proclaimed Asslick his "golden goose"), and you'll be just fine, darling! Who's the star? Mattie-poo is! Yay, Mattie-poo! Now get out of my dreams and get into my pants!  Oh, naughty wicked me... did I just say that?    A-hem.  Random Quote of the Day:  "I watched him for fifteen years, sitting in a room, staring at a wall, not seeing the wall, looking past the wall - looking at this night, inhumanly patient, waiting for some secret, silent alarm to trigger him off. Death has come to your little town, Sheriff. Now you can either ignore it, or you can help me to stop it."  - urlLink Dr. Sam Loomis ,  urlLink Halloween  (1978)
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was standing in a line at Subway this afternoon, waiting for my oven-roasted chicken breast sandwich (with only lettuce AND cucumber) on italian herb and parmesan bread when a man passed by me and holy moly, I could have sworn it was  urlLink Ben Frickin' Kingsley . He was of average height, a bit bald at the top, and held himself in a princely stature. What the heck could he be doing in a third-rate sandwich shop in San Diego? Sir Ben Kingsley! When I heard him speak, though, I was sure it wasn't him (he didn't sound English). Imagine my disappointment. Frickin'  urlLink Gadhi  at Subway.  In other news, I received a call from one of the companies with whom I interviewed  urlLink last week . The guy said that the girl they had initially chosen over me failed the screening. Huh. We all know what that means...  DRUGGIE ! Anyway, I told him I received a couple of offers from other companies (liar, liar... your frickin' pants are on FIRE!) and would really love to work for his company if he would only add a couple more dollars to the hourly rate. He said he'd let me know in a couple of days. Heh.  Random Quote of the Day:  "My line? My most effective one is to tell a girl she has hair like a tortured midnight, lips like a red couch in an ivory palace, and that I'm lonely and starved for affection. Then, I generally burst into tears. It seldom works."  - urlLink Ernie Malone ,  urlLink Gentlemen Prefer Blondes  (1953)
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to the  urlLink Con  this weekend. The freaks and geeks were out in full force. Every year, I usually go for two things: 1) the  urlLink Cartoon  panel 2) and the costume contest (always hilarious. GO,  urlLink Beast Boy , GO!), but this year I went for one reason and one reason only: the Man himself, Mr.  urlLink Ray Bradbury .     Ever since I read Zen in the Art of Writing, I've been inspired to write down my thoughts and feelings on paper in an attempt to quiet the maelstrom inside my head. I know that sounds very melodramatic, but I was a weird kid who listened to a lot of Nine Inch Nails, Garbage, and Marilyn Manson. Oh, and The Cure. And some Morrissey. I imagined myself as this tortured creature and devised ways to make myself more miserable at every opportunity. I never knew why I was so depressed or gloomy in those days, but I guess it was because I thought of myself as a writer in the vein of Scott Fitzgerald (alcoholic) and Ernest Hemingway (ended more than a few of his books with the main character walking alone in the rain... killed himself). And then came Bradbury. When I read Zen, I found a writer who was HAPPY to be a writer. Here was a man who woke up everyday with an almost unquenchable thirst to put words on paper and he was excited to do it. When he talks about writing, it's like hearing a ten year old boy talk about his Pokemon cards or whatever it is that ten year old boys are crazy about nowadays.  He is my hero .  So when I heard that Mr. Bradbury was going to be attending the Con to speak about his writing, I was all for it. I got to the Con early, determined in my zeal to see Mr. Bradbury and ain't no one going to stop me. Except my  urlLink caffeine addiction . Fifteen minutes before the seminar, the shakes, accompanied by the headaches, attacked. You know the kind.  Those headaches . I sent Tim ahead of me and told him I was right behind him. I did not anticipate the line. Oh, Dear God, the line. It was longer than the one for Jude Law's autograph. By the time I got my caffeine fix, the hour-long seminar was over.  I was crushed . I did, however, get this nifty picture.     It's a little small, but it's me and Mr. Bradbury. What a wonderful man. Fans were just going up to him and shaking his hands, telling him what a difference he has made in their lives, and he smiled at them and thanked them for reading his books. I mean, wow. What a gentleman. The other guests at the Con charged you $10 bucks just to pose with them (thanks,  urlLink Ernie Hudson !), but this man was willingly posing and talking to his fans.  What a guy  (and that's why I hate  urlLink Michael Moore  even more).  This man once said, "Not to write, for many of us, is to die". Well, you know what? I don't want to die. No way. Not me. So, Mr. Bradbury? If there's ever a chance that you read this, I just want you to know that I'm never going to stop writing. No way, sir. Not me. I've finally accepted who I am... a writer. Not for others, not for an audience, but for myself. And for me,  finally , that's all that matters.  Random quote of the day:  "I'm the key figure in an ongoing government charade, the plot to conceal the truth about the existence of extraterrestrials. It's a global conspiracy, actually, with key players in the highest levels of power, that reaches down into the lives of every man, woman, and child on this planet, so, of course, no one believes me. I'm an annoyance to my superiors, a joke to my peers. They call me Spooky. Spooky Mulder, whose sister was abducted by aliens when he was just a kid and who now chases after little green men with a badge and a gun, shouting to the heavens or to anyone who will listen that the fix is in, that the sky is falling and when it hits it's gonna be the shit-storm of all time."  - urlLink Fox Mulder ,  urlLink The X-Files: Fight the Future  (1998) 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Meron tayong kasabihan na kung wala kang mabuting masasabi, eh wag ka na lang magsalita. Aminado ako, ako na ang unang magtatatawa pag may na kita ako kakaiba at hindi ko naiintindihan. Ang problema nga lang ay medyo pikon ako. Balat-sibuyas nga. Kunyari, may nagsabi na tumataba na raw ako, eh di tampo naman ang reaksyon ko. Recently, may nag-tag sa comment board ko na mas gusto nya raw isang litrato ko sa isa kong litrato. Eh, siempre naman, ang unang reaksyon ko ay akalain na ang ibig sabihin nya ay pangit ako.     (before)     (after)       Paano naman kung ibig nyang sabihin ay mas gusto nya yung photographic aspect nung isang litrato kesa sa isa? Eh, paano kung mas maganda yung composition or lighting nung isa, di ba?  I was quick to assume  naman na  he was just making fun of me , di ba? Exception naman kung talagang antipatiko at bastos s'ya at talagang nang-aasar lang. Alam kong hindi ko na lang dapat pansinin, pero parang nasaktan din ako. Siguro ay sya lang ay isang taong walang magawang matino, pero  I guess  naapektuhan din ako. Parang akong tanga, di ba?  Pero alam mo, masyado nang maraming oras ang sinayang ko sa isyung ito. Kung ano man ang ibig nyang sabihin, sa kanya na yun.  It's a free country . Ang gusto ko lang sana ay maging mas makapal ang balat (o mukha) ko para pag may nagsabing hindi maganda sa akin ay hindi ko na lang papansinin.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went shopping with Stacia today. As usual, I had to find my pants in the little girls' section. Ugh. I hate being short. Since I'm not really very skinny, though, I had to buy the  fat  little girl's pants. Size 14 1/2. Looks cute, though.  Before shopping, Stacia and I ate at  urlLink Islands . I had half a burger (the one with the guacamole on it) and she had another half (the Maui burger which had mushrooms on it). We shared a plate of cheesy fries and felt disgusting afterwards. If you MUST feel disgusting, it's always good to be disgusting with a friend, and there's no one I'd rather be disgusting with than Stacia. :)  Afterwards, we visited  urlLink Bath & Body Works  where I tested perfume scents on Riley. Stacia, if you noticed that your son smelled like a two dollar whore, I'm sorry. I didn't want the scent on me just in case it was icky. Just kidding. I just wanted to see how it would smell on someone else. Why does perfume always smell better on someone else anyway? I bought the peony scent, because as much as I like the Warm Sugar and Vanilla scent, Tim and I have been spraying the stuff whenever we make a stinky in the bathroom, so I now associate the smell of vanilla with poopie. Lovely, huh? So peony it is.  Speaking of Riley, the kid made me realize that while I love children, I'm just not ready to have them yet. I must have worked off an entire meal just chasing the kid around! Which is a good thing, I guess. Thanks, Riley. I guess whenever that infernal biological clock tells me it's time to have kids, I'll just borrow Riley, eh, Stacia?  By the way, Mom says the company she works for might offer me the position for which I interviewed last Monday. They will probably offer me more money than the other company which offered me a job and where I'm supposed to start next Monday. The question is: Do I want to work at the same place as my mother? (Mom, if you're reading this, I'm just joking. Of course I want to work with you!)  Random Quote of the Day:  "You show me Regan's double, same face, same voice, everything. And I'd know it wasn't Regan. I'd know in my gut. Now, I want you to tell me that you know for a fact that there's nothing wrong with my daughter, except in her mind. YOU TELL ME FOR A FACT THAT YOU KNOW AN EXORCISM WOULDN'T DO ANY GOOD. YOU TELL ME THAT!"  - urlLink Chris McNeil ,  urlLink The Exorcist  (1973)
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I sure would like one of  urlLink these :     Man, I love these guys.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm employed again!!! YES! YES! WAHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!  Oh, and by the way,  urlLink The Village  sucked. It was weird, contrived, and maybe I'm not smart enough to understand a lot of things, but WHAT THE HELL WAS THE DAMN THING ABOUT?? I didn't even enjoy the eye-candy that was  urlLink Joaquin Phoenix  because he got all flabby and kind of gross. The movie was useless to me! Useless!  Random Quote of the Day:  "That I should want you at all suddenly strikes me as the height of improbability... you're an improbable person, Eve, but so am I. We have that in common. Also a contempt for humanity, an inability to love or be loved, insatiable ambition - and talent. We deserve each other."  - urlLink Addison De Witt ,  urlLink All About Eve  (1950)
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude, I found the  urlLink coolest chick  online. I've never actively sought out a friend online before, much less a girl, but when Dan sent me the ad, I instantly knew that the girl could be my non-homo-soulmate. She likes zombies, cheesy Japanese films, and comic books. She's a geek like me. I don't have a lot of girlfriends (girls usually hate me), but I think this girl and I could be friends for  real . I haven't met her in person yet, so she could be totally fuckin' crazy, but she  seems  nice on her emails. Dan hopes she would be hot, so if it worked out between me and her, I could set them up later on.  Work was good today. I can't believe tomorrow is Thursday already. Before you know it, it's Christmas and I'd have to get Tim something really good 'cause I still haven't gotten him a birthday present (I know, I know I'm an awful girlfriend, BUT I WAS UNEMPLOYED, OKAY? Alright, alright, that isn't an excuse, either). Anyway, my girl-boss is not the dumbass that I thought she was. I totally underestimated her. After all, she was the one who created her own position, convinced the owner of the company about how important it was, and managed to land herself a pretty cushy office. I'd say that's pretty smart, don't you?   Cute Oklahoma boss flirted with me today when he saw me at the copy room, looking like I was going to cry because the stupid copy machine wouldn't cooperate with me. PAPER JAM MY ASS! He was so sweet. Cute IT guy flirted with me, too. Hmm... it must be my new perfume... or I'm frickin' drop dead gorgeous.  Random Quote of the Day: "You be strong, you survive... You stay alive, no matter what occurs! I will find you. No matter how long it takes, no matter how far, I will find you!" - urlLink Hawkeye ,  urlLink Last of the Mohicans  (1992) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I had my first day at the new job today. Nice lighting, people are friendly. Nothing exciting to report, except there's a guy whose office is across mine who looks almost identical to this  urlLink guy .  Oh, yeah... I'll get some work done, alright. Ha-ha. My slutty ass is all talk. Everyone knows I'm too much in love with this  urlLink guy  to do anything!  Boy, am I glad to be working again. Still, you may feel free to donate to my Pay-Pal account as much as you wish!   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stacia, her family, Tim, and I went to the  urlLink San Diego Wild Animal Park  on Saturday. We saw some birds, some reindeer lookin' things, but no lions or antelopes or what-have-you. There was a safari ride thing that you go on for an hour and it takes you to the range where the animals graze, but it was neither wheelchair nor stroller friendly. But even if it were, it wouldn't have been a good idea for us to go. Imagine being stuck in a trolley like thing in the middle of a wild animal reserve where any hungry mountain lion can pounce on you the second you make a sound, and your 18-month old companion (Riley) decides to suddenly start shrieking because he's hungry. Yeah... not cool.  Today, my parents decided to have their house blessed. In the Filipino culture, that's when a Catholic priest comes and sprinkles water all over your house. During the ceremony, I had to restrain myself from saying things like, "What an excellent day for an  urlLink exorcism " and "Merrin!" The priest also decided to bless my mother. When he asked her if she would renounce Satan and all of his temptations, I was tempted to yell, "Your mother sucks cock in hell, Karras!" Oh, come on, how could I not? I had to leave before I could embarass myself and my family.  Tomorrow, I start on my new job. Hopefully, I won't hate it as much as the last  urlLink one .  Random Quote of the Day: " The evil that men should turn their brothers into beasts of burden, to be stripped of spirit, and hope, and strength - only because they are of another race, another creed. If there is a God, he did not mean this to be so."  - urlLink Moses ,  urlLink The Ten Commandments  (1956) 
    
</post>


</Blog>