<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haas..my new blog..simple one though. actually i also dunno why i start blogging..my previous blog webby lost le..haas dunno where it go liaox..anyway, today i went to jurong east to watch my sch badminton finals against rjc. i am in house committee so must go support..actually i kinda reluctant to go..thought it will be sian, but when i reached there, i could suddenly feel the passion and drive towards the school when i see all the tjcians cheering together wif the badminton team...the last match which was the critical match determined if we can win.   BUT  ...we lost the first set..den the second set, it was a close game of 17-15..de last set was the most excitin part and i guessed pei zhou, our badminton player tried his best..and we lost 15-3...haix..when we lost we were all silent while rjc hu were beside cheered like hell. pei zhou cried and was very sad coz he tried his best to win the second set..hoping and pinning that there will be a chance to win the 3rd set..but all was over...he laid on the badminton court..and when i saw all the badminton ppl went to cheer him up..i was touched...we cheered for them..and i was so touched that i nearly cried..i could realli understand how hey felt...it was a long way..they've went a long way to the finals...anyway u guys did a great job...tjc rox. today morning was our house committee investiture and we finally got our hc badges..haaas...=) 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Megapixel camera for quality printing  Up to 10 minutes video recording   Movie Director application for automated fun video production   8 MB internal dynamic memory with 64 MB Reduced Size MultiMediaCard (MMC)   Mobile Internet browsing lolx...this fone is so darn cool sia just that the shape abit farnie..lolx. hmm..yesterday, i went to sch to mug again for the 2nd time..but onli me and quan ming...i study kinda slow..onli finish maths sia. hmm..i was chatting wif jie at nite yest and i din even noe she had 2 blogs..hmm the other one is the private one. yup..haas..private blog for all the other sad stuff..hmm..actually its not wrong to haf one blog for sad stuff..haas..i shld also haf one hor..since this blog is called beary  happie  life...so must haf a beary  sad  life..lolx..kiex not farnie, anyways jie..hmm..u shld try to think of more happy stuffs, eh i noe that u find it useless telling ppl abt all ur stuffs..but hu noes ppl might be able to help u ritex..yar, maybe i'm just crapping lar..it's true that i this brother abit useless can't help u much~lolx..life's kinda different frm the past le..ppl do change..tt's all i hafta say for now. oh i watched the stupid soccer match this morning..portugal vs england..wah liux..the first half was so nice when michael owen scored sia..i was like jumping around with excitment but when rooney was substituted..i was like :"sHiT, vAsSeL!" and truly lar..vassel abit hopeless sia..i think rooney and owen works beta..lolx. that beckham even pro sia..he and his corner kicks lor...wah liux..shot penalty..wat sia. haiyohx..disappointed sia..eriksson now u very happie lor..bleahx. went back to cchms to see mr chua to sign sum stuff..den went back to tj today to mug..but din mug for long..kok wei came, followed by jing yi, hannah, quan ming and qing yu..hmm..den i left at ard 12. i proceed to bedok library to return the bk "Scouting In Singapore"..so heavy..yup but it's a gd bk. then i went to borrow "Scouting for Boys"..din finish reading it previously..hmm..so must read it after exams. bleahx..countdown..2 more days to JCT and i haben touch chem which is the first paper..tsk tsk..this is bad sia. oh..den today's korean jamboree meeting was abit miserable, onli me, seng tat and other 2 scouts..and we appointed the posts le..PL is weiliang, APL is me..QM is seng tat..lolx. all the ventures..yupx. oh..finally now at book 18..haas..sasuke brother is damn pro..but he's evil lar..kill own parents..hmm..naruto seems to be getting more exciting..lolx. hmm..nxt sat got STC appreciation dinner at aloha chalet @ changi village..hmm..then go there take testimonial..and we also haf pop bbq..lolx..so must chiong down.      lolx..special request by wan lin to put it at the blog....lolx..wan lin ah, if u and pei-han wanna see zhi wei den come cchms lor..lolx...hees..=P  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lolx..finally mugging sia..i went to sch today to study..the library as usual filled wif many ppl mugging. i saw jing yi, owen, kok wei, quan ming, qing yu and hannah..din sit together wif them to study..coz stress lar..i just started to study onli haas..den i wanted some peace..hees. i still got 5 days left..hmm..friday got korean jamboree meeting and i haben thought abt the shirt and badge design..haas..nvm leave it to the other scouts. i just now watching hai you ming tian 2...the show is kinda sad but i like it..hees..got li nan xing & ou xuan sia. the theme song, wei ming tian is also nice. i luv the song sang by tay ping hui, shou zhe ni...nice song..can go download..lolx     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        breathe easy...blue    Cruel to the eyes I see the way he makes you smile  Cruel to the eyes Watching him hold what used to be mine  Why did I lie Why did I walk away to fly Ooh why Ooh why   I.........can't breathe easy I cant sleep at night Until your by my side  No I........can't breathe easy I cant dream you had another dream without you lying next to me There's no way  Cursed me inside For every word that caused you to cry Crushed me inside I wont forget, no I wont baby I Don't know why (Don't know why) I left the one I was looking to find  Ooh why Ooh why  WHY.....   I.........can't breathe easy I cant sleep at night Until your by my side  No I........can't breathe easy (Breathe easy) I cant dream you had another dream without you lying next to me, there's no way No I.........can't breathe easy I cant dream you had another dream without you lying next to me, there's no way  Out of my mind Nothing makes sense anymore  I want you back in my life That's all I'm breathing for  Ooh I...................... Tell me why................ Ooh Tell me why I cant dream you had another dream without you lying next to me, there's no way  no no no no no  I................can't breathe easy I cant sleep at night Until your...by my side  Yeah I...................Can't breathe easy No I... I can't dream you had another dream without you lying next to me, there's no way There's no way   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       lolx..only 1 week left sia..die le lar, i still haben started studying. hmm..hafta start studying le. yesterday went to met dinesh sir at jalan kayu roti prata shop. had a long chat and after the chat i guessed the impression of dinesh in my eyes is much much more different. i now respect him more than ever...i guessed he's like everyone else but he's really a leader that i can learn and look up to. there's alot of things that he can share and we can learn. yupx..and i guess it's true that its time we as ventures shld take the initiative to do sum stuff to our unit coz he say whenever he come, the situation is always the same and he hafta spend abt 1 hr or so to nag...and i guess there isn't any change yet..esp to our store and den i guess..summore he's now ADC of katong so it'll be very busy and stressful for him. so me and houston will be going to sch tml to settle the store stuff first..coz weiliang, keat meng and jason is at fei yue..lolx..dunno if they enjoying themselves not..this time fei yue duno y not at chung cheng sia..haas, so sad. anyways, tml got class outing in the afternoon summore...4hm class outing..i also dunno wat they doing..and the bbq is cancelled coz no pit.haas..but we'll be going for monfort campfire lar..=)    Awsome! You are Sasuke!!    urlLink   Naruto Quiz     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   haas..sasuke sia, not bad lar..i thought i would be naruto..hees..still prefer him than sasuke.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haas..i'm back frm stc. the venue frm stc was changed frm chinese garden to chung cheng high sch at the last minute..haas coz the rent was too high and was not within the budget. anyway stc was real fun. i've learnt alot frm the cadet scouts though there can be times where they are abit naughty and can go out of hand..they r generally very cute..haas. the tents provided were just too small honestly..haas and they were too light, coz when nuttin is placed in the tent they started flying around..during he last day when we had camp development..pltc had one tent flying into the lake..in the end they had to sent sumone into the lake to take it out...i agree with wat mr raja said..it has realli taught us to be prepared..the motto of scout. i realli enjoyed the camp..having lyon as the camp chief is very gd..i thought he was those fierce type but he's actually quite nice. of coz most impt are the ventures i worked wif..the marlin ss, temasek ventures, tkss ventures, yuan ching girl scouts..they've been great. when we came in the first day..u can see james,wan lin and pei-han together...and of coz me,keat meng, weiliang, jason and jiyang together..den poor seng tat alone..den the yuen ching girl scouts and ren de together..but during the camp..till the last day u can see that we slowly mixed wif each other..it was damn fun..esp wif jonathen..yup..oh yar..forget to mention laughing buddha. haas..he is so cute and farnie..he is a farnie cadet scout frm keat meng's patrol..haas..when doing footdrill, he'll burp and ppl chest out, stomach in, he's chest out stomach out..haas..and he has that bugs bunny teeth.lolx..after the camp damn tired..we din haf much time to sleep..haas..but luckily it wasn't that bad..we didn't haf scouts waking us up..in de middle of the nite..after everything..we the ventures wif jon..went to parkway bk for dinner..and we saw cchms scouts haas..wat a coincidence..after that we went to marlin ss den..their den got air con summore and it was nicely arranged..better than ours in neatness..and they even had computer..haas..din noe wan lin is the vice-chair..dun look like one..though but she's got tat aura in her lar..can feel it. haas..i'm now damn awake..coz i slept til 6pm..then woke up..haas..too tired le. oh...de sec 4 ventures will be having pop..so gd sia got pop twice..one for passing out frm scouts..de other for "passing out" frm ventures..haas.it's on the 21st june..and the bbq is on the 3d july. haas..it's not combined..but the guides are also having the pop and bbq on the same day..and its becoz of fate that our pits are next to ech other..lolx..hmm..i still thinking whether to go for monfort campfire..coz lyon invited us personally but i got class gathering cum bbq..haas..i'm in a dilemma. oh yah...and the website for sum of the stc fotos http://sg.f2.pg.photos.yahoo.com/ph/bear_xiangz/album?.dir=/4138
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i'm off to pltc/stc tml le..hafta go meet jason, weiliang, keat meng, jiyang and jonathen at chinese garden mrt at 12noon tml..and we'll proceed to chinese garden. haas..this time we're under stc..Sixer's Training Camp..haf a chance to play wif the cadet scouts and interact wif them. they are darn hyper active de(from wat i noe)..they can ask u wake up in the middle of the nite to accompany them to toilet or they can wake up crying telling u that they lost their uniform..thus u wun haf a peaceful nite..lolx. let's hope that everything will be fine. yupx. oh..i haben come up wif the designs for the posters and de house committee t-shirts haas. nvm..still got lotsa time. anyway shao qi became the president for avc..congrats sia..i expected him to be lar, so obvious and i thought hubert would be the vice president..haas..but i think william got it. anyway congrats to those hu got into the committee..haas, it'll still be ahs domination..coz in avc, 99% of the peeps are from anglican so is definitely dominated by dem..lolx. oh i am now reading naruto bk 9...they are now still in the competition, fighting wif one another..so exciting. gaara is damn powerful..he's so cool.     hmm..i dunno when will i haf de time to go watch harry potter. haas..i think daniel(harry) has grown alot but not as innocent looking as last time. i luv emma watson(hermione), she is so pretty..   haas..and i can't wait to watch the movie..and i guessed this movie will be much more scarier than the previus 2..and much darker..coz of dementors..and more abt how the parents got killed would be known to harry potter..it's not sirius black but sumone else..haas..read the bk b4 but still wanna watch it.  It's not in the nature of the dementor to be forgiving  look at this picture it's so farnie..hermione and ron...nOOoO!..haas.lolx    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       oh..library camp starts tml and it sure will be boring de lor..library camp leh..can u imagine..wat stupid things will dey come out wif..sure all de lame games lor. oh summore now i'm switched over to Sixer's Training Camp to help le..coz sum stupid ventures frm some stupid sch say that they wun learn anything if they help out at STC so they wanna change wif us..so they go PLTC lor..under albert summore..hees haf a nice time dudes. oh today i had project work meeting as usual at 10am at tamp pavilion de burger king...we did sum discussions abt the survey lor and gotta go let mr thong approve de survey...den i went to search for my naruto book..haas guess wat?~i found bk 7~ HAAS it's getting more and more exicting lor..but i still dun haf bk 2 and 4..wah lao..so sad sia, sakura's hair become so short and sasuke kena de curse made by the snake guy..bleahz. yesterday we had pltc meeting at cchms but now it's useless le..coz we r not in pltc anymore..lolx. den wanted to play pool but coz we wear scouts pants den i tink weiliang go buy pants and houston and keat meng got bring pants..den i left..so i duno if they went to play. the sec 4 dis yr like very pro leh.haas..mid yr suppose to be quite difficult but yong qi told me her go 13 for L1R5..wah seh..i remembered i got 22 for mid year lor..haas. dey r damn pro. den i got nuttin much to do so i went to suntec..wanted to watch harry potter actually but i think..dun wan lar..i also dunno when 4hm dey all wanna watch leh..organise until dunno wat le..but the bbq is confirmed on the 19th le..haas. so long never see all my classmates. yup..coming back to wat i was saying..i went to play arcade instead at suntec..very long never go le..din noe that there's KOF 2003 now.haas the characters are damn cool lAh..lolx. den i walked back to city hall mrt..and on the way..i got nuttin to do so i was just counting the number of gals wearing   pink   shirt.and when i walked all the way out of city hall mrt..i found out that there are 256 gals in   pink  ..alot lor..it's like i every 6 to 8 gals i walk past i will see 1 gal in   pink   shirt...therefore i can conclude that gals realli like   pink  . i saw more gals wearing de lighter colour of   pink  ..dan de darker side of   pink  ...  light pink   represents the pure and demure side of a gal? on de other hand   dark pink   represents de wilder and hotter side of a gal..lolx..  gals and their   pinkish   world  actually i'm ok wif   lighter pink   lar..i hate those   hot pink   lor..hees..still prefer purple~green~blue..haas http://card3.silversand.net/diy/image/090666.swf the above webby is a flash of the song An Jing..not bad..=) 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yeah manx...i'm gonna complete my 17 hrs of library duty..once i finish and once i go for the library camp..i can quit library le..yeah. actually being a librarian not that bad lar..but hor its damn sian and must haf alot of time to do those dumb dumb duties..heeS. by the way i got ava, scouts and house com...so busy t's why must quit library lor...=). oh yup we had delta house com bbq at wan li's house on wednesday..her house is one of the semi d along meyer road. her house so white and got bamboo summore..such a pure and tranquil place..hees..tx wan li for letting us have bbq at ur hse and scaring all ur neighbours away.lolx. haas..everyone had fun lar..haas..eating and playing and of coz  TAKING FOTOS ..oh i've upload sum fotos le,can go take a look.  http://sg.f2.pg.photos.yahoo.com/ph/bear_xiangz/album?.dir=/b9ea     my seniors were all so crazy esp de gals coz sou yin's camera can take a foto wif 2 person kissing..but that 2 person no need to kiss de...u just hafta take one person kissing(facing de right)..and then take another foto of another person kissing(facing de left)..den combine it together..haas..sound so interesting. we left at abt 10 plus and i went home wif rachelle (serangoon gang)...lolx...and kena suan by all the house com ppl lar..*expected*  charlene =)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ah...chio bu..haas.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *sobx*.....i'm realli touched by this msg~~tsz ching u r realli a great sister..   *bEar: dun wan jie to worry abt u, then u better better better take care of yrself LOTs kayx!!! Jie will always be here 4 u derx!!! =) yeP. sAdnEss always find its way back to us, but we mus all stay strong to fight it away. will miss u LOTS LOTS when u're leaving 4 yr jumboree!!! still cannot watch twins effect 2 wif u.. the most i wait 4 u!!! =pPppp     &nbsp;  anyways...i let my mum noe my results den in the end kena scolded like hell..den now must go tuition..must go yum cha wif principal..haix. i die die also wun quit scout de...its becoz of scouts...dat i've learned alot...it's becoz of scouts...dat i've made alot of fwens..once a scouts always a scouts. life is tough ahead..and now i dun feel like going for korea jam..scared i cannot catch up..hmm.     &nbsp;  the street festival at tjc: de response so far is still average..haas...sumtimes the ppl just eat at the canteen and dun see ther performances but i think the 2 songs that the saxophone section frm tj band played was damn power lar...esp  can you feel the love tonight ...haas...de other song was  i want to hold your hand . de chinese cultural club performance was the best i guess..coz alot of ppl were attracted to it..and it was very farnie..lolx.    &nbsp;  on the serious note...wan lin thx for ur concern the other day...i guess i'm fine for now...dun worry abt me lar brother..oops..haas. eh...letitia waiting for ur reply..lolx..try to reply her asap...thx lots...thx to all those hu showered ur care n concern..bleahs..haas..jie, wan lin, qing yu, jason, sou yin, ee ling, shao hao...and more lar..yupx..realli i appreciate it.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       wat the hell..ok i actually type finish this post le..and my computer hang..and now i hafta type it out again..it just pissed me off..anyway happie bday to xue zhen...i jsut came back from delta hse bbq..and i spend the whole evening after sch doing the banner for racial harmony day wif the gamma hse peeps...i din actually paint much..but i went to tie the bamboo poles..anyway de bbq was still ok lar..at least still got ppl come..those much more enthu de lar..haas..and must thx the ava for their service..and of coz to my class peeps...gen ming, zhi mian, qing yu, jie yi, owen, ling yi n quan ming&nbsp;for coming...haas..at least u guys came..lolx. nowadays when i see ms lee i just find it abit stress lor.dunno why lar..bt i just got this feeling. the weather this few days keep raining....moody weather...i also realli dun haf the mood lor..sumtimes i am realli lost and confused and just realli dunno wat i;m doing lor....sumtimes i just wanna give up lor..i got scouts stuff...pdps...house com..so many stuffs to do and i'm really trying to study lor...it's realli a challenge to me in handling so many stuffs...i sumtimes just feel realli sad lar dat i din performed well...and i sumtimes realli haf no passion, purpose or drive in doing anything lor..project work is like so messy and so shit lor. i dun even haf the 3 basic tjc mottoin me..passion, purpose, drive..de sad feelings comes and goes off..everynow and then...i just feel like crying lar and i just want some pEace..       where is luv and humanity...life can be easy but it can get&nbsp;damn tough lar...until&nbsp;u haf lost confidence in everything...but that's not the end...life can be beautiful...but when there are happiness and depression...the beauty is just an illusion...friends out there hu care for me..thx alot...u realli haf the heart..and i realli appreciate it. thx alotx...jie&nbsp;u no need worry abt me..i guess..life still hafta go on...       &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh...stress sia, ms lee say wanna see me and talk to me..hmm means nuttin gd lar..coz i din do well for jct mar. oh.neway..the background music might be familiar to those a lvl chinese student hu took chinese listening..haas..this song was played on symphony 92.4fm...before the listening started..tis is one of the few songs lar..haas. the song is you raised me up by secret garden. joshn groban also resang the song..yupx..tt's all for that...i introduce u guys to this instrumental piece called..."merry christmas, mr lawrence"..nice music piece...check it out. ahh..i still hafta do so many things for the racial harmony things..hmm..abit rushed lor..coz gamma hse gals thought it was nxt nxt wk..but the racial harmony and street festival is nxt week lor...liux..den now so gan3...haix. sou yin, shao hao like very normal towards failing jct..haas..they find it very common..no wonder its caled COMMON test..ok not farnie...anyway, thx for those encouragement sou yin, shao hao..ee ling..yupx..but i think i still need time to settle down...it sounds as though its so glorious failing lor..bleahs...~u all like so relax even though u all failed..haas..pei fu ah...2 more months to prelims leh..u guys must jia you kies..and of coz the yr 2 peeps lor. i find that tjc is realli very mug lar...now i go everywhere also see ppl mug..the impact of jct is that big lor..now everyone is mugging...every minute, every second...eEEe..and letitia ah..haas..dun worry abt me lar..i'll jia you de..u also jia you yar, and hope that u can get ur reply frm wan lin soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           haas...florachan's acting not bad...i like the show that she acted in triump in the skies..lolx..channel u is now showing burning flame 2 mar.     ..i still prefer burning flame 1 lar..but i like the small gal..yao yao(jenny shing)..she so cute in de show..lolx. my mum just finished watching Hard Fate..not bad lar..also flora chan act de..haas.      haaas...nice nice..de gal and guy is a great couple lor..so pei4..haas..the guy so yandao..gal so chio..
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Arlows peeps..twins new album is out.    the new album is called girl power..i managed to get the album thru the fan club..coz that stupid youth idols closed down le..wth sia..neways, their new album is abit more different..less of the love songs, but more of those upbeat songs..and raps. there is one a few slow songs like "shou zhi you kui", "diu jia", "pai zhu shang"...i luv diu jia alot..its so nice  丢架 Sa: 咖啡杯都企不稳 我忍 只知不想我伤心 你要小心 临别亦要那么恨 语带兴奋 什么他真比我衬 觉得不应该再等  Gil: 傻女 为何要苦笑 明明我可以大叫 架己丢 或者就快不能了  Twins: 我的身心崩溃了 Sa: 终于我哭了 不必坐通宵 或者当初你只贪我喜欢笑 你我早已失去这需要  Gil: 当街痛哭了 不好意思打扰 或者应该亲口请你快走了 好走了 让我知道我们完了  Gil: 小心摸真你的手 你知 大家相识那么久 我哪知丑 宁愿拨去你的手 怕你一踫 十打纸巾不会够 泪一点出不会收  Sa: 谁管 凌晨眼肿了会怪我的气量窄 福气小 大癫大肺玩完了 甚至化妆都不要  Gil: 好彩我哭了 不必坐通宵 或者当初你只贪我喜欢笑 你我早已失去这需要  Sa: 当街痛哭了 不好意思打扰 或者应该亲口请你快走了 好走了 让我知道我们完了  Let it flow Let it flow I can't control So let it flow Let it flow Let it flow I lost my soul So i'll let it go  Twins: 好彩我哭了 不必坐通宵 或者  Sa: 当初你只贪我喜欢笑 你我早已失去这需要  Twins: 当街痛哭了 不好意思打扰 或者  Gil: 应该亲口请你快走了 好走了 让我知道我们完了   haas..oh yah..about the background music..haas.its força by nelly furtado. the meaning of the song means forward...in euro 2004 u can hear the music..força portugal meaning forward portugal..yupx. thats wat i noe lar. hmm..ok my jct was like so bad that i din actually pass any subject except for chinese lar..i left GP and econs haben get back lor. haix..never study enuf i guess and the paper was damn difficult and couldn't really finish the paper. now physics teacher change frm mr lim to ms choo..aiyohx..like shit lor..that ms choo sia, fresh graduate frm nus studying  PURE  physics..den she come and confuse us wif her  PURE  physics knowledge...oops lets hope that she dun get to see this lar. anyways..congrats to olivia for becoming the pres for ccms pupil council..and hui ying for becoming the secretary...these 2 section 4 peeps gt into PCEC..!!omg~haas..wat can i say...i owe u guys pizza hut lor..haas. yesterday i went to see NDP 3rd combined rehearsal..jason gave me 5 tix..so i ask jing yi to come..den she ask edric, emma, yeow sheng and wai seng..but in the end..edric and jng yi turned up. i waited for them..and went to get the tix frm jason and happen to see jie and the other YA..guess they having a debrief..haas. then later edric came, followed by jing yi and we were like abit sian..coz the rehearsal alot of mistakes de..haas..and there is this fat indian man(oops)...hu replace President S R Nathan...wth..and even the car he sat is not mercedes but an old toyota car..haas..wat can u expect....rehearsal lehx..but i like the part where the SCDF ppl did the traditional flying fox..and the commandos abseiling down from the grandstand..woah, they r damn sEH..after the parade(which was the onli interesting thing)..we went off..haas...buay tahan..den i went to find jason and took the chartered bus wif the ndp scouts to kallang mrt..den i decide nt to go ngee ann cf le coz so late le..den took mrt to bishan j8..go eat..coz bery hungry..yupx...back to today..i went to woodlands regional library to do research for PW...de research materials dere are quite gd...got the statistics..but not easy to find lar..and the old newspaper are all in the form of microfilms..and u hafta view if with the machine..which is occupied lar..dats why i din go and see..only photocopied some statistics..which i took quite a long time to find....hmm looks like jie have sum probs wif this irritating peep..haas.   33 more days to athens 2004 olympics games  de mascots look abit farnie  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       oh..just back from first aid course. i now every tuesday and thursday nite frm 6:30 to 9:30 gt first aid course at st john hq..today is the second lesson and we r learning CPR. today this guy called Mr Daniel, damn experience and of coz old lar..he come and explain all the first aid stuff and teach us everything..better than our lecturer Mdm How sia..haas..ok i've learn to firstly.. Danger :check for danger ard u..next  Response : pat or shake the person on the shoulder and ask..are u ok..can u hear me?...lolx..den can shout for help..dial 995 for the ambulance..and stuff liddat.  D anger  R esponse  A irway  B reathing  C irculation...haas..and when u confirm that there is no breathing and no pulse..do the  C ardio  P ulmonary  R esuscitation..haas..15 compressions, 2 breathe...4cycles..lolx. ok that's all for today. eRm...let's not talk abt jct..maybe if i'm feeling better than i'll talk abt it. anyways, today mr chin showed us spirited away during gp lesson at the com lab   de movie is so nice too bad we neva finished it coz 2 periods of 50 mins wasn't enuf to finish de show..haas...oh yesterday was a levels oral and i was like so nervous for the reading that i couldn't pronounce the words properly..conversation topic was easy lar...the question is "if u had problem hu would u approach to speak out all the problems.." yupx..and this saturday is a levels listening sia 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Twins - 眼红红   Sa: 仍然怀念他 一起去学吉他  一对黑眼圈 回望中三暑假  以后我都无掂过个结他  至于暑假…..  为求发泄出一切 流眼泪亦无它   Gill: 人人谈论我 将我当做笑话  因我失去他 宁愿天天请假  不过点都好过隔离班个同学ar  告左假之后 就无返过黎la  但能够接触恋爱 亦已赚到些牵挂   Chorus Sa: 我最初面红 现在双眼通红  再幼稚还是觉得恋爱如梦  Gill: 我再不面红 但愿不再冲动  爱到入城大也分开 预计之中  Twins: 然而我越说越激动  Sa: 这失恋感觉怎形容  初恋难忘 初次心痛  Gill: 拿着旧日合照 想起我在撒他娇  我得到的礼物都不算少   Gill: 仍然无电话 等于告别了吗  Sa: 初次感觉到 期待多么可怕 原来好恨得到一样野系咁辛苦嫁  Gill: 不过有得恨总好过无得恨  Twins: 但能够与他好过 别要动气责怪他  Chorus Sa: 我最初面红 现在双眼通红  再幼稚还是觉得恋爱如梦  Gill: 我再不面红 但愿不再冲动  爱到入城大也分开 预计之中  Twins: 然而我越说越激动  Gill: 这失恋感觉怎形容  初恋难忘 初次心痛  Sa: 拿着旧日合照 想起我在撒他娇  也许今天以为哭得太少   Gill: 但始终有日想起也都  Sa: 有一天会为这首插曲  Twins: 可笑/微笑
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haas..i was talking to kalyn, my angel just now and she remind me abt the yes 933 音乐日记 cd that she owe me..haas, lolx.i nearly forgot abt it lor. hmm dat cd is very nice..both 音乐日记 1 and 音乐日记 2..nice~now 音乐日记 is every weekdays at 2200hrs i think..still hosted by 灵芝..but i seldom listen le. last time i everytime listen to ufm 1003 coz gt 君伟..he's a gd dj..but he left ufm le to pursue other things..haas...den i'll also listen to 玛莉 on yes 933...~she also quite farnie de. 音乐日记 intro... 那时我们被困在路边 世界不过是一个小小屋檐  你说如果雨一直下到明天 我们就厮守到永远 ... 我喜欢打篮球的你，我喜欢会发呆的你，我喜欢弹吉他的你，我喜欢骂我无聊的你，我喜欢咬指甲的你，我喜欢在电话傻笑得你，我喜欢常搞笑的你，我喜欢犹豫不决的你，我喜欢试穿牛仔裤五次的你，我喜欢听我牢骚的你，我喜欢这么多这么多的你，你又会把我放在你心中的拿里呢?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gill: 又见了"我的宠爱" 谁愿接受这种意外 你赞我天生可爱 不愿看着我离开  Sa: 同伴也话我傻 喜欢受挫 宁愿情敌在伤我  Twins: 人天生根本都不可以爱死身边的一个 怎奈你最够刺激我 凡事也治到倒我 几多黑心的教唆 我亦捱得过 来煽风来点火 就击倒我么  Sa: 点解要咁姐  Gill: 点解唔可以咁呀  Sa: 你唔觉得好辛苦咩  Gill: 辛苦 但系我钟意呀  Sa: 算吧啦   Steven：我怕可一不可再 难道你被爱都有害 Kenny: 我确信天真不会错 威力会移山填海  Boy'z：同伴也话我傻 喜欢受挫 宁愿情敌再伤我  Boy'z: 人天生根本都不可以 爱死身边的一个 怎奈你最够刺激我 凡事也治到我 几多黑心的教唆 我亦捱得过 来煽风来点火 就击倒我么 谁恋爱就多障碍 死性我不想改 如我没有你的爱 我没法活得来 情人的存在 是我从来都志在 难在我拱手让爱  Boy'z & Twins: 人天生根本都不可以爱死身边的一个 怎奈你最够刺激我 凡事也治到倒我 几多黑心的教唆 我亦捱得过 来煽风来点火 就击倒我么     
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haas...today..eh oops..i mean yesterday, sunday..i went to met up wif owen to get the topo map..den went to meet albert wif weiliang,keat meng and houston to plan the monster camp during september. the camp is suppose to be so damn fun sia..haas..we were all thinking about farnie ideas and activity. the camp would be frm 4 sept to 6 sept and since jason never come for meeting becoz of ndp..haas..we decided to let him go to the tao nan p4 camp briefing on 4 sept..the first day of camp. hmm..we were meeting at starbucks...brainstorming..when wan lin and james came to pass me the topo map...haas...now got 2 topo map so dun need worry le. albert then started toking to james and wan lin while we did our planning. den james left halfway and albert the "chatting ultrman" continued toking and we were already under mental stress le coz cannot tink of much activities..till abt 7 plus..we went to burger king to have our dinner..and continue to plan until 10 plus..haas..pHew..finally we finished. we gave albert and made some changes wif the presence and sum suggestions frm wan lin..lolx. anyways  thx  to de marlin for coming down to give us the topo map..we'll sure return.. confirm + gurantee + chop . okiex..den we finished everything abt 10 plus and go home lor. reached home first thing..mum nag and nag say i too involved in scouts..bleahs..haas, must chiong for at least venture cord mar..she ask me put more effort in my studies..hmm...aiyah..i live a scouting life...lolx..must be  street smart  not  study smart  sia...like lester. hmm must go zZzZ coz me,weiliang and jason going to recce for our hike w/ the 2 topo maps at 1000hrs..while that keat meng go enjoy himself at sentosa..wth sia 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       oh..yEsh, jct finally over le. finally can take a rest..but actually i guessed i have been resting all the way..lolx. like no jct liddat leh..hmm. dun wanna tok abt it le lar..so stress sia, but ms lee ask us to enjoy while we can..haas. after jct means back to scouts stuff and house com stuffs. de september scouts camp badge is already out le..just dat i hafta contact leslie coz i think he wana advise me on some changes yupx.and i'm still working on the house com t-shirt..haas..no ideas sia. haas..oh hannah, rachel and deborah left singapore for USA le..hmm i'll miss my 3 little cousins..but they will be back nxt yr..lolx. haas..hao hao kor kor and deborah..lolx. oh..we had meeting today at tao nan this morning..for the p4 camp. haas..we'll be glad to help dem lar since dey ask us to help. it was a short meeting lar..and i dun see that stupid marcius around again..he like nt enthu sia...haas. anyways..we went to play pool after that until abt 3 plus..and den weiliang went to meet houston at st john hq to sign up de first aid course..but in the end it was close..lolx.haix..den me,keat meng and jason took 15 to pasir ris interchange and we met weiliang dere...but..when we reached downtown east..it was raining. so we walked in wif 2 umbrellas, 2 person to 1..den along the way..dinesh happen to saw us..so he fetched us lor..haas..our  GOD  sia. oh den we hang around the chalet frm 5 and suppose to leave at 6 but we decided to wait for yuan ching girl scouts and of coz marlin ventures to come..den we go. but in the end we took a few fotos..chat for a while..eat and left..haas. 5 of us rush down to east coast park in a cab...and go for scouts and guides pop bbq..din expect kelvin to come..long time no c him le..nt to say ming en & lester sia..haas. the bbq was abit sian lar..haas.coz of the juniors..haas..onli left us ex-seniors siting dere..toking..and haas..we threw keat meng and justin into the sea..yAy!..haas..yAwnx..gtg..slp ZzZ..rest early peeps 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      七里香  七里香  詞：方文山 曲：周杰倫   窗外的麻雀 在電線桿上多嘴  妳說這一句 很有夏天的感覺  手中的鉛筆 在紙上來來回回  我用幾行字形容妳是我的誰   秋刀魚 的滋味 貓跟妳都想了解  初戀的香味就這樣被我們尋回  那溫暖 的陽光 像剛摘的鮮豔草莓  你說妳捨不得吃掉這一種感覺   雨下整夜 我的愛溢出就像雨水  院子落葉 跟我的思念厚厚一疊  幾句是非 也無法將我的熱情冷卻  妳出現在我詩的每一頁   雨下整夜 我的愛溢出就像雨水  窗台蝴蝶 像詩裡紛飛的美麗章節  我接著寫 把永遠愛妳寫進詩的結尾  妳是我唯一想要的了解   那飽滿 的稻穗 幸福了這個季節  而妳的臉頰像田裡熟透的蕃茄  妳突然 對我說 七里香的名字很美  我此刻卻只想親吻妳倔強的嘴  haas..jay chou's new song..qi li xiang, nt bad lar..lolx
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      江南  曲：林俊杰 | 词：李瑞洵 | 编：   风到这里就是黏 黏住过客的思念 雨到了这里缠成线 缠着我们流连人世间  你在身边就是缘 缘份写在三生石上面 爱有万分之一甜 宁愿我就葬在这一点  圈圈圆圆圈圈 天天年年天天 的我 深深看你的脸 生气的温柔 埋怨的温柔 的脸  不懂爱恨情愁煎熬的我们 都以为相爱就像风云的善变 相信爱一天 抵过永远 在这一剎那冻结了时间  不懂怎么表现温柔的我们 还以为殉情只是古老的传言 离愁能有多痛 痛有多浓 当梦被埋在江南烟雨中 心碎了才懂    this song realli rox...i luv it lolx..there is even a bk that is written base on this song, the author was inspired by his song to write the bk also called 江南..
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okok..let me see,actually i dunno wat's the problem with the term HC. Isn't that term HC means House Comm, den why do some ppl still insist on saying its hannah cheong...omG!for god sake,i just treat her as a fwen lar..those hu noe me well would noe that i onli like sumone, and till now i still like her, so why would i like HC..i mean hannah cheong..lolx. Kok Wei enuf of this crap if not i would always show u the scout salute..and of coz i'll ask u to read b/w the fingers..(oops, BP pls forgive me for such dirty thoughts...a scout must be clean in thought and word and deed..i guess i haben reached that yet). anyway dudes it has been long since iupdate my blog coz i've been doing tutorials ahead esp for maths..and preparing for the korea jamboree trip. i'll be leaving tml..eh no today..haas coz its 0020hrs now..haas..yupx..i'm leaving at 2335hrs...but will be reaching the airport at terminal 1. jay chou's album is released today..haas..haben went to collect the CD that i pre-ordered..anyways jie i'll miss u like hell when i go to korea de, and for kok wei thx for helping me take down the notes when i'm away..i'll need to consult u when i'm back frm korea, if nt i can also consult boss or bosstress...muahahaha...and for ms lee..eh r u hinting me to buy korea ginseng mask..i tink ur facial condition already quite gd le..no need any ginseng..maybe ginseng hair removal..woah..eh just jokin lar..ms lee is a very nice CT honestly..lets hope she wun get to see this. oh yah..recently i guess our class habinng a war..nt the whole class but i guess it involves the gals and liling..ALC..tsk tsk. i gt no comments actually just that i understand she's kinda irritating..tt's wat i heard frm 0804 gals too..but when sumone of the same sex does not wanna tok to her or does not really befriend her..den her life would be miserable. If someone acts nice to u infront of u..and stabs u in the back..wouldn't that be a terrible feeling? i guess so..haas..lets hope that when the rain's over...the skies would be clear..lolx wat shit. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>