<Blog>


<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am a twenty-something male with a high school education.  I tend to think I am smarter than minimal amount of years in school and without sounding arrogant most people think so, too.  Although, I would have to say that the old adage "Wisdom is knowing what to do next and virtue is doing it" doesn't apply to me.  The later is what I have a problem with.  I tend to have a problem with finishing what I start.    So, here is my first step to recovery or one might say it's my path to enlightenment.  Within the next few monthes I plan to inform, anyone who is reading, about my daily trails and tribulations.    I also plan to make a history of my up bringing in Ohio all the way to date.  This may be a difficult task due to the fact I have blocked out or forgotten a lot about my past.  I can only explain this by saying that my move from Ohio to Texas was quite tramatic to me mentally, somehow.  There has also been some great loves of my so called life lost in the process and one of my motto's has been "it's easier to forget than to remember."  I guess you could say "I haven't got time for the pain."     
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was born in Kettering, Ohio.  My mother was still a child when I was born, only 18 years of age, and would remain a child at heart for the rest of her life.  Mom was great and the center of my growing world.  She always took good care of us children.  Mom wasn't too strict with rules, allowing us to go outside and get dirty, maybe track a little on the carpet but we were never the dirty kids or the runny nose kids, ear wax kids, hungary kids, raggedy clothed kids or any other little childhood dirty kid thing you could think of.  Nor was our house, She keeps everything that is her's in good order and clean.    She is also the greatest cook in the world, I don't care how good of a cook you think you are or your momma is, this woman cooks it better.  My Momma was a descendant of Jesus Christ himself because I don't know anyone else that can take salt and water, then turn it into a feast.  No lie.  None.  Just like Jesus can feed a hole soup kitchen with one fish and a loaf of bread, my mom can do that with salt and water.   She was a looker and still is.  Blonde hair, five foot nothing, funny as hell and the life of any get together.  She always calls it like it is, never cared if it hurt your feelings (unless it was her children, then she would put sugar on top) or if you didn't want to hear it, you always know what she thought.  Growing up, my friends would seldom make MILF remarks to me about my mother and would be the likely cause of my future therapy bills.  It's not her fault I guess, I should blame my grandparents or something, hell, they had her.  The last thing I would like to say about her is more like a warning for those that don't know her, she is a lot of laughs but you don't never, ever, ever lose your damn mind and talk back to that five foot tall woman with an eight foot tall back hand.  I swear it will strike you down like bolt of lightning from the heavens. (I think she played tennis in a former life.)  My father was 21 when I was born.  He's not very tall man himself and I've seen pictures of him thin when he was young but I sure don't recall those days.  I would guess that's due to his sworn diet of meat and potatoes.  My mother said and I quote "all he ever wanted to eat was hamburger and french fries."  This diet has brought about some bouts with heart problems but he still keeps kicking like the fighter he is.    My father is a very passive man, he would rather turn the other cheek than strike a fowl blow.  Allowing my mother to be the aggressor when came time to discipline.  His face has always seemed about ten years older than he was, as far back as I can remember.  He always has a good joke every time you talk to him and has a smile that would make a stranger feel welcome, he seems to go through life with a reserve that nothing is ever too bad.  When your down for the count and your waiting for the straw that going to break the camel's back, my father could make you feel better in one sentence.  My father has often worked two jobs to make ends meet but could never get ahead.  I can say that life has not layed a golden path for him but he takes it in stride.  He is a good father and man.  My mother and father had one other child before I came along, my older ogre...I mean brother, Darrell.  The oldest of eight children born to this family he had to assume the role of a leader.  He is almost the spitting image of my old man but has my mother's zest for life.  Darrell can find fun in almost any circumstance and, somehow despite his mild weight problem that plagues our family, is a natural Don Juan.  I can only say that it must be his rapist wit or maybe his keen sense for timing a ruffy deposit which makes him appealing.  He is very persuasive in any conversation and naturally intelligent which makes him a very tough competitor in any competition he enters.  He is calculating in his actions and every move seems to be made only after he has weighed the precise pros and cons of every situation.  Although we have had our differences over the years, when it comes down to it, he would be the only person I would gladly follow to oblivion.  I have always seen him as a great army general in likes of the astonishing Patton himself.        Most of our childhood was spent in or around Kettering, Ohio where my grandfather was a police officer.  I don't remember my parents ever being together because I was barely walking when they split.  My memory starts at about three years old.  We lived with my Mother and a guy named Brian.  Our neighbors was this couple named Bill and Pat which were totally cool and still to this day we refer to them as Uncle Bill and Aunt Pat.   Brian was a prematurely balding blonde asshole who had no kids so naturally he wasn't very patient when it came to us.  He never layed a hand on Darrell or I but just seemed to be forceful.  That's about all I remember of him.   Aunt Pat was a beautiful blonde with hair so long she had no problem sitting on it.  It was so blonde that it would shine and become almost a golden glare in the sun.  She was also thin and had a smile that lit up a room.  She always, always seemed very happy to see Darrell and I. Aunt Pat would quickly lean down, face to face with us, stare us in the eye with her blue eyed gaze and smile, then pinch your cheek like a grandmother who hasn't seen you since last Christmas.  You couldn't help but blush because even as a little boy her beauty was evident and the feeling of embarrassment inside for having a crush on Aunt Pat.      Uncle Bill was tall thin man who was the ruggedly handsome man that every chick seemed to want in the early eighties.  He had a huge fluffy, brown mustache on top his lips and when he would he let out his deep rubbling laugh it looked like it was going to jump off his face.  He was also in a band and some nights we'd watch them in their basement as they all partied down.  They did a renditions of "Cat Scatch fever" and "Free for All" by Ted Nuggent that were just like you were standing center-stage front row at his concert.  It took us a few years to figure out that it wasn't Uncle Bill from next door singing on the radio.  During one of the many band rehearsals was the first time I got to taste of what the big dogs drank, beer that is, the big boys drink, Schlitz to be exact, and it tasted like schlit.    One night at one of these parties Darrell and I were upstairs playing darts, mind you they didn't have the plastic dart machines back then.  While retrieving my set of darts my brother decided he was going to play through without the courteous shout of "FOUR!" and wouldn't you know the bastard nailed me right in the knee cap all the way to the bone.  (Crappy shooting if you ask me, I think at 4 I could have at least got an eye!)  Anyways, I started to cry from shear shock and funny thing is I don't remember it hurting very much.  Darrell did the nice big brotherly thing and said "quit crying you get us in trouble" which I did.  Darrell then pinned my shoulder to wall with one hand and with the other reached down grasped the dart.  I couldn't over power the bully he was and in just a split second he jerked the dart right out my knee.  Blood streamed from my wound like a water spicket.  Darrell being the brains of the bunch got me a towel and stopped the hemorrhaging before my doom was met through blood letting. What a hero. (Funny thing though, cause now he's a EMT now.  I'd say it's a his subconscious way of dealing with his guilt of the dart to the knee.)  Things seemed to go alright there and we had a few other good times, like playing doctor with Wendy from across the street behind our house under the giant pine tree, but what did I know.  We lived with Brian until Darrell was in school and I was in pre-school.   After Mom split from Brian we lived here and there for awhile and you could tell that it bothered my Mother because she didn't seem so happy go lucky.  We didn't mind the moving and as children with attention spans not long enough to watch one commercial without dancing the jig, we didn't mind the change in scenery.  Then came the day it happened. While we were rooming with friends of my mother's, Darrell came out of a room in which my Mother was in and said nonchalantly she wanted to talk to me.  I hopped up and went to go see what was up.  Mom was lying on the waterbed and the dark to conceal the fact that she was crying.  ( As an adult with children I can now understand why the room was dark because I've found that composure in front of your children is very important).  She asked in an audible whisper "Do you want to go live with your Dad?" trying to hold back the sorrow in her voice.  "Is Darrell going?" I asked, oblivious to what this question really addressed.  With the frustration from the heavy sadness in her heart and choking to fight tears she said "I'm asking YOU, if you want to go live with your dad."   Feeling the tension in my mother's voice "Yes?" I replied hoping it would be the right answer and subside her sorrow.  "Okay...He'll be here soon to get you" she said with a crack in her voice.  Filled with need to know and a feeling of dread that I was being cast away from my mother and brother, I asked again "Is Darrell going?"  "Yes" she replied as she rolled over to face the wall.  I turned and left the room with a feeling of uncertainty.  I was happy my dad was coming to get me but I was wondering if I would see mom again, soon.  Was this permanent?  Why can't we live with her anymore.  Then I realized...I didn't know my dad that well..."Well, as long as my brother's going with me," I thought.      
     
    
</post>


</Blog>