<Blog>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        woke up like 5.40am. yawnz~~~. brought a trolley bag n a sling bag 2 school. quite heavy. i was wif wui shing n the WU3 DAO3 gang [jiamin, cheryl n all those gals]n edison n wen long. turned out b quite a nice bus ride. along da way, most ppl were sleepin.then my bus was lost some where in malacca when lookin 4 da restraunt. turned round n round.  lunch was weird. fish.some of da guyz complained  then somewhere in malacca, the bus stopped at some convention center. went inside n bought lots of sweets n chocos. LOL. i also bought a watch. BEBY-G [fake one] for RM 9.90. yanyu n fengyi bought matching watches. quite nice-looking. hen3 you3 nv3 ren2 wei4. quite cute. jiamin bought balloons. so huge.  then there was sightseeing in malacca. did not listen 2 da guide. was wandering around. after that was SHOPPING! mahkota was huge. bought lotsa chewing gum. also bought me supper[KFC]. then i was so crazy 2 buy graph paper.LOL.  dinner sucked.  went 2 jonker street. bought some aroma candles. quite nice. at da hotel [finally!], i went 2 wenlong + edison's room. cheryl n qianwei were there. zhidong n wui shing came along. we watched PORTO VS MONACO 3-0. not live though. quite fun. at level 9, the WU3 DAO3 gang was there. yanling was doing a dare. she was supposed 2 sae to zhidong. DO U WANT ROOM SERVICE. totally LAME. lol.  b4 12am, went to some gals room to watch movie. that fat little boy from shaolin. so cute. laughed so hard. slept like 12.30am.    woke up like 6am. went 4 breakfast. after that more sightseeing at some temple. quite hot. more visiting. got warmer. some of da guyz bought flowery shirts. so GAY! actually, it looks quite good on them.HAHAHAHA! lunch at some restraunt. after thaT , I WENT  to tan kim hock, bought some food. lke 33 ringgit.  5pm was time 4 dinner. so early. so much chicken, i like it. but i ate too much till i could eat no more. then it was time 4 home. arghz~~
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yo, my 1st blog. Todae, i m quite happy. got back report book. 82.3, that's the score. actually should b lower... 2mr i'm going 2 malacca, muz wake up real early. >. 

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      nothing much realli happened. juz that me uncle passed away [he was a good man] n i went 2 NUS for some crazy camp. hahx, i luv NUS. still got homework not done. shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      todae, i went 2 toa payoh library 2 do CIP. then 9am i reached. met da person-in-charge then got down 2 bizness. some admin work. actualli not even admin work. i tidied up d place, typed some stuff n sort out some papers n removed some staples. liddat work n work. till like 4.40pm. haha. get 8 hrs liao. 2mr vicki joinin me.more fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yesterdae, i was in school takin part in da maths olmpiad thingy. representing 2f. anewae, da questions so tough man! actually it's worse than tough. it's mind-boggling. maybe worse. out of 35 questions like i noe onli 12.... or less. ken3 ding4 participation. arghzz. i mean so tough. some juz write in some stupid answer like 15806 or 3056 that kind. here's a simple one. 110,156,210,272,___,420. fill in da blank. actually quite simple. 110=10x11, 156=12x13, so da blank is 18x19 which is 342. geddit?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i m not a buddihst so i dun celebrate vesak dae. this afternoon, me folks brought me 2 suntec to eat lunch. [1st in class] Fish n company....quite good i shld sae. then at nite me dad bought himself a new phone. quite sleek. so he givin his old phone 2 me mum. me mum givin me her NOKIA 6610. hey heyz. me new number is 93588542.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      o no, i m neglecting m blog. arghz~~. anyway today's a boring day, staying @ home 2 study 4 chinese test n do me art. sighz~~. din watch euro finals. heard it was greece dat won. last nite me went 2 some wedding dinner. then de bride is lissy (ok name), den da groom is vivian (tot is gal's name?). den surprisingly met kaikeng. dunno y he was dere. hahax
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       oh man...neglected my blog 4 a long time ....oops, should pay more attention today 6th august is wilber pan's bdae[he rawks] n 2moro is zhang shanwei's bdae n de coolplay concert. i wanna go man!  today in dunman is like celebration...de whole hall was like mad...den got screamin n dancing n havoc. den 2f went 2 sing WE WILL GET THERE. i actualli tot it was pretty gd. but in d end it was 2k n 2b who won.  sob*  i m lookin forward 2 de longweekenddddddddddddddddddddd. can sleep more n no school. :D 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>