<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is what me and Mike found today before we went to the shed.   urlLink Yeah those are spiders  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so he's the story up to this point:  Graduate HS, went to WPI, transfered to Bryant College, Graduated Bryant College.  Other than that you'll need to know i live on Long Island (most boring place ever) and amd looking for a job or scam or something to make me money. This blog however is just so i can get a Gmail account. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So i got the gmail account i've been looking for (props to Matt for that) and now that i have invitiations they are going for crap on ebay. oh well. at least i got the ill gmail name. Not that i'll post it here but if you need to know it you will. in other news i power washed the deck and the porch. it took me a while but they both look alot better. i forgot to take pictures of the back deck (which was really nasty) but i got some of the front deck. they may show up on the website if i'm really bored. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so I'm back to buying, selling, fixing and/or renting houses. I got the 7 day trial membership to the  urlLink bargain network . I started looking around and saw quite a few interesting properties. I also saw a link to be Pr-Qualified for a mortgage. So I applied for that as well and within 20 minutes the phone rings. They called to find out some additional information so I talked with the woman for a little while and found out my credit score (711). It's kinda like finding out my IQ: I mean I knew it was good but I didn't think it was that good. Anyway they want to make sure I have enough money for a down payment before they can approve me.   What I'd really like to do right now is pick 1 more area to look into. Right now I'd like to find something either outside Boston or in troy. I'd like to find something a lithe more moderate. I mean Troy is gone be mad cheap because of the area but has college students to rent so that's a big plus. Boston is going to just keep growing so whatever I get there will continue to increase in value the way LIE has been doing. I'd like to find a nice area in western Massachusetts, or southern VT or NH. Then compare the 3 to see what's the best option.  Also I'd like to go to visit Matt to checkout some places in troy. And visit Michele to checkout places outside Boston. It'll probably be one big trip. I'm trying to work out some plans but it should be in the next week or two. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So last night Mike and I rearranged the whole basement. I also got rid of the big screen that didn't work. As for cleaning... Well that's a different story all together. For the most part we moved all the tables with the stuff that was already on them so the mess got rearranged also.  I setup my camera so it would take a picture every 5 minutes so you can see the whole process.  urlLink Pictures are here   And this is the final result:  urlLink TV side   urlLink Office side  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It looks like GTA has made the transition from a video game to the real world.  urlLink  Just check this out   Authorities detonated three explosions and fired at least 200 rounds against the heavy steel plates welded to the bulldozer  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so Craig asked me about this today so I figure it's another thing worth writing about. So here is how it works: you run this script and it goes to a list of porn sites with free sample videos. It goes to the links and downloads any movies it finds and saves it to a directory. Then you can sit back and watch it without bothering with clicking, downloading, popups, etc. If that wasn't good enough it downloads about 2 gigs of videos each hour you run it.   The catch? Well it downloads every movie it finds. So yeah you'll get some good stuff but you'll also get the gross, the wrong and the weird. My solution is to search the downloaded movies for keywords (like tran, gay, men, hentai, mature, old).  Here is the simple 3 step plan to free porno:  Step 1: urlLink  download the newest version of python   Step 2: urlLink  download this script   Step 3: Open the script in Wordpad and edit the line that starts with  "destdir ="  to point to where you want the files to download.  (note: make sure you have the folder made cause this script wont create it for you).   after that's done all you have to do is double click on it and it'll start downloading. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok so i'm basicly in charge of my dad's books for his company. It's good that i'm getting experiance with starting a business before i do it myself. this shit seems like it's gonna be a pain in my ass. but once i learn it once i think i'll be in much better shape. I'd still like to do the house thing but i dont think that can be my only job. i have to look into lost freight auctions in the area. those and auctions from public storage units. i dont know if i'll get anything good but pretty much everything is ebay-able.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I went wine tasting with Michele today. It was a really good time and now I have a list of places which give free wine tasting. After the trip was done I was pretty messed up. I've gotta do it again soon maybe before a ferry trip.  Each Winery will do things differently but you'll encounter one of these 3 things: 1) Some places charge you a small fee (anywhere from $3 to $8) and you get to taste a set list of wines 2) Other places will charge you per wine you want to taste. Anywhere from (50 cents to 4 bucks) 3) other places where you can to try whatever you want for free (these are my favorite)  There is a map you can pick up at any winery which has phone numbers and locations of all the vineyard so you can call ahead and plan out the trip. That's what we did once we got the map. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>