<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My husband, John, took the kids to Claire's, the girly accessories boutique in the mall. My older daughter, Chelsea (14 years) needed to buy a gift for a friend's birthday. As Chelsea and my middle daughter Emily (9 years) shopped, John and my son Andrew (5 years) found themselves uncomfortably alone. They soon realized they were the only two GUYS in the shop and not wanting to interrupt the girls' shopping momentum, he and Andrew sat down on the only chair in the whole shop, a high stool placed in a corner of the store next to a mica counter. Unfortunately, the guys didn't realize where they were sitting until a young woman, flashing with gold from her bare midrif to her eyebrows, nose and pouting lower lip, approached them with a sharp instrument. "Where do you want to get pierced," she asked. John and Andrew stared at Miss GenX with wide eyes and then ran for their lives!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Mommy, can you take me to the park so I can practice Cheerleading for school?" My nine year old daughter Emily clasped her hands together and pouted up at me. "Please. My friend's mother is going to give us pizza for lunch and everything. Please?" Emily is the one whose finger is always on my guilt button. So, I said, "Yes," figuring I could drop her off on the way to the grocery store. I have to say that I was a little concerned from the beginning. I never heard an adult's name come up regarding these plans. Also, the temperatures have been soaring in the nineties with no rain in sight. From the comfort of our living room, the day looked inviting. Blue skies, bright sun, vibrant reds and greens of grass, bushes and flowers made the view outside my window look like a postcard from paradise. However, when I piled Emily and Andrew in the car the heat made us feel like feel like we were chickens in a rotisserie. It was so hot the air conditioner required most of the ten minute trip to the park in order to cool down. Well, we arrived at the park and passed a family playing catch in an open field. We drove past the dog park where people were playing with their pets. We even passed a father and son fishng together next to a bridge, which connected the main park to a smaller playground. We drove around and around the park three times. "Is that your group, Emily?" I asked. "No, Mommy, it's not." I headed to the exit, "I'm sorry, but I think we should just go. Who is the grown up in charge of this thing?" Emily folded her arms, eyes hooded and sighed in disappointment. "It was just us, Mommy." I couldn't believe what I just heard. "You mean you planned this with your friends and the parents were never really involved?" I could imagine the other girls using the same pitch on their Moms. You know, the it's okay...they're going to give us lunch...if I can't go I can't be in the cheerleading group anymore...pitch. Then, when the parents realized it was Memorial Day they put a stop to the little girls' plans. Oh well, duped by my nine year old, again.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>