<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been a day of held back tears, feeling a bit emotional about things.  Not sure what though, maybe just a mixture of things.  The problem with me is that I can't talk about things, much to Donny's annoyance!  I used to be able to open up quite easily, but after a string of people using that to their advantage( most of them christians i might add ) I became more inward, just learned to deal with things my way.  So it's hard now to tell Donny whats on my mind, I want to, I really do, but somehow can't find the words when I need them.  It's just a matter of being less self-concience about myself, and with Donny reading me like a book anyway, I don't think I'll get away with keeping things to ( he's just handed me a note asking me to tell him whats on my mind ) myself!!!!  Suppose too, it's a matter of allowing myself to be open to hurt again.  Pain has made me grow as a person, but enough is enough, I've had a lifetimes worth, and I know with Donny, there will be no more.  Time to wear my heart on my sleeve again.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the beginning of a new blog and a new me. I have blogged before but it was way too depressing. This one will be much more interesting, probably the most talked about topic will be the wonderful people in my life. I will blog a lot about my new love Donny, who has taken me to places i've never been and it's an on going journey! I was single for 6 months after the break up of my marriage, and I have never been so grateful for my ex shagging someone else, as I would have still been stuck in a loveless relationship, hard though it was, I am me again, and it hasn't felt better. Not much more to say tonight as i've had a few glasses of vino and my brain wants to shut down for a while, also Donny is sitting here and I am feeling kinda horny. x x x   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's not been a bad week so far, got something to look forward to, we are all going to Donny's on friday, so my week is busy getting prepared for that, with housework etc.  Had a quiet weekend, on the phone and texting Donny most of the time so I didn't feel alone, really don't like weekends without him.  Last week of school till summer holidays and we are all looking forward to the break.  Got lots of washing to sort out so I'd better be getting on with it.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Didn't get to sleep till 4am, back up at 7.30 to get kids out to school.  Feeling bad about being a bitch to welshy last night, hope Donny doesn't get too pissed off with me.  Went to the shop after I dropped the kids to school and I passed right by strap on sally, as she passed me she laughed in my face, all I needed today, got in and just cried, I really don't need to be alone today.  I was going to just pack things up for me and the girls and catch a train to Montrose, stay at Donny's seeing his flat is empty, but I don't want to go without talking to him first,  just need to get away from this fucking place.  I haven't felt as bad as this for a long time.  I constantly feel sick and my head can't find any peace at all.  Can't even get in touch with Donny today as he is working.  Will phone him tonight and see what he thinks, was even thinking of going up on wednesday after Claire's graduation, the kids won't miss much on the last two days of school.  It just means I can get some space, I feel so trapped and out of control.  Might go and get a tattoo today, not sure what to get or where to get it put, but it's something to do. I pawned my wedding, engagement and eternity rings yesterday, didn't get much, they were worth as much as my marriage was.  I really need to get away from here and all the crap.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's 1:38am, Friday morning.  What a fucking night.  Can't sleep at all with everything going on in my head.  An old friend of Donny's got in touch with him tonight, saying she wanted to be mates, he text me to tell me, as I had already experienced this bunny boiler at the start of our relationship.  He told her that he would speak to me, but to be honest, how could he even think I would like the idea, he should have just told her no straight away, but he gave her a foothold again.  So I got her number, and had a bit of fun, after the day I had, I needed someone to vent my anger at.  I basically told her to stop texting Donny, or I wouldn't leave her alone, turning the bunny boilers tables.  I know that Donny asked me not to text her, but he is too nice to her for my liking, so I can't say I was.  I am not usually a possessive person, in fact I really don't like possessive people, but after everything I've been through, I can't take any sort of threat to my relationship with Donny, I'm fearful of losing him to someone else better than me, cause lets face it, I am old and haven't got much to offer.  I am so fucking pissed off tonight, but in a funny way, when I get pissed off, I get strength from somewhere.  I am not a weak person, I just allow situations to weaken me when there is no need for it.  God I need sleep, fuck yesterday and all that went with it, I couldn't even get a proper talk with Donny.  Someone was definitely out to piss me off!!!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've had a busy morning.  Things I needed to do, but would have run a mile if I could.  My head is spinning with it all, and I really need to find strength from somewhere.  Its hard on my own dealing with lawyers and benefit departments, they just confuse me, fill me with too much information and everything I long for seems so far out of reach.  Divorce proceedings are starting which is a good thing, it means I can finally close that chapter of my life and make plans for my new life with Donny.  The sale of the flat is confusing as are all the financial implications of the divorce settlement.  I need to get a job, so once Claire is at school after the summer holidays, I'll start looking.  We want to live in Montrose, but it's all very complicated, how do I get a mortgage if I'm not working there, so I will have to live there a while first, so then where do we live until then.  The ideal thing, so that Donny and I aren't living apart is for him to move down here for a while, but he would have to give up his flat, which would give us a route into Montrose, also if he moves in here, will John get stroppy and stop paying the mortgage, I don't know.  I feel like hiding away until it's all settled.  It's all too much for me to handle on my own.  One thing for sure is that Donny and I will get through this by hook or by crook.  I just need to have faith in the future.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I used to cry myself to sleep at night but that was all before he came I thought love had to hurt to turn out right but now he's here it's not the same, it's not the same  He fills me up, he gives me love more love than I've ever seen He's all I've got, he's all i've got in this world But he's all the man that I need  And in the morning when I kiss his eyes he takes me down and rocks me slow And in the evening when the moon is high he hold me close and won't let go, he won't let go  He fills me up, he gives me love more love than i've ever seen He's all I've got, he's all i've got in this world But he's all the man, all the man that I need
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Over the past few months, Donny and I have spent all our time together, but last night he went home and I won't see him for two weeks.  Last night was hard, watching him go, knowing that he will be 150 miles away, and longing for him to stay with me.  Today I feel lonely, the girls are at school then away with their dad till this evening and I don't know what to do with myself, I feel a wee bit lost.  The only strength I get is that I know I am loved by Donny and the girls, and though we are apart, they live with me all the time in my heart.    Life is good just now, after the trauma of a marriage break up and all that went with it, Donny came just at the right time to shower me with love and devotion.  We have had our problems too, but there is nothing going to stand in the way of true love.  I love Donny so much and I can see a wonderful life ahead, only we have a few obstacles to get over first, like waiting to sell this flat and us having to live apart till then, which is getting harder all the time.  Moving to Montrose will be the best thing for all of us.  I know the kid's will miss friends and their dad will be in Glasgow, but contact will remain and they will have a much better life there, with Donny and I giving them the best we can.  I need to stay strong for Donny, he will only worry if I start to fall to bits without him, but he is my strength, my happiness, my everything, he protects me from all that hurts and loves me so perfectly.  I don't know what I did to deserve him, but it must have been good!    Off now to find something to do, might even go for a nap to pass the time.  Will blog again tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>