<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I liberate the gristle from betwixt my teeth and wipe my face clean of my next-door neighbor's remarkable barbecue sauce I am reminded of the true meaning of this Memorial Day by our brave President, Mr. George W. Bush, who informed us today that "Throughout our history, America has gone to war reluctantly because we have known the costs of war" and that because of our troops in Afghanistan and Iraq "America is safer, 2 terror regimes are gone forever and 50 million souls now live in freedom."   If only the irony was intentional.  Now don't get me wrong; I have plenty of respect for our people over there.  On Sunday I met a man named Ben from the 82nd Airborne who's shipping out soon.  He seemed like a good guy, and I hope he comes home safely and doesn't do anything that he will regret while he's over there.  I know a soldier in Baghdad named Jackie who's a nice guy, a great Dad and a heck of a bocce player, and I pray for him almost every night.   But their courage and sacrifice doesn't change the fact that the commander in chief stood at the tomb of the unknown soldier today and cheapened the traditional Memorial Day ritual at Arlington.    America's civilian leaders were not reluctant to go to war in Iraq.  They didn't know the human and capital costs of this war.  It has not made America safer.  And the souls of Iraqis do not now live in freedom. More later on the change from a war on terrorism to a war on "terror regimes."          
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My planned launch of this blog is being delayed a little due to an unexpected, last minute project at work yesterday, and now because of a trip down to the Tar Heel state this weekend.  But I didn't want to create this thing on Friday and not post until Monday night or Tuesday, so I guess the first thing I'll say is good morning and happy Memorial Day.  Enjoy your grilled meats and salads, and take a moment of silence to empathize with the hundreds of families for whom this must be an incredibly painful holiday.  I'll be back on Monday to deliver my thoughts on a host of topics.  Have a good weekend.
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now I realize we could make a national sport of listing the ways in which the Bush administration has shown that compassionate conservatism was never anything more than a nifty slogan meant to assuage the consciences of voters who would otherwise have felt icky and selfish voting Republican.  There are people who make a living keeping track of this sadness, and they do it well.  Click  urlLink here  for my personal fave.    Too often though, the criticism is presented too abstractly, as a laundry list of programs and dollars.  An example of the kind of information that's all too often missing is found in a letter to the editor in today's     Richmond  [VA]  Times Dispatch  :   Editor, Times-Dispatch: Regarding the article, "Farmworker Program on Precarious Ground":  Federal programs that increase the self-sufficiency of America's poor often work behind the scenes in changing people's lives. Programs such as the National Farmworker Jobs Program (NFJP) are rarely publicized.  Dean Moore worked on a farm in the Shenandoah Valley earning $7,000 a year. Today, with NFJP's help, he is a truck driver who makes $2,300 per month and recently purchased his first home. Dinesha Ryan in Southside Virginia started working in tobacco at 14, and had earned just $810 when she enrolled in NFJP. Now, in college and majoring in electrical engineering, she will work at an energy company making $15 an hour. James Alvarado, picking strawberries, barely supported his family on $15,000. Through NFJP, he became a heavy-equipment operator earning more than $28,000 a year on a farm near Harrisonburg.   The Bush administration has requested zero funding for the NFJP and continues to maintain, against its own evidence, that the program is ineffective and duplicative. Fact is, it is more effective than most. In DOL's Workforce System Results, NFJP had an employment rate of 83 percent, exceeding every other DOL job program. Neither is it duplicative. Statistics show that DOL rarely serves farmworkers in other programs.  If eliminated, funds will not be transferred to states, giving governors an unfunded mandate to serve thousands of additional workers with multiple barriers with fewer resources. Policymakers should be wary of the systematic dissolution of poverty programs and their attack on farmworkers. Cecily Rodriguez. richmond.    Well put, Cecily.  You and Bob Herbert should make wonderful babies one day.  You think the administration is wary of the (succinctly phrased) "systematic dissolution of poverty programs?"  How do you square this stuff with the compassionate part of compassionate conservatism?  By putting your hand on someone's shoulder and telling him you'll pray for him after you flush the program that provided his livelihood?   Stay tuned for episode #474 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So L. Paul Bremer left Baghdad yesterday.    Whoa, everything's different now.    Seriously, though, I'm trying not to delve into Iraq too much at the moment because I'm having trouble balancing the need to respect the lives of people (of   all   nationalities) in harm's way over there against the need to recognize that the events of the past year are of greater historical magnitude than most of us are noticing right now.  Forest?  Trees?  Which to comment on?  Answers to this question only become clear during landmark events or mysteriously crystallizing moments.  But Bremer's exit strikes me as neither.    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You might notice that the frequency of new posts on the Nej Page is somewhat erratic.  There's a perfectly good explanation for that, and that good explanation's name is travel.  Since my first post I've been on the road with limited computer access for what adds up to 18 days.  But now, finally, I'm home for a stretch of several weeks.  My most recent destination was Cincinnati, which came off as an unlovable place to me for several reasons.  For one, I hate chili.  Also, I need a subway or a trolley or something.  Horse-drawn buggies and buses alone ain't cuttin it.  Third, and I know I'll sound like a grumpy old man when I say this, there were kids acting a fool all over the place.  Seriously, the entire downtown was like the movie theater at Union station (DC reference there, for all of my readers from elsewhere on the globe).  Fourth, and worst, Cincinnati fell into the dubiously distinguished league of places I've been to where people will say off-the-wall racist things to you so nonchalantly that it almost sounds like they're talking about the weather or the local ball team.  Yuck.   For sake of fairness, I should note that most of the people I met and worked with were cool, non chili-eating, unbigoted folks, and there was lots to do in the downtown area.  Also, it has a pleasant climate and an authentic atmosphere that comes only with age and lots of brick buildings -- Reston, Virginia it ain't.    Still, though, it doesn't make the list of cities I have to see again. 
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Juan Williams  influenced my education by no small measure;   urlLink Eyes On the Prize  starred in two of my college classes, and his political reporting and commentary set benchmarks I can barely even aspire to.  So I was surprised yesterday when he wrote an  urlLink op-ed in the New York Times  that seemed so, well, wrong.  Basically, he says Bush can get 20 percent of the African American vote this year for four reasons: 1) Faith-based initiatives are popular in the black community; 2) Kerry has done a crappy job of reaching out to blacks voters 3) Bush does a great job of appointing minorities; 4) Two thirds of blacks favor school vouchers.  Thing is, none of that matters because Bush has done such a poor job for his African American constituents on more important issues:  1) As shown in  urlLink a Washington Post poll , 88% of black Americans disapprove of Bush's handling of the war.  2) Bush opposes affirmative action and did so rather publicly during the University Michigan case (to say nothing of the fact that he'll likely use the word "quota" ad nauseum during the debates, as he did in 2000).  3) The  urlLink unemployment rate  for African Americans was 9.9% in May and has been under 10% for only 3 out of the last 12 months.     Black voters see that Bush has done a poor job with the economy, bungled a war that was never popular with them in the first place, and played the wink-wink games with racists that his party always does. If Mr. Williams had said black turnout was going to be dismal, or if he had said Bush might get 10 percent of the black vote, then his argument might add up.  But come November there is very, very little chance that 20 out of every 100 African American voters will cast their ballots for Bush.  Perhaps Mr. Williams was just trying to light a fire under the Kerry camp and, more generally, white Democrats.  If such is the case, kudos to him.      
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes you run your mouth and then get a little egg on your face.  Other times a big ol' cheese omelette covers you from brow to chin.  I think the latter applies to me and my stupid, platitude-laden prediction on the NBA Finals.  The Pistons, whom I considered little more than a speed bump for the Laker Express, played aggresively, selflessly and cohesively throughout the series, and 5 as one will beat a pair of giants every time.  Watching them was so reassuring; every time I let out a little shout of joy or admiration last night I was really saying "see Dad, basketball has    not   gone to hell in a handbasket after all."  Anyway, here's to the underdogs who got it done the right way: your 2004 NBA Champion Detroit Pistons.  Also known as the Michigan chapter of the Washington Wizards Alumni Association.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A favorite writer of mine by the name of Ralph Wiley passed away on Monday.  I don't know exactly what I want to write about when I become a big grownup of a journalist, but I'm glad I found his column on ESPN.com's page 2 because he showed me that my beat doesn't have to be a pigeonhole, no matter what it is.  It's worth your time to read some of these  urlLink tributes to him from colleagues and friends.       
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If Antonio Tarver can knock out Roy Jones, Jr., then Detroit can take a game or two off the Lakers.  The series, however, is in the bag for L.A.  4 Reasons the Pistons cannot beat the Lakers 4 times out of 7: 1. Bandwagon teams don't lose in the championship.  Bandwagon teams only go down against their own conference.  [bandwagon team - a team with a nationwide fan base of people who root for them solely because they win consecutive championships (i.e., Los Angeles Lakers, Jordan's Bulls).  antonym: hometown team.]   2. A motivated Shaq is still unstoppable  3. Experience   4. Kobe is innocent. (Point #4 does not reflect Dan's beliefs, but rather serves as his jab at those who would have you believe Kobe's middle name is Mumia.  Seriously though, the worst part of this whole debacle is the delegitimizing of the whole concept of sexual assault in the minds of another generation of young boys)     Here's hoping my first sports post doesn't turn out to be embarassingly wrong.   
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm giving out prizes to the first 3 people post comments on The Nej Page.   First: a drink or cup of coffee. Second: a lottery ticket. Third: a cheaper lottery ticket. Here's the catch -- you have to wait until I make a substantive post on which to comment.     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not one to support the concept of balance that says "well, since we spend so much time talking about all the people being killed in Iraq we should spend just as much time&nbsp;focusing on&nbsp;all the schools being built there too."&nbsp; That's hogwash.&nbsp;&nbsp;But&nbsp;I'm not just setting up a straw man -- plenty of people really believe that.&nbsp;   However, sometimes you come across a piece of good news that, while not the biggest story of the day, nonetheless deserves to be highlighted.&nbsp; From the "World in Brief" report in yesterday's Washington Post:    • ISLAMABAD, Pakistan -- The foreign ministers of India and Pakistan held talks at a regional conference, hoping to speed the pace of peace talks that have raised hope that the nuclear-armed neighbors might permanently end decades of hostility.  Foreign Minister Khursheed Kasuri met his Indian counterpart, Natwar Singh, over breakfast at an Islamabad hotel. "Our talks today were frank, they were honest, they were candid, they were friendly and they were warm," Kasuri said afterward. "Every issue of concern was raised by me and every issue of concern was raised by Mr. Natwar Singh."    Great to hear, no?&nbsp;   In other news, I'm homeward bound from the beach and the Nej Page is up again.  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be out of town and offline for the next week, but thereafter I'll start posting again.  
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Although it is not without its warts, I greatly respect Teach For America, so I was thrilled to see the Washington Post's Jay Matthews give it a  urlLink somewhat complimentary write-up  in yesterday's Washington Post.   [Full disclosure - I'm an alumnus of Teach For America's 2001 Mississippi Delta corps]  I was especially pleased that, unlike many columnists who have written about TFA, Matthews emphasized that while it's a good program, it can't even come close to solving the gross injustice that is the education gap between advantaged and disadvantaged socio-economic and racial groups in our country.  He's right about that.  Expecting TFA and similar programs to erase the education gap would be like expecting the  urlLink Abraham Lincoln Brigade  to win World War Two, and suggesting otherwise understates the crisis in urban and rural education.    He was also right to refrain from effusively praising Teach For America teachers' real but modest success, which was focus of a  urlLink recent study . He went too far when he said that their "gain was similar to my batting average in the Old Folks League going from .067 to .073."  Even if his math added up, the comparison trivializes teachers' efforts.  Still, his jist that Teach For America is a worthwhile organization that doesn't move mountains is right on.     For sake of balance and positivity, check out this  urlLink short bit of anecdotal evidence  on what Teach For America corps members sometimes accomplish.  To ignore the stars within TFA while discussing the program's impact would show disregard for their efforts, and I don't want to do that.             
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not the biggest baseball fan in the world, especially since Baltimore Orioles owner Peter Angelos threw an entire season a few years back (a la  Major League ), but last night I discovered that my fondness for the O's and the national pastime has been dormant rather than dead.  And there are two people I have to thank for this: Miguel Tejada and Chris Berman.    Miguel - the Orioles' shortstop and only all-star - won the home run derby at Houston's oddly named Minute Maid Park, and Chris Berman, who was announcing the event, didn't give him his due.  In the second round Tejada hit 15 jacks.  15!  That's a record for one round of home run derby.  And what was Berman doing while these balls where sailing beyond the field of play?  He was ignoring homer after homer while talking to Reggie Jackson about, among other things, Derek Jeter.  Because, you know, if there's one guy who doesn't get his rightful share of the limelight it's Derek Jeter.  The combination of an Oriole out-slugging a bunch of guys twice his size and a slipping ESPN anchor completely blowing him off aroused in me the two emotions on which every sports fan thrives: triumph and indignation.  That couldn't have happened if I just didn't care.  So I found out that somewhere inside of me a baseball fan still lurks.  Not that you asked or anything.  Cheers: Houston's Lance Berkman for energizing the crowd with an impressive couple of spurts in the home run derby.  Jeers: ESPN's inexplicably stupid decision to go with a pitcher's mound camera instead of the classic wide angle shot that shows you the ball's entire flight.  Easily the worst mistake I've ever seen them make.      
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      George F. Will's  urlLink column in today's Washington Post  failed the laugh test with flying colors.  That's the nicest thing I can say about it.  Or if I was trying to be like George I'd call it the cachinnation test and then allude to Seutonius or somebody.  Before commenting on today's column, though, I want to note that this is not the first time he's pushed wishful thinking as real insight.  Media Matters busted him a little while back.  Click  urlLink here  to have a look.    Late update: I just found a  urlLink blog post by Paul Waldman  that says pretty much everything else I was fixing to say about Will's preposterous "contribution" to the marketplace of ideas.  Best to direct your attention to his post rather than just crib it into mine.                 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't tell you how pleased and relieved I was upon hearing that Kerry had dubbed John Edwards as his running mate.  Edwards was my sentimental favorite from the primaries, and his ability to frame domestic issues in moral terms is important and refreshing.  I look forward to hearing him contrast his ticket with the Republicans'.  He'll be a smash at the convention.  His press hasn't been great thus far, and not just from the Washington Times.  Watch tv, listen to the radio or read a paper and you'll quickly learn that John Edwards is an inexperienced, smooth-talking, rich personal injury lawyer with a good stump speech and a stirring biography.  That's a short leap from an incompetent, slick, greedy ambulance chaser who'll sing you a hell of a tune.     Given that the Republicans didn't have the best luck against Clinton, you'd think they'd try to avoid reincarnating him.             
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Henry Waxman takes his congressional colleagues to task  urlLink in today's Washington Post  for failing to fulfill their duty to provide meaningful oversight over the Bush administration.  Definitely worth reading.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are many subjects just begging to make it onto The Nej Page today.  Before I weigh in on Kerry's choice of Edwards as a running mate, I need to share some thoughts on Fahrenheit 9/11, which I saw several days ago.  It didn't quite meet my expectations, but it was entertaining, moving and infuriating.  My mild disappoint is probably the result of unrealistic expectations.   My principal criticism concerns sequence.  After the initial chapters concerning the lead-up to and aftermath of September 11th, the movie transitions rather abruptly to the Iraq war, and then later backtracks to the run-up to it.  I would've reversed the order of these two segments.  It would've made for a more even, cohesive picture.     Stylistic concerns aside, the movie has one great strength - it breaks away from journalism that buys into what war correspondent Chris Hedges calls  urlLink the myth of war , which basically means that Moore strips the war of its delusional heroic rhetoric in a way no major outlet could or would.  Sectarian squabbles about the fairness of other aspects of the movie cannot detract from the real, horrific light it shines on our campaign in Iraq.    Note: I use the word sectarian rather than partisan because right wing voices are working themselves into a fervor of religious magnitude about this film.   See the movie for yourself if you haven't already.  Rarely will your $8 be so well spent.           
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy belated fourth of July.  Even though I was raised in the D.C. area (well, its outermost reaches) I never saw the Mall fireworks until yesterday.  If you live in the outer suburbs, going to the big fireworks display on the Mall entails traffic jams, sardine-packed metro rides, lots of involuntary flesh pressing once you get there, and sweat.  Lots of sweat.  But I was able to avoid all of that.    How, you ask?  By finding the grassy knoll.  Tucked somewhere in the Pentagon's vast campus lies a parking lot that backs up to a steep, short hill with a wide, flat top that provides a great view of the Washington Monument, Jefferson Memorial and Capitol.  And it's high enough to provide a view that's relatively unobstructed by trees and highways and other potential barriers.  So pretty much a perfect viewing spot.    The show itself was worth the wait, wet grass and bug bites.  I'm no pyrotechnician, but it was really well done and entertaining.  Beyond the mesmerizing colors, showers and booms, the crowd was striking as well; I hadn't ever thought about how resonant fireworks are to Americans.  There were probably one hundred or so people on the knoll, and nobody acted a fool, said anything obnoxious, intruded on anyone else's good time or did anything to draw people's enjoyment away from the spectacle across the water.  Once the shooting started, folks pretty much just shut up and stared, making no noise save the occasional ooh or ahh (except for the loud applause when a National Airport -bound jet flew seemingly straight through the spreading gold flames).     The point of sharing this is not to make some contrived point about unity or patriotism or nationalism or jingoism, but rather to just share what I saw.  Please share comments on what you observed or experienced this weekend.    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       1964 Johnson signs Civil Rights Act   In a nationally televised White House ceremony, U.S. President Lyndon B. Johnson signs into law the Civil Rights Act of 1964. The act, which was the most sweeping civil rights legislation passed by Congress since Reconstruction, prohibited racial discrimination in employment and education, and outlawed racial segregation in public facilities.  This landmark legislation came 10 years after the U.S. Supreme Court ruled in Brown v. Board of Education that racial segregation in public educational facilities was unconstitutional. In the decade that followed the 1954 decision, the African American civil rights movement made great strides in winning federal support for integration, and in 1960 John F. Kennedy made passage of a new civil rights bill one of the platforms of his successful presidential campaign. Vice President Lyndon Johnson served as chairman of the President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunities, and after Kennedy was assassinated in November 1963, Johnson vowed to carry out Kennedy's proposals for civil rights reform. On July 2, 1964, after lobbying hard for its passage, President Johnson signed the Civil Rights Act of 1964.   Today marks the 40th anniversary of one of America's proudest moments.  Even though the Civil Rights Act wasn't a silver bullet that made everything swell, it was a clear victory in the struggle to make America live up to its stated ideals of freedom, equality and justice.  Sometimes the good guys really do win, and one of those times was 40 years ago today.       
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday the Washington Post ran a column by former Nixon staffer and DOD bigwig Noel Koch advocating  urlLink the reinstitution of the draft .  He's a former speechwriter, so the article flows nicely and you can hear his argument gaining steam as you read, almost so much that you gloss over its fanciful delusion, glaring omission and fallacies.    I wouldn't spend my time picking at the article if it wasn't about such a grave subject. But since it is, here goes.  Koch rhetorically challenges the reader to "try to find a draftee who regrets his service to America." Perhaps he should head down to a VA hospital or homeless shelter.  Or for that matter, perhaps he should visit Arlington Cemetary.  He conveniently ignores the fact that  urlLink more than half of the 58,000 soldiers who were killed in Vietnam were there because they were drafted .  Isn't it kind of callous (dishonest?) to advocate conscription without at least acknowledging the fact that it can get thousands of Americans unnecessarily killed?      But he's not done yet!  Instead of merely glossing over the uglier aspects of the draft, Koch goes a step further and exaggerates its social benefits: "The draft shattered class distinctions.  It mixed high school dropouts with college graduates, rich with middle class and poor."  Come again?  How economically diverse were the Champagne Unit and similar outfits?  What was the socioeconomic makeup of the deferment crowd?  Maybe if he ommitted the word "rich" he would have something of a point here, but he didn't.   This fallacy leads Koch to a fundamentally ignorant conclusion.  He closes by arguing that the draft will produce a group of political decision-makers and advisors who "bring with them a bone-deep appreciation of the true costs of conflict.  Thus might we reduce the risks of counsel from those who have never had to learn the difference between a war and a cakewalk."  Anyone who's picked up a newspaper in the last year knows that the Vietnam draft spectacularly failed to produce such an outcome.  The dodgers, deferees, and privileged privates least familiar with the true costs of war in Vietnam were precisely the ones who led the charge to war in Iraq.  Bush and Cheney and Perle and Wolfowitz (and Clinton, for that matter) prove that the people who hold sway over decisions of war and peace are the same people who are best equipped to avoid the draft by one means or another.  Mr. Koch, don't push for the draft by ignoring its human costs, overstating its power to build bridges across class and race, and saying it will produce political results that it abjectly failed to produce in its last incarnation. "Why We Need the Draft Back" is a work of fantasy, maybe even mendacity, and it attempts to advance the most fundamentally undemocratic policy in our country since slavery.  I hope that the governing class doesn't swallow it.     
    
</post>


</Blog>