<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, i thought this site was something like a message board, BUT IT ISNT....damn  anyways, i think i'll have to think of something different to get the most out of it.  See you all at some other BLOG.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi all,  they say, "Al Qaeda is everyone's war, but Iraq is Bush's war."  Have your say, say anything you like.  Take Care
     
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A  = 87% & above =  4.00   B  = 75% - 86 %  =  3.00   C  = 65% - 74 %  =  2.00   D  = 60% - 64 %  =  1.00   F  = Below 60 %  =  0.00 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Grades & Percentage   A   = 	93% and above = 	 4.00    A-  =	90-92 % =  3.67   B+  =	87-89 % =  3.33   B   = 	83-86 % =  3.00   B-  = 	80-82 % =  2.67   C+  = 	77-79 % =  2.33   C   =	73-76 % =  2.00   C-  =	70-72 % =  1.67   D+  =	67-69 % =  1.33   D   =	63-66 % =  1.00   D-  =	60-62 % =  0.67   F   =    Below 60 % =  0.00 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        THE GPA STORY   The profound injustice with the students of Institute of Business Administration (IBA) with regards to their GPA has forced me to write something about it. I don’t expect things to change, because we are not in a habit of changing the status quo. Who bothers? But then, I think, there is no harm in hoping against hope.  First we must understand what we actually mean by the term GPA. The abbreviation of Grade Point Average: is a numerical measure of academic achievement based upon a computation figured from the number of credits and grade points earned per course. Since the GPA is a weighted sum of the student's grades, each of a student's grades is converted to a number on a scale from 1.0 to 4.0. Typically, a 4.0 corresponds to an "A", a 3.0 to a "B", a 2.0 to a "C", a 1.0 to a "D", and 0.0 to an "E" or "F".  Here is the real deal. Every now and then we come across well-designed job ads asking for some out-of-the-world positions with designations that sound that all of us are doing something extra-ordinary. I don’t have a problem with those hard-to-chew designations, but with what they ask to get there. If the company wouldn’t be asking for some 3 - 5 years of experience, they would be eyeing candidates with a 3.0 GPA. A candidate from IBA, who has earned his 3 GPA by scoring between 83 & 86, is lined up in the same queue as someone from CBM or others who can earn the same GPA by scoring 75. The difference between the lower limits of these two intervals is 8 (83-75). Now, either these 8 marks don’t mean a thing to the employers, who they are just being numb and busy in closing there eyes to the reality. I suggest, if the employers accept candidates for initial screening and interviews from institutes other than IBA on the basis of their 75 – 86 marks interval, then those IBAians should also be allowed to apply for jobs who score between 75 -86, irrespective of their GPA.  I don’t know whose fault is it - whether it is IBA, other institutes, or HEC. All I know is that it is the IBAians who are suffering. HEC is not maintaining a check-and-balance on what grade plans the different institutes are offering. Every institute is following its own grade plans. We are a free nation, but independence doesn’t mean doing whatever one wishes. There must be some control of any kind. I am going to post the grade plans of IBA and CBM for your ready comparison.   Thanks,  Mohammad Umar Murtaza 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>