<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Doug's Letter to the Editor   June 30, 2004   Last week, the Service Employees International Union (SEIU) drafted and passed a resolution endorsing same-sex marriage. This will bring equality to all of their members which is what organized labor is all about.   For example, the demand for domestic partner benefits, fueled by the AIDS epidemic, gained new ground in recent decades. Many employers have been forced to end a two-tiered benefits package that denied health care and other bread-and-butter benefits to unmarried partners of workers. I urge the Indiana AFL-CIO and its member unions to follow the SEIU's lead and to pass resolutions endorsing same-sex marriage. Businesses and the Indiana economy will benefit in the long run if we stand up for all working people in this state. Indiana will attract and retain the brightest and the best, both union and non-union.   Doug Smiley  Indianapolis, IN  http://dougsmiley.net 
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dick Cheney: A man of respect and dignity.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Iraq's Labor Movement Wins Support From U.S. Unions       Iraqi workers and unions charge that the U.S. is keeping wages low to attract foreign investors, as Washington plans the privatization of Iraq’s economy. The Bush administration sees Iraq as a free-market beachhead into the Middle East and South Asia.   Low wages have driven the upsurge in Iraqi labor activity, including three general strikes in Basra alone. Following the arrival of U.S. troops, Iraqi public sector workers began receiving emergency salaries dictated by the Coalition Provisional Authority—roughly from $60 to $120 monthly. Then the CPA’s Order #30 on Reform of Salaries and Employment Conditions of State Employees last September lowered the base to $40, and eliminated housing and food subsidies.      urlLink Colin Powell says the Bush administration vows to speed up job creation in Iraq . Let's hope the Iraqi workers are given the opportunity to organize their workplaces. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink New Orleans lost over 10,000 jobs in the last year . Why should you care about New Orleans? Because these jobs that were lost were high-paying jobs. These were jobs that paid the mortgages and helped send children to college. These jobs that were lost were not in the Midwest "Rust Belt" but were in the South which was supposedly the nation's leading growth region.  urlLink Here is a report saying that Tennesse lost 67,000 jobs in the last three years . The Bush job destruction machine is moving right along.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Andrew Stern, the president of the SEIU,  urlLink had some strong words for the Democratic Party and the AFL-CIO  calling them "hollow" organizations. Stern has hinted at breaking away from the AFL-CIO with four or five other labor unions to form a new labor movement. It is my opinion that we need to show solidarity with the John Kerry campaign for president and then make changes from within after we have our man in the White House.  urlLink John Kerry and John Edwards have been outspoken in their support of organized labor during their campaigns.    Labor has also received enthusiastic backing on the platform and from the Kerry-Edwards ticket for its foremost institutional imperative, the Employee Free Choice Act. (The House bill, authored by veteran California liberal George Miller, has 204 co-sponsors -- that is, virtually every Democrat in the House plus seven Republicans -- not that the DeLayniks have any intention of bringing it to the floor for a vote.)      I urge Andrew Stern and his progressive labor union to stand strong with the AFL-CIO and other working families in the effort to oust George Bush from the White House. We will have four years of friendly leadership while we fix what is currently wrong with the state of the labor movement. Four years to build a strong voice for working families and not four more years of defending what we worked so hard for.  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  The Chrisian Science Monitor has a highly interesting article  on the new overtime rules that will go into effect August 23rd.   Recognizing the complexity problem, the AFL-CIO asked three former Labor Department officials, who worked under both Republican and Democratic regimes, to evaluate the new rules. After proclaiming total independence, the three experts, in 40 pages, offered damning conclusions.  The rules exempt from overtime, they write, a greater proportion of the workforce than "Congress could have originally intended." They remove existing overtime protection for "large numbers of employees." They "failed to restore" an appropriate salary level requirement, and failed to establish "reasonable and clear criteria" for determining those not able to claim overtime, including executives, administrators, professionals, and outside sales employees. The rules could result in a "profusion" of court litigation.  Worst of all, the three held that the department in its rules "failed to protect and promote the interests of working people," a "core" mission of the DOL.   
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Blog for America  gives us an education on what Bush's tax cuts have done to the middle class and calls for a 're-framing' of the tax debate. We need to turn the tables on tax cuts and start looking at paying taxes like paying dues to a gym or a labor union much the same way Bushites pay country club fees.    Over the long run, we need to re-frame the tax issue more broadly. The Radical Right has sought to define taxation as inherently wicked in order to promote tax cuts, with the ultimate goal of starving the government of revenue and forcing cuts in vital services like Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid. We need to turn this debate around.  One idea is to talk about taxes as the dues we pay as citizens of this country. These are like the dues we pay to be as members of a community swimming pool or, for those more likely to count themselves as part of George Bush's "base," a country club. We benefit from the dues that those before us have paid to build the facilities, and part of our own dues go toward maintaining the pool or tennis courts for future members.   
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Next month,  urlLink six million workers will lose overtime pay . Many families rely on overtime pay to make mortage payments which could slow down the Real Estate juggernaut. Look for the Housing bubble to burst when people start skipping mortgage payments.
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Slate  has a  urlLink highly interesting article  on Ohio and what it means for both Bush and Kerry. 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Here is The World Socialist Web Site's commentry on the 9/11 Commission's Report .   On the most basic level, the 9/11 report is a whitewash. The 567-page document is filled with criticisms of the Bush and Clinton administrations and the performance of the government agencies responsible for intelligence, national security and emergency response. But the commission attributes all of these failures to incompetence, mismanagement, or “failure of imagination.” The fundamental premise of its investigation is that the CIA, the FBI, the US military and the Bush White House all acted in good faith.  The 9/11 report thus excludes, a priori, the most important question raised by the events of September 11, 2001: did US government agencies deliberately permit—or actively assist—the carrying out of this terrorist atrocity, in order to provide the Bush administration with the necessary pretext to carry out its program of war in Central Asia and the Middle East and a huge buildup of the forces of state repression at home.    It is my position that the 9/11 Commission failed to ask the hard questions...or maybe they knew but did not want to explore that path just like the Warren Commission failed to explore the Mafia link to the JFK's assassination. The CIA and the Mafia are one in the same. Both operate secretly and prey on the public's willingness to accept what is told to them by the elected officials.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NICHOLAS D. KRISTOF  urlLink reminds us of another reason to boot Bush in November  in today's  New York Times  Op-Ed.   Mr. Bush's Healthy Forests initiative, in its harsh early version, allowed logging companies to pillage federal land. The latest assault is President Bush's decision to overturn the Clinton administration's "roadless rule," protecting nearly 60 million acres of national forests from road building and development.   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Union delegates will hold a forum in Boston during the convention to raise awareness of workers' right to organize.  This election will mean so much for the AFL-CIO and unions in general. Much is at stake for unions and their future. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It does not matter about how much profits corporations are earning. If the workers are not getting their fair share then the economy stands still or goes in reverse. Look for inflation to rise in the coming months.   --------------------------------------------------------------------   3:09pm 07/23/04   Dow posts triple-digit decline, Nasdaq at 10-mo. low ($INDU)   By Mark Cotton   NEW YORK -- The Dow Jones Industrial Average ($INDU) posted a triple-digit decline and the Nasdaq Composite ($COMPQ) hovered close to a 10-month low in the final hour of trading Friday as investors fretted about the corporate earnings outlook for the remainder of the year. The Dow industrials was last down 110 points, or 1.1 percent, at 9,940.90 while the Nasdaq dropped 41 points, or 2.2 percent to 1,847.68. The S&P 500 index ($SXP) meanwhile dropped 12 points, or 1.1 percent, to 1,084.   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink A highly interesting Op-Ed  in today's  New York Times  raises the questions of what will we do when workers get displaced because of the increase in immigration. It is already happening with the low-skilled jobs and to the recent high-school graduates who are competing with the immigrants for the few jos that are created in today's economic environment. The article states that college graduates are holding their own that is if their jobs has not been outsourced across the oceans.   In the go-go nineties when there were more jobs than workers looking for work, the immigration vs. jobs available was not an issue. This has changed in recent years where there is now competition and a growing resentment. For years corporations such as Tysong Foods and Wabash National have been actively helping Mexicans relocate to the United States so that they can work in their plants and factories at low wages and at jobs that white high-school educated Americans did not want because of the adverse working conditions. Immirgrants are willing to work in dangerous working environments at low wages and take the jobs that Americans have passed over but now this is happening to the middle-class jobs with an increasing alarm.   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Special thanks to  urlLink Kmarx .  Bush Treatment of 9/11 Investigation  The commission published its report on 9/11 today.  With a thank you to the Financial Times as a reminder of many of these events, let's not forget some key moments in the history of the 9/11 investigation.   1. Unsupported by the Bush administration, acceptance of the investigation was forced by grieving family members of individuals that lost their lives to the horror of 9/11.  2.Bush, in an attempt to sandbag the process, names Henry Kissinger to lead the commission.   3. Family members counter the Bush administration's attempts to sandbag by pushing for disclosures from Kissinger on his clients that leads to his resignation.  4. The Bush administration plays politics with the commission's deadlines, before giving in to the committee's request for more time.  5. The Bush administration claims Executive Privilege in an attempt to keep Rice, Cheney and Bush from testifying.   6. The administration gives in to public pressure and allows Rice to testify under oath.  Rice's testimony leads to the most memorable soundbite of the hearings: Bush had been given a report on August 6, 2001, entitled, "Bin Laden Determined To Attack Inside The United Sates."  7. Rice's public statement that no one ever imagined terrorists using planes as weapons is contradicted by Louis Freeh's testimony that the use of planes as a potential weapon for a terrorist attack was known.  8. The administration gives in to public pressure and allows Bush and Cheney to meet with the commission privately.  Bush becomes the target of late night talk show barbs for needing to have Cheney with him when he testifies.  9. Bush and Cheney, in the face of evidence to the contrary, continue to spin that intelligence warnings indicated al-Qaeda attacks would be overseas and not here in the U.S.  1o. Bush accepts George Tenant's resignation.  11. Despite an Interim Report from the commission that states no evidence was found linking Iraq to the 9/11 attacks, Cheney continues to publicly link al-Qaeda and Iraq.   12. The commission rebukes Cheney's public comments that he probably had more facts than the commission on the al-Qaeda links to Iraq by offering Cheney an opportunity to provide them with that information. Cheney provides no such information.  13. Early reports indicate that the commission will tie Iran to al-Qaeda.  Iran had much to gain from the removal of Saddam and his secular government.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Ambulance drivers and EMTs could strike during the Olympic games.  If this happened in the U.S. this would be considered a terrorist act. After reading the article, I don't blame the emergency medical crews wanting the same bonus as the security force.    Wednesday July 21, 7:30 AM   Strike Threats Shadow Olympics in Athens    Ambulance crews and other emergency service personnel threatened on Tuesday to strike during the Olympics unless they receive extra pay for work at next month's games.   It was the latest warning by Greek unions seeking government bonuses for canceling vacations to be on full duty during the Aug. 13-29 Olympics.   "We have decided to strike during the Olympics if we do not get an Olympic bonus like the security forces," said Ilias Ioannides, head of the country's union of emergency service employees, which includes ambulance teams, paramedics and other medical rescue units.   Ioannides added that 2,600 emergency services workers have been specially trained to work during the Olympics, but he did not clarify what additional preparations were needed. A meeting is planned for Thursday to discuss possible strike plans or other actions.   Labor groups throughout the country have held strikes and rallies to press for Olympic bonuses, which have been promised to police and other security forces in amounts up to $3,000. But the government has so far rejected more concessions because of skyrocketing Olympic costs projected to top $12 billion.    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really think  urlLink Dennis Kucinich   has the right ideas and says the right things just like Ralph Nader did in 2000 but it is unfortunate that money plays a big part in politics. In the end the big donors choose the presidential nominee. Dennis Kucinich is a genuine people's candidate and it's sad that there is no more financial support for candidates who campaign on behalf of the working class.   Kucinich stands up for working people  July 17, 2004  Congressman Dennis Kucinich, in a fiery speech to more than 300 green-shirted public employee union members, accused President Bush of abandoning working people by supporting privatization and outsourcing. The labor rally, sponsored by AFSCME, aimed to gain the attention of the National Governors Conference, which was also held this weekend in Seattle. In addition to the rally, Kucinich attended a private fundraiser and an outdoor picnic with his Washington delegates to the Democratic National Convention while in the Evergreen state. Photo by Gerri Haynes.   
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The U.S. Department of Labor has launched a  urlLink website  to help the homeless. Read about it  urlLink here . At least the DOL can say that they did something during the Bush regime.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A long-time friend of John Kerry  urlLink  writes a highly interesting article  on why he would make a good president. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       On July 20, 1969, Apollo 11 astronaut Neil Armstrong became the first man to walk on the moon when he stepped out of the lunar module.    Let's return to JFK's dream of a society that has hope, dreams and possibilities and not a society of fear and pre-emptive wars.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A  urlLink Million Worker March  is being planned and it will be good to see workers joining together in a show of unified strength. We need to take to the streets like they did when labor was at its peak of power. We can't be afraid of tear gas, rubber bullets and bloody noses. We can't be afraid to be thrown in a jail cell overnight. We can't be afraid to stand up to what is happening to the working family thru outsourcing, rolling back of worker rights to organize, anti-labor legislation and anti-union corporations such as Wal-Mart who are actively involved in keeping workers powerless and without a voice on the job. Fight for the worker! Stay tuned for further updates on the Million Worker March. 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink LA Times  has a highly interesting analysis on what is happening the liberalism in America and where it is heading. (You'll need to register with the LA Times to read it.)  Here is a snippet:  This is due partly, I think, to the Democratic Party's more-or-less official response to its waning fortunes. The Democratic Leadership Council, the organization that produced such figures as Bill Clinton, Al Gore, Joe Lieberman and Terry McAuliffe, has long been pushing the party to forget blue-collar voters and concentrate instead on recruiting affluent, white-collar professionals who are liberal on social issues. The larger interests that the DLC wants desperately to court are corporations, capable of generating campaign contributions far outweighing anything raised by organized labor. The way to collect the votes and — more important — the money of these coveted constituencies, "New Democrats" think, is to stand rock-solid on, say, the pro-choice position while making endless concessions on economic issues, on welfare, NAFTA, Social Security, labor law, privatization, deregulation and the rest of it.   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink DNC blog  gives us an explanation on why Bush is taking a shorter vacation this year. Bush has taken more vacation time in four years than what most working families will take in their lifetime. Let's put Bush on a permanent vacation starting in January 2005 when John Kerry takes the Oath.
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink Brian Hull  reminds us what a great book  The Jungle  is and to find the uncensored version. Many of us read the censored version in school and much of Upton Sinclaire's socio-political commentary was omitted. This book, more than others, has importance and relevance. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I discovered  urlLink this highly interesting article   on the difference between labor uninions and trial lawyers in the South. All of the states that Mark listed in his post are Right To Work states except for Pennsylvania and West Virginia which so happen to be key battleground states for Bush and Kerry. It is no secret that the GOP supports the Right To Work Foundation and that the South is courting all the auto makers and other manufacturers to build in their states. I don't have the numbers in front of me but I do believe that many of the Southern states have the least-educated workforce in the nation. So the GOP and the Southern business cabal feed on the poor and ignorant to keep their machine greased and running. Anybody can see why the GOP hates trial lawyers and labor unions because they are in the way of their right-wing 'progress'.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The 2004 Democratic Platfrom  was recently released to the public and I'm disappointed that they left out any anti-war language but they submitted resolutions for a strong Iraqi National Defense as an exit strategy for the U.S. troops. There is also a call to end the U.S. dependence on Mideast oil by exporing renewable engergy alternatives. I have not looked at the Republican Platform but I'm sure I won't find any anti-war or renewable energy resolutions. Without a strong third-party cadidate, I'll be voting for the Democratic nominee in 2004 and supporting the anti-war effort.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink DCCC  is optimistic that the Dems can take back the House because of Tom DeLay's questionable fundraising. It'll be a good day when the top GOP snakes in Washington, D.C. slither away back into their holes.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "There's many other people that have gone to prison. Look at Nelson Mandela." Martha Stewart, July 16, 2004  urlLink in an interview with Barbara Walters.      
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Matt Gonzalez  describes the broken two-party political system and why voting for Nader is not a vote for Bush. We need only look at the two major candidates for president to see how much of a failure our political system is. On virtually every level of significance, the candidates appear to be in on the same ticket. 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning's  urlLink Op-Ed &nbsp;by Nicholas D. Kristof&nbsp;of the  New York Times  is&nbsp;very interesting. Apparently, the best selling books in the U.S are religious novels depicting Jesus returning to&nbsp;Earth and casting non-believing leftists into an everlasting fire.  &nbsp;    These are the best-selling novels for adults in the United States, and they have sold more than 60 million copies worldwide. The latest is "Glorious Appearing," which has Jesus returning to Earth to wipe all non-Christians from the planet. It's disconcerting to find ethnic cleansing celebrated as the height of piety.   If a Muslim were to write an Islamic version of "Glorious Appearing" and publish it in Saudi Arabia, jubilantly describing a massacre of millions of non-Muslims by God, we would have a fit. We have quite properly linked the fundamentalist religious tracts of Islam with the intolerance they nurture, and it's time to remove the motes from our own eyes.    I thought that Jesus teached tolerance and an understanding of all people and cultures so how did he turn into a militant? Did I miss that chapter in the Bible? No, this is the right-wing neo-con's new Messiah: a militant Jesus who despises those who don't worship him and a new found hobby of ethnic cleansing. It is a resemblance on today's society that these books are selling so well. Many disconnected people are searching for spiritual answers but a hero returning from the sky and casting the evil villians into an everlasting fire is not reality and its already been told in a story 2,000 years ago. I suggest that people start constructive reading such as finding peaceful ways to curing the earth's problems and wars. In fact, this is what Jesus preached when he walked this earth long ago.&nbsp; Let's hope peace prevails over the Christian Right's Jihad because there will be no hero returning from the sky anytime soon.    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.kokomoperspective.com/new/article.asp?6109   &nbsp; This is a real shocker. Local politicians can only do so much. The real decisions are made in a board room a thousand miles away or on the other side of the globe. 100 workers will be without a job in September in the small town of Kokomo, IN. This is an analogy of what is happening to the larger picture of the Bush economy. What kind of economy will we have when there are no good-paying jobs and people can't pay their mortgages? This economy is going nowhere and nowhere fast.  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://blog.dccc.org/mt/archives/000605.html    And to get back to your question, we're putting our credibility on the line. We think that the election, if the election were held today, there would be no question but the Democrats would take back the House.   Let's hope that we get that chance to have an election. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Arianna  has the lowdown on Bush's flip-flops. Good ammo to defend yourself against your conservative friends. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Mass. may make health care a legal right.  Once again, Mass. leads the way for working families.    The amendment states that "it shall be the obligation and duty of the Legislature and executive officials ... to enact and implement such laws as will ensure that no Massachusetts resident lack comprehensive, affordable and equitably financed health insurance coverage for all medically necessary preventive, acute and chronic health care and mental health care services, prescription drugs and devices."    While debates on gay marriage amendments have gotten headlines, the Mass legislature just voted to put a constitutional amendment to make health care a legal right on the ballot for voters. If they approve it this year and in 2006, the state will become the first in the nation to give health care constitutional status. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it seems that the Federal Marriage Amendment went up in flames today. This was the GOP's last effort to put a wedge between the Dems and the voters. Bush's hopes for a decisive re-election just go darker. Let's see how these neo-Cons conjur up a new wedge issue.  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While Bush is praising the 'slow,steady growth' of the U.S. economy; his job growth prediction is way off the mark as  urlLink Brad DeLong   points out. This is another example of Bush misleading the working families. The Democrats need to jump all over this at the convention in Boston.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll probably watch the DNC Convention, and I'm looking for something to talk about.  With the explosion of blogs on the Internet I'm looking forward to reading what the People's opinions are rather than the mainstream talking heads' scripted responses.  I think the main point of the DNC convention will be to raise the level of political discourse.  Here are five questions I want to have asked at the Convention:  1)  Where is the Democratic Party headed?   This is not something easily presented on commercial media, because the 'he said, she said' style of partisanized reporting obscures intra-party discussions that are not acrimonious.  Nevertheless, this is a critical question that we need to address, and are starting to talk about.  2)  What is the role of the executive branch in our political system?   It's hard to remember a time of legislative importance relative to the executive branch.  Nevertheless, the apogee of the imperial Presidency is the political convention, with a centralized media apparatus focusing entirely on the national election of one man.  It's time we examined this structure.  3)  How can the Democratic Party work to build channels for effective political communication?   What are the obstacles to such channels?  There will not be another chance to ask this question with 15,000 media personalities in one room.  The 'establishment' will all be in attendance - it's time to meet them, learn about them, and figure out how to reconcile the two parallel worlds.  4)  What is the role of bipartisanship in politics?   Is political polarization a bad thing, and if it is, what can the Democrats do about it other than abject surrender?  The most endangered species in politics is the political moderate, both on the left and the right.  What does this mean?  If the coming battle is truly epic, what happens to the losing side?  Will Kerry be impeached if he doesn't take Congress as well as the Presidency?  Now is the time to ponder political extremism, and what the appropriate response might be. Dare I say socialism?  5)  Where is the Democratic party on intellectual property rights?   This is the political issue that concerns the craft of blogging itself - fair use, regulation of the internet, and copyright.  Whether you are at the Convention, watching it on TV or not, please consider making suggestions for what we should be talking about.  Now is not the time to be complacent and passive. Much is at stake; civil liberties, gay marriage rights, a declining labor movement, a weakening of environment laws and regulations, outsourcing of high-paying jobs to lower-paid workers overseas, NAFTA, the list could go on. This is our time to consider the Democratic Party and what it means to oppose Bush's right-wing stranglehold on the issues I just mentioned.  Let's use the time during the DNC convention well because time is running out on our freedoms.  Doug Smiley
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Far-right ideology based in Christian religious beliefs and subsidizing corporate profits for big pharmaceutical companies are the cornerstones of Bush's AIDS policy.   Bush has pushed an abstinence education policy proven to produce the opposite intended effects (more sexual activity and less safe sex) and has demonized the condom use policy advocated by most of the international medical community in compliance with his right-wing religious philosophy. Critics charge him with putting ideology above science, even distorting science to satisfy religious beliefs about reproductive rights, sexuality, and AIDS prevention. See this article.   This ideology also supports the adminsitration's opposition to generic drugs. According to AFP, a Bush-affiliated organization attacked generic drug manufactures at the recent Bangkok Conference, claiming the drugs aren't cheaper, effective, and may be dangerous. Backed by pharmaceutical interests, this campaign seeks to use the $15 billion Bush has promised to subsidize corporate profits at the expense of the people with the disease.   While over 4 million people have died since Bush promised the $15 billion, all he seems concerned with is ideology and profits. This administration is perpetuating an atrocity.  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       U.S. Mulling How to Delay Nov. Vote in Case of Attack  Sun Jul 11,12:00 PM ET       WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. counterterrorism officials are looking at an emergency proposal on the legal steps needed to postpone the November presidential election in case of an attack by al Qaeda, Newsweek reported on Sunday.    urlLink Link   The Bush administration knows that Kerry will sweep the elections in November so they are using the fear tactic. Typical right wing politics. Look for the Homeland Security Department to raise the Terrorest Threat Level soon. We are on the verge of a dictatorship. 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Nathan Newman  gives us some insight into the anemic job growth:   Even more startlingly, of the 509,000 in new total nonagricultural employment from February to June , 495,000 or an astonishing 97% of the cumulative increase were part-time jobs-- showing why the average work week has been dropping so dramatically.  This "recovery" is like no other in post-WWII history. Job growth is anemic and the jobs created generally stink. Profits are soaring, wages are stagnant, and benefits are being slashed.   Nathan makes en excellent case for workers to organize. The high skilled jobs are going to India and other parts of the globe leaving Americans with little to choose from. 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink AFL-CIO Looks Beyond Unions        "Labor's not big enough," Ms. Nussbaum said. "We aren't growing. Our greatest challenge has been growth, and we've been stymied in our efforts. The A.F.L.-C.I.O. is the biggest labor organization in the world, but we're only a small percentage of our work force. We know that's got to change."      A new arm of the labor movement is getting non-union workers involved in issues like health care and minimum wage. If the AFL-CIO can't grow the old way of organizing workers then it will try another way of going door to door, people to people to get out Labor's message.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Greg Palast  tells dubya to cough up the loot from Ken Lay.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink American Editor of Russian Forbes Killed   So it would seem that Putin's government is not putting up with predatory capitalist bandits. It would seem that Mother Russia's interests are more important than Western capitalist thieves who want to plunder Russia's resources.  
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Watch the Dean/Nader debate at the  urlLink NPR  website.  July 9, 2004 -- Independent presidential candidate Ralph Nader and Howard Dean, the ex-governor of Vermont and former Democratic presidential candidate, debate the role of third parties in U.S. elections. Dean argues that Nader's candidacy could help re-elect President Bush in November. Nader says both parties are too beholden to corporate interests. 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Steve Hammer  has just informed us that there is a  urlLink JFK speech on steaming MP3  available for our listening pleasure and education. Was JFK looking 40 years into the future when he spoke these words that have so much meaning for today?
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink World Socialist Web Site  discusses the findings of the New England Journal of Medicine about the effects of the predatory Iraq war is having on U.S. troops. It seems that a large number of service men and women are returing home with post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) and other psychiatric difficulties. War is hell but suffering from a war over a lie is unimaginable. Let's bring the troops home safely and soon. Let's end the U.S. occupation of Iraq and Afghanistan.   A study published July 1 by the New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM) found that one in six soldiers returning from Iraq was suffering from a variety of emotional problems, with lower levels of mental disabilities exhibited among those who served in Afghanistan. The report, conducted by a team from the Walter Reed Army Institute of Research in Washington, D.C., is the first such assessment of war-related psychiatric disorders made while military action is underway. Most studies in the past that have focused on the effects of combat on mental health were performed years after the fighting had ended.    urlLink Read more... 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The U.S. Intelligence Committee released a 511 page report detailing the CIAs error in sending young soldiers to Iraq to die in vain. http://talkleft.com has the lowdown.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's never going to end. Five more US soldiers gave their final measure for Bush's war based on false intelligence. Who knows how many of the 20 "wounded" are going to be scared for life, possibly missing a limb. End the American occupation of Iraq immediately. Bring the troops home safely.   http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/5322157/  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Kenny Boy Ley Indicted   One of capitalism's poster boys will face justice but with Bush in office I'm sure he'll get away with a slap on the wrist. This man single-handedly ruined retirement savings for hundreds of thousands and nearly caused the U.S. stock market to crash. I'm not sure what type of punishment this deserves but I hope the people realize that corporate CEOs and CFOs are not working in the best interest of the shareholders but their own pocket books. Will Americans remember these criminals like they remember Richard Nixon's Watergate scandal? Or will history repeat itself again?   Onward to socialism!
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my opinion, the Democrats are fielding two candidates who are not necessarily anti-war but they do offer a way out of the mess and an end to the suffering of the Iraqi people.   The Democratic platform does not describe the Iraq war as a mistake nor do they call for the withdrawal of US troops from Iraq. It is my hope that the lie that Bush used to go to war will never be forgotten. There were no WMDs and Saddam was never a threat to the US.  Another thing to keep in mind; neither party has denounced a draft that is sure to come if the US maintains its imperialist presence in the Mideast. 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Brian  has one of the best takes on John Edwards being picked at Kerry's running mate.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink U.S. airstrike in Iraq kills 12   One week into Iraqi Sovereignty... U.S. forces drop two tons of bombs on a purported militant safe house in Fallujah, killing at least 10 people.   Which begs the question, WHAT THE FUCK? But seriously, if the Iraqis are liberated now, does that mean they are ordering the US to bomb them? Hmm...yeah, another daily lesson for us not to believe jack shit.  
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks to John for  urlLink pointing out  this imortant date in labor history.  July 5 is also an important date; it marks the 70th anniversary of Bloody Thursday, the most dramatic day of the San Francisco General Strike. This strike gave birth to the International Longshore and Warehouse Union (ILWU), which broke from the mobbed-up International Longshoremens' Association (ILA) that is still the dominant union on the East Coast.   The general strike was a watershed moment in labor history that gave birth to much else besides, including -- so I am told -- SEIU Local 250, the country's first healthcare workers' union, and a local which today probably has at least twice the membership of the entire ILWU. What the ILWU lacks in size, though, they can make up for in potential power -- the ability to shut down the ports is no small power. They have often done it not only for their own betterment but for higher political purposes: from the boycotts against imperial Japan and apartheid South Africa to the political strikes against the imprisonment of Mumia Abu-Jamal, the WTO, and the war in Iraq, the ILWU has not only bargained but unilaterally imposed conditions and lent strength to prominent political struggles. For this, they have always faced repression, from the time the government tried to revoke the citizenship of ILWU president Harry Bridges and have him deported (he was an Australian immigrant, and they said he had falsified his citizenship application when he said he was not a member of the Communist Party; this may have been true, and I have seen it said that Bridges was not only a Party member but a member of the Central Committee -- but I haven't paid much attention to the details, and quite frankly, who cares if he was?) to the first use of a Taft-Hartley injunction not against a strike but in the case of a lockout, under the current George Bush.   So everyone should give a shout-out to the ILWU and to the continuing American Revolution, beginning with a rededication to our task at hand for this November.  
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink MaxSpeak  has the lowdown on last Friday's Job Growth numbers and Bush's overusage of "confident" and "steady growth" terminology.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Those who profess to favor freedom, and yet depreciate agitation, are men who want rain without thunder and lightning." -- Frederick Douglass   "All men having power ought to be distrusted to a certain degree." -- James Madison   "I distrust who know so well what God wants them to do because I notice it always coincides with their own desires." -- Susan B. Anthony   "It is the first duty of every citizen to question authority." -- Benjamin Franklin   "War is an instrument entirely inefficient toward redressing wrong; and multiplies, instead of indemnifying losses." -- Thomas Jefferson   "True patriotism hates injustice in its own land more than anywhere else." -- Clarence Darrow 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink New York Fire, Police Unions Say Talks At Impasse   Strike During GOP Convention Possible  POSTED: 12:08 pm EDT August 10, 2004 UPDATED: 8:30 am EDT August 11, 2004  NEW YORK -- Police and firefighters announced an impasse Tuesday in their contract negotiations with the Bloomberg administration, refusing to rule out a strike or sickouts during the Republican National Convention.  "Everyone has a limit, and the mayor needs to know we're close to our limit," said Stephen Cassidy, president of the Uniformed Firefighters Association, at a press conference at City Hall.  For the last two weeks or so, off-duty police officers have been showing up at Mayor Michael Bloomberg's daily public appearances and picketing outside Madison Square Garden, the site of the Republican National Convention beginning Aug. 30.   Several other city unions, such as District Council 37, the city's largest, have already accepted a 5 percent raise plus $1,000 over three years with 2 percent coming from productivity enhancements such as lower pay and benefits for new hires.  A mayor's spokesman said Tuesday that the city's last offer to the police and fire unions was a $1,000 lump sum payment plus an 8 percent pay hike -- though 5 percent of the raise would come from productivity enhancements.  The police and firefighter unions said they had no intention of accepting productivity enhancements, which they denounced as "givebacks."  Police have been without a contract since July 31, 2002, and firefighters since May 31, 2002. The situation fits a pattern of retroactive contracts and negotiations that routinely ignore expiration dates and end in arbitration.  But Tuesday, the police and fire union representatives said they deserve more significant raises than other city employees. The police union declared an impasse in its negotiations with the city several weeks ago, while the firefighters said they reached the same conclusion this week.  "Mike Bloomberg says we're no different than people that push paper," said Cassidy. "That's a joke. It's a disgrace. It's an insult to the firefighters and police officers who risk their lives every day."  Bloomberg has said the city cannot afford to give significant raises to municipal unions.  "Using the DC 37 framework which has been used to reach agreements with 140,000 city employees, we have offered both unions raises of up to 8 percent with a $1,000 lump sum but about half would be funded by productivity enhancements, which both unions have balked at," said Bloomberg spokesman Ed Skyler. "In the meantime, it doesn't matter what tactics they use, the mayor isn't going to be intimidated into making a bad deal for the city."  Leaders of the police and fire unions also said they would not guarantee that they would not strike -- even though such a move is barred by law.  "We must keep in mind that the frustration level is high and we cannot count anything out in our struggle," said Patrick Lynch, president of the Patrolmen's Benevolent Association. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If the capitalist free-market should prove to fail, as it looks to according to the recent performance of Wall Street, what shall replace our current system. Surely an economic system that benefits all citizens and not just the wealthy could be within our grasp. We have the common decency as a people to ensure the means of production does not have power over the means of consumption. I propose we move towards a socialist America based on Marxist theories. We can offer free universal healthcare to all and offer a decent standard of living for those willing to work in the new system. The competition to get ahead of your neighbor would be eliminated because we have conquered the corporate rule over society. Let's move towards socialism and a more human society and replace Wall Street with Main Street America.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lately, there hav been several articles and other commentaries on the terror risk to Americans.  urlLink Here is a chilling Op-Ed article in today's  New York Times   that says we are at the greatest risk of a nuclear bomb destroying a U.S. city since the Cold War.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink  It's No Accident  reminds us how good it feels when a fraud is removed from the U.S. presidency such as when Nixon resigned thirty years ago . I hope we can feel the same sense of relief after Kerry is legally elected in November and we send Bush back to Crawford.
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Massive demonstrations planned during the NYC GOP convention . According to  urlLink this article ; %83 of New Yorkers are opposed to hosting the convention. It should be an interesting week.   Thanks to  urlLink Bombs and Shields  for pointing out this good news.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Here is some in-depth analysis of the current state of the U.S. economy  and where it may be heading depending on how much the foreign investors pull out or invest.  Dramatically, the US$ has signalled it will go weaker, after some tap-dancing noise. Wall Street indicators say a meltdown is underway, that may accelerate into a sell-off. Momentum swing counts say perhaps back to October 2002's levels ( "soft landing" ) and perhaps back to 1995's levels - e.g. to S&P500 535 ( an unexpected "hard landing").  Which indicators say a meltdown is underway? Well, have a look at the massive price relativity patterns being tested or already showing support failure on the US Dow Jones Industrial Average, Dow Jones Transports, US Airline Index, NASDAQ Composite Index, S&P 500, S&P Retail Index, Morgan Stanley Consumer Index, Philadelphia Bank Sector Index -- and while speaking about banks, have a look at J.P. Morgan ["JPM" -- NYSE] . $Gold gapped up $8.00 today.   My forte is not investments but clearly anyone can see that the economy is having problems if you read newspapers such as the  Wall Street Journal  and  The New York Times .  urlLink Here is another article on a similar theme  but focuses on George Soros' opinion on the economy. With the American economy so reliant on oil and China's exlposive growth and their hunger for oil, until we move from an oil-based economy we as Americans will lose our "superpower" status in the very near future. If you ask me what to do with your extra cash on hand, I would suggest puting it in a money market fund at your local bank or under your mattress.
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Brian  continues to write well at his blog.  urlLink His latest post about the recent Bureau of Labor Statistics report on job creation is highly interesting .  Jobs are a commodity that can be and are currently being exploited and manipulated to maximize profits. Descent jobs are scarce and eager workers are plentiful to fill those positions. Demand is greater than supply which lends to a downward pressure of wages. It’s a race for workers to find descent jobs while the market is flooded with other workers looking for descent jobs, so it’s only natural for companies to offer less money for the same position, because someone out there will fill it. It’s only natural, but it’s not fair, it’s not moral and it’s why we see companies that are making record profits reduce their labor costs by shipping jobs overseas, or closing union factories and opening non-union factories, or outsourcing their work to contract workers so health benefits are no longer the responsibility of the company.   It's time workers realize that we are all one class...a working class and that the ruling class has failed us. Thus, we must take action..strong action to regain what we have lost. I propose building a Workers Party or Labor Party (not the Labour Party of Tony Blair) that will fight for the working class. A workers' revolution is in order and is long overdue.
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a highly interesting article posted at  urlLink AlterNet . I wanted to blog about the abuse but after reading this article my heart is saddened by what is happening at U.S. prisons at home and abroad. This is a must-read article for anyone interested in human rights.   Our soldiers abroad seem to have acted out behaviors that Americans condone, yet don't face up to, at home – some of the most sadistic practices employed in the U.S. prison system.    When we tolerate abuse in U.S. prisons and jails, it should not surprise us to find U.S. soldiers using similar methods in Iraq.  George Bush said he was exporting democracy to Iraq, but he seems to have exported a much uglier aspect of American public policy – some of the most sadistic practices employed in the U.S. prison system.     Read entire article  urlLink here .
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink From today's  New York Times  :  The fallout from the hiring slump has spread to many employed workers in recent months, as pay raises have failed to keep up with inflation. Over the last 12 months, weekly pay for rank-and-file workers, who make up about four-fifths of the work force, has risen only 2.3 percent, while prices have increased more than 3 percent. But the best sign in yesterdays otherwise grim report may have been the earnings gain in July, erasing an outright decline in June. Average weekly pay for rank-and-file workers rose $3.25, to $529.09, in July.   Could it be that the reason why the weekly pay for rank-and-file workers rose is because the employers are squeezing as much time from them as possible. Employers may not be hiring new employees but they are working the current employees as much as possible thus the increase in weekly pay. This is a growing trend among employers. Recently,  urlLink DaimlerChrysler and Siemens fought for and won longer working hours from the German labor unions in an area where unemployment is at 9% . In this new class war, it will be the worker against employer, it will be worker salary and benefits against corporate profits and investor dividends. The battlefield is on an international level where the worker is not able to move to another country like the corporation. If labor is to have any fight at all it needs to organize the workers in China and East Asia.
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink Only 32,000 jobs were created last month . This was bad news for workers and it was bad news for the Bush campaign.  urlLink The stock market ended at its lowest level of the year today  as the U.S. economy sputters and bleeds jobs.  "It's a huge disappointment, a big surprise," said Scott Brown, chief economist at Raymond James in St. Petersburg, Fla.    Economists said the data, coming only days before the Federal Reserve (news - web sites)'s next meeting, showed the economy had yet to regain momentum after a speed bump in June. Expectations on Wall Street had centered on a 228,000-job gain.      urlLink The economic outlook for next week  is pending on the Federal Reserve's interest rate decision and on the fluctuating price of oil.   However, analysts see little relief from the market's current malaise, as investors fret about oil prices at 21-year highs, geopolitical worries and the economy losing steam.  U.S. stocks closed at the lowest levels of the year on Friday after weaker-than-expected data from the July jobs report stirred investors' fears that the U.S. economic recovery may be weak.   What does all this mean? It means if you have a job today you should count your blessings and pray it will not be outsourced. It means that if you are in school you should get the best education possible because competition for the remaining U.S. jobs will be stiff not to mention competing with foreigners who come here to work. It means our economy is not the same one just ten years ago. Globalization has made its mark on the job market. Labor is a commodity and it is now an international commodity. I'm not so sure things would be different if Gore had been in office or how much things will change when Kerry becomes president. There need to be real change for the situation of the working class to improve and it is my opinion that time is running out. Things could very well get worse. Labor is a commodity and the investor class is wanting the job done for the lowest cost even if it means massive job losses here at home. Welcome to the reality of class warfare.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Central Labor Council  will be hosting a massive non-violent demo during the GOP convention. It sounds fun. It's time like this that I feel left out of the action by living in Indiana. But then again, it's times like this that calls for each citizen to be active. I suppose Indianapolis could use a non-violent demo during the Labor Day weekend. But more than likely we'll just go along with the flow.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink A research study funded by the Natural Resources Defense Council has concluded that air pollution will become a bigger health problem in the near future.   By mid-century, the number of summer days with good air quality will decline 26 percent, from an average 50 days per summer to 37 days, the study found.  That, in turn, could lead to more hospitalizations for respiratory diseases, such as asthma, researchers said.     It is my opinion that cleaner burning fuels need to be used. Europe is using a clean version of diesel fuel. America should also use cleaner diesel for heavy trucks. This would help but in general, people need to find alternatives to driving such as commuting, biking, walking or using public tranportation.  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink UFCW Canada has organized Wal-Mart in Quebec.   "This is great victory for the workers in Jonquière, and for Wal-Mart workers everywhere," said Michael J. Fraser, UFCW Canada's national director.   "Wal-Mart is on the record stating they support workplace democracy," said Fraser. "The majority of workers in Jonquière have spoken, so we expect Wal-Mart to listen and get down to negotiating a first contract without delay."    This is a step in the right direction for workers everywhere who are employed at Wal-Mart. With a  urlLink sex-discrimination class action lawsuit  hanging over their head, it would make good business sense to not fight unionization and cause even more bad news for themselves.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Used by New York labor unions to designate worksites using non-union labor-the rat. He and his union brothers will be welcoming the GOP to New York.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The DNC's Blog  urlLink gives us the lowdown  on the reaction, or lack thereof, of President Bush to the 9/11 Commission Recommendations. urlLink    Americans want to believe — and should be able to believe — that no matter how partisan the administration is, some things are beyond the reach of politics. Terror alerts ought to be one of those things. We ought to be confident that when a special report breaks in with news that the nation's security level has been raised, that it's not being manipulated for political ends.  But when Tom Ridge uses the announcement to campaign for President Bush and when the rise in alert status comes as the result of no new intelligence, why should we be surprised that many Americans and various news outlets have started to question whether these alerts are politically motivated?     Using fear as a political tactic is uncivilized but considering that the GOP is not civilized I'm not surprised at their logic of fearmongering the public.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Here is a detailed article  on the damage Bush had done to working America. In summary, 5.3 million workers lost their job between January 2001 and December 2003. Younger workers are finding jobs but they are lower-paying and offer less benefits.  In addition, finding new jobs remains difficult, an indication of the slow economic growth in recent years. According to the DOL, about 65 percent of the long-tenured displaced were re-employed at the time of the survey. Further, it appears longer-term or chronic unemployment is disproportionally affecting older workers. In January 2004, re-employment rates for workers ages 20 to 24 and those in the middle-age group (ages 25 to 54) were 65 percent and 69 percent, respectively. By comparison, re-employment rates were lower for older workers ages 55 to 64 (56 percent) and 65 years and older (24 percent). Large proportions of older displaced workers were not in the labor force when surveyed, having left as what the DOL refers to as "discouraged workers." 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ACLU rejects $500,000 in response to "blacklist" rules   NEW YORK - In a letter sent today to the head of the Combined Federal Campaign, which administers charitable donations from federal and state employees to more than 2,000 non-profits, the American Civil Liberties Union said that it would reject $500,000 in contributions from private individuals rather than submit to a government "blacklist" policy.   If an organization wants to live under such draconian rules, fine -- but the ACLU apparently isn't inclined to sell out its own employees. And while forgoing half a million in funding on principle is pretty ballsy, that shortfall will be made up in part by increased donations from other sources who admire their stand.  The ACLU has inspired me to donate more money in response to their principled stance. There is no reason why the government needs to know the names of an organization's donors. Either the organization is a security threat or it's not. Monitoring the names of donors is ineffective as a security precaution, as well as a privacy invasion that takes us straight down the road of blacklisting and McCarthyism.  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The latest from Soldiers For The Truth .  "McCaffrey always said that it was going to take someone getting hurt or killed before our leaders wake up and not run us into the ground," says Soldier No. 5. "Now that he and the lieutenant got killed, I still see no upward learning curve from our officers."    Incompetent. From the current brass on down this is a disaster. This is a failure of leadership which is as profound as the Viet Nam war.  We are going to pay for this for a long time. Rummy has gutted the top brass who actually knew what they were doing and it will take a generation to raise up a new coterie, under the best of circumstances. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CounterPunch has an  urlLink interesting interview  with Noam Chomsky.  MIT Professor Noam Chomsky is one of the world's most perceptive social critics. I had the opportunity recently to ask him some questions concerning a range of subject matter. Professor Chomsky's latest book is Hegemony or Survival: America's Quest for Global Dominance. Other works, many recently reissued, include American Power and the New Mandarins, Manufacturing Consent, and Deterring Democracy.   Professor Chomsky goes into depth discussing the Bush administrations interventions in Haiti and the rising progressive movement in Latin America.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will be rare plug on my blog. Please visit  urlLink The Progressive Book Club  and sign up.  Special thanks to  urlLink Atrios .
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Steve Greenhouse of the  New York Times  writes about the internal feud among labor unions . Meanwhile,  urlLink airlines look to stay afloat by shedding pension funds . Clearly, the AFL-CIO has its work cut out whether Kerry wins in November or not.
    
</post>


</Blog>