<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok This might be a bit of a heavy start to my blog, but I really didn't want to start with a stupid "first post yay!" kind of thing.   anyway this is an email I sent to "Helga the help" the resident concerning the replies she/he got from a newsletter concerning Islamic people.    urlLink     I sent helga an email telling him/her my thoughts on religion, and helga was cool enough to reply :).  anyway I just thought you might want to read it.    note: I am not a racist, I only hate all religions :)     -----Original Message----- From: sporadicmedia [mailto:pevee@sporadicmedia.com] Sent: Saturday, May 15, 2004 7:12 AM To: helga@liquidgeneration.com Subject: islamic people are stupid!+my thoughts on religion  http://www.liquidgeneration.com/helga/?st=8  These letters are just a prime example of how stupid Islamic people are.  The world would be a better place without religion.  All religion is based on fear, "if you don't believe you will burn in hell".  People cant sort out there own problems so they turn to a church or other religious house of damnation and get told what to think, and how to live there life's.  To me that is so wrong.  I myself was forced into the catholic faith when I was barely out of my soiled nappies.  Another person deciding that there child should be involved in a religion before they can even speak is bullshit.  I was taught that this was what I should believe in and how I should live my life. I was being lied to. Ever since I realised I could be in control of my life, and I researched the catholic faith, coming to the realisation that I did not believe in some of the Catholic Church's ethics and greatly disagreed with parts of it.  So now I Type as a happy atheist, knowing I can live my life the way I want it as a good respectable citizen of the UK.  Don't even get me started with the rest of those cults, err, I mean religions.  So that's my 2 cents, whether you wanted it or not.   Steven McVeigh, 15  , United Kingdom       after a few days of thinking that I wasn't going to get one, I received a reply     Hi Steven!   Thanks for your input!   I hope that the extremists that draw their arbitrary line in the sand simply so they can have something to believe and someone to hate will soon be marginalized into the bowels of history along with the Roman Empire. Unfortunately, unlike the Romans, who, for all of their flaws, presided over one of the greatest expansions in military evolution, the fundamentalists have not really had a single worthy contribution or single original thought for which we will remember them.   If the "15" after your name is your age then I must admit to more than a little jealousy because when I was 15, I still believed everything people told me. More power to you.   All my love,   Helga     I hope this constitues as an interesting blog post :)    bye bye's!  pevee   P.S. Lindsay Lohan is freekin hot!  urlLink   
     
    
</post>


<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeh, with only days to go, the new series of The Sleepover Club begins this Tuesday!  I know,  Pevee  cannot wait, can you?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      FOOOK MI! the aliens am cuming...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       http://www.saddleclubtv.com/home.htm   THESE FOOKIN HOES HAV NOTHING ON  TSC    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the new series of the sleepover club is gonna be sooooo good!  ive got a hard on just thinking about it!      M3MB3RZ GALZ DOU GOTTA'R B3Z K00LZ!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yep - We are all missing you Sleepover Club!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Because of the Football,  The Sleepover Club , is no longer being shown.  Pevee wants to make a petition. But I said, let them have their Football, not like they going to win.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My absense has been because of a heavy dosage of anthetmines that I took when i found out they weren't new episode.  BUT NOW I KICKED THE HABIT!  I attended lynny rhodes drug clinic, and all is well now.  to show my disgust to CITV i present you with the "council estate ugly sleepover gals"   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pevee is really sorry about his posts (ie. the lack of them). I have asked him to post tomorrow.  But I can just feel it in my bones, that I will have to badger him.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yea - Life goes on! Its weekdays, and Sleepover Club is back!  Today's episode, 2 of the member had a little bit of a fall out. But they soon patched it up :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Only hours to go, till our next filling of The Sleepover Club.  Good luck to Tom (and anyone else), who is talking exams over this coming week!   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is the weekend, so  The Sleepover Club  is not on!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You are a  fool !  Stop talking rubbish, thank you.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I watched "the sleepover club" for the first time today, and at the risk of pevee killing her self, it was nothing special.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Although it is just repeats, we still cannot miss it!   Pevee  is getting over this day, by day.. Just give him time.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      CITV seem to be pretty good at the storytelling. They have tried to make it "sound", like the episodes they are currently broadcasting, are from some  new  series.  They are infact just repeating the previous series, which they have already shown. I can also say that, because of this  Pevee  has been very upset, and has not felt able to write a review.    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         ARRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRGH  ARE YOU FOOKIN READY!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have my  lube  ready,  do you?    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes! Only a few hours to go now.  We cannot wait, I am sure  Pevee  will post a review, as soon as the episode has been broadcasted.  Although he may need a few minutes, "private" time.    
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>