<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am watching The Man Who Fell To Earth,with David Bowie, its very interessting adn exciting (Sci-Fi) Thats just about it right now folks stay tuned for a nother day of blogging coming soon. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its now 7:19 and i'm listening to make up, or wig in a box from the musical, Hedwig And The Angry Inch, i'm not sure if i've told you about it already but any way its a romantic, dramatic, comedic, musical journey through a little german boy named hansel's life. It all starts when Hansel is laying on a bomb crater that he's found near home. sun bathing naked, face down. (in east berlin, at this time the wall is erected) and an American G.I, Sgt. Luther Robinson, who is obviosly trying to abduct poor little hansel. Luther: Girl, I sure don't mean to annoy you but, My name is Sgt. Luther Robinson. (Hansel turns over revealing his penis, or his "little bishop in a turtle neck" Hansel: I'm Hansel. Luther is silent and then offers him candy, he takes it runs off, and goes back the next day to find Luther, luther tells him he loves him, they get married after, Hansel gets a botched sex change operation, Hense the "Angry inch", Luther leaves him, hansel finds a boy named tommy, they colaborate and make music, tommy runs off after finding Hansels (now hedwig, using his mothers name) inch and uses his music to becaome a rock and roll icon, and hedwig shadows his tour with his band "the angry inch". GO BUY IT GOD DAMMIT!  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my brother hates teh normal and he hates warm leatherette, i dont expect you to know them, i'm just complaining about everyones ignorance and stupidity that they cant enjoy some orgasmic classic new wave techno... thats all, thast all i have to say please leave me, just leave.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its a new day, i didnt brush my teeth last night or this morning, its 11:36 and i havent ate breakfast, and my aunt is coming over for her birthday and i have nothing for her, as you can see i'm very well on top of things, one day closer to the next day and one day closer to death, lets celebrate... golden years, gold, wop wop wop.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.myrobotfriend.com a very impressive tehcno band  www.ebaumsworld.com hillarious site with humorous footage, go and laugh your ass off www.bibliomania.com now this is impressive, find almost any book you want and read it online. go and read.  visit these sites and have some god damned fun!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The wind is changing, i feel it in my gut the door has swung and swayed before but never has it shut this pain i feel, can it be real i feel i want to read the letter without opening the seel this feeling has makes my face light up this feeling is crushing me i'm falling this feeling is ruining me i'm bawling i feel my stomac falling i am falling i am falling i have fallen 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my head is made of sperm and my car is made out of warm leatherette and my boyfreind is made out of plastic what a world... this great man ... this is crap.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We're watched in the home and we're watched while we sleep, and its all this gorvernment we love to much. Its time to put rhe cap on the camera and enjoy ourselves by ourselves and brush out teeth in peace. Do you understand? We're televised and doped by tv and relgion. Shut them up punch em in teh teeth and we can live in peace goddammit! Get it?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is myself. the male female.. tis a rare breed... tis.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i greet thee! welcom to my "blog" I'me here to ramble on about my life and my goings on. well sit back with a bottle of absinthe in hand and listen to me god dammit!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i havent posted in a while. my appologies. I've just been a bit put off since i killed my Fiancé. its starting to haunt me. ssshhhh. dont tell a soul. no words.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>