<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just looking at a webpage dealing with the Chinese year chart.  Turns out I was born in the year of the 'Sheep' and my element is 'Earth' (Stability, reliability, practicality, industry, prudence).  I think I'll take a few moments to tear this stuff apart...  The Sheep:  "Socially, domestically and politically, people belonging to the Sheep category are the least likely to make waves."  - Um, I can be a pain in the ass because I sometimes make waves... *shrugs*   "They respect order and pay attention to rules and regulations that are laid down by laws and by society." - I've always thought I've had a rebelious spirit...  "Whether it is because Sheep are such nice and pleasant people or whether it is because they are born under a lucky star, fortune seems to favor them." - Since when do I have good luck and fortune?  Bleh, I don't believe in luck anyway.  "Yet many seem one way or another to attract success and money whether through legacies, patronage or popular acceptance via the mass media." - Does this mean I'll be famous?  O.o  "Endowed with innate intelligence and artistic talent, the Sheep will fare well in business." - Can't argue with that :P  "They can be a bit too undisciplined and at times show a morose, misanthropic side." - Yup.   "Although Sheep prefer an uncomplicated, easy life, free of conflict or problems, if danger appears, especially when it is a matter of saving their own life or that of others, Sheep are extremely combative and put up a ferocious battle." - Grrrr, rowr! Don't mess with a mamma bear.  "They leave decision-making to others, but cannot be forced to follow a path they do not like." - Partially true...  "Their lack of self control and the mysterious delays which beset their lives make people lose patience with them easily." - I'm a pain in the ass then?  "And though they can make themselves agreeable when they want to, more often Sheep take advantage of others, sometimes even living entirely at their expense." - That ain't my bag baby!  "Sheep are frequently religious, but whatever religion it is, it will only be praticed to the point where it interfers with their comfort and everyday routine. They are not prepared to put themselves out for it, although Sheep are often drawn to the fantastic, the supernatural, occultism and the reading of horoscopes." - I am religious but not into supernatural/occult stuff... and I swear this is the first horoscope thingie I've looked at seriously.   "Generally, those born in the Year of the Sheep are attracted to the Arts and many are highly creative. But they are practical too, so that for them Art must also be functional and, conversely, everyday functional objects must also reflect inherent beauty." - This is fairly true... I feel like I have lots of creativity, just don't have a good place to use it for a practical purpose.  "With their strong artistic inclinations, it is not surprising that Sheep-folk have a keen eye for beauty and that they simply adore exquisite things. Just as psychologically they need peace and harmony, so physically they need to be surrounded by beauty both in their living and working environment. Without pleasant or conducive surroundings these people could so easily become depressed and dispirited." - I do prefer quality things (good, expensive chocolates etc.), mostly expensive things I can't afford.  Yeah... I have a tendency to become depressed and dispirited when I'm unhappy with my surroundings.  "Sheep don't believe in saving money and would rather overspend on luxuries." - I have $17.45 in the bank... *blinks*   "If you have a nice country home full of good things and good conversation, frequented by artists, don't ever let a Sheep through the door -- with his love of creature comforts, you may never be able to get rid of him!" - That's not very nice to say!    "The Sheep often struggles in youth. The second phase of the Sheep's life will be tempestuous romantically, but there will be a lot of luck in old age. This is because all the good deeds that the kind-hearted Sheep does for others return to him." - You reap what you sow?  Hmm... I'm in trouble.  I just know I'm gonna be the old lady with the house of 100 cats.  "Romantic problems are often frequent in the life of the Sheep and because of this he may experience emotional agitation. In matters of Love, it is the Sheep's heart which rules its head. These people work best as part of a team, so a secure, stable and loving relationship is essential for their emotional well-being." - Well, I've had nothing but shitty relationships so far.. too married, too young, too dishonest (cheater!), too much of a coward (asshole!).  "Perhaps more than any other sign, Sheep are home-lovers and are tailor-made for marriage and family life." - Right... and this explains why I'm still not married??  "Next to love and security, they crave peace and harmony, consequently they will bend over backwards within their relationships to keep things running smoothly. As they hate discord of any kind their partners shouldn't ever expect them to get embroiled in an argument for these people will simply retreat into silence." - Yeah, that's pretty much true.  "As lovers they can be clingy and dependent. They like to associate with others stronger than themselves." - Stronger than me, yes... not sure about the clingy and dependant part though.  "Highly sensual, they adore physical contact; however, despite all their need for tranquility, partners of Sheep should note that these people want what they want and will all too often wear down opposition with protestations in order to get their own way." - You know it!  "Sheep women dream of marriage with a rich man, an affaire with a generous boyfriend, or a liaison with some influential patron. Failing this, she will be happy living at home with wealthy parents."  - No, no, and no... hmm...  "She is the stuff of which are made courtesans, prostitutes, management consultants, public relations officers and other parasites." - Wow prostitution... and just when I lost all hope of finding a good career!  "She is also the stuff of which great artists and writers are made." - Booyah!  "The Sheep's color is pink." - What's up with that!?!?  I don't wear pink! :|   -- Listening to... Linkin Park - My December --
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is my first post, yay!  How exciting... bleh.    Anyway, I've decided to rant about my work.  I work at a gas station right now as I take some time off from school (university).  The pay is crap ($7.60/hour) and there is a lot of politics.  I've been there for a year now and I technically have seniority but my manager is dicking me around.  She's not giving me enough hours so I have no money right now.  I have to get a new job, one that pays more than $10/hour so that I can get my own place.  Getting tired of being screwed over, being forced to train people in one shift (which is impossible), and watching people I've become friends with quit because of all the shit.  Bleh...   -- Listening to... Hoobastank - The Reason --
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lately I haven't been doing a whole lot.  Getting up at noon then sitting at the computer in my chat rooms just joking around with people.  Sometimes I download some music.  This sucks.  Its not all that fun and its not productive.  I need to start getting my act together.  Today I at least looked for a new job and printed off some possibilities to send my resume to.  While I did that I still didn't send the resumes themselves.  BUT, it stops here.    I work tonight so I'll try to catch up on my reading tonight.  Tomorrow I will get up early.  7:00 AM sounds good.  I'll update my resume and write up some cover letters then send them out.  I work at noon until 6:00PM so I'll leave it at that for the morning.  However, in the evening I should do some cleaning and laundry.  I can do my laundry while I clean the basement in general.  Need to throw out some garbage and stuff.  After the basement is acceptable, I'll try cleaning my room, then my office.  I think I'll leave the kitty litter until Saturday morning.    I'll be happier when things are neat and tidy.  I should make a list of things to get done for this coming week as well.  Anyway, gotta go to work...   -- Listening to... Alicia Keys -  If I Ain't Got You --
     

    
</post>


</Blog>