<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   After a lot of thought behind whether to blog or not, here I am. The first step being finding the right nomenclature. Even after I found one (and more), someone else probably had opted it already.  Finally ended up with the word 'quotidian', couldnt get this off my mind, because this is what life is all about, routine and ordinary. Albeit this too was not available, I suffixed it with life, since that is what I would be writing about.   Lets see how the experiment works out.   As for today, its a Sunday. The best of all days (or is it Saturday, since the next day is Sunday?). Ended up solving the crosswords and jumbled words in Indian Express with KS and PV. Once I had intended to write an anagram solver on my own, but like most of my other attempts, this too didnt end where it should have. But today, the attempt revived only to find that there are hundreds of anagram solvers available for free.. so why reinvent the wheel?   Well, a good option.. but doesnt it help you to go through the grind of writing an anagram solver? Point to ponder.. but I got my work done, have to wait for the results next weekend.   Watched 'Passion of the Christ' yesterday. Really gory! Didnt evoke any other emotion. I was wondering whether I might be convinced to get converted to Christianity after the movie.. but that was not to be. A lot of people even today die such painful deaths (the Iraqi prisoners or more commonly people dying of prolonged illness).   The land of Palestine and Israel associated with the Jesus of Nazareth is still bubbling under savagery and bloodshed. Is there ever going to be an end to this? 

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   25 years before, on this day, I came into this world! Completely unaware of the life that I was going to live on and the kind of person that I would be. What must have the feeling been like? To be born?  It is never easy to let go of anything in life, whether good or bad, once it becomes a habit.   Its a good feeling to complete a milestone. And I would say that I was rather successful, of course interpersed with big failures (failure in terms of the end result, but not in terms of the struggle involved).   I hope to become a better person by the day. God bless me with opportunities and the perserverance to see them to completion. Stay with me in good and bad times! You are me and I am you! Thank You! 

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yet another week gone.   I have started swimming. Kicking the first day and sinking the next, floating the third day and sinking again. Its a great experience and ever since I started it, one could say those 45 minutes in the morning when I am inside the pool trying to learn is the best in the whole day.   Its been raining cats and dogs here in Pune. Its not torrential, but enough to irritate you at times, especially when you reach home at 9 after a hard day's work, totally drenched and find that you have to cook and eat alone.   I was reading 'Golf and the Spirit' by M. Scott Peck. This author has got me hooked. I really liked 'The Road less Travelled' and now this one. Some day, when I have enough money to spend on golf, I would like to learn the game. My only exposure to golf so far has been the miniature golf (for very small kids) at Tasmania.   A few quotes over the week:  a) There was once a man, who felt that the secrets of his success were his self-determination and self-reliance. He had very little gratitude.  b) A philosophical definition of 'passion' and 'affection' : Passion is the pleasure or pain arising from the prospect of future pleasure or pain. Affection is the 'desire consequent thereupon'.   Learning philosophy or psychology, doesnt make you a better person, it takes as many years of practice and penance to reach the state of 'nirvana' as for a person who doesnt understand the Ps. Only that reading the Ps makes you more aware. Once again, it is full of debates and discussions with no end in sight. If there is light at the end of the tunnel, its probably the headlight of a train coming right opposite to you.  Anyway, live on... 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What makes me get back here? What makes me want to speak out and write? Perhaps, its the need for a sounding board.   And a sounding board that doesnt respond or judge you is what a blog can provide.   Watched Mani Ratnam's latest flick 'Yuva' yesterday. The direction as such has the Ratnam taste and the story as such was also good. But somehow, it didnt strike a chord with me. It speaks about awakening amongst the youth. Although my head says that people should be aware and awakened, I think I myself am half dead. As in, I dont really care the way the country is moving ahead.   There was a time when I felt I could change the world, but now it simply doesnt affect me. There are always going to be rich people and poor people. What am I going to do?   I really appreciate Gandhiji in that respect. How could he get so many men and women to die for Satyagraha? That was MASS AWAKENING. It doesnt need a story teller or a movie. It needs a role model.   People just grow up without any guidance. Most parents themselves are a confused lot. What can they give to their children? There is no goal, no aim... probably India got freedom when it didnt know what to do with the freedom.   Should I appear for an IAS? Is that the way to go? I dont think so... If you really are interested, it doesnt take an IAS or an IIT or an IIM to anything.   Sometimes, the best option is to do nothing but wait...  Phew, I am becoming a 100% cynic.   Set small goals and achieve them. Talk to people, know what they think, exchange ideas and be OPEN. Thats the key.  Lets wait and watch.  And yet another happening, after a long wait for 122 years, I was lucky enough to see the Venus transit between the Earth and the Sun through KS's telescope. Astronomical changes keep happening, but the astrological significance definitely lacks logic. People publish predictions and the truth in it remains to be seen.  Once again, lets wait and watch.  

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Its been a week since I last blogged. It had been a good week. I am starting to learn to be friendly with people.   There is something that has changed. I have started practising to shift thoughts from things that distract and disturb me. There are other activities, a whole lot of nice people around. I just have to be open minded.  The other day I saw a woman speak on TV. She had been battling with cancer for a year, overcame it and she said something really true 'Its your choice' whether to be happy or sad.   Everybody in this world has some story to tell, if only you could give an ear, empathize with them...I need to learn to do that. Break the barrier that I have created myself.  Had a nice lunch with nice people PV and KS on Saturday at Ambience. Simple food, few people around. Its good to be with people like them. People who are just there, they dont judge you or form opinions.   Yesterday watched 'Hum Tum', a nice movie (very similar to 'When Harry met Sally'). It really shows how men are when it comes to commitment. Women are naturally stronger at heart and come with extraordinary determination.   I feel proud that I am a woman.   I am grateful to God for the best mom, best brother, good job and supportive people around. Its upto me to not revert back to the past. And I know I will be alright.  And above all, God is with me!   

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Your thought is a tree rooted deep in the soil of tradition and whose branches grow in the power of continuity.My thought is a cloud moving in the space.&nbsp; It turns into drops which, as they fall, form a brook that sings its way into the sea.&nbsp; Then it rises as vapour into the sky.    &nbsp;  Your thought is a fortress that neither gale nor the lightning can shake.My thought is a tender leaf that sways in every direction and finds pleasure in its swaying.    &nbsp;  Your thought is an ancient dogma that cannot change you nor can you change it.My thought is new, and it tests me and I test it morn and eve.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  You have your thought and I have mine.&nbsp;     Your thought allows you to believe in the unequal contest of the strong against the weak, and in the tricking of the simple by the subtle ones.My thought creates in me the desire to till the earth with my hoe, and harvest the crops with my sickle, and build my home with stones and mortar, and weave my raiment with woollen and linen threads.    &nbsp;  Your thought urges you to marry wealth and notability.Mine commends self-reliance.    &nbsp;  Your thought advocates fame and show.Mine counsels me and implores me to cast aside notoriety and treat it like a grain of sand cast upon the shore of eternity.    &nbsp;  Your thought instils in your heart arrogance and superiority.Mine plants within me love for peace and the desire for independence.    &nbsp;  Your thought begets dreams of palaces with furniture of sandalwood studded with jewels, and beds made of twisted silk threads.My thought speaks softly in my ears, “Be clean in body and spirit even if you have nowhere to lay your head.”    &nbsp;  Your thought makes you aspire to titles and offices.Mine exhorts me to humble service.&nbsp;     You have your thought and I have mine.&nbsp;     Your thought is social science, a religious and political dictionary.Mine is simple axiom.    &nbsp;  Your thought speaks of the beautiful woman, the ugly, the virtuous, the prostitute, the intelligent, and the stupid.Mine sees in every woman a mother, a sister, or a daughter of every man.    &nbsp;  The subjects of your thought are thieves, criminals, and assassins.Mine declares that thieves are the creatures of monopoly, criminals are the offspring of tyrants, and assassins are akin to the slain.    &nbsp;  Your thought describes laws, courts, judges, punishments.Mine explains that when man makes a law, he either violates it or obeys it.&nbsp; If there is a basic law, we are all one before it.&nbsp; He who disdains the mean is himself mean.&nbsp; He who vaunts his scorn of the sinful vaunts his disdain of all humanity.    &nbsp;  Your thought concerns the skilled, the artist, the intellectual, the philosopher, the priest.Mine speaks of the loving and the affectionate, the sincere, the honest, the forthright, the kindly, and the martyr.    &nbsp;  Your thought advocates Judaism, Brahmanism, Buddhism, Christianity, and Islam.In my thought there is only one universal religion, whose varied paths are but the fingers of the loving hand of the Supreme Being.    &nbsp;  In your thought there are the rich, the poor, and the beggared.My thought holds that there are no riches but life; that we are all beggars, and no benefactor exists save life herself.&nbsp;     You have your thought and I have mine.   According to your thought, the greatness of nations lies in their politics, their parties, their conferences, their alliances and treaties.But mine proclaims that the importance of nations lies in work – work in the field, work in the vineyards, work with the loom, work in the tannery, work in the quarry, work in the timberyard, work in the office and in the press.    &nbsp;  Your thought holds that the glory of the nations is in their heroes.&nbsp; It sings the praises of Rameses, Alexander, Caesar, Hannibal, and Napoleon.But mine claims that the real heroes are Confucius, Lao-Tse, Socrates, Plato, Abi Taleb, El Gazali, Jalal Ed-din-el Roumy, Copernicus, and Pasteur.    &nbsp;  Your thought sees power in armies, cannons, battleships, submarines, aeroplanes, and poison gas.But mine asserts that power lies in reason, resolution, and truth.&nbsp; No matter how long the tyrant endures, he will be the loser at the end.    &nbsp;  Your thought differentiates between pragmatist and idealist, between the part and the whole, between the mystic and materialist.Mine realizes that life is one and its weights, measures and tables do not coincide with your weights, measures and tables.&nbsp; He whom you suppose an idealist may be a practical man.&nbsp;     You have your thought and I have mine.&nbsp;     Your thought is interested in ruins and museums, mummies and petrified objects.But mine hovers in the ever-renewed haze and clouds.    &nbsp;  Your thought is enthroned on skulls.&nbsp; Since you take pride in it, you glorify it too.My thought wanders in the obscure and distant valleys.    &nbsp;  Your thought trumpets while you dance.Mine prefers the anguish of death to your music and dancing.    &nbsp;  Your thought is the thought of gossip and false pleasure.Mine is the thought of him who is lost in his own country, of the alien in his own nation, of the solitary among his kinfolk and friends.&nbsp;     You have your thought and I have mine.     

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here&nbsp;goes the meaning 'A personal belief or judgement that is not founded on proof or certainity'. Fundamentally its just a vague idea backed by confidence. Everybody has an opinion, this has been true probably&nbsp;ever since the human race has arrived.  &nbsp;  In the earlier days,&nbsp; opinion was limited to small social circles. But with growing globalization, the world is becoming one and the one who appears more confident is able to impose his opinion on others. And people who really dont care to have an opinion on something are not considered to be fit for the society. With media attacking almost every aspect of our life and publicizing well spoken opinions, people who dont really think are left confused. People who dont think are left to follow the ones who shout loudest.  &nbsp;  People seem crazy for an outlet, just like this blog and just like me. Now that I have an opinion on opinion, why should I even bother to publish it, why not keep it to myself. To some extent it is good to think, but thinking about things that are not needed at all seems foolish.  &nbsp;  Every channel you flip, you find people debating and discussing stuff, things like is TV having a bad effect on society,&nbsp; should ragging be allowed or not,&nbsp;should capitol punishment be eradicated from India? Sometimes I just feel, why should I really be bothered about all this? So many things keep happening in this world, who am I to keep track or to decide and give a verdict (opinion - a euphemism for verdict).  &nbsp;  As long as nobody is reading what I write, I dont have to feel guilty about publishing an opinion. Its just that I have to consolidate my thoughts somewhere and I have access to the Internet and blog because I can access it sometime later.  &nbsp;  Guess I am becoming a real cynic. Doesnt matter, I really cant help what I am.    Out, out, brief candle!    Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player    That struts and frets his hour upon the stage    And then is heard no more;    it is a tale Told by an idiot,    full of sound and fury,    Signifying nothing.        

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Slow down, you crazy child you're so ambitious for a juvenile But then if you're so smart, tell me Why are you still so afraid?  Where's the fire, what's the hurry about? You'd better cool it off before you burn it out You've got so much to do and Only so many hours in a day  But you know that when the truth is told.. That you can get what you want or you get old You're gonna kick off before you even Get halfway through When will you realize, Vienna waits for you?  Slow down, you're doing fine You can't be everything you want to be Before your time Although it's so romantic on the borderline tonight Tonight,... Too bad but it's the life you lead you're so ahead of yourself that you forgot what you need Though you can see when you're wrong, you know You can't always see when you're right. you're right  You've got your passion, you've got your pride but don't you know that only fools are satisfied? Dream on, but don't imagine they'll all come true When will you realize, Vienna waits for you?  Slow down, you crazy child and take the phone off the hook and disappear for awhile it's all right, you can afford to lose a day or two When will you realize,..Vienna waits for you? And you know that when the truth is told that you can get what you want or you can just get old You're gonna kick off before you even get half through Why don't you realize,. Vienna waits for you When will you realize, Vienna waits for you?   

						
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is in the painful memory of leaving a dear friend remembering the last sight and the tears that followed on 18th June 2004.      When tomorrow starts without me    And I'm not there to see,    If the sun should rise and find your eyes    All filled with tears for me;     I wish so much you wouldn't cry    The way you did today,    While thinking of the many things,    We didn't get to say.     I know how much you love me,    As much as I love you,    And each time that you think of me,    I know you'll miss me too;     But when tomorrow starts without me,    Please try to understand,    That an angel came and called my name,    And took me by the hand,     And said my place was ready,    In heaven far above,    And that I'd have to leave behind    All those I dearly love.     But as I turned to walk away,    A tear fell from my eye    For all my life, I'd always thought,    I didn't want to die.     I had so much to live for,    So much left yet to do,    It seemed almost impossible,    That I was leaving you.     I thought of all the yesterdays,    The good ones and the bad,    I thought of all the love we shared,    And all the fun we had.     If I could relive yesterday,    Just even for a while,    I'd say good-bye and kiss you    And maybe see you smile.     But then I fully realized,    That this could never be,    For emptiness and memories,    Would take the place of me.     And when I thought of worldly things,    I might miss come tomorrow,    I thought of you, and when I did,    My heart was filled with sorrow.     But when I walked through heaven's gates,    I felt so much at home.    When God looked down and smiled at me,    From His great golden throne,     He said, "This is eternity,    And all I've promised you."    Today your life on earth is past,    But here life starts anew.     I promise no tomorrow,    But today will always last,    And since each day's the same way    There's no longing for the past.     You have been so faithful,    So trusting and so true.    Though there were times    You did some things    You knew you shouldn't do.     But you have been forgiven    And now at last you're free.    So won't you come and take my hand    And share my life with me.     So when tomorrow starts without me,    Don't think we're far apart,    For every time you think of me,    I'm right here, in your heart.  

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today is 3rd July 2004. 4 years back on 3rd July 2000, I had joined PSPL. Thereafter its been a roller coaster ride for me.   I remember the first day when I had to leave my home in Mumbai to come and earn in Pune. The pain in my heart on leaving my home, I still can feel it. I remember my first salary when I didnt have my mother around to cherish it with me.   The first 6 months on bench was quite painful. Then I moved to Products, where I got the chance to prove myself. And I have done it quite well. enSure is established in some sense with 3 big sales. I have really earned my money.   The friends I made here, the love that I lost, the people that I meet on and off, its truly memorable.   Now, I feel I need a change. Why?. Its probably too full of memories here. Work doesnt seem as challenging any more. Its challenging in terms of spending each day at work fruitfully, but not like before. When I joined it was a 150 odd people setup and yesterday we were celebrating 1024. Things are changing.   I have an offer from a small setup. I feel I would be a good big fish in a small pond. Hope to change soon. God help me make the right decision. My heart says its time to move on! This is the phase in life where I have had to let go of everything that I had thought of making a permanent feature of my life. I know there is something else in store for me. What is it? I can only wait and watch.    

						
</post>


</Blog>