<Blog>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    crashed out!&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The first bash at this to test and see!
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomb of Agamemnon&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After waking up this morning with my face 'still' swollen, and throbbing away after the dental surgeon drama I decided to  get out and about  a bit and take a mystery drive down south into the Peloponnese and see what I wonder across.   I ended up driving into this village called "Mycenae" and found myself checking out ancient ruins of the  urlLink Citadel of Mycenae . There were heaps of tourists, so I ended up strolling amongst them being "Archeological?" There was an English speaking group with a guide so I tagged along with them for a while, taking in what the guide had to say about this and that.  It's amazing to think that these ruins were built around 3,500 years ago and the area first settled by Neolithic people in the 6th millennium BC!!!   An interesting part was the 'Tomb of Agamemnon' or also known as the 'Treasury of Atreus' which is an ancient beehive shaped burial tomb. It's pretty impressive stuff! So, after my archeological wondering around I jumped back into my car and headed down the road towards the coast on the look out for a beach!  Ended up following a track through olive groves and more olive groves which ended up at the massive beached cost line which was completely deserted! So, there I was at this beautiful beach. Just me, myself and I, the sound of the waves, the sun and the mountains in the far distance.. I contemplated stripping off naked, and decided 'for' the idea. I had a great swim  ~  urlLink just me in my birthday suit ! And, why not? After all, it was my birthday! 
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Deserted Beach&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pain killers and Congee! The meeting with the  urlLink Greek Dental Surgeon  was last Saturday. It is now Tuesday morning and still it hurts! Furthermore there seems to be no sign of the swelling decreasing yet. Actually, it still seems to be on the rise and the left hand side of my face is slowly swelling up like a carnival balloon. From what I have read the swelling is suppose reach its peak after 48 hours after which the swelling starts to decrease. It’s now been about 72 hours of painkillers, antibiotics and ice packs and the situation is still not getting better. So what is going on? What a joy ride this has turned out to be. ‘Not!’  Oh well, at least I can look at myself in the mirror and be amused at the site of my swollen face.  I am on a  soft food diet  and have been feeding myself Congee for breakfast, lunch and dinner for the last few days which has been very interesting indeed. These days I’m becoming an expert at the art congee making!  What you do is; boil rice ( 4 parts water for every 1 part of rice)  and then let it sit for about 30min, heat it up again and stir like mad for 5min. Stop, wait for 5min again and continue doing this for a few more times and you end up with Congee!! Tastes good with ginger put in at the beginning of the process and then half way through start adding in strands of chicken and heaps of garlic with onion and then right at the end tossing in an egg and a bit of soy sauce if you want to be flashy! It is delicious and just the thing when you are in the condition that I’m in and sure beats the baby food option.  Orrrrrh…. I’m not feeling good at this second, head is now spinning and I’m now suddenly feeling as if I’m going to throw up. God! Must have been that pain killer (Ponstan) that I took 30min ago….or was it the milk that I drank with it to wash it down?  Oh no! I better take a lie down and organise a bed side bucket!  Oh geezzz…..this is not a joke!  Ohhhh noooo....  
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Impacted tooth!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When a tooth is prevented from erupting into the mouth normally, it is said to be impacted. The presence of impacted teeth in the mouth is a risk factor for problems such as infection, cyst formation, or damage to adjacent teeth.  The removal of impacted teeth is an operation, much like any other operation. A flap of tissue has to be opened to gain access to the tooth, and often bone has to be removed and the tooth has to be sectioned. Your jaws will swell considerably and will be very sore. The swelling will make it hard to open your mouth for a few days. You will need to take pain medications for about two to five days afterward, depending on the extent of the surgery and your body's response to it.  You will also have general body weakness for a few days.  Possible complications   In the lower jaw, particularly, there may be a healing complication known as a dry socket. With dry socket, healing progresses normally for about three days, and then there is a dramatic increase in pain in the socket and radiating to the ear.  Sometimes sharp edges of bone may surface during the healing process. This does not necessarily need to be treated. They occur because of the body's work of reshaping the tissues in the area formerly occupied by the tooth. Unless the edges cause great discomfort, it would be best to let them alone, and the healing processes will smooth them out.  The roots of lower wisdom teeth may lie near the main nerve to the lower jaw, and the crowns may be near the nerve to the tongue. In about 1 to 2% of the cases, these nerves could be damaged during removal of the tooth. The result would be numbness in the lips, chin, and teeth on the side affected, or in the side of the tongue. Movement would not be affected--only sensation. Expect some difficulty in using your mouth for several weeks, until it accommodates to the change. The nerve may take a month or several months to repair itself. It is not very common for this numbness, if present, to be permanent, but that is also possible.  It is also possible that the roots of upper wisdom teeth or other upper posterior teeth may lie so close to the wall of one of your nasal sinuses that the sinus wall would be perforated during the operation. This would result in some bleeding through the nose. Sometimes, in rare cases, the wall between the tooth and the sinus can be so delicate that attempts at extraction cause the tooth or a piece of the tooth to be displaced into the sinus. If this happens, an opening would have to be made into the sinus to remove the tooth.   The degree of risk of complications varies from patient to patient. If you are over age 25 or 30 when the impacted teeth are removed, you have a greater chance of complications, because of the increased density of the bone. The risks increase with increasing age. If the teeth are extracted before their roots are completely formed, the risk of complications is usually minimal. The position of the teeth in the jaw and the difficulty of the surgery also affect the degree of risk.   I'm getting really really worried at the moment...help!!     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Problem Tooth!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wondered into one of the towns many dental offices this morning were I met the 'Dr Papadopolous' explaining to him about a sore tooth! I don't think he understood a word I was saying as he was talking back to me in French! He took an x-ray and had somebody from the waiting room to translate to me what he wanted to tell me. So apparently I'm off to the local hospital on Friday for an  operation  by the   Surgeon!  I am already scared out of my brains !! Or was the translator from the waiting room just taking the fun out of me and enjoying the horror written all over my face! Hmmm.....? I go back tomorrow to collect more details with regards to the  operation !  I am worried.... 
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Crashed!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last summer I dropped me Spedos! (from the washing line that is) Now, if you are into Swimming  Spedos are 'Holy' particularly the ones bought in Australia, because the ones in Greece are just not the same.    So, my Spedos dropped off the line and landed smack bang with a "soggy splash" sound on top of one of the older Greek monks who are forever walking down the footpath. It landed right on top that black hat hing?  I rushed down, kids playing on the street were laughing and giggling away in Greek,looking at me and my confrontation with the monk. The scene made me laugh too, which made things worse. The old Greek monk was not impressed! Not impressed at all.... He got worked up  Greek Style  saying something? And loudly!! I did say the "signomi" word( that is ‘sorry’ in Greek) but, whilst doing so I could not get my cheeky Australian grin off my face. In the end I did get my spedos back, but only just!    Since then I don't see monks strolling down my street anymore. And the kids on the street? Well these days when ever I'm walking by their hopscotch markings chalked out on the road or their skipping rope sessions playing away there, they all scream out "hello" "hello" and they remember and  love me  for the incident. I have become a local hero! 
    
</post>


</Blog>