<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the day I am supposed to hand in my Thesis. Not much guessing needed for the progress i have made, easily comprehended from the topic title. I am feeling the strain on my head and the sinking sensation in my chest. I have been trying to solve endless chains of equations to no avail. At one instance, i felt like "John Nash" writing maths solutions on the window. That thought spurred me on a bit last night before the motivation flickered with each stumbling block i encountered.   I woke up today wanting to see my supervisor. One thing is weird though. Some clashing emotions (or should i say intentions) brewing inside me. On one hand, i know that i need to see him desperately to seek enlightenment, on the other hand, i am reluctant to see him due to the fact that i have been a notorious student of his who disregard the importance of doing serious work early. Long story on the later. I just made up my mind, after typing the last three sentences, that i have to see him today no matter what. I guess i have to get ready and rush to uni to work things out.   To end today's posting, I know I should not be stressed and worried. Panic is out of question if I have faith in HIM. Being stressed and panicky is just a show of distrust to His promise.  I would like to end with these verses from the bible.   Mat 6:25  Therefore I say to you, Do not be anxious for your life, what you shall eat, or what you shall drink; nor for your body, what you shall put on. Is not life more than food, and the body more than clothing?  Mat 6:26  Behold the birds of the air; for they sow not, nor do they reap, nor gather into barns. Yet your heavenly Father feeds them; are you not much better than they are?  Mat 6:27  Which of you by being anxious can add one cubit to his stature?  Mat 6:28  And why are you anxious about clothing? Consider the lilies of the field, how they grow. They do not toil, nor do they spin,  Mat 6:29  but I say to you that even Solomon in his glory was not arrayed like one of these.  Mat 6:30  Therefore if God so clothes the grass of the field, which today is, and tomorrow is thrown into the oven, will He not much rather clothe you, little-faiths?  Mat 6:31  Therefore do not be anxious, saying, What shall we eat? or, What shall we drink? or, With what shall we be clothed?  Mat 6:32  For the nations seek after all these things. For your heavenly Father knows that you have need of all these things.  Mat 6:33  But seek first the kingdom of God and His righteousness; and all these things shall be added to you.  Mat 6:34  Therefore do not be anxious about tomorrow; for tomorrow shall be anxious for its own things. Sufficient to the day is the evil of it.   Mat 7:7  Ask and it shall be given to you; seek and you shall find; knock and it shall be opened to you.  Mat 7:8  For each one who asks receives; and he who seeks finds; and to him who knocks, it shall be opened.  Mat 7:9  Or what man is there of you, if his son asks a loaf, will he give him a stone?  Mat 7:10  Or if he asks a fish, will he give him a snake?  Mat 7:11  If you then, being evil, know how to give good gifts to your children, how much more shall your Father in Heaven give good things to those who ask Him?   To readers out there, God loves us.  My panic has avaporated. I am soothed.  Hopefully my next posting will be a happier one. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I  spent around one whole minute, thinking of the first letter to type. I went through my keyboard horizontally with my index finger, deciding on an auspicious letter to press. I finally decided on the letter "I" for simple enough reason. This blog is  about "I". So the journey begins. This is "I". Welcome to "I"'s world. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been spending my time reading entries by miyabi-chan. From what i gathered, this girl is very complicated. However, she gets me thinking. She makes me more aware of my inner feeling. I became sensitised by the presence of it deep inside and i am glad. I am awakened. I can imagine my inner self stretch and yawn... shaking its head, opening its eyes sparking with wits and giving a very cunning and naughty smile. This will be the first step where I grow  exponentially.   Watani came to my room not long ago. Last night, She asked me whether i could drive her to uni today if it rains. I told her i will drive her IF IT RAINS. She agreed and said that if it does not rain today she will walk to uni. Well, just now when she was in my room, not only she "ordered" me to photocopy some stuffs for her, she also asked me to drive her to uni despite of the sunny day. She said she is lazy. Well, the car is lent to Louise, so even if i want to drive her i cant. But, I should have told her first and foremost that she should walk as it didn't rain. Instead I told her that the car is not with me. I can see clearer how my friendship with annabel is so superficial and lack compassion. It is always me showing her care and helping her out of shits, she has never reciprocated at all, not at all. It's not that i am giving expecting something in return, but the fact that this has gone too far. It is true sometimes even without saying, that sometimes i can imagine that i am turning into her dog. agreeing to every request of her. The inner self has awakened, it is struggling through all these injustice. something has to be done. In the meantime, i will concentrate on my work. I must score!  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stumbled across this on the web:   "it's not about how much I do for you  or how much I give you provide for you or support you  and it's not about what's happening in your life that requires my presence or what you think of as burdensome  because it isn't and this is what I do, not for everybody,  but for you for the one I love because this is all I know how to do, learned to do, grew up knowing that this is good and this thing I do makes me happy and makes you happy and makes both of us happy. so I do all I can when I feel what I feel is right because I feel right when I am with you and all else don't matter as much to me because unconditional is how I learned to do this and unconditional is how I will do it because it feels natural and honest and me and something that comes naturally for me. moreover what you do for me is something that you don't know that you do for me as much as I do for you in many ways you don't even know, like my guide, my balance, my missing pieces, so don't worry about this or that because as long as you and I are you and I then it doesn't matter what I do and what you do for each other as long as it's each other right? we're home together. i'm glad i can be a part of that happiness. that i was part of something great in your life. the things you are thankful for, i remember, all without you saying a thing. because you don't need to. and though i am forgetful, and though i fumble with thoughts and my clumsy words, i am clear with my feelings, those feelings i never forget. what is true and real and lively i feel and i remember. I love you."  These lines depict love in such a vivid manner, anyone who is in love before will read these and stares into space, recalls the feeling one possesses. Love is so beautiful this way. No matter what happens, separated or together, if the love is still felt, it remains beautiful.   I start to wonder, when will I love like that again. Will I be able to ? I dont know. The feeling of love for someone is one that you keep safely inside your heart like a precious treasure. Smile.. smile smile.. love is beautiful. it is to draw a smile instead of frown. :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The day started lazily. I crawled out of my bed to eat lunch in dining hall after refusing to get up and hid under the quilt for the entire morning, hmm not entire morning.   well, i slept at 6 am the night(morning) because tong has serious problem with his relationship with Sulyn. Sulyn apparently suggested a temporary separation regarding their relationship, citing reasons to have some time to think about whether or not to continue with it (in my own interpretation). Well tong was very down, so we spent time listening to him and talking to him.   woke up 2.5 hrs later, needed to send our car (me and teong) to the mechanic (BEn) servicing. came back at ard 10 30 am and called bel to make sure that she is away from her bed, sitting on her chair doing her essay. Ended up chatting with her till 11 plus, due to her reluctance to pry herself away frm the beloved bed. She said, the bed now is her refuge from the amount of assignments that she has to do. she is stressed to the level that doing no work seems like a breeze, a temporary reprieve despite the nightmarish thought of looming deadlines and blatant time-wasting that accompanies it. And she also has weird dreams about dating a guy that she used to have a crush on in JC. Then we started talking about the past again. the sharing of the past no matter how dark and awful seems to bridge our distance. Well i decided to sleep after the fone conversation  I think i have veered out of topic, the realisation hit me when i recalled my topic header. Yes Kelong referee! I played the final of the UWA 5 aside soccer with INDOSS team. The game started well with us trying to neutralise their relentless attacks. The half time score stood at 1-1. It was quite a tightly contested soccer match.  The second half started. Here comes the part where i think is one of the worst refereeing that i have ever experienced in my whole life. They were attacking. Boon intercepted a pass, the ball bounced off his shin and Mark our goalie decided to catch it.The opponents started to appeal for backpass. Up to this point it was a normal circumstance that u would encounter in a soccer match.   Ok now lets start with the key events leading up the the refereeing farce.... After the incident above everyone looked at the referee for decision. How he reacted to this was incomprehensible. He had two choices: To award indirect free kick, or to signal play on! or just simply stay cool and dont move. For this referee.  He started walking into the pitch slowly (the referee always stayed by the sideline in this small scale soccer match). He started mumbling, Mark then let go of the ball from his grip as everyone has stopped the play to wait for the indirect free kick we have expected to be awarded to the opponent(though it was not so fair, but well..). So the ball is now on the ground, with the referee strolling and mumbling, who knows what, into the pitch. Out of everyone's expectation, He just woke up from his "marijuanaish effect" and said: " Hey! play on! continue!.... The opponent just gratefully discovered that the ball is just under his very nose, and tapped it into the goal with our goalie still trying to figure out why the ball is kicked at the goal( Our players were equally open-mouthed). 2-1 to them , the suffocating feeling of injustice filled our eager but overworked lungs, the air was harder to breathe in as the stench of unfairness and unsportingness have polluted the very air, relentless arguments were useless, the goal stood. Simply kelong, no other word, you can imagine the avid S-leaguers chanting: " Referee Kayu, Referee kayu!" Or the more familiar Mat's referee abuse:" sial lah! referee kelong man! kayu sia! The match ended with us losing 3-2, and to think that it was the final...(*a deep breath...and a long sigh).
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This has nothing to do with my thesis.  Well, to start this... i am thinking of a question... Why do SOME people enjoy talking about other people behind their back so much that it become a habit that everytime when congregated in a group, the topic about certain person, be it close friends or strangers will surface. It is like a contagious disease spreading to other people in the group and causing the group to divide and becomes more sensitive towards certain issues. I agree that it is inavoidable to engage in light topics, or even diss and bitch,  In my own opinion, this is impossible to avoid because it is bound to happen that one day, you are just so pissed about certain matter or person that you just have to voice it out. Well, i believe that there is a healthy level to that and a choice can be made between: 1.voice it all out in the open, with the goal to gain crowd support and to have something interesting to talk about in the group, or 2.to voice it out with a close friend with the intention to sincerely express the personal unhappiness, done in such way that you want it to stay low profile, minimum damage, and resolved as soon as possible with the least amount of trouble. well... if it can be solved that is.  Gone is the usual carefree and fun elements, replaced by whispering and serious dissing and bitching about another human being in a big group as if it is a new trend. Unhappiness towards a single individual spreadt and shared, logic to dislike discussed and embraced. Rumours which might not be 100 % true are confirmed and believed. Silence in the group is almost taboo, something has to be spoken about and discussed regardless. It is disappointing. I am disillussioned. I cant deny that i am the guilty party the problem i have mentioned. Up to this point, I am going to make a conscious effort to refrain from all those. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>