<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dating certainly had its advantages. As well as its detractions. However...vividly sticking out in my mind right now are the sugary messages on the answering machine. Getting home now generally consists of me walking in, visiting the cats (foster children of a failed relationship) and checking my messages.  But i'm not privy to anything except the drone of friends, the greetings of parents, or the pleas from work.  And the more than occasional hang up. All that i long for on the answering machine is the short, sweet message from that person that *really* cares.  The person genuinely interested in where you are and why you aren't with them.   The only thing i can liken the messages to is a shot of Bailey's sipped after a long day.  Warm, sweet, slightly intoxicating, and just damn relaxing.  With a nice swathe of comfort draped over the top.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.uclick.com/client/wpc/db/2004/05/30/  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Look! Its me as punk-Rocky (if you don't know me, I'm on the right) with Punk Rock Sam!  I suppose I ought to find a picture of normal shaggy indie me...but pictures are a rarity reserved for special occasions: like punk-Rocky!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Or the shizzle. If thats your sort of thing. I remember when 3k was FAAAAST. Getting 170k from my DSL line feels like heaven. Wow, i need a life!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't really understand them.  Actually, its the whole slutty culture.  Its disturbing.  I, unfortunately(?), have this desire to keep myself unsluttified (not virgin, just not one night standy) in the hopes that the "right girl" does the same for me and we can have this same view of sex and the world. However...that seems like it is rather far fetched.  Maybe its the town i live in.  Maybe its the people i'm surrounded by.   Whatever it is, its making me depressed and kinda anxious about "losing time" now when i ought to be out banging hoes in order to keep my tally up to par with the next serious girl I date.  God knows I don't think i can date another girl that has totally eclipsed me in that lovely number. Sure, I'm insecure.  And old fashioned. But ... damnit, can't we have SOMETHING that is still special between  two  people? The society and the television are so damn intrusive on every aspect of people's lives that ... god ... its impossible to share ANYTHING with just one other person. And, once again, i'm NOT advocating virginity.  I'm just advocating ...   feelings/emotions/connection. Where did they go?  When, exactly, did it become OK to share every part of you with everyone in the world just because it gives you a pleasant muscle spasm? Can't we just let it be OK to not fuck everyone you meet at a bar? Can't we not glorify the culture of sex as just the end of another night? I suppose my bitterness is in part because I see a lot of people out "having a good time" and, yeah, i'm jealous.  I want to live the life.  But I just can't break away from this ideal i've built for myself.  And i can't let go of the thought that eventually I'll meet the girl that did the same. Seeing my perceptions crumble is crappy.  Expectations lead inevitably to disappointments.  Which is unfortunate as I tend to live in my head a lot. In summary: I just want a chick that isn't a slut.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Probably" in english usually denotes 60%+ certainty. Its closest relative in japanese is 90%+ certainty. I can't help but wonder if that tells something about the ingrained attitudes of the people of both cultures/languages. Unfortunately I'm not energetic enough at the moment to explore the implications.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not so much a well thought out topic.  More just a fact. Its all hitting me that pretty soon someone else's business is going to be in my hands. Now, its not that big of a deal in the grand scheme ... but. Jeez ... someone's life work, and they are trusting 23 year old me to keep it going during these less than easy times for the industry.  Heh.   Good luck! I need Miss Cleo. Or a shrink. Whatever.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, i'm thinking about handing out a list of music to "girls" that I'm interested in. Now, this probably sounds presumptious and a bit egotistical...but really, its just  important to me. (And I wouldn't actually do it ... that must count for something.) If you can't stand Belle & Sebastian...do i REALLY want to spend a considerable portion of my free time with you? If Elliott Smith makes you want to vomit, yet you'll gladly throw on Chingy ... would I even be willing to share a lane with you on the freeway, much less my kick ass apartment? I can accept people not having actually heard this stuff. That is quite alright.  We can work with that. But .. music is a big part of me and my life.  And ... well, why go through the hassle of not being able to talk about/agree on something that matters that much to me. It wouldn't work out in the end anyway, why waste time? Sure, we could get our rocks off for a few weeks or months.  But i'm not so into that if I'm not into you.  SO: This is a reminder to future me: When you start dating some lady -> Find out what she's into first.  At least that way when you break up you won't have to throw away her crappy CDs again.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Weird. I suppose its the first day thing. I'm sure in 4 days I'll forget that I even have a blog. The appeal lies in the fact that its a personal diary of sorts left open for anyone to read.  Yet noone will. Nice. Except I know that some friend of mine will read it. So it isn't 100% candid. I'm still wearing pants. Which is a good thing.  Unless you're into that type of thing, but even if you are, i barely know you, and I'm not into that type of thing with folks I barely know. Note to self ... find out if "Its addictive" or "It's addictive" is correct. Grammar counts! And so does dracula on Sesame Street. Neat-o.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, you need to be motivated towards something. I'm relatively "content" with my station in life. Middle class average decent existence. I'm extraordinarily happy that i don't live in a shitty country (not that I love ... like ... approve of ... am not em-bare-assed by ... am not disgusted by ... our government). I'm thrilled that i have a job. Even more stoked that i can pay my atrocious rent. My only real problem is that I'm lonely...and not good with getting un-lonely (namely: getting un-lonely involves effort). However: Woopdeedoo.  In the grand scheme of things, loneliness isn't exactly something one ought to curse their whole being for. AND! According to a great number of friends: "It'll just happen" ... So, sitting at home.  Doing jack.  Blogging.  These are all apparently relevant timesinks.  Because: Eventually, it'll just happen. --- I, however, don't really believe that too much. The right thing may just happen.  But I'm afraid that you kinda have to make some things happen in life, otherwise only shiftless and lazy people would get ahead, get dates, get elected. And, from my experience, at least 85% of the people that have been in either of those previously mentioned states had some DRIVE to get there.  Some motivation to just go out.  Get out.  Do something. Perhaps blogging counts as something.  However, a cursory search of Santa Barbara blogs on here ... not too promising.  A bunch of other dudes with time on their hands. It appears there is competition in my little world of "waiting for it to happen." And those folks are probably more clever than I. They probably carry flags. Dash cunning. And here I am.  Un-motivated.  And apparently not concerned enough about it to change anything. Thats the killer of motivation.  You either have it.  Or your don't. Check yes. Or no. Unfortunately, I'm just a tongue tied, awkward guy that can type relatively well. Not much use for that in the real world.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Right-o. So, it was a lovely day today.  Santa Barbara is enjoying our normal 70ish weather (gives us "locals" the opportunity to complain about the heat wave to each other... quite exciting!) and the shop isn't excruciatingly stressful at the moment. Things will change right away though. Anyway, i was listening to Elliott Smith again today (like every day...X-O is stuck in the CD player in my car after all) and got kinda sad (which is probably an acceptable reaction to Elliott).  Then i started wondering about the " urlLink murder " business. I'm not sure i buy it.  Maybe i just don't want to accept the murder theory, since suicide seems a predictable end to an artist that changed my life (in reference to: Kurt Cobain killing himself when i was 13).  HOWEVER! If murder is the case: WHAT THE FUCK?!?? How in god's name can someone date Elliott FREAKIN' SMITH and then want to kill the guy? Puddles. Sometimes i don't understand the world.   Scratch that, sometimes i do understand the world. Normally i don't.  This is yet another case.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so, since i couldn't think of anything to write about and noone reads my blog to post comments, i figured I'd give myself a topic to discuss. Monopolies.  Are they really *that* bad? I mean ... they say Microsoft has a monopoly.  Yet, Microsoft is one of the biggest innovators in their industry, primarily because they want to keep their market share. I suppose I'm unclear about the problems of the monopoly in the modern economy. -> Monopolies hamper competition ...  Perhaps.  Hmm.  Someone let me know! (hehe, its like screaming into the blackest forest in the deepest night ... noone hears my call, noone can come to my aid!)
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      OMFG!!!11 My blog is here! P|-|33r me! -- Right-o. I guess a post asking what I ought to post is somewhat begging the question, but I truly am at a loss. Suggestions? (This is where i'm asking my legions of adoring fans to give me some insight.) Puddles. I have no fans. Oh well ... perhaps we'll hear more as ideas jump to mind.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I’ve been tossing around some stuff in my head after seeing Rebekah. This is the first time we’ve talked in person since the break up and it spurred the rebirth of a lot of forgotten memories. While I would be lying to say that I am completely over everything, I do feel comfortable saying that I am about as close to being over *her* as is possible given the limited time I’ve had alone compared to our time together (4 months versus 3 years). But, yet again, I’m reminded that the little things are gone … and that those are what are missed the most. It isn’t so much that I miss her part in the memories or even that her memory haunts me.  She isn’t so much the factor. What I miss the most is the innocence and the end of it: the leap to adulthood that I took; she was just a part of all of it. There are circumstances and situations that are now gone and I’m somewhat lamenting their disappearance. Little things … I remember when we first started dating: I was 20, still in school, only one real relationship under my belt (a high school romance at that) and still very much a child. She lived an hour away and just outside the radius of free, local telephone calls. Those first few months saw huge phone bills, massive gas costs, and several early morning drives that felt like battles against the rising sun. They also gave me the last taste of childish romance.  I was full of naivety and excitement regarding the world and my freedom as an adult. I suppose that it really is a glorious time when you first release the tethers of childhood, latch onto a partner and explore the world that has always been so foreign (and exciting). *That* is the feeling I miss. I can’t quite explain the feelings … but there was some kind of “naughtiness” to the whole situation that was just intoxicating.  I had never been privy to this world, and everything I did felt remarkably similar to what I’d imagine Charlie felt like when he first discovered that Willie Wonka’s factory was indeed his. But … here I am now.  The factory is mine.  The Oompa Loompas are on strike and our shipment is behind schedule. Life isn’t so exciting anymore and I feel as though I’m never going to be able to look at love with the same fresh arrogance again. Not to be pessimistic, because I know that love will happen again. I also know that once again my life will be “better than ever before” and I’ll be “more in love than I ever thought possible.”  I know this will all happen and I’m not especially impatient. I’m just reminiscing about that “first” time, when everything was bright and the innocence felt sinful. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, in case you didn't guess: Rebekah. At my doorstep. Weird. Random. Not as awkward as I'd imagined it would be. We had a good long chat for a couple hours.  She took some remaining stuff from the days when it was "our" house. No bad blood. She is a sweet girl.  But not mine anymore, and i'm happy that i'm at a place where (despite all the other shit in my life going wrong) i'm ok with it. Huzzah. Spiderman 2 tonight! wootini (to quote jacob).
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      But it's weird. Thats all. When i was happy and content in my relationship and life, i was *terrified* of death. Almost literally every night I would sit awake at night and worry about dying.  Thinking i had cancer or something silly like that.  Picturing all the scenarios of my death and how horrible it would be for me to abandon Rebekah. Then. She breaks up with me. I realize that ... life does go on.  We weren't as meant for each other as i was convinced. And she obviously didn't have the same fears of leaving me alone as i did regarding her. Yet, now i sleep very soundly at night. I don't worry. However, other parts of my life are lacking. So i get to be unhappy when I'm awake instead. - I guess my point is that it is unfortunate that my personality is one that when i should be the absolute happiest, i invent big worries and fears in my head to ground me. And then when I'm rather unhappy, i sleep soundly. As if i'm more comfortable that way. Weird.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jeremy donated me a desk in his move to Boston. So, i've upgraded. w00t. Unfortunately, i'm gonna need either a new chair or a wireless keyboard to make this work comfortably. Fortunately(?), my backspace key is wearing down rather quickly. I'm not sure what that says about me as a person/typer ... but can it be good?
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      All I’ve ever wanted is for some picture to say one thousand words for me.  I’m always tongue tied and finger cramped when it counts, yet if I could just rely on a simple point or nod towards one stunning shot, well, I believe all my troubles would disappear.  Unfortunately, I can’t seem to create the pictures or the words.  And I’m stumbling through it all appearing aloof when all I want to do is pour out my heart to some phantom passing from my life.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, i've been in touch with most of you anyway. But, ya, i haven't been blogging much lately. Work is a freakin' bear.  For some reason I'm there everyday.  And it feels like nothing is getting done. Amazing what a bit of extra responsibility can do to crush self confidence re: a job well done. Ah, but that is neither here nor there.  Work isn't life, nor should it define it. =D On the personal front:  I like my friends.  You all kick ass. I think i actually like this girl i'm "seeing" ... but i'm not sure on the status of our relationship. Seeing as how she is an employee, stuff is simply more complicated than it otherwise ought to be. I watched High Fidelity yesterday again. Its quite the appropriate movie for me. My favorite line is something along the lines of: "It only matters what you like, not what you are like." For some reason I believe there is a lot of relevance there, at least regarding my little connection with my employee "friend." Perhaps more depth later, whether anyone cares or not. Anywho. Off to go climb a big plastic rock. Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have what i think is a date tomorrow. Its with a coworker. As manager, that makes her an employee. :-/ SO, good + bad. Huzzah. But ... she's super cute and has great taste in music.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      More of my yard.  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My Yard  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Innocent question time: Is feminism MORE: How a woman sees herself. Or: How men see women. Just curious.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My personal feeling has been that Kerry, so far, is unable to drum up *real* firm support from his base.  A lot of dems that i know (people that *loathe* Bush's policies) are only voting for Kerry because "He isn't Bush." At the moment, this proverbial boat of "voter languor" is the one I see myself stuck in as well, and I'm keeping company equivalent to a cruise ship, not some summer schooner. The most disappointing part is that this was supposed to be a big election year, at least for me. Things were supposed to change; the people were going to say "Hell No!" to special interests, corporate greed, and unjust wars.  Now we're simply mumbling something about "change," yet unclear about how to go about it. And that is a damn shame. Especially considering that I feel as though a retarded monkey with a severe drug problem would do a better job than Bush's entire White House staff. AND I'M NOT ALONE! I suppose my questions are: Where is the democratic leadership? Where is their tenacity? Why won't they point fingers? Blast the truth about the current administration all over the media.  Don't pull punches. Don't roll over. The right wing has a veritable hit squad of AM radio and cable news that pummels every Dem any chance they get. And they STILL manage to convince America that the media is dominated by the left! Why can't our side do the same thing? Why is their no blitz at the Right? The fact of the matter is that our side *actually has* the integrity and the truth behind it.  USE IT! Don't let the "Michael Moore's" be our only voice. Skewed story telling is just more fodder for the attack dogs on the right. Get some real messages out there.  We don't have to lose the election. We NEED a landslide.  The left needs to BLOW THIS ELECTION OUT. And we need to follow a win up with real change. But can Kerry deliver us anything? Can he change the situation? Or will it be another non-descript president that doesn't do much for the people and opens up the door to more Right Wing Tyranny in four years? At this point I'm pretty unconvinced of any reason for optimism. I guess no matter what, I'm confident that Kerry won't dig us into any more Bush-esque holes; and as all is said and done, he sure would be a hell of a lot better than Bush. But, even the monkey isn't looking too bad at this point.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Pessimism never created a job. (Quoted from a GWBush television ad). I dunno...maybe its a good message.  But... You know. Then again. Not to play devil's advocate ...  But... Umm...being an optimist when things *SUCK* kinda makes you an idiot. Or blind. And. Well. Voting for a "leader" that merely wants us to think "everything is OK!" when stuff most definitely is NOT .. well, that's just as shameful as being the one responsible for said shitty situation. That's only my opinion. You draw your own conclusion.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ya. I'm taking Christine's advice. I'm gonna find me a dorky girl. Seeing as how i'm a dork at heart, it ought to work out well. Right? I can't keep up with those fast ladies. A cute dorky indie girl. Keep yer eyes out.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                         Introverted (I) 57.58% Extroverted (E) 42.42%  Imaginative (N) 51.43% Realistic (S) 48.57%  Intellectual (T) 51.35% Emotional (F) 48.65%  Easygoing (P) 52.78% Organized (J) 47.22%  
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      But not a fun way to live your life. I am not a fan of being cooped up in the house, unfortunately its hard to get out.  I've been living so long in this state of ..wait..wait..wait..wait..wait.. that it is hard to get into the mindset of BLAM! Make it happen! BLAM! I think trying new things might be fun!  Go out, explore, parasail. So, i need to go places/do things i wouldn't normally do. Fun stuff! This will be the new single Rocky. The one that realizes it was her loss. (Yes, i finally realized that ... like 2 days ago ... ) I had forgotten that *I* am *FUCKING AWESOME*.  I'm attractive. I'm smart. I hold doors. I buy flowers. I'm just a damn nice, good guy. So, I'm the damn nice, good guy that is going to start enjoying himself. yay. I'm getting self confidence if it kills me. ^^
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Megan cut my hair! I know i don't look happy (i was listening to idle chatter), but I'm very happy with its resurrection!  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Link . Ok. So J-Lo can get married like 17 thousand times. And not a squeek from the "family first" right wing. Serious gay couples want to enjoy the benefits of marriage and the country is in an uproar about the disturbance of the american family.  The president even proposes a constitutional amendment TAKING RIGHTS AWAY from a group of people.  Yay America!  Amend the document that has stood for so much progression and freedom in this country to restrict the rights of a minority group.  w00t. Oh well, what else do I expect from the administration and its media empire that brought us "Halliburton: The Little Company That Could (Bend the Rules and Make Billions)" and "Iraq 2.0: Upgraded For Justice (Osama bin Laden not included)" However, we gleefully let family killing media whores like Lopez get away without a scratch. Nice. Very nice.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just saw it. I really enjoyed it. However, i love the books. So, my tilt on the review is extremely biased. Definitely better than the first 2 films...just like this book was better than the preceeding entries. Good show.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I wish i had it.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was going to upload a picture of myself. Megan (@ work) cut my hair and kind of fixed it. Its (obviously) long, like i wanted.  But it at least makes me look like a real boy. However, i don't have a USB thing for the camera. Maybe tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sweet.         You're Vietnam!      After years of muddling through on your own, you've finally repaired  yourself to a point of respectability. &nbsp;You would have been much better off had  people you didn't like not kept insisting on spending so much time with you. &nbsp;But  those times are fading quickly and these days you're pretty sure you won't get burned.  &nbsp;Star power!   Take the  urlLink Country Quiz  at the  href="http://bluepyramid.org">Blue Pyramid     
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dude, i look something like like breckin meyer. Thats creepy. Check out this  urlLink page . Not a flattering picture. How about  urlLink this . I guess there are worse people to resemble.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, Dick Cheney worked for Halliburton prior to being Vice Pres. Halliburton then gets a huge contract to rebuild Iraq (after the "war" ... heh). This was ... a long time ago. Why did it take THIS LONG for people to see  urlLink this . The jist of the article is that, suprise! dickypoo used his position as vice pres to secure a contract for Halliburton. Duh. Now, my main issues are: One. Why wasn't a bigger deal made of this when it being pushed through? ANYONE with half of a retarded monkey's brain would realize Dick (god i love that name) was pulling strings. Two. What kind of fucktards are running our country? Did they really think that people wouldn't catch on? Which I guess leads me to Three.  How in God's name can anyone say we have a "liberal media" in this country when people like Dick aren't raked through the coals multiple times and then left there to BURN when they pull shit like this? Shouldn't the media RIP his ASS like they did to Clinton for his AFFAIR? And WHY OH WHY is Bush and Co still in the White House? And, more importantly, WHY OH WHY is it so narrow at the moment between him and Kerry? How HOW H O W can almost FIFTY PERCENT of registered voters think "Bush" is A STRONG ENOUGH LEADER for our country to get us out of the mess HE got us into? My god. This TRASH makes me want to get into politics ... if only because apparently they'll let an irresponsible drunk with a pile of psychotic friends into the white house nowadays.  And I aint got jack else to do. I suppose I ought to start drinking heavily.  And make sure my friends don't get treatment.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Went to a friends graduation instead. While it definitely wasn't as exciting. Or probably as fun. I'm glad i did it. But i'm still bummed I missed the show. >. Oh well, graduations don't happen often. The Shins will probably be back in a year. But I'll tell you one thing Christine: If you get your freakin' Masters when I'm supposed to see Belle & Sebastian, I don't think we'll see a repeat performance. You'll just have to send me pictures.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I'm going to download Instant Messenger. I'm feeling social.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Haven't posted anything today. I guess days off do that to me. Relaxed.  Listened to music. Played an INSANE amount of games. The tune of ~9 hours of XBox and ~2 of PC. And I can't say I'm finished. But no blogging. I reaffirmed that Death Cab for Cutie is actually a band I'm into. Well, at least I'm still digging Transatlanticism. All of their other stuff kind of bores the hell out of me. Not in a hideously negative "turn it off" way, just in a "I'd rather listen to the Postal Service if i'm going to listen to Ben Gibbard" way. Anyway. Hmm ... ya. Thats it.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dude. I went in to get a TRIM. I've been growing out my hair for a couple months. A trim. Take out the "poof." Take off the "big." Ick. My head looks horrible. I think I'm going to shave it or buy a hat. We'll see. Over-reacting: Maybe. However. I REALLY FUCKING LIKED MY HAIR! I just needed a damn trim. Now, for at least a month, it is going to look like shit. :-/ These are the things in life that make me angry. This is my nemesis. I suppose I am a yuppie.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So here is the generic response: While I respect the views of my friends, as the one experiencing my life firsthand, I reserve the right to have different interpretations of my life events and changes. Lets jump in with the "beer thing."  Ya, thats really not a big deal.  And it hasn't removed my motivation. I started "drinking" literally 3.5 months ago.  Precisely when Bekah left.  Amazing. On the other hand, my lost "sense of motivation": Ya, unfortunately(?) that seems to have left a couple years ago. About the time I moved in with Bekah. It was right then I realized that striving and striving for some outside success wasn't making me happy and wasn't what I wanted in life.  Ya, I'd gotten straight As in school, graduated valedictorian, got all As in college (except the few Bs from those that didn't understand my genius ^^) but it wasn't ever really fulfilling.  Not something I deeply wanted.  Just how it happened.  I was smart.  I got good marks.  I never really worked for it. But moving in with Bekah made me HAPPY.  Truly happy. I think that is what a lot of those that grew up with me didn't/don't understand.  I was finally really content.  And i wasn't drinking at that time.  I'd just found what I had wanted from life.  And I'm afraid its really the only thing i want: To live a very simple existence with the person I'm in love with. I suppose that makes me a romantic in some horribly shallow sense of the word. I don't have great academic aspirations ... and i'm not entirely sure i ever truly did; it seems I always held them as a response to the goals of my peer group. I thought that was all you needed.  A great education and a great job. But it seems different people can have different life goals. I, honestly, don't need riches.  I don't need a PhD.  All i want is an average job that pays the bills and allows me to save just enough money to be comfortable. Work isn't life.  And i personally don't enjoying treating it as though it is. What I really want from life is to find that one person that I am happy with.  And that is happy with me. The "problem" now is that: without a great value placed on where I spend those initial 8 work hours, I can't find the motivation to be miserable striving to spend it somewhere else.  To change my station. And i suppose this makes me quite unattractive. But, at the moment, its me. And what some people may find hard to understand, so I'll repeat it...I was TRULY DEEPLY HAPPY with Bekah.  My life was fucking brutally shattered just a couple months back.   Game over man.  I was going to marry the girl.  That wasn't lip service.  I believed the rest of my life was there in front of me and I was quite excited about it. Losing that does take a toll on a person.  And i know i fucked up.  I know that the relationship wasn't meant to be.  And i learned a lot from it.  However, it still hurt.  It still hurts. And yeah, i may seem different. But ... I'm sorry.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A nice  urlLink article  with some fun Questions for ole Bushy Poo to answer.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Any random visitors: Bypass this top post.  ^^ It'll bore the hell out of you! Go down to the weird random me stuff. Try three or four down. Thats when it gets into the personal invasion territory. ^^ And thats the only reason I'd write this. But, you know. You could always take a look at  urlLink kittens !
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why can't I? Umm... Right-o then. Seeing as how apparently this rift has developed, I suppose I'll do my part to peer inside. (Kinda like the last  urlLink Indiana Jones  movie...) My opinion is this: Life is never static. But it also doesn't run in chapters. It is hard to define clear endings; 75% of the things in my life are static, while there is a constant 25% in flux. We can try to mark and celebrate some grand transformation, a lush introduction into some foreign world.  But in reality, adulthood doesn't just *boom* happen.  In fact, it never *happens.* It is just always happening. I've been living an "adult" life for several years now.  But I'm the same person.  My tastes may have changed.  My looks may have fluctuated.  Priorities shifted.  But I'm still me. My roots haven't been changed.  And they can't. As it is, perhaps I don't like the town i grew up in. But don't negatively judge the dislike I have for a place that I have fully experienced, simply because it is the place you feel the most comfortable. Different people have different tastes.  That is what makes the world work.  There is someplace perfect for everyone. @ Jacob: Jake, our experience isn't going to be clear cut with sharp periodic beginnings and endings.  We should hang out now b/c we are friends.  No more, no less.  Enjoy the time we have.  But don't put more symbolism than is needed.  I want to be friends with you guys, and I have always enjoyed it.  But I have always hated "coming of age" ... at least once i discovered it isn't true.  At least not for me personally. @ Brandon: Life has to keep on going, buddy.  We can't keep things the same.  We can't jump back to a time we remember fondly.  We have to (like i said before) enjoy the time we have ... NOW.  Don't regret that the past is over and our worlds are changing.  We are still friends.  Circumstances are different.  Thats all.  Its really not that bad. I honestly don't have any answers. Tensions run high.  Emotions get all filazzled. But there are reasons we are friends. Why should those change just because we are in different places (physically and emotionally)? Bottom line. Once again. We are friends. Thick and thin. Deal with it.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love the fact that I'm addressing and writing this to  someone . My tone is one of exposition to an audience. Yet I have no audience to speak of. Perhaps I have a  urlLink secret santa  of sorts I'd like to read this. And just in case. They may happen upon it. I want  my  self  to be  crystal  clear. However, as they are a secret santa, I don't know who they are.  Or whether they will come across me. Or whether they exist. Ho ho ho.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Constantly at work I thought of little things I'd like to explore. But i didn't have paper.  Or a pen. So, i lost all of those "brilliant" topics and am stuck with this one. "I'm tired. Light posting." Going to watch a dvd. Drink some Coronas.  Steam some veggies. Let life pass me by for a bit. -- However, if I drink enough Coronas, I'll probably enter a bunch of nonsensical posts. Have fun wading through! Cuz it just may be a long night.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I've grasped the reason this blogging deal is so attractive to me personally (and perhaps others). I'm really into the idea of it as a personal diary wide open for anyone to wander in and see. It encourages me to gush out those things I normally wouldn't verbalize, but also allows me to articulate them into complete thoughts. If I were writing it *purely* for myself, I wouldn't write at all ... in my head is where stuff that is just for me resides. But, instant publishing gives me a reverse voyeurism buzz; the knowledge that i'm standing naked in front of a window.  Sure, it seems darker in my apartment than outside.  However, i can't be sure.  And maybe the glow on this screen is giving everyone a full frontal of me in my private glory. So, like the tarted up neighbor we all spied on as kids, I'll put on something sexy in front of my open curtains, because if someone's watching, might as well make it worth their while. Its the little risks that are profoundly attractive. The release is just an additional perk.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I finally got my IPOD. It rules all. Kicks mucho behind. I love it. I'm thinking about getting a G4 PowerBook as my next purchase... Apple is slowly but surely winning me over. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      And hey, as long as I'm whining... Lets finish the story: So, yeah, it is a weird situation. The primary (from what i can gather) reason she is going to Japan is because she needs to discover something about&nbsp;love and fate. There was a guy that was totally into her despite herself that she neglected to feel similar for. Then he decides to move to Japan, and she finally figures out that she may really be into him. Now she needs to go and find out. - Here I am living on my own, taking a vacation from being "me" for a while and trying to get out of the bottom i've been stuck wandering for months. Just out of a serious relationship that i can't quite seem to&nbsp;eliminate completely and definitely not looking for completion. - For no reason at all we decide to strike up a relationship. Two people on very different ways, with very different personalities that don't have the time to make any significant connection. Looking for nothing. But, we've both managed to complicate the other's life&nbsp;(this is true, at the least, for me) to a complete mangle of what was wanted for the moment. In my case I'm completely grateful for the shake up, despite how much it is hurting to have to get over someone before i can really even care for them. For her, while i don't know what is in her head, I'd imagine it is something along the line of "I don't need this guy complicating my already twisted life." I have nothing but esteem for her influence to me, she is probably contemptuous of mine. She'll be happy to abandon the situation. I'll be sad to see her go. - While i suppose that isn't exactly the finished story, I hope to&nbsp;find the resolution&nbsp;as wonderfully turbulent as our time together. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok. So, we all know the Emilee deal. The coworker. Went out, had a good time? Right, that one. Well, it seems that she has taught me a lot about myself that i wasn't aware of either because: a) i didn't look b) i simply couldn't see Now .. she is leaving. And i'm actually finding it hard to deal with. I wasn't planning on having real feelings for her. But, unfortunately, with people that help you grow internally, you grow attached to them. Some kind of symbiosis that&nbsp;thrives on emotional development. Anywho, now: I've discovered that despite how convinced i am that she is crazy, she is&nbsp;also a super fascinating person. And she really&nbsp;may not be&nbsp;any more crazy than your average friend. I'm thinking it is more that she doesn't insist on hiding&nbsp;her insanity&nbsp;once she is comfortable with someone. She is a genuine person, a control freak, able to do anything she sets her mind on, terrified of failure and a maze of character quirks. And i really like her. This leaves me with a bit of a quandry in that i have to decide if i should just leave it as friends with (maybe just perceived by me) a strong sexual tension or try to make something happen. But even this isn't a cut and dry choice...as i have the contending reality that she is leaving in a bit more than 2 weeks to go to Japan and then moving straight to San Francisco upon her return to the States.    
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've decided not to feel guilty about whining on my blog. And i've also decided that due to this non-guilty feeling I will be whining more. The way i see it is: this is a diary/journal thing ... very cathartic, but only if i don't worry about my audience. So, i will feel free to whine. Because god knows if i do it out loud i am&nbsp;a "negative jerk."  Anywho: On with the whining! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dude, these&nbsp; urlLink two  are soooo now. ^^ This album is one of those things that may not exactly impress your friends, but it sure will boggle the hell out of them. One of the weirdest (yet most fucking brilliant upon REPEATED listenings) albums i've heard in a pretty long time. If anyone decides to listen to it...well, most likely you won't. But if you do, maybe take my advice regarding listening to it. Listen to it once fully. Make yourself sit through it. Seventy six minutes is a lot to digest. :) Then after a break, go back to it and start with track 7 and listen through. Once it finishes, take a break. Listen to it from track 5 on. Take another break. And listen from beginning to end. The thing to remember is that if you don't like this album at first, you almost *have* to listen to the work&nbsp;a couple times to give it the full chance it deserves. Hopefully, you'll fall in love. However, if you aren't into weird, sometimes noisy and incomprehendible pop, you will likely loathe this album.&nbsp; Which is a shame because it really freakin' rocks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Polyphonic Spree - Together We're Heavy Ok, so i started the day recommending this to Bekah. Now i'm going to finish it recommending it to everyone. This is possibly the most sugar coated up with people sound ever but it is FUCKING AMAZING. I can't say it is the best album ever, or even top 5. But, wow, the 2nd track "Hold Me Now" is possibly the most amazingly positive *sound* i've heard in ... a looooooooong time. Please trust my judgement. Just listen to the one song. Pirate it. Whatever. Its fucking beautiful. And yeah, i imagine of the 7 people that read this, maybe 2 will like it (yeah, i know your guys' taste, but i can't help but throw out recommendations, no matter how doubtful it is you'd even listen to, much less like, it), but whatever. If you 2 that like it wouldn't have heard it otherwise, this is totally worth it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Since i know how much everyone *loves* this topic: I talked to bekah today via text messaging. It started out innocent enough...i told her she'd like the new  urlLink Polyphonic Spree  album. Then we ventured into more personal territory and I decided that I'm not ready for that (read: i kinda misinterpreted something and was turned off by the fact that i got freaked out by what i misinterpreted).   I'm trying to be a good exboyfriend. I'm nice. But i'm really probably not ready for personal life info. Unfortunate, but true! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Everything is going relatively OK for once!! Stress levels dropping. Drama subsiding. Looks like in no time at all everything will spin into hell mode again. Or perhaps i'll be able to enjoy the calm for a while. BTW, you all should watch  urlLink Control Room . I'd recommend it over F-9/11 as far as politically informative movies go. And it has also thrust Al-Jazeera into my daily news reads list... In case&nbsp;anyone is curious that is: &nbsp;  urlLink http://english.aljazeera.net/HomePage   urlLink http://reuters.com   urlLink http://www.bbc.co.uk/news  &nbsp; And there&nbsp;are a healthy number of blogs that i rely on for political news&nbsp;as well. &nbsp; Lately its become a bit too stressful to know exactly what is going on in the world...but it certainly helps me gain a bit of insight into the gravity of my "problems." 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'd laugh hysterically. But, unfortunately, its not funny. Looks like  urlLink they're up to it again . The story so far: So, lets spin Iraq into a 9/11 connection. Ok. Now we'll fight a war ... get some oil and such and an increased reach in the middle east. Huzzah. Ok, the war went badly ... but, hell, we're still in power for another few months (hehe, or longer, if we have our way with the "elections") lets start drawing connections between Iran and 9/11. Ha! Then we can start static in Iran and have even more sway in the Mid East! Huzzah! Saudi Arabia? What's that? -   The sad thing is ... either the government thinks people can't see through their translucent policies ... or they&nbsp;know that American's really don't care anymore. Anywho. Lovely. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Great song. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sweet! I went climbing today. Hurt my foot. (Rock climbing shoes have 0 support/padding ... try not to land on jutting rocks.) Skinned my hands apart (typing is damn near painful). Had a great time. I am super excited about the fact that pushing my body harder than i thought i could is so DAMN FUN. At this moment i am completely exhausted (pardon the sentance structures) but extremely pleased with the fatigue. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      That I can't even begin to want to blog it. Current main concern is: (as usual) Massive drama in ladyville. Well, not massive, but everything gets magnified when it is an employee. Oh well. She's a super sweet girl. She's really cute. She's intelligent. We LIKE the same music/movies/activities/food/stuff. But, alas, we aren't at all alike. And i have fun with her. We have great chats. But sometimes her polar opposite personality makes me wonder about any future. And then i remember that this is a "destined to fail" fling. She is moving away in a month. She is an employee. There's really no chance. There's actually no reason to care one way or the other. But i do. Its my nature.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Link . The world is truly coming to an end.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Off the newer Blonde Redhead album "Misery is a butterfly... The video for  urlLink Equus  is pretty awesome...it helps that it is probably the best song on the album. This is the stuff i'm listening to now ...  Blonde Redhead .. Deerhoof .. The Fiery Furnaces .. I think i'm going insane. (un?)Fortunately i love it. And smileys. =D
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Whats wrong with  urlLink this  picture? - OMFG, I can't believe what an IDIOT our president is. [sigh] Democrazy kicks ass. In case you don't want to click on that one...  urlLink here  is the AP link and article:  "Bush misspoke as he delivered a speech at the signing ceremony for a $417 billion defense spending bill.   "Our enemies are innovative and resourceful, and so are we," Bush said. "They never stop thinking about new ways to harm our country and our people, and neither do we."   No one in Bush's audience of military brass or Pentagon chiefs reacted." 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Based on who is covering. So, today's big headline so far is a downed US helicopter in Najaf, Iraq. Ok, the coverage varies: The BBC posts this image:   Ok, brown people with guns. Scary! No wonder we're fighting!  Reuters posts this image:   More brown people with guns. Same reaction as above.  FoxNews:   Hmm...lets entirely remove the human consequence of this conflict and just show some torn wreckage. Get people pissed off at the obvious monetary toll the "rebels" are taking, but don't show them any American blood.  Al-Jazeera:   Suffering. That is the consequence. This is what our stupid war is all about. The human cost is inherently the highest. Everyone is capable of pain, suffering and loss, no matter where you are from, whose army you support, or where you happened to have the fortune or misfortune of being born. - But as long as we can peddle it as: us against them, black against white, freedom and prosperity against fundamentalist terror, we'll get the full ignorance of the American and British people behind the cause. Kinda sickening. Note: I haven't had time this morning to read all the articles, so I am just judging by the images they chose to associate with the story. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...And, here is me in the morning.  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love cartoons. And dogs. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Horrible snapshot of myself after the loooong day...but it was asked for!  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Cat has a hairball.  This is gonna be icky. I have an iPod.  I love it more than any *thing* ever.  Probably the best purchase a music lover can make. (And yes, i love music, but not ALL music, just the "good" stuff! :) ) I got a real haircut, its short now! I'm thinking about shaving clean and wearing my glasses to look like an 18 year old. :) Had a great time with the Brandonius this weekend. Life is mellowing out. I've learned a lot about myself in the past 2 weeks, and i think everything will be ok. I've also witnessed a lot of "movie scenes" lately .. Quite vague, but exciting.  Basically, when you are in a moment and for whatever reason you notice that what is going on around you (or to you) would be perfect on the screen to describe a facet of life. Thats all. Haven't been rock climbing in a while. Bummed about that. :( Going to try to go this week .. but we'll see. :-/ Realized I write fragmented and choppy. Gonna put a stop to that.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>