<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey Guys! I Just Got This Blogger So This Is My First Post! Today I Went Rock Climbimg @ This 1 Fitness Gym In Fresno 4 My Cousims B-day It Was So Cool But It's Harder Than You THink! It's The Last Week Of School But I Don't Know How To Feel: Happy Or Sad? IDk But Harry Potter comes Out on Friday! I'm sO Excited! Well Gtg Bye Ppl!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hehe haha i am in such a good mood rite now and i don't know why! well all i do all day is sleep watch t.v. And get online! in the evenings i go to softball practice which i really like bcuz there are really cool and nice ppl on my team like Kelly she is soo cool and is like the craziest person i know bsides me ! lol and both briana and breana their always funny and Alysha CAN'T FORGET CHICA!@ what can i say about her? there are no words thats how crazy she is1 andrina is cool and so are bernie and bonnie there are some ppl i don't get along with but hey thaat's fine ur not gonna get along with everybody. it's wierd cuz most of these ppl are diff from my freinds at skool and i thunk that's really cool to know so many diff types of ppl. i miss some of my freinds at scool like maritza and jehni all thst laughs good times good times. but it's cool. oops i almost forgot erica or mabey i didn't want to include her! ::suspisious face:: lol j/k or am i? no really i'm j/m well gtg much love from me\
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      okay yall we gotta set somethings straight. these are the hottest guys oit there right now 1.Daniel Radcliffe 2.Chester Bennington 3.Drake Bell 4.Bam Margera 5.Orlando Bloom 6.Johnny Depp 7.Jake Epstein 8.Rupert Grint 9.That malfoy dude from harry potter but idk his name 10.Hoobastank's lead singer I think his name is Doug 11.Hoobastank's drummer 12.Tom Cruise 13.ryan Gosling 14.Matthew Perry 15.adam Brody 16. Benjamin Mckenzie 16.Jake Gyllenhaal 17.George Clooney 18.Brad Pitt 19. Matt Damon 20.Jude Law 21. a guy So that is pretty much the list so if u have anymore u want to add or if i forgot anymone comment okay well laters haters lol remember that kelly well bye yall 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Whew now this is a subject i can babble on 4 hours about. i simply luv Daniel radcliffe.My Bum sister shares the same birthday as him July 23. this year he will turn 15. whew now that's a hot 15 year old. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey guys! yesturday was also the premire of the new degrassi season! soo loking foward to new episodes! i'm kinda upset because i read somewhere that they aren't gonna show the episodes where manny finds out shes pregnant. i hope they do cuz i know those are gonna be good episodes. well gtg now. much love,
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesturday was the last day of skewl and it was really sad. everybody was crying, well every body except for those ppl with no feelingsi cried a lot and it's not even my 8th grade year! Next year it's is my 8th grade year and i will definently cry alot 10 times more than i did this year. yesturday was cool too cuz something happened to my friend that i know she really wanted that to happen and she was really happy. yesturday i went to go see Harry potter with some freinds and it was sooo cool. I LOVE Daniel Radcliffe he is soooooo hot. His eyes are so beautiful they can look green or blue depending on the light. I know somebody else who has really pretty eyes!hm... who could i be talkin about erica? lol. well that was my last day of skewl c-ya laterz. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>