<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Baking Class.  I now deciding (  and should decide fast ) what class to take this month. 1.) 02June2004,Tuesday: Basic Cakes & Icings for Beginners here in Makati(10.30-3pm) = 1,500 2.) 02June2004, Wednesday:  Secrets No More, in Boni Serrano (9-5pm) = 3,000 3.) 09June2004, Wednesday: Brownie Workshop in Boni (9.90-4pm) = 2,500 4.) 18June2004, Friday: Brownies and Bars in Makati (1.30-5pm) = 1,500  What am I gonna take??  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Watch SCHREK2.  I have to admit, I didn't watch the first one.  Forever, I promise to look for our original dvd copy, Original of course(wink!wink!), before the week ends.  It's been quite a while since I last laughed out (too) load in a movie house.  I wasn't the only one laughing though - almost everybody inside the 7.30pm showing of the film in Greenbelt3 Cinema1.  Hay, nice to have a very generous big brother - of course, he was the one who treated his immediate family to a P150.00 per pax THS movie and hear this -- Dinner at Good Earth, too!  How cool is that?!?!  Terrific Sunday wasn't it?  We had Lily on the pond for appeatizer and chicken and beef with veggies for main menu.  You gotta try their Green Iced tea - just refreshing.  The restaurant's ambience is calm and rested.  No load music and service was fast.  Well, you gotta have early dinner if you prefer to eat there.  At 6pm, ppl start to wait for their que to be seated.  My siblings and I have a silly joke about the elevated part of the restaurant.  It's made of hard plastic with minimal lightings below.  The plastic must be rally tough - with all the weight and movement.  I told my kuya that if the elevated part of the restaurant has reached it weight quota, certain events might occur in the restaurant.   1.) the plastic blocked will light up randomly and pick the "lucky" person booted out from the area. 2.) the sensor on the plastic will pick the heaviest person in the area and a spot-light will light that person in all sides. Then, with shame, he might just leave the area.   3.) after sensing the heaviest person in the area, the plastic blocks under that person's chair will eject him out of the area(bad idea).  ***hay, the things that run through my brain. ________  Dad was sweating excessively yesterday.  We went to mass in Greenbelt.  Nearing unloading area, dad felt his knees weakend, thus asking us for a candy.  Me and kuya left them and parked the car.  Forgetting about the candy, we proceeded to the movie ticket booth to purchase the 7.30 Shrek filming.  I was texting dad that we would follow them as soon as we secure the ticket.  I have totally forgotten about dad's condition.  In the line, Kuya got a call from Daddy - he was mad.  Then, we remembered about the dulsi.  tsk tsk tsk.  After the mass, they got food and I went to get hot choco for daddy upon his request.  They got choco squares from  Chocolate bar and Rum and Raisin ice cream from Haagen Daz.  _____  Blogging:This is nice - just like therapy.  (Not that I've been to periodic paid check-ups with a psychologist.  Why, where did u get that info? Who told you?  heheh JK. Hi Ms. Anee of UST, College of Science Circa 1996-2000!)  This is a good day, but what about days with tornados or typhoons in my life?  Will I be still honest in this journal?  We'll see.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Process Anger was from a book Everything I Know by Sharon Strassfeld.  I read about the book from Joanne Rae M. Ramirez's article, The Gift of Space, in Philippine Star dated 08 June 2004.    The simplicity of Ms. Ramirez's article makes it dear and readable - not too fancy and yet entertaining. Especially her articles that relates to her son, Chno.  (blank)  The best anecdote would be process anger that most people must master.  I believe that masking anger will make you nuts.  It's like playing stack blocks ( I forget the name, Uno ba?) --  when the pile is too tall and you reach the rim of your patience and with a little shake - the blocks fall apart, causing havoc. Do you get what I mean.  Magulo, bahala kayo kung di nyo ma relate!  hjejejej  take care U.  I'll post some of Sharon's anecdotes next time.       
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Process Anger.  Don't mask it with humor or bury it away smewhoere.  Anger, real anger, is like yeast.  It can become its own living organism and bubble away, spreading everywhere.  So learn to talk. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mikee and Me. Manor Hotel, Baguio in 2002 &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Xis Aileen, Buttercups and Me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    With my dogs:Pao and Onyx - they were given to friends for care.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Enchanted Kingdom: 26 December 2003, Tines' Birthday.  Top from left: Kim, Tata Mebs, Ken, Bam, Mikee, Mon-Mon. Below:Louie, Tines and Mac.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mamang in her favorite green dress! Picture taken in Ken's 14th Birthday in the Seminary.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Self-portriat!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>