<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      car shopping today went well. i'm really looking at two cars, the nissan spectra and the a saturn coupe. both have the basics that i want, sporty look, power everything, sunroof, standard transmission etc. the spectra has got more balls than the saturn but i think i'll get a better deal with the saturn. this is my first experiance buying a NEW car. soo many choices, i feel like a kid in a candy store..hehe  still no real resolution on the female issue. seems as though it get more complicated whichever way i go, so i think my plan is going to be to just ride out the storm and hope for a better days in the future. i know i know not a very creative solution but i honestly can't think of anything else.  on a different note i was thinking about the relationship my generation has with their work. my parents worked three jobs when they were younger and to this day i haven't know them to complain about it. they saw it as a chance to make money and as simply doing what you needed to do. it's strange that just one generation later we see people who can barely handle working one fulltime job and endlessly complain about how much they do. i really believe if we worked harder as a generation we would not only do better personally but do more for each other. not to get too religious but catholics believe that forgiveness/redemption is not based on faith alone but also on good deeds. maybe if we did more for each other on a regular basis we would all be better off, then again that's just my opinion...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So alot of weird shit has been happening to me lately. For some reason, a reason which ill-ludes me, I can not seem to have a normal everyday boring relationship. There always seems to be some kind of drama or opstical. One of my more intelligent female friends seems to think it's because I don't choose the right kind of women, i should remind her that there aren't many women out in the world like her. Well if anyone has any tips on what is the right kind of women, I'm open to suggestions. Maybe it's that I just don't know what I want. I suppose when one thinks about it, my issues aren't that different then anyone elses but that doesn't help me feel like i'm not alone in this deal. I guess when it comes to these situations, in the end we are all really just alone in a crowd...
     
    
</post>


</Blog>