<Blog>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      PICS. YES.    urlLink Tiffany and Maggie   Let me go through a little history of both of them.   Tiffany (Girl in the front) - I knew her since 6th grade. We're going into 11th this year. We weren't friends back then, but we knew each other. End of 7th grade, we were in a group to perform a play, I started coming over to her house a lot, and it eventually came to the point where I came over every day just to see her. We just started off as friends, but one day, she gave me a note as I was leaving. I read it on the way home on my bike, it was about how she said she started to have feelings for me. So the next day, I gave her a note telling her how much I liked her. This went on during the summer every day or so. Finally, I had to take a trip to Canada to see my cousin. We were both saddened by it and decided to keep a diary/journal of what we did each day and how we felt. I came back a week later, we exchanged notes, and asked her out. It was horrible too. I was leaning in to give her a peck on the cheek, she thought I was leaning in to give her a kiss, so it ended up being a sloppy kiss. I said,"will you go off with me?" I was so surprised about the kiss, I messed up and accidentally blurted that out. I said I would give her some time to think about it. As I was going home, she came up running behind me with my backpack (I forgot it there. -_-) I said thanks, and as she was running off, she said yes. I rode home as fast as I could like a happy little seventh grader...which I was. The next day, we hung out, and we broke up as I was leaving. She said we she wasn't ready, as she had just broken up with a guy in the week before. So...we broke up and stayed as friends. Years went by, me and her stayed as friends while still falling in love even more as the years went by. I feel if I were to marry someone, she would be the perfect girl for me. She has just been there for me for so long. Tiff, I know you'll be reading this, just want to say I love you.   Maggie (Girl in the back) - Let's see...I've known this girl since 6th grade too. Me and her talked to each other once in a while, but not really, and when we did, we just talked about chess. Me and her played a few games against each other, if I recall correctly. 7th grade, during the time school was ending (but before I started knowing Tiffany), I used to sit next to her during 6th hour, Social Studies, we would talk once in a while, and I found her to be quite nice. I thought it would be neat if I ever went out with her, but never thought much about it, as we did not keep in contact much. 8th grade, we talked, but quite less than any other grade. Every time she signed my yearbook, it was about chess. >_ =O) We hung out through summer, ran, stuff, and so on.   School started for 10th grade. Glad to get back to school. Became closer friends throughout the year. Stuff, stuff... During the ending of the year, me and Tiff started fighting more and I became very...mean and exclusive. I talked to Samantha and Maggie a lot on what I should do. I was just looking for someone I could talk to that would just listen, as I needed to vent, but their opinions helped when they did give some.   Sam - Thanks a lot, you've listened and not blurt out anything. I will be glad to listen to you when you need me to. You've been becoming a great friend to me too.  Back on track. So I kept talking to Maggie and Sam about how I felt as the weeks went on. Tiff and me got into a huge fight, one unlike any others, we made up three days later. So couple more weeks went on, until it was summer again.  Summer 2003 - I started hanging out at Maggie's house. Every day I spent with her, I started to realized that I found her presence to be very comforting. I bought some roses and wrote a note deciding to ask her out, she said no, and I won't go into any further details on that. So we just went on being friends.  One day, Maggie, Tiff, Josh, and me decided to go swimming at Maggie's grandma's house. (Josh is another cool friend of mine.) We started to play some Truth or Dare out of pure boredom. It got to the point where people were dared to kiss each other. Won't give much details on that, but those two kisses from you two felt...nice...there was just something so comforting about it when I went to bed thinking about it.   Anyway, you probably noticed that ">:(" at the top, so I guess I better explain it. Tiff was dared to tell why she broke up with her boyfriend, what she told us pissed me off. It did. She told us that her ex had punched her about four times in the stomach and kicked her after she had fallen on the ground. While she was on the ground, she started coughing up blood. He did this just because Tiff spent the day with Maggie and Josh. You don't hit a girl, especially one that is my best friend. It's pathetic!   I'm going to stop there, as I feel like I shouldn't be going into this too much. Tiff, I apologize for what happened, you didn't deserve that, no way in hell. You might say you're okay now, but feel free to talk to me when needed.  I guess I better summarize this up, as I'm getting sleepy...  Tiff and Mags, you two are great friends, no doubt about that, I love both of you so much for all you have done for me. There are tiny stuff that you guys have done for me that have made me appreciate our friendships. Let's go out and eat next week! I'm paying! ;)  Please leave your name if you are signing.  urlLink  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>