<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: Ha, my sister bought this Chinese zodiac book yesterday; I think I’ll just extract some of it in relevance to me. Righty-o. The book is called  The New Chinese Astrology  and it is by Suzanne White. I find it sketchy in some bits, but hell, astrology is a lot of bullshit mixed in with some realism.  ___________  Ah Virtuous Rabbit!    You seek harmony. You are careful and practice discretion in all things. When you sense a conflict lurching your way, you skitter off and hide. Distinguished, diplomatic and well-mannered, you are also as nervous as a rabbit. Culture and refinement comfort you. You don’t hate money either: you know instinctively how to earn and keep your fortune without flash or flaunt. You favour traditional antique furnishings over chrome and glass contemporary. You’re a soft-stepping go-getter… Ambitious but never aggressive, strong but never rough. Your brand of wisdom says that ‘He who fights and runs away lives to fight another day.’   You are hypersensitive- squeamish, even. You are a bit of a hypochondriac: an innocent hangnail on your big toe alarms you. ‘Call an ambulance; Get me to the emergency room!’ Chronic illnesses- migraine, asthma, hay fever, lower back pain, warts, hives- you’ve tried them all.  Buy yourself a big house in the country, then fill it with brilliant, well-behaved kids. Choose a partner from gentle Coats, scrupulous Pigs or loyal dogs. If you’re feeling lavish, remember that Snakes are delighted to languish on Rabbits’ velvet divans. Avoid Tigers, Roosters, and Dragons. You plan your life to run smoothly. And usually it does. But should spontaneity enter the picture and events go awry- you freak out. Take my advice and lighten up. Not only on yourself but, more especially, on the rest of us.               Rabbits are discretion incarnate. They live quietly, in refined surroundings, prefer to ask very little of others and are not keen on entertaining just any old company. Rabbits observe the world from their place on hearth, meticulously scrutinising their own and others’ behaviour. No matter how successful or socially respectable they are, Rabbits often feel unsure of themselves, worrying about the impression they make, wondering if their gestures and actions are acceptable and decorous enough to pass muster with higher-ups.  Although he always claims to be ready to learn new things, the Rabbit is not a willing traveller or changer of address. Ideally, he lives in a harmonious relationship in a lovely home with close friends and family nearby. Despite his native curiosity and dreams of touring exotic lands, home is still the best place for a Rabbit. He feels safe and secure, comfortable and cosy in his own home and would prefer never to spend so much as a night elsewhere.   Nothing gets under the Cat’s sensitive skin more irritatingly than disorder. He is fastidious about structure. He hates chaos, deplores anarchy and refuses to have anything to do with liberalism. Although he might claim to adhere to the principles and espouse some of its more humane aspects, the sternly traditional Rabbit does see any better way to run the world than to maintain a rigid social structure- even at the cost of justice and, if necessary, under the yoke of tyranny.  Therefore, he possesses an odd combination of conflicted characteristics. He sincerely believes in justice, yet, he is mostly unwilling to stick out his delicate neck to make certain that it gets done. He will speak at length about his pet theories and share his rigid opinions on many issues, but when it comes to defending them, debating openly, or standing up for issues he claims to hold dear, the Rabbit disappears.   Rabbits cling to old-fashioned tenets and are virtually cemented in their ways. They feel that dissension should be kept out of life altogether, preferring to ignore discord and pretend that violence never existed. Rabbits like books that don’t upset or frighten them, rigorously avoid seeing disturbing movies or TV shows and steer a wide berth around truth-revealing confrontations.  The Rabbit constantly seeks protection from reality. You will rarely find one of these vulnerable creatures beating a path to the scene of an accident. Rabbits are afraid of their own shadows and do not want to live in or deal with tumult or upheaval. They also hate tardiness and have no patience with procrastination. For the Rabbit, all aspects of life should be clear-cut, well thought-out, on schedule and up front. If Rabbits had their way, all human beings would be preordained, by birth, social status, and degree of civilisation to fit neatly into ‘life slots’, do their respective jobs well, marry, procreate, die and get buried in the local churchyard.   Messiness and confusion are the Rabbit’s worst enemies but should he encounter either, the Rabbit rolls up his sleeves and dives in to put it to rights. Rabbits will take charge of de-mildewising your fridge, untangling three hundred feet of garden hose or clearing weeds out of a vegetable patch in a trice. Rabbits so dislike anything they feel is opposed to the natural order that they often jump self-righteously at the chance to make order out of chaos. Some call it meddling.          ___________  And since I’m a fire rabbit, I decided to write up what she put for fire rabbits xD Apparently Harry Belafonte and Fidel Castro are fire rabbits. Amazing innit. ___________  Fire often brings instability to the staid Rabbit yet also adds verve to his prissy, over-correct nature. He cannot be called aggressive, but the Fire Rabbit is generally somewhat feistier than his fellow rabbits.   Genius thrives in this Rabbit. Many great writers and musicians, painters and poets were born in Fire Rabbit years. Emotionally intuitive, he can pick up extra-sensory messages in others and frequently knows how to transform them into poignant works of art. This Rabbit will also have an incisive sense of humour and knows how to charm people with it. Others usually enjoy his company and find his wit intelligent and easily applicable to real-life situations. The Fire Rabbit is the least shy of all Rabbits. He can handle fame and deal competently with the public without needing to flee the spotlight.   He is no altruist, however. He is supremely self-centred and wants his way in most relationships. He can be strong in the gave of opposition- if he needs to, he will bare his claws and hiss loudly to warn off attacks- but he would prefer to play a waiting game, using devious tactics to avoid confrontation and skirting most thorny issues. The anguish the Fire Rabbit experiences during a waiting period can cause him serious health problems. He is not naturally well equipped with inner conflict. Yet he creates it by holding his real feelings in while waiting for the moment to strike. If he could learn to be more humane, put his ego in his pocket, acquire a knowledge of how to care for others and exchange his feelings more readily, he could avoid engendering complex chronic health problems such as depression and neuroses later on.  People accuse Fire Rabbits of arrogance. He may at first seem reserved and aloof. Mostly he attempts to present an affable façade but sensitive people are not fooled. He is over-confident and full of himself when it comes to matters of the mind.   The fire Rabbit reads a lot. His memory is vast and its information well organised. In discussion he can be arch and pedantic, causing his friends and family to spend many a yawnful evening hearing him out on subjects of arcane interest to nobody. Others, again, don’t count for much- and their opinions, frankly, bore him.   Government jobs and administrive posts attract and suit the Fire Rabbit. He will be at home in the snobbish, gilded atmospheres of embassies and diplomatic missions around the world. He also makes a wonderful business executive. Not only is he capable of brilliant management, but the Fire Rabbit has a way of infusing his workplace with that special Rabbit flair and elegance and he can spot problems before they can happen. No budget-conscious, caution-loving, self-respecting, hotshot Fire Rabbit would ever allow a small financial deficit to grow into a looming red figure on the bottom line.  ___________  This is more accurate xD And best for last is the bits I find laughable.  ___________  Your Best   Colour is grey Flower is rose Fragrance is Shalimar  Tree is poplar  Flavour is tangy  Musical instrument is piano  Birthstone is sapphire  Lucky number is 4  Your Favourite   Food is fish (HAHAHAHA)  Animal is squirrel (I mentioned one in a bit I wrote two days ago)  Drink is Bordeaux  Spice is pepper (Yes, actually, it is)  Metal is bronze  Herb is tarragon          The Rabbit is Yin  The Rabbit's Motto is: ‘I Retreat’   In pussycat mode, the Rabbit person is sensitive, tactful, home-loving, refined, prudent, discreet, long-living, ambitious, cultured, well-mannered, artistic, considerate, scholarly, suave, graciously hospitable, modest and unimpeachably virtuous.  But rub his fur the wrong way and he becomes snobbish, secretive, pedantic, complicated, haughtily indifferent, self-indulgent, hypochondriacal, punctilious, judgemental, self-righteous, deceptive, self-centred and terminally condescending.  ___________  Errrr, is there a lesson in all this? Yes, if you’re going to buy me fragrances, buy me Shalimar heh  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Link of the Day: http://www.somethingawful.com/articles.php?a=2228  Current Book: Anne Rice's  The Mummy    Rambles: BLARG
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just remembered something my dad said to me. "A girl will never remember a single good thing you do, but will remember all the bad. SO for every bad thing you do, ten good things need to be done to lighten the bringing up of that one bad thing"   This has, so far in my life, been true.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: On the way up to Taman Safari, I saw this old bloke giving his handphone to a little girl to play with. If I had had my camera out at that time, it would have made a great picture. The girl's face was one of pure joy, and the old man had a kind look in his eyes. Weird how I noticed that, instead of everything else going on in the streets.   Well, I have over 100 pictures of the animals over there, and from this i'll probably end up with 10-20 quality ones xD Well, what you gonna do eh?   My computer still sounds like its going to blow up, despite two check ups from the computer guy. Those bastards are like doctors, they treat one thing and fuck up another xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Quotation that Expresses This Post : I write entirely to find out what I'm thinking, what I'm looking at, what I see and what it means. What I want and what I fear- Joan Didion    Song of the Moment :  Sailing  (yes the one by Rod Stewart, but performed by the London Symphony Orchestra)   Movie of the Day : With Honours (This is one of a few movies which I truly like)  Rambles: Ha, I did a lot of insight today; listening to Santana does that to me for some odd reason. I’ve been a fucking jerk for the better part of my life, and by better part I’m not talking about a majority of years, I’m talking about my life in the past three years or so. Before those years, I was a sorry sap of a person, and hell, I maybe still am, even if I don’t feel it.   I won’t go into my history, that is a bore which no man should rightly endure, or woman for that matter. People believe you should keep the past at hand, this only works in some cases.   FOR EXAMPLE, do we keep pictures of things we want to forget around?   No, in most cases, because we’d rather not remember some stuff.   I keep pictures of the first time I went out with Murti, along with Krystabel, because I considered the time fun. I keep pictures of me with Kristine, simply because I’d like to remember I knew somebody as quirky as here at some point in my life. Even the time Arty came late by hours was provided a great time.   I don’t keep pictures of Jessica, and though this seems cruel, my whole life around that time sucked more balls than a poor whore addicted to crack. Even in my mind, I’ve erased almost all events that happened that one year, save the good times I had with Fudge, Christina, and William.   I think everybody does this, at some subconscious level or another, and those who don’t end up psychopaths. I know this is rather silly sounding, but most of those people simply don’t outgrow such bad memories, and have them playing 24/7 in their head. I know that feeling well, and its shit, imagine having that going on day after day, week after week, and so forth.   I would honestly fucking hate it.   Well, despite knowing that my recent life has been rather gifted, I tend to disregard this fact just like I used to neglect people who I thought just called themselves friends. Some people do just get off calling you a friend and leaving you, but some of the people I know I doubt would do that. Better give them the benefit of the doubt at least   Anyways, back on the matter at hand. I have two great brothers (Both of them seem to like hanging around me now, even though when they were younger they stayed away), an alright sister (she hasn’t stabbed me in the back yet), a great dad and mom (Ha, yes my dad gets pissed off with me for silly things, but hey, parents do that. Get angry at parents at the time, but never keep it, doesn’t help one single bit). I took like 50 pictures yesterday just of my two brothers while they were playing outside, and while I did, I couldn’t help but grin and laugh. Its funny how they can be so annoying or so cute when they choose to be. I wish I could get the photo blog thing to work, but my net is fucked up. I swear, those two kids used to be the death of me, now they’re the reason I smile at all.    My friends are fantastic, even though I take the piss out of them regularly. In the past year or so, I’ve had the time of my life practically doing nothing with them. Just hanging around them not talking is great, since they amuse me even when I refuse to admit it. I don’t think anybody understands why I stay silent when I’m around them, but I feel its easier to remember moments when you’re just an onlooker, and some day in the future, you can just bring them about again even if you haven’t seen them for years.     What I guess I’m trying to reach at in this post is a universal thank you to those around me, something I could never do myself without thinking I’m a general idiot. As well as thanks, I’d also like to ask for forgiveness. This may be too much to ask of most people, but hell, whatever. I won’t go into personnel things about each person, but here are some things I could apologise for.   - Over-reacting (Ha, this is true whenever I really like somebody, I can’t seem to just deal with shit normally)  - Being over opinionated (Dear me, this is something I’ll never be able to help, but what the hey)  - Being a general arse (I can’t be screwed to stick in every single bad things I’ve done so I’ll just classify it as a general arse =D)   How many people read my blog that actually know me is less then five, I think. Probably one in fact. Maybe not even that. I doubt anybody reads, but in a way, that’s why I quit xanga. People I knew read it, and it bugged me just because. I think the only reason I use a blog instead of a real journal is because I can’t be fucked writing by hand xD  I’m off to Puncak tomorrow; get the bracing mountain air into me and whatnot. I love the mountains. Ideally, that’s where I’d get married, which I plan on doing when I’m thirty-so xD I think people rush too much, and it fucks shit up. I know these two people who are already engaged and they’re only a year older than me at most. Fucking silly I thinks, considering they’ve never met in person. Don’t get me wrong, they’re both great people, but I think talking online and talking in person are two different things. I know this one from experience, heh. Back to the subject, the mountains. It’s just so much fucking better than the beach, because for one, you don’t get a fishy smell. I hate fish. I hate seafood for that matter. And you don’t have to deal with sand (This comes out of irritation of having sand stuck in my underwear xD).   My new camera is a blast, I got it for 2 million less then I originally could have, and this includes a bonus bag to carry it in, and a memory stick worth 256 MB. That costs around 1 mill itself. By carrying it, I’m developing hand muscles xD I swear, its like holding the lightest barbell in your hand, and depending on how long you shoot for, you could probably develop muscles.    Anything else I need to cover? No, not really. Actually, I’d like to state listening to Rancid’s  She’s Automatic  (Love this song) and then listening to Marvin Gaye’s  When a Man loves a Woman  certainly sounds odd. Now  Jungle Boogie  by Kool and the Gang is on, don't ask.  I listen to the oddest mix of stuff. On my Winamp playlist, I have music from Athlete ( You got the Style ), MC Hammer ( You can’t touch this ), Johnny Clegg and Savuka (Surely you know the song  Dela ), the London Symphony Orchestra (James Bond theme), Aerosmith ( Crazy ), Daft Punk ( Digital Love ), Iron Maiden, Barenaked Ladies ( One Week ), Coldplay ( Yellow ), Earth, Wind, and Fire ( Dancing in September remix ) and this is just off the top of my head xD   Well, that’s it, I’m off… Later on.    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Joke:  Becky was on her death bed with her husband, John, maintaining a steady vigil by her side. As he held her fragile hand, his warm tears ran silently down his face, splashed onto her face, and roused her from her slumber. She looked up and her pale lips began to move slightly. "My darling John," she whispered.  "Hush, my love," he said. "Go back to sleep. Shhh. Don't talk."  But she was insistent. "John," she said in her tired voice. "I have to talk. I have something I must confess to you."  "There's nothing to confess," replied the weeping John. "It's all right.  Everything's all right, go to sleep now."  "No, no. I must die in peace, John. I slept with your brother, your best friend and your father."  John mustered a pained smile and stroked her hand. "Hush now Becky, don't torment yourself. I know all about it." he said, "Why do you think I poisoned you?"   Rambles: Sorry, i've been bored and busy xD So instead of making my usual quality posts, i'll just insert a character I made recently.   Charon The Mad Man:   Name: Charon, sometimes Mr. Jovial  Age: Eighteen Gender: Male Race: Habarian    Class: Psychopath/Mass Murderer    Facial Description: What made Charon such a successful pickpocket was his face, for he possessed a visage which was truly run of the mill. There is nothing extravagant on it, no moles, no freckles, just the coarse remains of a man built by hardship. Charon’s hair is a dull green which could pass for dark brown under the right lighting,  and his eyes are of Habarian traits, meaning they possess a gold tint to them, and his teeth are just average. Never once has Charon shaved, and so a thickened beard runs around his face.         Clothing Description: Charon’s choice in garments is simple and effectively helps him blend in with the crowd. His pants are made of rough browned cotton, and his jacket is of tanned leather, sewn so badly it’s unfeasible to think anybody would pay for it. Charon, however, did not pay for it, so it’s alright. For shoes, he uses leather as well, but though these are well-made, the soles are coming off and the flaps are unhinging. The socks under this formerly elegant piece of footwear are tattered in so many places it seems impossible for the socks to hold together.    Weapons: Charon has always made due with the world around him, and has been reputed to kill people with a numerous range of weapons, from a dead fish to a wooden spoon. He is no professional killer, and he is no assassin, and due to the anarchic rule of Habar, he never needs to clean up his messes. Everything he has used, he has learned to use on the spot, and while some require more improvisation than others (Charon had once killed somebody with a single small cube of ice), Charon feels that a weapon is a weapon and therefore its purpose is to kill and the method on how to do it is always there, waiting to be discovered.   History: Charon was born into the world a murderer, responsible for killing his own mother within the first minute of his life. His father, a negligent alcoholic, dropped Charon as he carried him in his arms a day after his birth. Not only had Charon been born to a drunkard and a dead woman, he had been born a bastard child, for neither of the two had ever been married.   Charon was in the care of his father for nearly two years before the man traded him for a pint of beer, not realising what he was doing. The bartender, knowing he could get a hefty price off of Charon by selling him as a slave, went to the black market and did just that. Once again, Charon traded hands, this time to a homosexual paedophile named Bill.   Bill was a politician of high standings in Habar, the city which was the exact anti-thesis to utopia. He preferred his boys to be at least four before he molested them, and he would regret that with Charon. For day by day for two years, he messed with Charon’s genitals, pretending he was playing a game with Charon. What he didn’t know was that Charon, though a child, knew what the fifty year old professional liar was up to, even though he didn’t know the word for it.  When the day finally came, and Bill entered his room at night, Charon brought down a knife he had stole from the kitchen upon Bill’s cock. While Bill cried in pain, Charon swung again and again, mutilating everything from Bill’s face to his legs. Nobody paid any attention, for they heard screaming, confronted murder and thievery every day. Who cared? Charon ran from the house, clothed in an oversized jacket he had stolen from the old man’s closet, and ran until he could run no longer. He passed out after three days of aimless wandering, from dehydration.   When he awoke, Charon found himself tied to a bed, with a syringe sticking out of his arm. Connected to it was tubing, which itself led to a plastic bottle containing what seemed to be blood. Charon screamed. To his side came a man and a girl, the man looking around thirty, and the girl in her late fifteens. Both had dilated eyes, seeping eye-bags, and translucent skin. The girl was first to speak, introducing herself as Rachel, and even introducing the guy as Ox. They told Charon of how they had found him on the street, covered in blood, and how they would take care of him now.   Charon lived with these people for scarcely three years, before losing his mind when he heard them talking about selling him, Charon, to buy some more of the devil powder which they snorted after and before every love session. Ox had been surprising easy, for despite his big bulk, his veins protruded, and the wire Charon had removed from the bed had cut through the neck veins easily. Rachel was in some other mental plane when Charon took her out, and she had been easier still, pleasuring herself with her dirty fingers, hiding her privates under a holy book as if God could not see what she was doing. Neither had very much money on them, and at seven Charon couldn’t exactly earn a living in the city.    Thievery became his game, and Charon was a magnificent player. But his life maintained its inconsistency, and he mistakenly picked the pocket of a cult leader called Simon. This man was becoming increasingly powerful in the city, and his control over his followers using various narcotics and alcohols combined together disallowed any competition from rising within his sect, named the Asylum of God’s Children. In an instant after Charon’s hand reached behind the man’s serape, two bulky, brainless goons were on him, and Charon received many a blow to the guts before passing out.   When Charon awoke, he was in the Asylum itself, a former cathedral with windows that had been shattered by one of the many thousands of riots that had stormed by here before. He was tied by his feet, hanging upside down, and he could feel the blood rushing to his head. Simon the Minister stood before him, his black fancy wig crawling down his back like a snake. Simon offered Charon a proposal, one which involved Charon become a cultist. The deal was this. Charon was to become a pamphlet boy, in charge of handing out leaflets regarding the Asylum, and picking the pockets of all those who refused. This way, the sect could gain money from its non-believers as well as the currency it took from its own members. In return, Charon would get free lodgings and not be killed.   Charon had, by now, gotten far more than a taste for what life was like, and he accepted the deal, no questions asked. Years passed, and by the time he was twelve, he was much higher in position than a pamphlet distributor, and served as a right-hand man to Simon himself. To be highest on the food chain was Charon’s goal, and one night he slipped powder into the wine of the Minister, a powder which disabled the vocal chords from working as well as functioning as a tranquiliser. Simon was fully conscious when Charon began carving open his ribcage, and yet he could not scream out loud.   Charon escaped the Asylum before the cult found their leader dead, and though they vowed vengeance, they fell into disarray with nobody to lead them. It was by chance that a month later, as Charon went from inn to inn, hiring himself off as a gigolo, he met his father. Despite being at such a young age when he had last seen him, Charon knew who it was well enough, but questioned him on his life nevertheless.  The man was still a fucking drunk. Charon brought him outside the pub, and killed him with his own hands, savouring each tooth that fell out of his old man’s mouth. The next day, Charon sold his father’s corpse for beer money, it was only fair.   Now, years later, Charon is eighteen, and has killed at least twenty men, seven women, and three children. He suffers from a number of mental disorders, schizophrenia and psychosis being two of many. He is unemployed, and makes all his money off of his victims. On an end note, Charon rarely makes any sense when he talks.       
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That camera I mentioned DOES allow you to control shutter speed...  Oh dear sweet God...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Feeling of the Day : Majestic   Book of the Month :  1984  by George Orwell   Song of the Day :  Wipe Out  by Steve Vai   Rambles : Well, I got back from Singapore, and rather than bore you with a day by day account, I’ll just summarise the trip eh? I spent a lot of time going with my dad to deal with stuff related to getting his work visa renewed. Didn’t do much else except eat. Well, I bought two CDs, two jeans, and a book.   I chatted with two girls there, both who I’ve never met before, so that was cool. While we’re on the subject of beauties, I fell in love while I was in Singapore. I fell head over heels in fact. God, she was such a beauty. Great lenses, great frame, manual focus, auto focus, oh baby. The  Sony DSC-F717 . Now, my only drawback with this baby is that you can’t control the damn shutter speed, something that is becoming increasingly a need for me (I who like to experiment… Hot ladies, who like to experiment too, give me a ring-a-ling-ling). Well, it made my mind perform multiple orgasms anyway. From this I conclude my mind is a woman, and now I am stuck trying to figure out how she manages to live in this body which pays homage to masculinity and chauvinism. ANYWAYS, I need to find a digital camera which fills my every need. If you’re a single camera, call me.     Finished reading  1984  and it is a good break from the usual stuff I read. I highly recommend it for anybody who liked  Animal Farm  (also by Orwell). Favourite bits from it? Well, the repeated mantra is one.  “War is Peace Freedom is Slavery Ignorance is Strength”   And the other would be the whole book xD    Topic : How I Can’t Be Screwed To Make Another Topic Right Now  See title above.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: I'm going to cut straight to the chase here.   I'm pissed off.  And according to this book i'm reading, I must ask myself why I am pissed off and what I can do to fix that.  Why Am I pissed off? Because i'm reading this book My solution? I stop reading this book!   What's the title of this book, I hear you ask. "How to be a Happy Teenager". Yes, I hear you, you're asking yourselves "What? Our beloved Damien is reading a self-improvement book? What in God's name?" Well, i'll tell you this. I'm only reading it because the old man wants me to. Why? Well, let me tell you a little story of what happened the day I got my report cards back.   I was lounging in my room, cool and suave, when suddenly I heard the door to my house open, and I knew my parents had returned from the school, and thus, had finished picking up my grades. The dull, patterned footsteps of my father raised up the flight of stairs, and  I decided to face my fears of him shouting in my face for getting a C in math.   But lo and behold, he shouted at me for not getting a B in computer! Ah, computer class, and a computer teacher who's so fucking retarded that you could stone him to death with jelly and he wouldn't realise it until he's lying in the ground dead. Well, he probably wouldn't realise it even then.   Back to my story. I argued with my dad, and I am within reason for this. I know I deserved more than a fucking C for computer. I told him my teacher is a complete idiot and etc, and that if I saw him any time soon I would speak to the bastard myself. My father seemed to accept this, but with him, he never lets up.   Two days later, he tells me and my sister he's got this book called "How to be a Happy Teenager". Now, I once more protest, and tell him that those books are bollocks, and that i'm happy enough with my life as is. He tells me that I should be more acceptant of other people's ideas, and that not everything I don't like is stupid. He told me that if I truly liked my life, why did I get a C for computer.   I lost my mind, and went into Crazy Dammo mode. I told him once more that its my fucking teacher who's at fault here. And then the truth slipped out from him. My com teacher had told my father "I don't enjoy programming". Now, allow a moment to ponder this. Why, if I don't like programming, do I have Visual Basic on my computer? Well, I let my father ponder that very question, and he did not have an answer.   But, regardless, I am now forced into reading this crap arse book all because my fucking computer teacher gave me a fucking C. That cunt crapping fool.   Well, i'm off until thursday-friday, 'till then my splendid readers, Dammo Out.   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      http://www.intellectualwhores.com/masterladder.html  I can't help but agree
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Random Humour of the Day : I need somebody really bad… Are you really bad?  (stolen from somebody’s MSN name)    Joke of the Day : On a transatlantic flight, a plane passes through a severe storm. The turbulence is awful, and things go from bad to worse when one wing is struck by lightning. One woman in particular loses it.  Screaming, she stands up in front of the plane. "I'm too young to die!" she wails. "Well, if I'm going to die, I want my last minutes on Earth to be memorable! I've had plenty of sex in my life, but no one has ever made me really feel like a woman! Well I've had it! Is there ANYONE on this plane who can make me feel like a WOMAN??"  For a moment, there is silence. Everyone has forgotten their own peril, and they all stare, riveted, at the desperate woman in the front of the plane.  Then, a man stands up in the rear of the plane. "I can make you feel like a woman," he says. He's gorgeous. Tall, built, with long, flowing black hair and jet black eyes, he starts to walk slowly up the aisle, unbuttoning his shirt one button at a time. No one moves.  The woman is breathing heavily in anticipation as the stranger approaches. He removes his shirt. Muscles ripple across his chest as he reaches her, and extends the arm holding his shirt to the trembling woman, and whispers:  "Iron this."    Rambles : Oh sue me for liking a sexist joke xD I have nothing to say, I’m real tired from a writing spur I had earlier on… REALLY TIRED… I won’t be here on Tuesday and won’t be back until Friday I think. Off to Singapore.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Quote of the Day :  You can't be a real country unless you have a beer and an airline. It helps if you have some kind of a football team, or some nuclear weapons, but at the very least you need a beer- Frank Zappa     Rambles : Well, i'm re-posting the little work I did on the Seth Leon series a long time ago. I think I did a fair job on it, and I touched up on it a bit earlier on. Shit, when I woke up, I had a blank mind, and tried working on some fiction, but I almost went crazy. So I put on the classical music and fell asleep. I feel better, but still blank. Anyways, SIT back and enjoy Seth Leon.    Creative Writing : The Lament for Tommorow   Chapter One   The sky seemed chaotic, with so many explosions occurring at once, and each one a different hue than the other. The festivities on the ground were just as frenzied, with countless people dancing and singing, often drinking while performing these two activities. It seemed everything was well, and it denied the onlookers any sight of the evil afoot. But such merrymaking often does, and is the result of the fearful nature of man who tries to escape whatever problems they may have by simply declining the truth, and covering it up with make-up. This was the case of the current on goings, for outside the decorated city’s stone walls a war was going on. Men, and women alike, were being slaughtered by already stained swords. And this, all whilst the people of Paleno drunk themselves into stupors of happiness. They, who were fleeing from these worries, would be caught sooner or later. Only one man that night saw this, but he was no wise man of the court, nor was he the ruler.  From his window, Seth watched the members of this defiance-of-truth dance, following a single woman, dressed more spectacular than anyone else, as she dodged through the many twisting streets of Paleno. It seemed like they would follow this woman anywhere, be it a happier place, be it possible, or a more depressing state. Seth wondered whether they would pursue her to death, which lay with baited breath outside the city’s stately gates.  “Tonight, may God forgive you all for lying to both yourself, and Earth herself.” Seth muttered under his breath, so alike to a prayer, except devoid of his two hands clasping each other. And Seth watched on from his small jail cell, positioned atop a tower reaching high enough to behold the entirety of the city, and thus lacking of bars adorning the windows, for only a suicidal man would dare jump from such a height and hope to live. And because those who hated life and at the same time were criminals were not greatly cared for, the architect has decided to make the windows grandeur. In the day, the sun would burn the imprisoned in all its glory, and in the night, bats frequented the cells, pestering the cellmates, sometimes to points of insanity. Not only this, but if a man inserted into this tower looked down from these windows, they would almost immediately feel vertigo. But Leon was immune to the feeling, and as he looked down on the procedures he felt nothing but the sense something was to soon turn the smiles upside down. He now noticed, when he looked into the sky, that amidst the display of explosions, there were no stars, and instead, a crimson trail ran itself from one side of the horizon, to the other. It indicated no signs other than those of ill nature, and this very show of nature only strengthened Seth’s belief that soon it would all be done. And with this sign, he faced his back to the window, letting the moonlight bask his bare neck in its shine, and placed his eyes upon the grimy walls. Standing out amongst the dirt was a single flower, a periwinkle. It had somehow grown out of the wall, perhaps from a seed planted by an inmate from times long past, and had survived its conditions, and not only this, but actually made itself to be one of the most grand flowers of the city, and for that matter, the world. The hue of the petals for a single instant reflected themselves in Seth’s eyes, and in the next, had disappeared and the plain white replaced itself around the hazel. And although the sounds from the ground far below the room in which Seth stood continued to travel, he made rest with little trouble.    Chapter Two   “Wake up!” The warden yelled into Seth’s ear, and followed it with a backhand across Seth’s shoulder.  The prisoner jumped from, what the warden called his bed. The cover of the bed was sewed from multiple fabrics, all of which didn’t suit the one that lied by its side, and the insides of the bed were stuffed with what was apparently wool. But Seth never complained, and instead put up with each torment that made its way towards him.  “Yes?” he replied, after rubbing the sand from his sides of his eyes.  “You are wanted by his majesty.”  Seth let out a few blinks, and then took a deep breath. “His excellence knows I exist? A man such as me is known to his lordship? Oh thank the Heavens, that the lord of Paleno knows my name!” And these words of mockery were followed by a brief laugh. “Tell the despot I shall see him not!”   The warden did not look happy. “It is not your choice, Mr. Leon, to see him or not. I will take you before him whether it is your will or not.” The warden extracted a small flail from the belt around his waist, and seemed to judge its weight with is hand in a more than intimidating way.  Seth wondered about his next course of action, and decided it best to just follow the poor man doing his job.  “Alright I shall come.” And the discussion was concluded.  No further words were spoken as these two men travelled down the spiral staircase, passing by many cells, both lived in and not. The screams of the imprisoned wailed on long after they were gone.  It had been half a year since Seth had first travelled up this very flight of stairs, and this was the first time he was travelling down them. Time had long since passed from when Seth had exclaimed in the marketplace that the city would fall. But still he believed it would happen, and that it would happen very soon.  As the guard opened the door at the end of the stairs, the sunshine poured into the gloomy ground floor of the tower, destroying the darkness and replacing it with itself.  This sunlight was nothing like the one that the prisoners had to endure, which tortured them into sweats and death, but was rather refreshing to Seth’s skin. A breezy wind washed over him now, once again nothing like those experienced in the height which bit into the very bones. Seth could not have been happier with his present situation, and apart from the approaching meeting, he felt it to be a perfect day.  Through the streets Seth was led, and still the guard continued his vow of silence. The townspeople seemed to recoil in horror as they saw the man that Seth was. Seth towered high amongst the town people, often by a foot or more, and had for six months remained unshaved. And so, for this very reason, a brown forest had made a home on his skin, now so pallor. Apart from these two aspects, Seth looked more than ordinary. He was clothed in a simple, white, cotton shirt, and black trousers which hung loosely around his legs, and dropped to his heels. From there a simple pair of shoes covered his feet, of auburn hue, dulled only by lack of use. There were no rips in the materials of which the two main pieces of clothing were made of, and yet on the tall, pale man, they were seen as having these holes. Seth understood this, as he understood a lot. Common people would only see their side of the story, and if something did not fit into their perception of life, it would either be erased from knowledge or dressed to make it correct. A man of muscles and great height walking through the streets of a town like Paleno was unnatural, and to look like a well dressed man whilst doing this was not heard of. And so, the holes were created to fit the savage image projected by the man named Seth Leon. And so he ignored the people who gawked at his figure, and continued on towards the palace. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Person of the Day : Saparmurat Niyazov (Pulling off dictatorship in the 21st century,  urlLink http://www.somethingawful.com/articles.php?a=2094 )    Song of the Day : If You Think I’m Sexy- Rod Stewart     Topic : The Illuminati Facts  The Illuminati, ah, the very mention of its name inspires conspiracy stories to be told, and the weak-minded to cower in fear of this secret society. It is my attempt today to separate the facts from the fiction, but you never know. I may one of them myself! Hahaha, sureeeeeee.   Lets start with the facts eh? ‘Illuminati’ means “The Enlightened Ones” and is thought to have been established in the 1500’s, in Italy. During that period, scientists were being prosecuted as heretics by the Church, and so the scientists had to find a way of communicating their ideas to each other without the risk of being discovered. One of the known Illuminatus, and apparently one of the most influential, would be Galileo Galilei ( urlLink http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Galileo_Galilei ). Despite covering their tracks well, they eventually fled Italy, fearing that the Church (the big brother of the 16th century) was closing in.   This marked the end of the Illuminati dedicated to science, and started the anti-Christian Illuminati. The Illuminatus that fled Italy joined ranks with mystics, prophets, and the like, who had all themselves been declared heretics. Regardless, the Illuminati were deemed Satanic by the Church, called Shaitan (meaning adversary in Islamic, and being the root word of Satanic). So you see, the term Satanic means different things in different times. Regardless, the Illuminati maintained their name, and became considered one of the most powerful anti-Christian groups around, and a threat to the Church.   Despite assimilating such members as the alchemists, the Illuminati found refuge with the Freemasons (another secret society which isn’t as covert and maintains life to the present day). The Freemasons let the Illuminati into their lives, and eventually became used. Now, understand this, their have been Freemasons in seats of power for quite the while. Before I continue, I’ll name some so you can understand the power that the Illuminati potentially possessed. George Clinton (third American president), George Washington, Benjamin Franklin (one of thirteen Free Masons to sign the American Constitution), Franklin D. Roosevelt (32nd president of America), Colonel Harland Sanders (KFC), and many, many more. The last I added in as a joke, but he was a Freemason. Anyways, though we know Lucifer to be the devil (as dictated by the Church), the real meaning of Lucifer is “Bringer of light”, which can be summarised in the word “Illuminator”. They intended to bring the world under “New World Order”, using a principle called the Luciferian Doctrine.    Anyhow, you can see that at one time or the other, the Illuminati had the power that it is often credited of having nowadays. I’ll explain why they don’t in the fiction. Next paragraph please.   Look on the American dollar bill; see the pyramid with the eye? This is the biggest argument that conspiracy buffs focus on when they tell you that the Illuminati are taking over the world, because this symbol is the Illuminati symbol. What they don’t tell you is that the pyramid, which is uncapped, is a symbol of a nation which has not yet fully grown, whereas the eye is an ancient representation of spirituality. Despite this, there are beliefs that Franklin pushed this idea with the subtle help of the Illuminati, but this goes proof less, and means jack squat.   You know, looking at these theories sickens me, so I’ll let you look  urlLink http://www.suite101.com/article.cfm/ritual_abuse/53556    And I’m getting lazy, xD.    Post Note : Arty’s going to be angry at me for getting lazy      
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Game of the Day : Tetris. For all those who don’t know what this game is, here you go.  urlLink http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tetris    Rambles : No more using codenames, I can’t be bothered xD This means you, yes you, Fungus, won’t have that name anymore xD So, let’s go on with the day…   Today was great I guess, got the report cards back today… I got B’s in everything except Indo and Computer. That teacher is going to die, I bloody got an A in the last test, and I didn’t do half bad in anything before that. Half the time I listen to him, all he does is repeat himself, the other half of the time, he’s reading aloud what I’ve already read in the text. When you ask him a question, he uses the “Oh, I don’t know the answer to that, look in the text…” Fucking cunt bucket turd monkey wench.   Then went to Town Square to meet Murti, who came late! Late, late, late! But it gave me time to exercise, I haven’t done much of that for two weeks xD Weird thing is, as I was walking, this strange, queer looking couple (a man and a woman, just weird looking) said “Hi” to me. The first thing I thought of was “Shit! These are those people that like spicing up with their sex life with a third member, ah ah ah”. And I walked off as fast as I could.  Mur finally came, and after buying the tickets, we went on our merry way to Starbucks. There are way too many Starbucks’ in the world today. Regardless, after some palaver, went off to get my cappuccino blast (because that’s what Dammo’s do). Then the movie. Troy, ah Troy. The movie of some distaste in my mind lately has held true to my expectations, and that will be in my topic today. Some kids in the movie theatre kept chattering aimlessly. Now, if I was less lazy, I would have gone down there, searched for the kid, and socked him in the eye. No, probably the groin, because their voices sound so much funnier after a successful hit to the groin has been incurred.  After the movie was over, we hung around with some other people for ten minutes or so. I can’t stand smoke, I felt like socking two people after the movie was over. Maybe the movie made me more violent. Nah, movies don’t do that xD Made fun of Arty some, and jested at Jana, oh life is beautiful.   Then Mur and I had supper, more palaver (though the eating made this less so). Then, off to Christina’s house to pick up her shoes. Then, after dilly dallying there for a few minutes, we went back and left in my car so we could drop ‘Princess’ Mur off xP   And now I’m home, whoopity doo xD   And on another note, Kristine smsed, good stuff. HELLO IF YOU’RE READING.    Topic : Troy the Movie vs Troy of History   I’m lazy, so I’ll bullet point everything so that you people will be able to easily compare the two x)   First off, Troy of History. There is no conclusive evidence of Troy existing, so this is off stuff in the books  The Iliad  and  The Odyssey . Anyway   - Achilles’ mother knew he was going to die, so she hid him in the court of King Lycomedes. Where’s the puncher? He was dressed as a woman.   - Achilles’ is said to have died by Paris’ arrow (knife in some versions) during a truce between the Greeks and the Trojans.   - The Battle of Troy lasted ten years.   - Paris is said to have kidnapped Helen (though some say she came willingly, the little slut).   - The first time the Greeks set out for Troy, they couldn’t find it, so they returned home.   - Ajax falls to madness, kills some cattle, and then kills himself, after Hector falls.    - Patroclos was Achilles’ friend.   - Paris is received in the house of Menelaus alone, without his brother Hector, as part of a deal with the Goddess Aphrodite.   - Both Agamemnon and Menelaus did not die.       Now for Troy the Movie.   -	Achilles’ mother knew he was going to die but she encouraged him by saying that he would live forever in story, as opposed to only living for a while in the tales of his children’s children.  -	Achilles’ lives until the Trojan Horse trick is implemented, and then dies by Paris’ arrow. He gets hit by a number of arrows to the chest after the heel shot (oh, that scene reminded me of that scene in LOTR: Fellowship of the Ring)  -	The Battle of Troy lasts what seems to be in the movie a couple of days. Extremely disappointing, despite the fact that The Iliad starts in the tenth year of the battle.   -	Paris romanced Helen back to Troy. Naturally, because Elves are so damn pretty.   -	The Greeks seem to find Troy in one shot.   -	Ajax is killed by Hector.   -	Patroclos was Achilles’ cousin.   -	Paris and Hector come to the house of Menelaus on behalf of peace between Sparta and Troy.   -	Agamemnon and Menelaus die!    Yes, I took time to compare the two, just to prove I don’t criticise without reason.                 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Music Genre of the Day : Classical (I’ve been listening to Mozart for the better part of the day, now I’m listening to various classical artists)    Quote of the Day : You live and learn. At any rate, you live- Douglas Adams   Flash of the Day : http://www.albinoblacksheep.com/flash/french.php   Rambles : I’m amazed at the number of people who try and make arguments without backings. Had an argument with somebody yesterday about God, she was saying she hated him etc. When I asked why, she had no reason, but she did make a lot of comments on religion. I conclude from this she hated religion, and because God is the core focal point in religion, she hated him. Stupid…   You must not lose faith in humanity. Humanity is an ocean; if a few drops of the ocean are dirty, the ocean does not become dirty - Mahatma Gandhi  I often forget that.   Well, sometimes I wonder how virtuous I am. I don’t belong to any religion, so I take it upon myself to judge how loyal I am to God. Sometimes I feel I’m not very loyal, because I question what happens to me, and why it has to happen to me, despite knowing that you have to take the good and the bad. Sometimes I feel that I am, because I seem to be surrounded by people who pray to religion rather than pray to God, which is awfully fucked up. These people have attitudes that follow the “Oh, I go to church, so it’s alright for whatever the fuck I do the rest of the time”, and these are people that have criticised me for not choosing a religion. It pisses the righteous fuck out of me.   I can’t write much more, I’ve been sapped of energy since yesterday. Well, i'd like to state that CB idol was alright, I enjoyed seeing the teachers perform. Only in CB do economic teachers rap, and do computer technicians break dance xD On this note, I end with a congrats to Christina for winning xD      
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The word God comes from the Old English/German/Norse language family and is equivalent to the derivatives of the Latin word Deus. The meaning and etymology behind the Germanic/Indo-European word God as used in English and its cognates (such as Gott in modern German) have been hotly disputed, though most agree in a reconstructed Proto-Indo-European form ʒuðán, which means something like "possession" or "inspiration", and could be related to everything from the old Germanic divinity Wotan/Odin to the Greek word khute, meaning "libation".  Taken from http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/God   I find it strange that its roots included possession, because what word is often connected to that? Demons, ghosts, etc, is it not? Yes, I really have no time on my hands...   Despite my own believing in God, I hate religon, and this page has quite a bit of stuff on religon.   www.jesusneverexisted.com    And now for a stupid religon site xD www.xxxbible.com No, its not about porn, its about people who want to make up for their sins. You should see some of the stuff these people are into, it scares me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Enough said... Internet here chokes the donkey, literally...  I'm using my downstairs computer, which is as slow as a snail on ganja... The net, however, is faster... God knows why, for we use the same service provider...    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Philosopher of the Day : Socrates    Rambles : Grade twelve graduated today, and unlike the previous graduations, I actually feel a sense of loss this time around. I was close friends with three of them and I was on ok terms with the rest. That’s better than relations with my own class (all the people I bothered closely befriending have left xD).   All names in the following paragraph are aliases x)   Well, it was surprising to see Tino cry, she’s one of the people who I’ve always thought had a bunch of mental strength. Funny hugging her after as well, her grad hat kept falling off until she finally just clung onto it. Maurice was obviously her usual self, and I swear she could have killed me with her hugs. Then she bit my bloody shoulder! Damn her and her rabid mouth xD Fungus was her usual self, no hugging from her. God I’m going to miss that class… Tino leaves tomorrow at 6 am, so I’m not going to see her again until October. I think I’ll call her later, say good-bye one last time. GOOD LUCK TO ALL GRADE 12 STUDENTS!   I got a class blog started, though I have misgiving to its activity.    Topic : The Laziness of Man   .......................    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: Donnie Darko is a good movie, one of the better movies I’ve watched in a while, which leads to my topic. Where action movies with pretty boys have taken reign (LOTR, Troy), I’ve been having trouble finding thinking movies. I’ve had to watch a few old movies to satiate my craving for intellect. Ah well, what can you do, so many stupid people in the world, mostly Americans. I’m not being racist, it’s true. Americans make up a fair share of the audience and because directors want to appeal to the masses, you get a lot of action movies.     I won’t go into this further; I’m currently off in my own realm. I had to run away from reality because I just saw a chick cosplaying as Squall, and that has hurt my mentality.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, this is just something I wrote, and its still really sketchy.  _____________________________   Prologue    Crescendo,  Crescendo, My Innuendo  Excerpt from  The Book of Half Truths , Sage Halen.    If a half truth is a lie, it can be implied that  Truth = Lie x 2  Therefore, truth is two times worse than a half truth. It can be concluded that telling half truths is better than telling the full truth.   Excerpt from  A Mathematical Breakdown of Morality , Fay Reese.    Chapter One    The bells of Saint Samuel tolled, ringing over the city below them. The bells told all below that it was now twelve, and the sun told them that it was still daylight. Two rival factions stood facing each other, makeshift weapons in hand, such as oak-handled brooms and butcher knives.  On the east side of the city there stood the Prophets of Change, a party of religious zealots who felt that bloodshed was the only way to move the world on. They are famous for their acts of self-torture.  On the west side stands the Guild of Iron, a party of men and women who devote their lives to the creation of both life and merchant goods. Though they hate death more than Mega Theorin, they are all willing to kill if it means others won’t have to suffer such a fate.  The obvious differences between the two have led to their fight.  Dais, a member of neither, watches through a looking glass, his mortal frame located within an apartment building safe from any blood that will fall this day.  Behind him lies The Book of Half Truths, considered satanic by both the Guild of Iron and the Prophets of Change. Not many can fathom the meanings included within the book, and those who cannot simply put off the book as a juxtaposition of nonsense and garbage, and accuse those who have the knowledge to read it of being liars. This is because those who know the prophecies contained within the book refuse to tell the undeserving.  Dais the Huntsman, who understands Sage Halen’s forecasts, has the book open to the page where the event unfolding outside his window is located. The words read.    And maybe the folly of two,  Two who are many,  Will clash,  Like church bells,  And unleash a bloody hell,  Merry blue!  Chop chop, before all else!    	Often prophecies make little sense, and are written so that they can be applied only after an event has happened. Sage Halen’s divinations are likewise, but unlike other forecasts into the future, they are rarely applicable to anything but one certain event.  	Outside, the killing had begun, and it already looked to be certain death for the Prophets, for the Guild was putting their hammers to good use, bludgeoning countless men and women to death.  Dais couldn’t help but chuckle as a zealot of religion stabbed out a guildsman’s eye with a fork.  And as suddenly as it had begun, it ended. The city watch had come and put an end to it, apparently out of nowhere. Them in their blue uniforms, some now stained faint shades of dark red, had rounded up both parties and marched them off to the city jail, where, no doubt, the battle would continue unless they were put in separate cells.  “Just another day in the city Xesses” Dais said, apparently to himself, but you never knew.         
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bad Joke of the Day : How do Electricians greet each other?  By saying “Watts up?” (HORRID)    Flash File of the Day : http://www.albinoblacksheep.com/flash/avocado.php (Fishy lasers, err)   Saying of the Day : Quid Pro Quo- Meaning, in Latin, “Something for Something”. Used when people are exchanging information.    Rambles : Oh I just love Latin; all the words just sound so much devilishly superior to any other language. I love English, Latin, and German (I love their swear words). Otherwise I have odium for language; I’m ineffectual at recalling stuff. Same reason I hate math, too many fucking formulas.   Well, today was just dandy, it suited me fine because nothing happened. Right now I’m downloading shit from Fileplanet. Too bad I don’t have a membership, otherwise I wouldn’t have to wait minutes upon minutes to simply corroborate that I want it downloaded, and then wait hours upon hours as they actually DO download. Ah well, pays to be economical I guess.   I found beef jerky today, proper beef jerky at that. Good job Dammo, pat yourself on the back.   Finished reading  Hannibal , and I have to say it is millions of times better than the movie. Go read it; I swear you’ll find Dr. Lecter to be one of the most fascinating characters ever created.    Topic : How You Can Go Fuck Off  Step One- Turn off your computer Step Two- Get off your arse Step Three- Mosey outside and look at the sun (See? You’re not burning up)  Step Four- Depending on your age, you may wish to either A) Seek a Job B) Do fuck all with friends. If you don’t know what friends are, here, follow this link. http://www.infoplease.com/ipd/A0449793.html. Or for more realistic definitions look here, http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=friend&f=1.    There, you see? I’ve done a good deed in telling you people to go get your own life and step reading about the lives of others. Claps all around.     End Note : Oh don’t hate me, you backboneless, limp-wristed, sherry sipping, cosplaying (definition- http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=cosplay&f=1) whelp.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hotspot of the Day : http://www.eff.org/ Fight the power!   Quote of the Day : “We shall not flag or fail. We shall go on to the end. We shall fight in France. We shall fight on the seas and oceans. We shall fight with growing strength in the air. We shall defend our island, whatever the cost may be. We shall fight on the beaches. We shall fight on the landing grounds. We shall fight in the fields and in the streets. We shall fight in the hills. We shall never surrender.” – Winston Churchill    Rambles : Here I am on a Friday afternoon, doing fuck all. Friends are off watching  Troy , which I’ve heard doesn’t stay true to the story but is full of action and pretty boys ( LOTR: ROTK  anybody?). God, I’m sick of this lack of backbone, even in action movies. Problem is, whenever I openly criticise these movies, people flag me from all around telling me I have no taste. Bastard arse cunts.  Van Helsing  was a crap movie, I cannot say this enough. The women were alright, now, if they had cut out the bits where they turned ugly along with the rest of the movie, it would be an 8 out of 10.    Idea : This next bit will hold no interest for non-gamers so don’t bother reading. You see, I was thinking, why don’t they invent a proper real time strategy game? I’ve followed the genre since  Age of Empires  (I think  Civilisations  is more of a strategy game so it doesn’t fall under RTS). Anyways,  Empire Earth, Rise of Nations, and Empires: Dawn of the Modern World  were all fantastic games in the right direction, but I think that each is good in only a certain area while it lacks where the other are good. Follow me?   Now, before I continue, it is worth mentioning that  Rome: Total War  (http://www.actiontrip.com/previews/rometotalwar_p.phtml) looks fucking sweet, and may have just what I will soon talk of wanting (it sure looks like it), but I’m not sure yet so I’ll just state everything I’d like to see in RTS games of the future. Bullet point form for your viewing pleasure.   -	Real sieges on walls. I hate how in all these games you simply attack the wall until it is destroyed. Do you think that’s how people did it back then? Not very practical is it? In  Empire Earth , you could use a siege tower to climb over the walls, and that was a cool idea, but it is inaccurate. People used siege towers and ladders to climb onto the wall, not directly over it. Which brings me to my next bullet point.  -	Walls should feature troops on them. Walls weren’t just massive amounts of stone that awaited assault; they were often manned by archers and swordsmen, if the enemy got to close. I would really like to bring my longbow men up onto the walls and have them rain down arrows on my enemies. -	Realistic injuries. Ok, it may seem like I’m nitpicking here, but for God’s sakes, not all cavalry units die just because their horses die, and vice-versa. I’d like to see horses dying while their master’s live on as a weakened foot soldier. Likewise, I’d like to see people with arrows sticking out of their bodies. Of course, if somebody gets shot in the head, I expect them to die. Is it asking too much? Yes, I guess it is.  -	People remaining dead on the battlefield. I hate how they suddenly evaporate or turn into skeletons AND THEN evaporate. It would be cool to utilise these corpses by making them into catapult ammo or even sticking some of their bodies to the castle walls and gates to bring fear into the hearts of the men who dare assault your walls next time. Or you could toss them into a bonfire and send the smoke (and along with it, disease) to your enemy, provided the wind is right. -	Realistic wind would be funny and cool, I mean imagine having your enemy come at you with a tempest against them and when they try to shoot off their arrows, they come right back at them. Ok, so that’s kind of stupid and pointless but I amuse myself.  -	Torture chambers. If anybody has played  Dungeon Keeper , you know what I’m thinking of. Instead of killing all your enemies, it would be realistic for some to give up if their hero or leader has died. Then, instead of questing around the map for your enemy’s stronghold, you’d just send those surrendered units to the torture chambers where a torturer unit would ‘persuade’ the information out of them. Of course, you’d have to hear their screams to enjoy it, why not? But, to be realistic, they’d sometimes die and you would learn zilch.  -	One of the things I liked about  Empires: DotMW  is that you could actually set fire to your enemy’s buildings and raze them. This should honestly be implemented into more RTS games because I’m sick of slashing buildings into destruction. -	Real diplomacy. How the fuck do you communicate with people without people? Get what I mean? We should have democrats and such to converse with other players, who would have immunities and such which, when violated, would bring about war and other such things. In  Rise of Nations , trading is done by caravans, which I think is good. It makes sense.  -	Also in  RoN , roads become established around the city, and to trade neighbours. Its realistic. More games should have this.   Ah, I’m out of ideas. Another look at  Rome: Total War  shows me that it looks like the idea of walls I presented is a reality, joy is me. Maybe, one of these days, I’ll review a game rather than ramble on about a fantasy game. Probably not.             
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Dumbass of the Day : Sean Paul    Song of the Day : Venus Reprise- Eric Johnson    Rambles : Today has been nothing much, so I won’t go into much detail on that. Reason for my dumbass of the day is because I had to endure the torture of that song, argh, devil knows its name. It goes something like… Wait, I just remembered why I hate it so much… Its  A)	Cyclic B)	Impossible for me to understand So sorry if I can’t provide you with the lyrics. I would listen to the  Macarena  song for eternity if it meant not listening to that song for a micro-second. Savvy.    Topic :  Beyond Good & Evil   No, not the book by Nietzsche. No, not the game. This subject is about why movies picture the world in black and white. Now, I’m only going to scrutinise one movie, but if it is so demanded, I’ll analyse more to demonstrate what I mean.   Let’s take  Hannibal , the movie. Because I’m reading the book, I have a lot to evaluate the movie with. NOW, for anybody who hasn’t watched  Silence of the Lambs ,  Hannibal , or  Red Dragon , let me fill you in.   There’s a bloke in these movies named Hannibal Lecter (doesn’t the name just dispatch chills through yer bones?), who is, in simpleton terms, a psychopath. This guy is probably one of the most chilling villains I’ve ever seen, simply because he’s intelligent, and can be compassionate (not a great deal but still). So why is he a psycho? Most people don’t rip your liver out for a meal. Now that we’ve established him to be an academic cannibal, let’s get into the film.  Throughout the entirety of this movie, Lecter is painted as a disturbed madcap incapable of feelings and such, and makes him a character you have no sentiments for. THE STEREOTYPICAL VILLAIN. You’re probably asking me “how else should we feel about a human eater?” Well, in no point of the movie do you discern Lecter’s background, (SPOILER ALERT), where his sister gets eaten up while he’s a child. Yes, there’s a reason he’s the way he is, it’s his past. You discover this in the book, not the movie.   Why?   BECAUSE THE DIRECTOR WANTS YOU TO FEEL NOTHING BUT SPITE FOR HANNIBAL. Why though? Why not create a little sympathy? Because the director feels that he should never make the viewer question whether the villain is really so bad after all.   Why not? Because otherwise we wouldn’t want the typical action movie so badly as we do now.   It’s a sad truth that the majority of people fail to think for themselves and believe that the world is divided in two halves, good and evil. In World War 2, it can be said the Allies were the good guys, and the Nazis were the bad guys. Truth be told, it was the case. Now, in Iraq, the American government pushes that they are the ones doing good, and the Iraqis are the evil bastards who deserve to be killed. Is it so? No. Lets not get into politics though, that will be for some other time.   Point is that the public demands this sort of movie because they can’t think that maybe the bad guys are actually good at heart and such. It makes us easier to see them die. We watch war movies because we’re convinced that the people we follow are necessarily in the right. In  Star Wars , we root for the Jedi, and boo the Sith simply because the Jedi are said to be good. We accept that as a fact. Which is why I applaud Lucas for  Episode 2 , which brings about the question of bad in good. I hated the movie, but I applaud the thought.   Ah, I’m beating around the bush. I’ve already made my point.   Arguments? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Poem of the Day :  Fire and Ice  by Robert Frost  Some say the world will end in fire;  Some say in ice.  From what I've tasted of desire  I hold with those who favor fire.  But if it had to perish twice,  I think I know enough of hate  To know that for destruction ice  Is also great  And would suffice.     Food of the Day : Cheese Cubes    Fact of the Day : Häagen-Dazs is not German, it’s American. The founder of the company, Reuben Mattus, started it all in, where else but New York, America. Reason I mention this is because it’s a common held belief that because of its name, it’s German, and even some of the people who work for it think the same. You learn something new every day don’t you?     Rambles : Today was average. I awoke at eleven, and went to a party at around 3:30-4:00 pm. A pool party. Which means? Ding ding ding! BIKINIS… Hahaha, of course, that’s the only reason I went. No, not really, it’s because I felt bad for not going to the after party on prom night. Well, it meant I got to hang around with people, so that’s good. Now, an excerpt from a conversation with my friend Christina, though it’s not word-for-word.    Her : When you’re a kid your idea of flirting is picking and playfully hitting a girl.   Me : *lightly punches her leg and giggles* That’s not how we flirt anymore?   Yes, call me juvenile. I like to enjoy small jokes like that. I wish flirting was so easy now, i'd be the king. Not that i'm not right now... Err, piss off... 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Link of Interest : http://www.somethingawful.com/articles.php?a=2074   Quote of the Day : “Dr. Lecter has no interest in hypothesis. He doesn’t believe in syllogism, or synthesis, or any absolute.”  “What does he believe in?”  “Chaos. And you don’t even have to believe in it. It’s self-evident.”  From the book  Hannibal , by Thomas Harris    Question of the Day : Why is it that if you get a woman you’re said to have “nailed” her? A nail is a noun, and is the object which you are trying to bring into the wall. When something is nailed, it means to be already inside the wall. Would it not be better to consider the term “hammered”? I think everybody should start going, “Ah, I hammered this chick last night, smooth deal that.”   Rambles : Today sucked more balls than a hooker addicted to crack. The art exhibition went horridly, for it was a seemingly never-ending flood of kids, then a short calm, and then another flood came. Then there was nothing but boredom. I did however get further in my reading of Hannibal, so that’s alright. Then when we were packing up, I helped carry out the plants, and ended up receiving friction marks on both my arms. Doesn’t hurt, but it really takes the piss all the same. Then I helped fixed a red-eye problem in a picture for a friend, and then I went home. And now I’m here. Whoopity-doo for you, yes?    Topic : Feminist Nazis   Wonderful image that creates in your head eh? A woman with hairy armpits wearing a sleeveless shirt extending her arm and shouting “Heil Female!”. Don’t get me wrong, feminists kind of have a good reason to hate us men, I mean we DID oppress them for centuries upon centuries. But when a woman dares demand they receive equal rights and yet play the “I’m a woman” card when they like, I say they can go fuck themselves. THEY CAN GO FUCK THEMSELVES.  Let’s picture this. A woman demands a job, she’s put with the rest of them in the line, and if she’s skilled enough, she gets in. If she’s not? Oh, its obviously female oppression in the work place. SUED. What a load of bullshit. The same goes for racial equality. People should not get jobs for their skin colour, but for their ability in the workplace. Would you rather have a woman doctor who knows fuck all, or a male doctor who knows what he’s doing? The answer is obvious, unless you’re a blind ignoramus. In the case of the latter, you should go fuck yourself and leave this blog RIGHT now.    End Note : Maybe I’ll add more to this argument later. Maybe not. Probably not. Ah, I won’t. I’m a lazy retard xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Rambles : I would like to start this off with a thought I had earlier on…  Having sex to an altered version of Queen’s Bohemian Rhapsody.  Think about it…   Scene : Man and woman in dungeon, leather and chains   Woman : Let me go! *fake screaming*  Man : Bismillah! *pelvic thrust* We will not let you go!  Or   Scene : Man and woman in bedroom, wearing formal garments, perhaps after a wedding and the woman is having second thoughts NOW.   Man : So you think you can love me and leave me to die. *numerous foreplay acts can be inserted here, nipple licking/sucking can be one of them*  Woman : Oh, baby, can't do this to me, baby. Just gotta get out, just gotta get out right here *rips clothes off, and if you chose to nipple lick rather than caress, she probably already has her top off*  Sorry, these thoughts cross my mind every so often xD I just like to prove porn can have stories if you try, and that I would obviously change the porn industry if I decided to join it xD  Coincidentally to these thoughts, I was just watching  Coupling , and Steve mentioned the four pillars of heterosexual manhood. " Naked women, lesbians, stockings, and Sean Connery best as James Bond, because that is what being a boy is" . I have yet to meet a guy who isn’t into any of these things xD  In my case, I like all four xD  A little too much information, but by now you should expect things like this to creep in every so often.  An interesting thing came up when I was searching  Coupling  up on Wikipedia. My first result?      Coupling    From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia.    Generally, coupling means a    mechanical       connection    between two things. For example    railways       carriages    and    wagons    are coupled together. Other examples of link  coupling  include    clamps   ,    nipples   , and    vices   . Coupling has other specific meanings in physics, electronics, programming and entertainment.      Nipples xD  Now, onto more serious issues…    SUBJECT : MORALITY  There are three kinds of people I can’t stand.   MIMES CLOWNS FANATICS   Now the first two are bastards, but only the last is a cunt bastard.  I’m not talking just about religious fanatics (though they will be what I really hit hard on in a while), but also anti-religion people and anybody who fanatically follows anything.  Now, onto bashing fanatic religious people. I’m sorry I have to do this, but if I keep this bottled up I’m just going to burst.  I fucking hate anybody who can preach one religion so vividly and yet be completely ignorant of other people’s religions to the point where they basically take the piss out of one belief that they find “stupid”.  I fucking hate anybody who can preach religion and yet believe people deserve to suffer because of their people’s mistakes in history.  I fucking hate people who cannot, or will not, question things that are posed to them, and prefer to follow the “I don’t think for myself because that would be too hard, so instead I’ll read this book and just do as it says, oh sheep that I am”.  Look, I respect every religion and every form of practice, even the really odd ones such as those of the College of Thelema, or Rastafarianism. How a person finds belief is up to them, but where it goes to the point where you would be, say, racist to another because a scripture says so, or kill somebody because it says that is the only way to get to Heaven, then it becomes folly.  Books like the Bible, the Koran, etc, they are all guidelines. I honestly don’t believe they are the word of God transcribed, but more the ideas with which one can try and find peace with one self. Morale guidelines. The basic concepts of helping your neighbour (in the sense of helping those around you), not killing other blokes or dames, etc, those are all now embedded within our morality.  Most people KNOW it’s wrong to do these things because of centuries of conditioning to these ideas. Not because we know these things straight off the block, but because these ideas are carried on to us through our parents, our environment, and religion.  Unfortunately, you can also be conditioned badly. You can be taught to accept shit without question, to hate others simply because their skin is a different colour. It’s an unfortunate truth, because with knowledge (and here I rip off Spider-man) “comes great responsibility”.  Humans are gifted in the fact we can usually learn things, and then forget them in favour of higher greatness. I myself have gone through this phase time and time again. I’ve burnt my hand and learned not to touch fire. I’ve learnt, at one time, not to trust people because they can stab you in the back. But in the same way, I learned to trust this isn’t always the case, because of the friendship I’ve managed to find in a unique few.  I used to maintain that religion was one major fallacy, and now I’ve given that up because I know that religion isn’t something that’s physical but more of something we find in ourselves. To error religion for the Church, for the Temples, for the Mosques, would be like mistaking a wolf and a dog. This is to say that on the surface, they share common characteristics.  You can say that religion is the Church because that’s who maintains the faith. But beneath the shell we find that the religious community is made up of people, and it is the faith within these people that makes the difference in that religion.  But here you question that if a person belongs to a religion, they obviously have faith. No, not always. I’ve met my share of people who belong to a religion not of their choosing, but rather of their parent’s choosing.  In this respect, I am lucky. I was brought up Christian, reading the Bible a shitload, then my parents got divorced, and I lost my faith in God, abandoning my religion for all it’s worth. Then I found God when I was in thought about everything that had happened to me, and I was able to build some basic morals off of what had come to pass. Then I read up on Buddhism, and became deeply interested in all the concepts within it.  But I question a lot of things within Buddhism; otherwise I would just be accepting everything like a sheep. To adhere to everything would mean I have to be unconcerned with making money, but I can’t be. I have to try and work hard to make enough money to help my family through school and whatever other travesties that may befall us. I can’t devote everything in my life to help power a cause higher than myself, but I can try.  And this is what I mean by guidelines. I twist and bend them just enough to fit my own reality, not the reality of others who might have been able to do these things. I’m also lucky in the respect that my father is the same as me, and has always encouraged me to always think for myself. He himself is Buddhist, but he has his own guidelines which he follows.  I still pray to God, even though I should pray to Buddha. Why? Because I believe they’re the same. Some figure which exists on a higher plane of knowledge than I do.  The question of how in the Bible God didn’t want us to become more intelligent from eating the apple came up and  somebody  stated that it was because we shouldn’t be as wise as Him. I thought this really stupid. Sorry, I couldn’t help it. The idea of a greater-than-life being, somebody devoid of such feelings as envy or jealousy, thinking we shouldn’t strive to know more is just horridly ridiculous in my mind. For me, my life has been a constant path of knowledge, and I know if people all had the information on what happens in war or murder, it wouldn’t happen. Knowledge has always brought power.  In the Cold War, the world was on the brink of destruction because two nations wanted all. It was knowledge of the extinction of life that let us through that ordeal. If the Premier of the Soviet Union, or the President of the USA, hadn’t known what would happen if they both released the quantity of nukes they had, the world would be rubble.  The issue of reincarnation came up the other day in Asian Studies, and  somebody  (the same  somebody  as above) said something I sincerely felt like killing them for. They said reincarnation was a stupid idea. I felt like strangling that person. To me, Heaven and Hell has always been a silly way of trying to reach a better state. The whole idea is to work to live in a place where all is good.  Reincarnation as preached in Buddhism is so that as we work ourselves to be better, we may eventually attain Enlightenment, and with this we can help others. It isn’t as selfish as the quest for the individual but is for the betterment of everybody. Sure it seems silly, and you may never think it will happen, but doing things because you want to help others seems like a better way to approach a peaceful state of mind than for your own privilege.  I really better stop xD If anybody has any sensible opinions which don’t involve bias as to how I constantly seem to take the piss out of the Church or religion in general, please comment. The only reason I use the Church is because it’s the only one I have any familiarity with, and I don’t have the right to condemn things I don’t know enough about. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One thing to say, and one thing only...   Man on Fire is the best movie i've seen in a LONG time. By the title I figured it would be shit, typical action flick, but God it was so much better xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Rambles : Today started off really shitty, I was depressed before I even got to school, and depression helps increase the power of The Sickness. Well, I felt so shitty when I was in computer class that I took it out on Angel with a stupid question xD Then in my own presentation I kind of just let go, since I knew without my stunning voice at optimum capacity I would need to… improvise. Too bad I didn’t do the bows and the “haligato” beginning.   Anyway, the day got better as it went by. Managed to take a good picture of Yoshi (never thought I’d use good and Yoshi in the same sentence). After a little editing it looked even better. I also caught some nice ones of the people in P.E.    MY FUCKING FOOT FEELS NUMB . And I should go to sleep soon.   So piss off. But before you do that… Click Here- http://www.deviantart.com/view/9312410/  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    b&w of mikey
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
                  urlLink  Am I cool or uncool? [CLICK]        You are  urlLink Trendy ...       You're a trendsetter.. well more of a trend follower. You have a few 'cool' friends who don't mind you hanging around for a laugh. It won't be long before you're climbing the ladder to cool status. Keep up the good work!!       urlLink  Cool quizzes at Go-Quiz.com                     D     Dignified       A     Amazing       M     Mystical       I     Influential       E     Earthy       N     New        Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
           Dammo is poisonous! Induce vomitting if ingested.      N   POISON       Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com     Rambles: Out of interest, there was a point in time where if I sweated from my face, my eyes would sting horridly. Too much acid in my body or something 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
           How to make a Damien         Ingredients:   1 part intelligence  3 parts humour  5 parts beauty        Method:  Stir together in a glass tumbler with a salted rim. Top it off with a sprinkle of emotion and enjoy!         Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com      Rambles : Well I'm sick, so sue me xD I'm allowed to take stupid quizzes if it's just to distract me from looking at porn. Damn... Must... fight... the... urge...  
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is a rather nice picture of Mike and Monita, I finally got around to editing it and colouring it in Tritone xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Rambles:  Mortality. We all become aware of it, sooner or later. In the past two years I’ve become aware of it more than ever. Why am I suddenly mentioning it? Well, I was looking through pictures of my two bros, and realised I don’t have any pictures of either my mother or father.     I worry a lot about my family, even my sister. People seem to think I hate her outright, for no reason at all. No, I’m just angry at her constantly xD I mean whenever I tell her to do something for her own good she tells me to shut up, and nobody seems to understand this. She refuses to listen to anybody in my family, and therefore I get irate. What’s my point? I don’t rightly know.     Ah well, I can’t seem to make up my mind on what I should further write. So I’ll just post random pieces of writing I’ve developed in 2004, none of which are finished.    ___________________       Story One: The Messiah   (Two days old and it looks like I may continue it!)      The sun glimmered through a crack in the cobalt curtains, but this alone was not enough to awake the person under the blanket.     The mini-compo sounded off, playing what seemed to be a darker, more sinister version of lounge music.     A rustle in the bed.     Awaken, and come hither, through the lands of the wakeful.     A yawn.    A grumble.     The door to the bedroom opened, screeching ever so silently as it did.     “Wake up!”     Then the door was closed, and the air of finality on those words was absolute.     The being inside the bed grasped outwards for the remote control and, out of habit, immediately found the power button.     In a laid-back and graceful motion, the blanket was lifted, and soon the teen stood on the ground, feeling groggy.     Slowly, he made his way towards the redwood door and with a twist of the doorknob and a push with his forehead, the door opened up into the hallway.           ___________________     Story Two: The Sins of Heaven   (An Extract from a Role-play battle)      Time: Indefinite, Place: Cloud of Warriors, Heaven      “Sir Adrian Tafford, your presence is requested on Cloud Nine. I repeat, your pre-”     The knight held his gladius right at the obese messenger-angel’s belly. “QUIET! My head hurts, I drunk  a lot  last night.”     “Yes Sir” A globule of sweat descended the angel’s round face. “May I go now, Sir?”     Decanus waved his left hand dismissively and waited until the angel had gone to return his sword into its sheath.  What a grand start to a day . You could just feel the sarcasm ooze off him.         Time: Indefinite, Place: Cloud Nine- The Cloud of Pompous Angels Galore, Heaven      “Tafford, stand to attention!”     Adrian was currently rubbing his temples with his fists, looking at the fluffy ground, trying to purge himself of the pain he was feeling. Owing to this, he didn’t hear the words the first time spoken.     “Tafford, I said stand to attention, whelp!”     A lucid foot came sliding into the knight’s stomach, and resulted in a lot of vomit on Adrian’s part.     “You could have asked nicely…” Decanus put in after he was sure he wasn’t going to misplace anymore of last night’s supper of beer and eggs.     “I’ve heard a lot about you Sir Adrian, and despite you looking like a overall wreck job, I hear you’d be the perfect man for the job I’m about to put forward.”     Adrian mumbled something around the grounds of “Pompous windbag.”     The speaker apparently didn’t hear, or chose not to. “Have you ever heard of Heretic?”     Despite recovering from a hangover, the name rung a bell almost instantly. “The sword?”     “Yes, the sword. Well, it used to be under the direction of Sarakon, as you may well know, but it appeared he had a change of heart and decided it would be perfectly safe floating in the infinite plane of the Nexus. Silly bastard.”     This time Decanus’ words were crystal clear. “Don’t scandalise the name of any warrior, no matter what side he plays for, you portly bastard.” Sarakon, despite his misdoings, was a stalwart warrior who Adrian had paid some attention to during his ‘lunch breaks’.        The speaker laughed. “You’re well aware that I could send you to hell for that remark, right?”     Adrian let out a vocal roar to clear his head. When he finally looked up, he saw who had been speaking. ‘Twas one of the Cherubim. They had some sort of vendetta against him; God knew why, wherever HE was. “Yes, you probably could. But Hell isn’t as bad a place as most people make it out to be. At least you wouldn’t be there…”     The Cherub Adrian spoke to became flustered. Such creatures were often talked to with reverence and a certain kind of fear. Adrian’s voice and soul carried neither. “Well, moving right along,” The Cherubim twiddled his chubby fingers, “Heretic was taken from its resting ground by a demon named Morkrall Dalarion.”     Decanus grumbled. “And let me guess, I have to get back Heretic, and either destroy it or reseal it properly, right? Will I be getting some mystical scroll to help me in this?”     “No…” A pause. “You will give it to me…”     A spark of anger flared through Adrian’s eyes, and it now chorused through his voice. “What, do you hope to control that damned sword’s power? Do you think you could charge the Seraphim with such a weapon?”            “Why else haven’t they destroyed it? That thing is beyond good or evil, it is in a rank of its own… Now, I am not asking you, I am telling you, claim it for me…”    Adrian knew better than to argue, but even in that moment, he knew that he would not give the sword over to this ostentatious fuck. Tafford mock-bowed, and then exited, stage fourth dimension.        Time: Five Hours After Sunrise, Place: Naturo Village, Paradise      Sir Decanus had, after consulting the pub master in Heaven, discovered the locality to where Morkrall was to be hiding. Now he was here, Adrian figured it to be the perfect place for any madman to be hiding with such a weapon as Heretic.     Yet, some things nagged at Adrian’s mind, like a whore demanding more money. First of all, how fucking powerful would one have to be to rupture a seal established by Sarakon, who was acclaimed to be both a fair fighter and a magician much mightier than Tafford himself? Secondly, how could anybody have carried Heretic for an elongated period of time without news of mysteriously killings? Both irritated Adrian like an itch that would not go away, and both indicated this Morkrall character would be a lot stronger than a few of the folks Decanus had met on the plain, and more recently plane, of battle.     But first things first. Adrian had to scrutinise out the lay of the land. This place was altogether new to him, and did not seem to cite the same laws as Earth. The people, the Paradisians they liked to call themselves, were all a great deal merrier than Adrian would have liked. You could not pass a single one without being greeted with a “Howdy How” and a doggedness of shaking hands. All of them were possessive of blonde hair, and yet relatively dark skin. Their eyes were truly interesting, sparkling of multiple colours at once, like a rainbow caught in a twirling vortex. Otherwise, they were what could pass for human.     The place itself, this Naturo Village as it was called in their dialect, was an attention-grabbing feat of architecture. Not a single building was attached to the ground in any direct physical means of contact. The village was, in fact, suspended from the bulky branches of what looked to be enormous oaks. Copious plateaus made up the village, seemingly divided by age, with the oldest living at the bottom, and the youngest living at the top. Decanus figured this to be because air got thinner the higher up you got.     Despite the population of the village only reaching two hundred, three hundred and fifty if you included women and children, there were hundreds of bridges and ropes, all artificial and yet wrapped in wildlife as if they were parts of it themselves. It seemed there were farming communities up here as well, actually harvesting sap from the bodies of these great trees, and, as Adrian had first found out an hour back, it was an astonishingly good hangover cure.     Finally, there were the physics of this place. It seemed that the gravity here was lighter, which may have attributed to the enormous growth of the trees themselves. He had seen men jump from building to building, despite being at least ten metres apart, and it was after seeing this that he had asked his guide why they had bridges at all. The guide’s reply? “Its for you smelly tourists…” The man had grinned, and Adrian could not help but grin along.     And now this had all been taken into consideration, Tafford could properly conduct his investigation. He did not expect to find anything here, for it was after all the first of fifty villages here on Paradise that Morkrall could be hiding on, and there was thus a 1/50 chance that he would be in this one.     Personally, Sir Adrian had his reservations about the whole mess. He couldn’t tell a Seraph, for the Cherub would denounce these accusations, and as it stood, Adrian was off a lower class, and wouldn’t be believed. He couldn’t tell Michael or any of the other archangels, because if they got involved, they could be cast into the abyss themselves. And if Tafford did actually find the sword, what then?     The sword would almost instantaneously take control of him, and Decanus would try to please its whims by bloodshed. And if by some chance he resisted its powers, what then? He couldn’t return it, for that would result in certain chaos in the realms of Heaven. He could try and destroy it, but he knew nobody who had heard of a way. And the final act of resealing it seemed idiotic. Some fool would only unseal it and this whole process would repeat again, but the next man charged with finding it might be one who didn’t have as clear a head as Decanus.     A voice rung in his head, the voice of Sir Harold Orpheus. “First things first, you can worry about the number two later!”     He nodded to himself, and Adrian began walking across one of the bridges which led to the top level, and from there he would work downwards. A sound plan indeed.                    ___________________     Story Three: The Revolution of England   (Part of a role-play, that’s why some of the transition are dodgy at best. The dialogue of Liam is written by Simon, friend of mine)      “Hands against the wall sonny boy, that’s right, spread your legs…”     Adrian faked a grin, but hoped it looked natural enough. “Look officer, what have I done?”     “Nothing…” The old bloke raised a whitened eyebrow. “Yet…”     In a minute, the examination was over, and the policeman told Adrian he was “free to go”.     “Thank you officer, you keep holding up that law eh?” Adrian let out a chuckle, waved at the frowning old man and swivelled around on a single foot.     He started at a fair pace back towards his house, relieved of the fact he hadn’t been carrying his pop’s classic Derringer handgun. This, Adrian hid in the old family Bible, via method of cutting and removing a square block in the middle of all the pages. Nobody touched the Bible anymore; it held no solution to the jobs being lost to the aliens who were content on being paid less for more hours.    Adrian had heard the other day some foreign sympathisers saying that the foreigners deserved the jobs if they would work for less. Adrian had almost said out loud that they only worked for less because they didn’t know any better. But a cop had passed by, and Adrian had kept his mouth closed.     Making such remarks now was punishable by a full investigation of your house, and questioning of all your mates of your behaviour as of late. It was as if anybody who hated the situation was a member of the People’s Army.     Fucking loony.    Adrian smiled, he was home. He had made it through yet another day of craziness. He knocked on the door, and it opened minutes later, his mother was on the other side.    “Adrian! Where have you been? You know with all these people thinking they’re guerrillas running around you should be in by six. I mean honestly, just an hour earlier a hooligan was running around in his underwear pulled over his head claiming he was the messiah and that he would free England of all these dirty job-stealers.”     Adrian laughed. It was probably Kingsley on another of his beer runs. “No need to worry mom, I was just seeing some friends, you know. Ah well, I’m tired, I better sleep eh? Night night.”     His mother gave him that eyebrow that said “You are such a weird kid.” But her mouth said “Fine, sleep tight.”     One step, two step, three step, four step, five step, six step, seven step, eight. Adrian’s turf now, he grabbed the brass knob and turned it. A creaking as the handle turned, from lack of oiling, and soon the mildewed pong of his room engulfed his senses. He noted the time on his digital alarm clock; from years ago when his family had still been doing great, and it told him it was barely ten minutes past seven.      Ha, she worries too much, that old girl does      Alone in the corner of his room, by the dusty window, atop a small table, was a radio that looked as if it had been built during World War 2. It worked well enough though, and this Adrian now turned on. He moved the dial slightly, pointing it to 87.2 FM, known as Revolutionary Radio to some.     It was an entirely legal station, but what the government didn’t know was that the second word in each song could be pieced together to form a message alerting rebels of news the government would no longer release on TV or radio for that matter.     Today, after almost two hours of listening, Adrian found the news to be quite interesting. It was something about a raid on the docks by a group of beggars. Though the attempt failed, it was more than the IEA had ever done. Adrian wished for something interesting to happen for once.     He remembered it had only been two weeks since he and Liam had first joined, and they had both expected it to be a far more adventurous lifestyle. So far the most audacious thing they’d been forced to do is pick up canned tuna rations in what was supposedly a black market, but from the woman in charge, it seemed to be just your everyday grocery store.     Adrian took a seat on his old hickory chair, and tapped his fingers restlessly against the redwood desk.          A rustle outside the window. Adrian turned his head. Slowly he edged his fingers across the desk, towards the window frame, and he pushed upwards carefully. When the window was a quarter way open, Adrian let out a careless whisper. “Who’s out there?”     No reply besides the faint puff of air that breezed by. Then another rustle, and suddenly something shot out of the bush. For a split second, Adrian thought it to be the hand of a SAS operator, but this was stupid. He hadn’t done anything, technically. Ah, a chipmunk.      You’re getting tense, Adrian mi boy. You need a beer like you need a woman      Adrian grinned and spoke out to himself; hardly realising he was doing it. “But now even sex is considered tyranny, since you never know  what  you’ll murmur into your lover’s ear…”     No copper was wandering the streets tonight, and even if there had been they wouldn’t have heard it. The window led out to the backyard, little as it may be, was not near much except the wildlife. So far as Adrian had heard, the birds had yet to be trained to eavesdrop on suspects.      I think you should go get that beer     Adrian nodded to himself, and opened the window wider, keeping it ajar by using a wooden ruler as a prop. He went back to his drawer, opened it, and took out his wool coat. At 5’7, Adrian didn’t exactly stand out in the crowd, and the coat helped his indistinctness. Along with this, he removed a panama hat, black in colour with a white headband. What could he say? He loved his hat. After grabbing a red crayon from the desk, which he stuffed into one of many pockets in his coat, he lobbed himself carefully out the window, onto the somewhat soggy grass below.      Time to move      Adrian moved quietly towards the meeting place.     He had left at around 9:27, and it usually took ten minutes to get there, give or take. No patrols tonight, they were probably busy busting some footie hooligans. Apparently England had lost to France,  again . The England team were poorly equipped these days, and horridly trained. It was a pain in the heart for anybody who had supported England even two years ago, before it had gotten terribly serious.       The meeting place was a dilapidated Tudor-styled house; it had been many years since this place had been occupied (for more than a few hours that is). Adrian brought out the crayon and made a stick figure drawing by the glass to indicate he was here, to anybody who knew the code; police would hopefully look over it as a child’s drawing.     There had been only ever been three people who knew it, and one of those was currently being held in jail for speaking out towards the PM. The other was Liam. Where the fuck that guy was, Adrian didn’t know. Did it matter? Yes. For all he knew, Liam was occupying a cell right by Kira.     After warily entering the house by the door, for it was hardly ever locked, he went over to the cooler, and opened it. There was some inexplicable link between the people who used this house as a meeting point. Though you hardly ever knew the other visitors, there was a rule at re-stocking the cooler when it was vacant, out of courtesy.     The choice of beer was usually alright as well, but it looked like tonight Adrian would have to be content with Foster beer, an Australian brand much cheaper than either Amstel or Carlsberg. He took it down like a man, and reclined on a single sofa chair. It was comfortable here, if you didn’t mind the occasional rat and such. Thoughts came to you in a flood when you were here.     Who was it he had mentioned earlier? Kira right? Hah, her. She had been younger than them both, but mad. Pure, utterly mad. The kind of gal guys fell for, but was scared of at the same time. She had been arrested at least a year ago for denouncing the PM as the horrid result of a rape victim. Adrian had fancied her, in a way, but she had always been more like one of the guys than gals. In fact, Adrian swore she could have beaten up half the guys he knew. Wherever she was now, she was sure to be yelling her head off      Adrian took another beer from the cooler, and popped it open. He let it get some air before drinking from it. Usually he wouldn’t loiter here in the dark for very long, but tonight he felt something was going to alter his life, and it was for this he sat perfectly still, listening to the sound of his heartbeat. He hoped he would also be able to hear the heartbeats of the police who could, at any second, bust in on his alcohol-induced meditation.     And he thought he heard a sound.       “Fucking hell! So dark in here I didn’t even see you man, Jesus, gave me a bloody heart attack.”     Adrian simply grinned, bringing his free left hand around and onto his head, and scratched his scalp apologetically. He waited before saying anything further, he knew better around Liam. Whenever the guy got jolted, he needed his beer in his hand before relaxing.     “So, anything new?” Liam’s usual matter-at-hand tone.     Adrian downed the rest of the beer, letting it stay in his mouth for a while before sinking it down his throat. Much better.  Onto business .      “I suppose you’ve heard of the thing down at the docks?”     "No, what about the docks? More immigrants coming in the country on the ships?"  Said Liam between gulps of Fosters.     Adrian grinned. “Nah, not this time, apparently some beggars got busted down there for a raid. It’s amazing how they seem more intent on helping themselves than this bloody IEA. I thought we were getting ourselves into action!”    Liam scowled and shook his head in disgust. "What do you expect mate, fucking majority of people these days are out for themselves, and can you blame them? Most of us that do our bit for the country end up dead pretty quickly, just a shame that more people are interested in looking after themselves than sorting this country out."    Adrian nodded while listening, his body in a slightly hunched position in the chair. A spark flared through his eyes, the dangerous kind that meant he was thinking something big. “Why don’t’ we take initiative eh? Why not? We’re supposedly fucking equals in the IEA, I’m sure they wouldn’t mind if we somehow managed to somehow humiliate parliament.”      Liam smiled voluntarily as he cracked open a second beer, which fizzed up uncontrollably and oozed out of the top, forcing Liam to put his mouth to the foaming liquid and do his best to drink it up rapidly to avoid excess spillage. "Well," he coughed "It's all well and good, us taking the initiative and you're right, I think we should. But we've got a long way to go before we can attack parliament directly if it's just the two of us working for the cause. We need to start off small, rally people to the cause and then do the bigger things. Going for the jugular right now is a sure way of ending up like the Butsfarm lot"    Adrian simmered down. Personally, he tried to avoid mentioning the Butsfarm incident, simply because Liam had history there. “Yes, I suppose you’re right. But you know how it is now, you can’t get into a group bigger than five without looking suspicious, and you can’t exactly trust anybody anymore. You remember what happened to Bobby? Got turned in by his own lifelong buddy he did. Sad shit right there.” Adrian took a breath of air, not exactly fresh but whatever. “How are we supposed to rally causes when this is the state of situation?”    Liam took a long sip of his beer while contemplating how he'd answer. Truth is he had no answers, the situation was pretty bleak for the Independent English army, but they had to at least try something. "There's not much we can do, aside from lead by example. If we can start making successful raids, getting our group known on the streets, sooner or later people will join. We may not be able to trust them all but that's just a chance we've got to take man, sometimes to win a war you need to take risks"    Nodding, Adrian brought both his hands through his hair, sifting out any dust that might have been in it. “I can’t think of a better idea.” He turned, faced Liam, and grinned. “You still keep that  diary  of yours? Maybe that holds the key to this whole mess.” He chuckled. You never knew, maybe Liam recorded stuff of interest in it, such as envoy visits and the likes. Maybe not.    "Yeah I still keep the diary, there's not much of interest though, just notes about my day, the situation. The usual stuff really, there was a recent article in the Informer that I glued in there though, something about a French Police official visiting the Met to discuss some of this policy unification euro bollocks". Liam yawned, cupping his hand to his mouth. "Not sure what we can do about that though."    Adrian tapped at his temple with his fore and middle fingers, and after a few seconds, stilled them as they touched his skin. “Hm, you know how, even now we’re all still pretty much united against the French right? Well, he’s obviously not going to be well guarded right; I mean French officers aren’t exactly allowed to be roaming our streets eh? And English guards, almost certainly not. If we somehow managed to get him in our grasps for a few minutes, we could probably tie some fucking large wooden sign around his neck telling the EU to go suck balls or something.” Adrian lacked the democratic tongue. “Plus, France would be pretty buggered about how England just let a representative of their frog-eating race get captured by  hooligans . No doubt parliament will launch a front against these  hooligans  to protect their image, but its doubtful they’ll do much more than just accuse the People’s Army of England for it. The people though, they might just try dig deeper and find us responsible. I know it’s faulty, but I’m hoping you could fill in whatever I may have missed.”       Liam scratched his chin. "You're right that no true Englishman likes the French, but don't forget this is all Europe shit now, they'd have no problem sending French EU officers to accompany him, but I doubt there'll be any English people rushing to keep him company and because he's such a low profile person you're probably right about the security too. and despite his low profile, an attack on him could raise our own standing quite a bit, locally at least. I wouldn't want to really hurt him though you know, maybe rough him up a bit and deal with the guards but i don't want to do anything too extreme to him even if he is French."    “Right, like you wouldn’t use an iron gauntlet to slap his face.” Adrian smiled. “You know, this might just work… But we’d have to get lucky about the security, hopefully they’ll only be carrying batons and pistols, but if they’re using sub-machine guns, we’ll have to call it off. But where in London could we POSSIBLY catch them off guard? We’d have to both watch the convoy along with our own backs for patrols.”    "Ah come on man," Liam interrupted, "With London's winding streets, alleys and all that one way system shit there must be plenty of places we can ambush him"    "Like where, you have a better mental picture of the place than me."    "We need to know where the fuck he's going first obviously. You done with that beer yet? I'll get us a couple more cans" Liam said as he took a half step to the fridge and delved inside for more booze.     “Been done for ages, man.” He sighed, looking at the empty bottle with a far off look in his eyes. “What’s the time?”    "Fucking twenty past, mate." He called without looking back from the fridge. "Twenty past ten on a spring night, we should be down the pub or something, out on the pull" He said sounded disheartened as he handed Adrian a can of Fosters and cracked open his third, which thankfully was less energetic than the last one.     Adrian popped his open and simply took a sniff at it, holding it under his chin with both hands. “We always could go down to the pub, see how things are going.” He laughed. “Maybe we’d even catch a decent show on the telly there.”     TV was horrid for the most part now, and hardly ever was in English. You had the German melodrama shows, the hairy French women parading naked through magical fields, and Swiss cheese critique shows. He took down the beer as an image of some French lady paraded her hairy beaver towards the mental screen in his head.     Ah, the lines of a song came into Adrian’s head, a Rolling Stones classic. He hummed it out loud, trying to sing at the same time. “I see a red door and I want it painted black…” He stopped. “You know what, I better be going home, I promised me old man a day ago I’d get the kitchen door fixed, and I think I’ll be needing my energy tomorrow for it.”    Liam nodded and grinned "Fairplay mate, I think I'm just going to stick around here for a bit, have a few more drinks and then I'll sod off myself. Won't drink too much though, don't want to be stuck with the job of restocking the fridge, cost me enough last time"     “Later on, man.” He laughed. “See you whenever that sherry-sipping bastard comes around. Hopefully a few times before unless we want to end like Swiss cheese.”     Adrian picked himself up, and the beer was already heavy in his gut. He made a short salute in Liam’s direction, and hobbled off. It had turned out to be an alright day after all. They would show what it meant to be English! Eventually…   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Currently Reading :  At The Mountains of Madness and Other Tales of Terror  by H.P Lovecraft     Rambles : It is Sunday night, and it would be a sin for me not to write anything in my blog, and as a rule of thumb, God cannot sin xD That reminds me of something I talked to Annisa about. Something about me being listed in the bible as God xD     Heathen talk! CURSE HIM!    Anyways, you’ll notice that though only a day has passed, I’m reading another book. So maybe you didn’t notice, and if you didn’t, you make me sad.  Switch Bitch  was REALLY short. Lovecraft is, in my experience, fucking excellent with his words, or a fucking tart. His scary stories truly are scary, as opposed to the shit movies they come out with these days.  The Ring ,  The Stupid Movie that Begins with The , etc. But then you have his meh-ish stories which make you think he’s a bloody retard. If you can, try pick up his  urlLink  Cthulhu Mythos   stories, written in the later part of his life, and are much grander in ideas. For a week or so I tried imitating his style and failed simply because the imagery is just so vivid and yet, simple.       Have I anything else to talk about?     No, not really, I’m sorry. Today has been trying in so many ways.   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Currently Reading:  Switch Bitch  by Roald Dahl    Currently Watching: Coupling       Rambles: You know, I think my brain has the equivalent of a menstrual cycle, except its yearly xD And it doesn’t bleed, it goes soft… And not soft as in dull, but soft as in mushy love soft. Of course, this is good if I’m currently in a relationship, but this year has found me empty handed. And now, I have seen two romantic comedies in one day. Three if that’s what you classify  Meet Joe Black  as.     NOW, what the fuck is up?     First,  Rules of Attraction . Or is it  Laws of Attraction . Fuck me dead, I don’t remember. This was forced upon me, by oh dear cousin Krys. Not forced, more… I felt it my obligation not to argue with the movie choice. Scarily enough, I didn’t have too many problems with the movie, it was less flawed then let’s say  Troy  or  Return of the King , two movies shit-note-worthy.     Second,  Love Actually … Shite, I actually like this. Let’s not go any further… Except Keira Knightley is the hotness xD     I apparently need sex, I think that’s the piece of advice I’ve received that has beaten around the bush the least. Of course, the sex could just be a metaphor for some kind of physical relationship. With some people you never know xD     
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Currently Playing :  Little Miss Can't Be Wrong - Spin Doctors      Rambles : I'm going to be frank... My balls hurt... I was in the shower and I hurt myself on the doorknob x( Nobody really needs to know the details, but there was no blood! That's really positive when it comes to dealing with a man's fruit and vegetables.     You can tell when I start off with a "My balls hurt" paragraph, you know its going to be shit xD     Anyways, Yoshi asked about my I'm A Dinosaurus Roar Roar title, and i'll answer now, with a link. I was browsing  urlLink Something Awful  a month or so ago, and they had a song competition type thing, and one of the songs involved a rapping dinosaur and its probably one of the only decent rap songs i've ever heard xD     But you will need to understand what a dinosaur is before being able to fully appreciate the beauty of the song. urlLink  Click here       Without further ado,  urlLink Click Here  for the amazing song "I'm A Dinosaurus" by some guy called Benjamin xD Right-Click on it and save target as... Otherwise you'll have to fockin stream it.     Need a download accelerator so you can resume downloads when you're on shit connections?  urlLink Click here!     Need a better browser?  urlLink Click here!      Using XP and you want to try and speed it up?  urlLink Click Here!  (Be warned, I cannot ensure any damage done, but I use it and my computer is alright)    Need to clear up some space quick?  urlLink Click Here!  (Its shareware, but you can use it once and remove tons of useless gunk using the Wizard function. First time I managed to get rid of 100 mb of shite that served no purpose on my com)    See? I couldn't write my own article tonight so I just posted links... Aren't I great?  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    To try and colour in my photo manip. sketches, see how this compares xD  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Would you believe I sketched this? It's actually a picture I took in last year's graduation. But thanks to my photoshop skills, I developed a Sketch Action which turns photos into sketches. Oh well, Arty and Nikita xD   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Its that guitar again, and once again he looks like he's enjoying himself too much. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Who looks more homosexual? The guy with the finger in his mouth or the guy in shiny red? I can't decide xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Watch out! He's HORNY 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Prom- Angel illumnated by the lighting brought by the real professinals. You see? I really am cheap, I make use of other people's money to my own benefit. Savvy 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yes, Zio's House, Yoshi was just knocking himself out 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The Monkey and The Pig, same place as the last pic xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Monita and Michelle... Ummm  I think we went to Frankfurter in Town Square and met up xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Christina looking the stoner
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Aren't I a creative bastard tonight? I just came up with a Johnny Howard (Australian Prime Minister) song...     I hate that bastard...   _____________    Who has bushy eyebrows,  And lives in Australia?   JOHN-NY HOWARD! JOHN-NY HOWARD!     (Chorus)   Johnny Johhny Howard,   He's a prick,  So Full of Shit,  With His Politics    Who fucks the people over,  Day in and day out?   JOHN-NY HOWARD! JOHN-NY HOWARD!    (Chorus)      Who gives rough anal,  To kangaroos in free time?   JOHN-NY HOWARD! JOHn-NY HOWARD!    (Chorus)     Who licks the Yankee arse,   of President Dumb Bush?   JOHN-NY HOWARD! JOHN-NY HOWARD!    (Chorus)    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Hello dammo, i was just looking at all the blogs and your blog caught my eye. Now my problem is that, im a smart person, but sometimes im a lazy fag. Im the type to do things at the last minute, for example assignments, essays etc. Also i cant seem to study, and by the time i have a test i fuck it up. How can i change my attitude towards studying and doing assignments before the due date.   __________    Aw, I hate serious questions like this, but I guess I will try to do my best to answer this. Let’s start.      You claim to be a smart person, and lazy. This is actually a major problem with smart people, they feel they don’t need to study shit because they’re smarter than everybody else, and therefore studying would, technically, be degrading.         Now, there are two approaches I can think of approaching this with, neither can I assure will work (Because for each individual there is a different solution, and nobody can give one single cure that will work for all, blah blah blah, so you have to adapt what other people say to fit yourself)       First Approach     Think of all the negative aspects of your life. This may seem highly stupid advice which a pale-faced Goth would adhere to, but by doing this you automatically cancel out the whole smart thing. But don’t do this until you get depressed, we don’t need any more idiots dragging themselves around. Anyway, after this effort at being more realistic in your outlook on life, you will find that no matter how smart you are, it’s usually the people who work hard who end up reaping benefits. I can think of a few people who aren’t smart, so to say, but they’re a hell of a lot better than me regardless.      So yes, simply put, think of all the things that you don’t know about, and try to put an effort into the things you DO know about to make up for your lack of knowledge in particular fields.        Second Approach      I don’t know where you are in life, but when you say studying I’m put in mind of high school and university. If you’re in the former, my advice is to simply think about aiming your highest so you can get into a good uni. If you’re in uni, think about what you want to become. Doctor? Well like fuck a hospital will hire somebody inefficient like you when there are plenty of other choices.      The short-term pleasure of not doing stuff because you’re lazy is worth fuck all in the long run, where you’ll be walking around begging for cash. Whereas though you don’t get to lounge around right now, you can become rich later on and spend your time as lavishly as you want then.      So which would you rather be? A young bloke/dame who does nothing and enjoys it right now, or a slightly older man/woman who cruises the seven seas in search of BOOTY! In either sense, I guess xD  __________________      Alas, my headache prevents me from thinking more at the current time, so will that do?    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
           Serious Question of the Day : Why the hell is it that feet smell and noses run?       Currently Playing :  Jungle Boogie  by Kool and the Gang       Rambles : You know, since my time in CB, I have never felt so tired from doing P.E. Maybe some times back in UWC where you had to run around a proper athletic running thing (My mind is dead), but not since then have I tired. Thing is, I had a cough, so I felt crumby going into P.E xD But you know me, being the symbol of uprightness I am (in this case I uphold a reputation to stink at P.E, both physically and mentally xD).      On the upside, I’m going to be healthy this year.      On the downside, I’m going to be tired this year.      On the upside, I’m going to become diligent in all that I do, because of the intense training.       On the downside, I’m going to be tired this year.      Yes, I am truly a virtuoso when it comes to describing how I feel. I even use big words like virtuoso when I’m feeling in the dirt to make up for stuff xD      You know, I believe a person can only not be in love for a period of time before immediately seeking out a member of the opposite sex. For my readers Fudge and Alec, it is o-k if you seek out members of the same sex; I’m not going to make any comments. Well, I probably will, but you can ignore it xD      ANYWAY, this stems from the fact that even though you don’t have anybody special in your life, you try to seek love from things like your pets, your friends (your pet friends?), your sex-stimulating devices of both electronic and just-plastic nature, whatever. So, with this in mind, love is what powers us to do things from good to bad.      We seek friendship- GOOD      We seek sexual climaxes- Umm, really depends with what exactly. If it’s your pets, ummm, I think I’ll just skip this.     We seek… Ow, my fucking head is throbbing. And now that it is, we seek to cure pain. In doing this, we seek to gain love from both our body (You know, not like physical love, but love like “Hey, thanks mate, that headache fucking hurt, eh?” And no, I don’t have a Canadian/Australian brain, lord be thankful) and from others who may later suffer the same conditions. Like Christopher Reeves (That arse) who, only after becoming crippled, started donating funds to try and cure it. Because of his pain, others may be able to walk. Awwww     Anyway, my head is actually throbbing right now, so I may need to go off now, since I’m done with whatever homework I had.       Later on           
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
           Rambles:    Well this is good; I can take a break from the Ask Dammo segment, because that is just EVER so stressful.      Yesterday my brother came into my room, and I was unfortunately leaving to take a shit at the time, so I said I had to go to the toilet. He replied by asking me if I want a “nappy” xD Smart kid.      Now, for the more serious issue. In EAP today, Yoshi brought up the idea of becoming roommates when we go to Uni. Being the totally heterosexual individual that I am, the first thought that came into my mind was not “Oh, people will think we’re faggots”, no, that thought came second. My first thought was “hmmm, this could be a good thing.” But now I will analyse the good and the bad properly.         The Good         Cheaper lodgings. Dividing the rent of any flat would be great, since this means I get more money from whatever it is I’ll do for a part-time job.      Better food. Let’s face it, I may be a living god, but anything of food based substance I will ultimately make it inedible. He can apparently cook, that’s a plus. Less costs on having to constantly buy take-out xD      Lack of loneliness. This itself creates less chances of becoming depressed and thus incapable of continuing on when shit goes bad.  Sure, I’ll be constantly surrounded by countless babes, but this is beside the point. The feeling of loneliness stems from having no real connections to people, so you are actually better off with just normal friends then having girlfriends who you actually have to care about to the point of sexual interests. I mean, friends you don’t have to please them in the same way I guess. xD Easier maintenance.      I can’t think of anything else xD                The Bad                Like, the whole idea is so totally grosssssssss. Hahaha, no, it’s just odd. As if spending all this time with my family hasn’t been enough to crush my liberty, leaving and ending up with an old mate again? Poh xD      I’m honestly scared to death of the following scenario.            I come home with a stunning beauty, like the previous days, but this time the plan in which Yoshi buggers off someplace else for the night has gone terribly wrong. He comes out of his room and says out loud “Heeeeeey Daaaaaam, you seen my hand lotion?” Off scampers the chick, to tell all her chick friends that I’m gay.          *shivers*          frustration that comes with marriage xD You have to see the person every day, no breaks. I’m not ready for the commitment xD        Conclusion       It actually seems the good outweighs the bad. Ugh. Well, we’ll see how shit goes in the near future. Hahaha, I can always look back on this for final conclusions.     And you can always COMMENT. SLUTS xD            Everybody can comment, but it’s under anonymous if you’re not a member. Aren’t I the best-est?           Praise Dammo!         
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes Annisa, I was wrong x(  But unlike you, I don't suffer from massive agony when i'm corrected xD   Anyways, on the Ask Dammo segment, put requests in the latest post xD  I can't be bothered to check all my old ones 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Ask Dammo, Question One           
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Now Playing :  Rockin’ in the Free World  by G3    Rambles  : It’s been a trying day, I mean GOD we had English homework. I didn’t really mind the assignment, as some people did *glares*, I just hate these minimum and maximums. A minimum of a 1000 is acceptable if you’re talking about writing four-five paragraphs, but 300? You kid me. So I ended up writing only an intro, two body paragraphs, and an end. Like, wtf mate?         Well, you may have noticed all the pics littering the first page; I was just overcome with glee with Hello working speedily xD All are taken by me, I think. The monkey is, most definitely. The only ones that aren’t involve the prom pictures ^_^ Damn you have to hate that smile.           I really need to get seriously started on writing. I mean, let’s face it, if I did, I’d be even more known than I am now. And I have fingers… Nice fingers… Hairy, but none the less, FINGERS.         Me and Fudge were wondering which superhero girl we’d do, since I saw Annisa’s one about male super heroes. Unlike her, we just went for looks (Shallow for a puddle). I think I ended up thinking either Elektra or Jane Grey.         Well, its night time, and I’m getting tired.         I could start writing up my thoughts on current issues, but my thoughts are so deep and complex people seem to have trouble keeping up with the groove… Maybe I’ll start a evaluation type thing, where I find something to read over/listen to and review, and save you trouble from buying crap stuff like CD’s, books, etc. *cough* Of course, my tastes are superior to a fault.     Any suggestions? As long as its reasonable, I’ll try and review it. Even concepts, ideas, the like, whatever.         I’ll be like “ Ask Jeeves ”, except I’d be “ Ask Dammo ”, and you’d get witty retorts and swearing instead of information. Ok, see? It would also be full of lies xD       ENOUGH RAMBLING         
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Hmmm, Prom... Seems like a long time ago xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Why does Mike look like he's wearing make-up? xD Poor Yoshi, standing in the back
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I could try better xD Bad lighting 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    His guitar, his soul, his dildo o.O 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Look a monkey with a carrot
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    He almost looks like he's working xD I can imagine him going through the streets with that thing 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    What the hell is with Mike's face? 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Ha, damn kids xD   Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Rambles : First off, I’d like to say, thank you Blogger for the rich text support. It’s ace. Hello is working too now, so I’m really happy xD Trying to post pictures up now, but thanks to a slow net, that won’t happen anytime soon.        Let’s see… I bought a bunch of pirated CD’s, oh woe is me xD Hardly any of them worked, so that blows. Most of the Phill Collins  Greatest Hits  works (spare one song), and so does G3’s  Rockin’ in the Free World , so it’s all good.     I'm finally reading Brave New World, by Adlous Huxley, and its, quite frankly, disturbing. I mean these people exist 200 years after Ford. Not Anno Domini, no, I mean after Ford's T-Model car xD So the time they use is A.F. And they refer to their leader as "His Fordship", and to top things off, they do the sign of the T, which is like the sign of the christ, but a T.  Then you have the issue of how they encourage children to have SEX with each other.  But like  1984 , its dystopian, so its understandable.      GOD i'm loving this rich text editor xD      I stayed up for an hour listening to Yoshi talk last night, and though this itself wasn't bad, hearing him repeat himself was xD So if you're reading, take it as a hint not to over do the talking  xD       Ca Bau Kan , this book we're reading for Indonesian, has crushed my soul. I am blank reading this.  I tried reading a page, then I nodded off almost.      Ummmmm,   HELLO SEXY       xD Random outburst.       urlLink Click Here  for Porn     *sigh*      Though i'm over the whole "I need a girlfriend" stage, I do want one because when you stay up talking to a GUY it gets depressing xD       Oooooo, yes I wish it would rain down on me now      Who wants a picture of me with my new haircut? Nobody, good xD          
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Book of the Day : See title xD It's the book that inspired Blade Runner, or became, either way. I've never watched it, but the book is damn good.    Song of the Moment : Phill Collins- Both Sides of the Story   Find yourself in the gutter in a lonely part of town where death waits in the darkness with a weapon to cut some strangers down sleeping with an empty bottle, he's sad and an empty hearted man all he needs is a job, and a little respect, so he can get out while he can  We always need to hear both sides of the story  A neighbourhood peace is shattered it's the middle of the night young faces hide in the shadows, while they watch their mother and father fight he says she's been unfaithful, she says her love for him has gone and the brother shrugs to his sister, and says "looks like it's just us from now on"  We always need to hear both sides of the story  And the lights are all on, the world is watching now people looking for truth, we must not fail them now be sure, before we close our eyes don't walk away from here 'til you hear both sides  Here we are all gathered in what seems to be the centre of the storm neighbours once friendly now stand each side of the line that has been drawn they've been fighting here for years, but now there's killing on the streets while small coffins are lined up sadly, now united in defeat  We always need to hear both sides of the story  And the lights are all on, the world is watching now people looking for truth, we must not fail them now be sure, before we close our eyes don't walk away from here 'til you hear both sides   White man turns the corner, find himself within a different world ghetto kid grabs his shoulder, throws him up against the wall he says "would you respect me if I didn't have this gun 'cos without it, I don't get it, and that's why I carry one"   We always need to hear both sides of the story _______  I love the bolded part, dunno why   Rambles : Well, first day of school. While Mur is complaining about not being in school and everybody thinking she is, i'm complaining that I actually am in school. It's not that it was bad, it was just hard getting used to listening to JENNY rambling on xD Kidding, if you're reading. Otherwise the day went fine, computer class was interesting because I found some really stupid pick-up lines and we (we being the guys, no doubt) got a kick out of it.   Thanks Fudge for the love dice, but as i've told you, I gave those two bringers of sexual pleasure to Christina, for no doubt she will find more practice with them. She almost verbally orgasmed when she got "lick neck" if I remember correctly xD  Hmmm, the new P.E teacher isn't just going to let us lie, damn. He's actually looking forward to P.E class, whereas I guess our old teacher dreaded it, since we were all so lazy xD   I don't really have much to say, apart from the fact that on saturday i'm going to shave my hair off xD I HAVE HAD ENOUGH WITH THE HARRY POTTER CRACKS. I go into Brew and Co, the barista tells me I look like Harry Potter. I go looking for games, the person selling the games tells me I look like Harry Potter. At least if I trim my hair off, and then grow a goatee (which will be a pain), i'll look like Jean Reno, and though he's French, he's better than that twit of a child who plays Potter xD   Anyways, its Potter who looks like me, not the other way around.   Ai, later on 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: Alright, a different perspective on that conversation in my last post.   Knowledge is Power.   Now, going on this,  We know that smoking is bad for you.  We know that doing drugs is bad for you. We know that drinking is bad for you.   Its common knowledge now, we see evidence of it daily, on the telly, in the news, wherever. And yet people continue to do it, why?   In this same light, I know that my argument, no matter how valid in my own eyes, may not hold that same jurisdiction in another’s.   Therefore I may not judge somebody for not listening.   There, it took me a while to get this outlook but there you have it. By just looking at this from another angle, my general anger at that silly argument has been quenched xD  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: I got a good idea on how practicing is different from preaching. I set out today with some things in mind. One was to try to cause no harm to others, verbally or physically, and in this, I failed with the damn slip of my tongue in regards to Zio xD Sorry man. The other was to something good in those I saw and did not particularly fancy. This I accomplished. Therefore, I am not so much in regret that I failed one, because I managed to achieve the other. This may seem a bit silly, but you cannot build a world in a day, and you will naturally fail at some things, but you can always learn. Moreover, I intend to xD   Well apart from this, I have to thank Murti for the interesting conversation. I had just been arguing with Krys about clubbing, and I was somewhat irritated at how she seemed to perceive my arguments. No doubt, I was at fault, but her dispute made little sense to me. I will put out some of the strange highlights I found… Bemusing?   Her: people are the ones that give the club a bad name Me: oh great, people are the ones who give the club a bad name, quality argument that... You're saying if all the wrong people were not to go clubbing then it would be alright, thats like saying war is fine if the soldiers don't attend Her: exactly. there wouldn't even be war if not for the soldiers    Now, here I was rather speechless. She seemed to be agreeing with me, but disagreeing at the same time x( Makes me a sad Dammo.   Her: i don't think most ppl indulge in reading books or writing stories as having fun Me: *shrugs* But then again, reading books and writing stories doesn't exactly promote a negative lifestyle does it  Her: its not negative, but its not that positive either Me: Its positive for the writer because they're releasing their creativity, its positive for the reader because they're learning things Her: look, i see clubn as FUN cuz i get to hang with my friends and ya know have fun with them if you think i indulge in clubn due to sex, drinks, and drugs whatsoever, well then ur terribly wrong der haha people can be influenced by books did you know certain books are just like watching tv they can poison ur minds Me: right, so your argument is that certain books poison the mind correct? now, certain clubs poison the body and the mind Her: I mean i love books, i love readin them...but at times i wanna just relax and have fun Me: It just so happens the percentage of which these clubs pollute people is high Her: haha it does not poison the body and mind stupid Me: I'm sure there's some decent club Her: it just depends on the person like moi, i haven't been drunk once i haven't taken drugs ever Me: Ha right right, then I can say the same  It depends on the person who's reading the book  Honestly, I don’t like arguing with most people, because there is some reluctance in trying to argue from the neutral standpoint. Trust me, I try to stay as hard as I can to not be a kill joy, but when you look at it from the perspective of some person who has just entered into our civilization for the first time, you notice that a lot of stuff we do is horrid for us, and we don’t notice it because of the positive aspects. Thing is, these positive points can usually be found without the negative.   Ah well xD To each their own, I’m trying to hard to accept this.  Notes on the Post Title: I really want to find the book, written by Adlous Huxley I think            
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Rambles : Today has been fair, I had a fascinating dream to start with, can’t remember why it was interesting, but it was… I think xD   Went to Senayan and Ratu Plaza today with Zio, so that was cool, getting out of the house. I bought a bunch of dvds xD A list? YOU WANT A LIST?! You don’t? I’m giving it anyway xD   -	Joe Satriani live in San Francisco -	G3- Live in Denver (This is just so fucking awe-inspiring; I can’t put it into any other words. I spent the afternoon watching it and I was put into tears by the fucking beauty of Vai, Satriani, and Malmsteen performing together at the end)  -	Santana’s  Supernatural   -	Pink Floyd’s  The Wall   -	The Fisher King   Well, it’s a bunch for me xD   Guess what I’ve been reading, on my own liberated will?  The Art of Happiness  by Howard C. Cutter and His Holiness The Dalai Lama. I’ve been thinking about shifting my religion to Buddhism, since I can sincerely say I feel about it strongly, the concepts and such. The fascinating thing about the Dalai Lama is that he doesn’t segregate things into good or evil; it’s either positive or negative. You wonder what’s the difference? Well, he classifies it into whether it’s positive or negative in the quest for happiness. I’ve digested a lot in the two days I’ve been reading this, and though I hate the guy who writes it, I become spellbound with His Holiness’ words.   Ah well, I thought I’d never see the day where I confirm to any religion, but if I do, it will be to Buddhism, and it will be quite soon. Odd really. xD   Anything I want to add? Hmm, I’ve been thinking about relationships a lot while reading this book. The Dalai Lama states that most of the time people get into relationships for pleasure, not happiness, and this is pretty much true. He also states pleasure can be bad in the long run, also true. Whenever a girl complains about breaking up with some bloke because he’s an arse, my mind is urging me to tell her to shut the fuck up and tell her it’s because she chose the wrong dude. Of course, I shouldn’t, and I don’t think I have.   This leads me to choosing the wrong girls, and it is ALWAYS for the wrong reason xD I can say this after honestly looking over my past. I’ve always wanted the wrong type of girl, and for the wrong reasons. I was a suicidal-want—to-be for a year or so, and I sought relief and I thought I could only find it in intimacy with a chick in the way Hollywood so amazingly visualises. This was so horrid I didn’t come to think about sharing a regular kind of intimacy you can find in just normal friends. Therefore I spent a lot of my time agonised, when really I shouldn’t have been. Falling in ‘love’ with some superficial girl is like smoking, it’s a brainless compulsion which needs quitting.   I’m shallow; I’ll be the first to admit it. I have a classification system which goes  elephant lady  meaning  wouldn’t fuck her if I was stone drunk , to  fuckable  where she isn’t great, but she’d be alright in the sack, and then finally  Triple S- Sexy, Smart, Sweet , aka the  perfect girl . I will look at a person; notice every single flaw in their face and body within around two-five seconds. I remember when I was hanging out with some of the other guys I know that I saw this chick who they thought was hot and I pointed out that she had a strange chin compared to her forehead, or something. I didn’t know what she was like in terms of personality, but I blew her out of my mind because of a small facial blemish.   Now, today, when I was in the mall with Zio, I couldn’t help but smile at some of the girls that I had previously classified as one step short of being fuckable. I don’t know why, but I just felt a lot better about myself, and I couldn’t help but feel kinder to others. Then when I was about to leave home, my uncle who was picking me up didn’t come for around 40 minutes. Last time this happened I blew my head, consuming myself in rage. Today? I just smiled and studied the place around me, the faces of some of the people I saw. When he got to me, finally, he apologised and I just said “Its alright” smiled, and shrugged it off.   This change is great simply because I feel better as a whole. I noticed people looking in a “fuck-you” way in the parking lot, I really didn’t care. If they don’t want to look at me as just another person, fine, not my problem, I tried not being a cunt and giving him a glare, you can’t ask much more.         Funny how I can change so much just because I put my mind to it. I hated that “How to be a Happy teen” because it was superficial advice. Made no sense to me. Eastern wisdom is so much more developed than Western, despite the fact it seems all Western countries developed technologically faster. Ah, I’ll shut up now, I’m babbling xD   Peace out my brothers and sisters!  That sounds silly, but I don’t careeeeeeee            
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Story : Shit, I had the most fucked up dream last night. And when I say fucked up, I don't mean flying mushrooms, talking alien brains, and xenophobic foreigners. Ah, I better write what the dream is before I forget.   Main focus of the whole dream was this girl called Ella, and the period is what I'm guessing the future (Unless we have flying cars right? More on that later). Anyways, this dream starts off with me at a party with some friends, Zio, Yoshi, and Christina. With the exception of William, these are the people I should be hanging with today. That explains why THEY were there.   But there was this other girl. You guessed it, the mystery gal called Ella. When I say she's perfect, I dead mean it. Hot as fucking hell, great body, and an amazing personality. Her face looked Eurasian, not too skinny, not too fat. She was wearing this great black flowing dress. Now, in the entire dream, only two people knew her, Christina and Arty (more on this later). Anyways, I became attracted to her in the period of one night, and when she was about to go, I asked for her address, and like in this other dream I had she said "not now". Alright, no surprise.  Then a few days later, another party, same people. This time this Ella dame and I were a lot closer, god knows why, but when the party ended, we went down in this flashy elevator. Once again, I asked for her address, and she suddenly broke down in tears. Obviously I was thinking "Wtf?" Then, as soon as the elevator doors sprung open, she started running out into a crowd of people, and when I say crowd I dead mean it, there isn’t a centimetre free of human life. So basically I chased her through the crowd, who wouldn't do this if they thought they knew the perfect person? Thing to note here it was dark and lamps on either side of the pavement were shining yellow, brightening up the night sky greatly.   Thing is, she was always at least a few metres ahead of me, so I finally gave up when we reached this breathtaking park, collapsed and pretty much yelled out "God dammit, stop running, I like you!" And she suddenly stops and turns around and replies with "God, that's not what girls want to have, we want gifts!" How surprising is this? xD Dedication of love is much less than physical presents. Anyways, I smiled at her one time, and turned and started running back for the apartment where the party was, but as I did, I bumped into Arty. And she makes mention of the fact that she knows Ella, and that she saw me chasing her, and then walks away into the crowd. Obviously I shrug this off as coincidence, and return to the building.    The next day I went to a Metro (Department store here) in the air in a bloody hovering car. Now, I was planning to get her chocolates and some jewellery, but as soon as I got out of the car, I slipped, and luckily got hold of the rim of the car, so I was hanging out of the car, with nothing below me but air. But in the name of infatuation, because that's what I think it was now I think about it in reality, I managed to get back up and immediately started running through the store looking for the exact stuff I would buy Ella.   THEN MY SISTER WOKE ME UP! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!   *sigh* Now I don't know what happened after... Chances of seeing her in my dreams again are very slim. And god do I mean she was perfect, it saddens me deeply she doesn’t exist. Now, time for analysis, because I like performing my own analyses, not trusting generalised dream interpreters.    Why I had the Dream : This I know, it’s because I talked with Christina before going to bed about why I haven’t met with a young Julia Roberts or Catherine Zeta Jones. This comes from the thought that I look like John Cusack xD And then as I was nodding off I remember thinking about meeting the perfect girl. So maybe it was that, but if it was, why would I only now have this dream? I’m sure I’ve thought of it before.   The First Meeting : Now, I know why I chose Eurasian for this girl, it’s because I find Asian-European mixes to be hot. Don’t ask why, it’s just this odd thing I figure to be true in most cases. Now, the fact she only knows Christina at the party could be a depiction of that conversation I had in real life. Now, as for her response of “not now”, this doesn’t baffle me at all. Whenever I even think about asking a girl out, I expect a negative response, whether it be going someplace or going out as a couple. The fact Ella is no different could mean she’s a representation of the girl in my head, the one that will reject you every chance they get.    Another Chance : The fact we meet again could be my brain trying to pretend that you always get a second chance. In most situations, you only get one, or so I’ve learned. The descent in an elevator rather than a winding staircase is good, because it means a straightforward solution to the problem. How do I figure this? An elevator goes from Point A to Point B in a straight line, whereas a staircase often has you turning or even when the staircase is straight you’re moving diagonally. Anyhow, when Ella starts crying after I ask her for her address again, I figure this could be telling me that persistence doesn’t always work. Dunno. The crowd, to me, represents confusion, so if Ella runs through it, it could just be that she’s amazingly bewildered, and the fact that I follow her through it makes me bewildered as well, then. The night sky being illuminated by lamps could mean this is artificial, rather than where a day sky would mean natural light. One of the reasons I therefore think I was simply infatuated with this dame.    The Pursuit : When we chase, she’s always metres away from me, out of grasp for what seems to be forever. This could mean I’m never going to find the perfect girl, or it could mean that it will just be really hard, because she does stop after I pronounce my feelings for her. The fact she tells me she wants a gift is rather odd, because I’ve always thought that women are money diggers, so this reinforces my former stated idea that Ella is your common girl. Bumping into Arty, this bit is odd because I can’t make head or tails of why I would. I won’t pretend I can figure this bit out.   The Store : Now, onto the Metro scene. I arrive in a hover car, of all things, maybe significant of my feelings being elevated. The fact I fall out could indicate that I’m just going to loose this ecstasy, but me getting back up represents that I will get it back again. Chocolates and jewellery, stereotypical gifts for a stereotypical girl, apart from the beauty that is xD Running through the department store could mean I’m trying to make choices, but I’ll never know because of being woken up.   Feel free to leave your thoughts, and yes, I did actually do all this interpreting myself. I feel some dreams mean more than others, and that to each person an object could mean another thing, thus my distrust for dream dictionaries.      
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: I just had to paste this in, since i'm just so fucking proud of myself xD  ______ I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: wha? spell check is saying the word lamellae is wrong because of number agreement    Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says: I told you my word is better than yours  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: but i must consider revising!  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: maybe the fucktard of a paperclip can help  Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says: lmfao  Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says: That paperclip is a cunt, it keeps asking if i need help, DO I LOOK PSYCHO TO YOU?!  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: lmao  Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says: I thought of that one myself ______     Yes, I found it amusing, I don't give a fuck if you do, cunt.  EDIT: This happened slightly after I posted that.  ______  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: tell me when its done  Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says: *refuses to tell*  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: grrr, you swine  Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says:   I be a cur, that I be, but at least, my swarthy friend, I would not fuck a tree  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: wow, did you just make that up?  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: put that in your bog too xD  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: lmao  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: blog*  I'm a pirate! That I be!  I sail me ship upon the sea!  I stay up late - till half past three!  And that's a peg below me knee! says: I suck  Crowley: Illustrating My Point With A Blade for a Pen says: I concur ______  Yes, I know how to make people feel special  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, I haven't been posting much, but that is only because i'm trying to figure out html and these blogger tags. I plan on renovating this blog with a template of my own so it will be filled with Dammmo joy. Yesssssssss my precious.   I'll probably give up in a few days, but root me on anyways  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Favourite Thing of the Day : The Three-Fingered Salute (Ctrl, Alt, Delete)   Rambles : Well, I just took this quiz thing, saw it on Murti's blog decided I might as well. Boredom does weird things on the mind. Since blogger doesn't work on html directly, and since i'm too lazy to figure out a way of putting it in, here you go, my results.    Name : Damien   Age : 16  Sex : Male  Sexuality : Straight    Flirting Skill Level : 11%  Kissing Skill Level : 91%  Cuddling Skill Level : 22%  Sex Skill Level : 30%   Why They Love You : You are too good to be true   Why They Hate You : You can be selfish  xD Riiiiight *twiddles thumbs* Ideally they would have been over sixty but what the hey.    Tommooooorrroooow willll takkkeeeeee ussssss awaaaaaaay  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Remember that monkey picture? Well here it is, WITH LIPS 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Eat that! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    69% *giggles* 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I'm MUCH more stressed than that right now xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I would just like to inform you, whoever may be reading this, of the new link in my friendly blogs section. The 'You Stupid Bastard' one xD   This new blog currently consists of myself and Alec, and hopefully others in the future. The main goal of the blog is to write articles on whatever we feel like, as opposed to the whole point of these individual blogs where the main purpose is to inform others on our own lives.  As you can already see there, i've bastardised American Culture and written a preview review of GTA: SA.   If you are interested in joining our team, leave a comment in the latest entry in You Stupid Bastard, and i'll try and decide whether I want you in the team.  Obviously the requirements are high xD An at least average grasp of the English language and the ability to humour people.  That's all.   I'm bored.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Hahaha, in the real picture you see food in his mouth, so I decided to give you guys the cartoonised version 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Random Thought:  They could not have picked a better name  than “The War on Terror”. It’s not “The War against Terrorists”, no that isn’t  going to frighten people. Terror, as in “The Reign of Terror”, and as in  monsters with bloody fangs.  The deliberation behind using the word  terror was well thought out. America is viewed as on of the most dominant  nations in the world (I refuse to believe they are, because strength can never  be found in one source alone), and yet their people live in invariable horror.   “Fuck, man, that kid is carrying a plastic sword, he’s a terrorist!”    The irony. Anyway, where does the authentic terror come from? Is it  really from people like Bin Laden or is it from the American government itself?  Fear has always been a good way to control people, and that’s why dictatorships  can do astounding things if the country is at heart.   More and more  each day I find that America is adopting a system much alike to Orwell’s vision  of dystopia in 1984, Ingsoc (Oh, go  urlLink read  the book already,  you can even find it online. I even provided the link you cunts).   Your  thoughts?       Moron of the Day:   urlLink Article Found  Here    After finding an air sickness bag in a lavatory with the  letters BOB written on it, a United flight attendant concluded the meaning was  "bomb on board" and alerted the captain. The captain figured that was  reasonable, and  urlLink returned  the LA-bound flight to Sydney . 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Link of the Day:   urlLink The Yatta Video  (Japanese Men In Fig Leaves)               Rambles:  About the link, don’t ask. Please. Just don’t. I find the song amusing, that’s all. I’d download it for some stupid comedy xD              Anyway, as you’ll notice on my sidebar, I support Mozilla Firefox and Thunderbird. For all you people who don’t use the internet very often, let me enlighten you.              ONCE upon a time, there was an evil beast named Internet Explorer. Microsoft incorporated it into Windows, those bastards. They also made you use Outlook if you had a lot of e-mail.              But then Mozilla came, and gave us a new browser. And then they gave us another called Firefox. It sped up web page loading! It allowed us to skin it as we liked! It gave us the ability to utilise nifty extensions like Dictionary Searches! And Thunderbird did the same for e-mail!              So go grab your shit today, just click on the buttons.              I was going to write an article on Writing Better Blog Posts but I got bored xD              I started on a short story today, and it’s so far called “Sin”. No more will be revealed, even though some of you may know more details on it xD              And fuck me blind, the last episode of “Race to the Altar” is on, thank GOD. Stupid reality tv bullcrap.                    Don’t mind me, my head feels like it got hit by the 5th elephant. Don’t get that joke? Don’t worry xD     Second Link of the Day:   urlLink Tunak   urlLink Tunak  Tan (Please,  urlLink click this  to understand what drove me to download the thing in the first place. They look funny don't they? And then click either of the "Tunak" hyperlinks to download the actual video. I included two different locations in case one wasn't work, how kind of me)  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rambles: I'm running out of title ideas...            Insanity Test         Username          Age           Your problem is       Schizophrenia        Will you ever be cured?      (8)  -  Very doubtful.   - (8)      Just how crazy are you? -  91%                                                                                     This   Quiz   by  urlLink  insanitydefense   - Taken 173724 Times.              
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Currently Playing:   Free to Go  by the Folk Implosion   Flash of the Day:   urlLink This Land  by  urlLink JibJab  (I’ve actually had it for a while but I only just remembered to give a link)   Quirky Links for the Bored :   urlLink Star Wars Gangsta Rap  (No longer do we have east side and west side, but dark side and light side, *sigh*)   urlLink Mack Daddy Mario 3  (The Barbie Girl song in German?)   urlLink Harry Potter Puppet Pals  (Bother bother bother)   urlLink Harry Potter Puppet Pals 2  (Voldemort is a dolt)   urlLink Princess Hears a Strange Noise  (These next two are by the people who made South Park, for the love of God don’t click)   urlLink Princess Meets Officer Friendly     urlLink Banana Phone  (I still can’t get this out of my head)   urlLink The 5th Avocado  (I luff this)   urlLink French Erotic Film  (No erotica, the title really fooled me)   urlLink Badger Song  (And they say on the 7th day of watching this, the girl from the Ring comes to take you…)   urlLink Gaydiator  (I shall cheer for you...)   Rants : I hate the fucking service around here. I have a problem with my net, we call the company, and they tell us “disconnect the power supply in five minutes”. That’s the remedy they have for EVERY problem. CUNTS.   Rambles : Whenever I have nothing of flavour to write, I just post characters I’ve written up. This next one is… Fucked…  Name: Roland Age: Twenty-Four Race: HumanSex: MaleKingdom: Libaterra Class: Brahmarishi of Odd Weaponry Weapon: There are those who would use a sword against you, and those who would use a bow. Roland has never liked such things, thinking them too refined for his tastes. The weapon he’s best known for is his own body, and is deftly accomplished with it. They say he can fracture walls with his groin alone (PELVIC THRUST). However, if he is feeling kind, he will pick up whatever is around him and use that. Once he beat somebody to death with an ice cube for calling him a pervert.  Innate magic ability: The Brahmarishi of Odd Weaponry is chosen once every five centuries, and this trade is one that is branded within the very blood. So, when Roland was born, they knew he was the next Brahmarishi due to his uncanny ability to make women’s bras pop open with his glance. A very notable facility, wouldn’t you say? Physical description: Roland is hardly muscular in his build, and is better called lank. Of course appearances are deceiving, and until you actually try and put a blow unto his body will you believe how truly powerful he is.  He is shaved completely bald, and is devoid of hair (that’s what bald means!) on his head, eyebrow hair, nasal hair, anal hair, pubic hair, and so forth. This is the way of the Brahmarishi, for only a true Brahmarishi could take the continuous shaving of his body.  For clothes, the Brahmarishi may only wear three articles of clothing. First there is the compulsory, black fedora hat. Then there is the towel of everlasting wear, which is fastened around Roland’s waist and can only be dropped by Roland himself. Finally there are the groovy sandals of dance that the Brahmarishi must don. These sandals allow Roland to pull off complex dance moves such as the Moonwalk. Why? Who cares? Character description: Roland thinks of himself as a living God, and he has every right too. Because of this, however, he rarely finds companionship. One-night stands, yes, but not camaraderie. They say even cats cannot stand his stuck-up attitude. Because of this, Roland is forced to find amity with items such as beer and drugs, neither of which apparently screws up his body system. Will he find friends in the upcoming adventure? Stay tuned. Background info: Roland was born in Somewhere, Libaterra. The small village of Somewhere is unknown to most people because most people are retards. Anyway, for millennia, even before Libaterra came into existence (how the fook is this possible), the people of Somewhere had always been the chosen clan to carry on the title of Brahmarishi of Odd Weaponry . There is something to be said about the clan of Somewhere however. They are a people who breed off each others. Yes, you heard me. They’re like rednecks.  Anyway, Roland was born in the Somewhere year of the Gallivanting Prairie Dog. As mentioned earlier, he was chosen as Brahmarishi after popping his twenty-year-his-elder sister’s bra wide open. As was Somewhere tradition, his sister gave her breasts to him for feeding, because Somewhere tradition dictated that whoever’s bra was popped open was the one to feed the chosen one. One note of mention, Roland’s sister is hot.  By ten, Roland had finally gotten over the whole breastfeeding stage, and he was ready for training. Unfortunately, the Brahmarishi pretty much just has to re-learn his skills rather than learn them anew. So yeh, Roland had everything figured out in a month of time. It was like riding a bicycle. So he went back to breastfeeding.  But, alas, his sister had grown tired of the constant nourishment that her brother sought, and so she knocked him over the head, threw his body over a mule, and slapped the ass’s arse.  When Roland finally awoke, he found himself in Trinity Gask. Furthermore, he found that the women of Trinity Gask liked the “suckling of the breasts” and so he managed to live very well off.  Due to a very lazy writer, we’re going to skip to recent times. When Yamoto decided to drag their foreign buttocks into Libaterra, Roland knew his calling had finally come, and he stopped with the breastfeeding.  So now he goes around in his mighty towel, sandals, and fedora hat looking to heal the world. Make it a better place. For you and for me and the entire human race. Yes, I just had to rip off Jacko.   My Service to God : Because Annisa so kindly asked, I’m going to translate Yoshi’s last blog entry to the Queen’s English. Only because I can’t go in, figure out his password, and edit it myself.  “God, we have to stay at school Friday afternoon?” That was what was in my mind when I got Annisa’s SMS. Well I tried being innocent and pretended that I never got the SMS by not replying to it but the entirety of my biology class reminded me. So yesterday I stayed at school to finish my bio poster.  It was quite fun staying with Angel, Monita, Annisa and Mike, but GOD the girls kept ordering me to get stuff from the resource room. Didn’t they know I had sore legs because of the PE class the day before? Well it seems like they just liked torturing me by ordering me to get stuff from the resource room (which, for me, seemed miles away due to my sore legs). So, after a while, I just gave up. The next time they told me to get something, I rejected their order. Well I guess by doing that I made somebody mad. After the girls tried ordering me to get the UHU glue, Angel got up and took it herself, and when she came back she muttered something about how easy it was to get something. Well, HELLO, I HAD SORE LEGS HERE! After we finished the work, I apologised to Angel, and she said she wasn’t angry at me. Oh well. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Talk Like A Pirate   I'm sorry =( I just like pirates 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
               urlLink     Dammo spins tunes as   DJ Postal Outlaw      http://quizme.stvlive.com/djname/quiz.php                  I rawk xD 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Sneeze Fetish Forums    And you thought gamefaqs was full of idiots… Well now I give you a brand new category of people, people who dig sneezes. Don’t believe me?  urlLink Go here    Onto the show… ----   ON SNEEZE CD’S     Aussie’s roommate said  “what if i made CDs of me sneezing (female sneezing) so that you could listen to them in ur car or where ur unable to get on a computer? would ne one buy them?"   My Notes:  Oh yes, I’d love that. As if my own sneezes didn’t make me orgasm enough xD ----   ON SNEEZE PORN     Amsugar said  “hi. please excuse the spam. i made this amateur porn video a few years ago. the girl is super cute, but i was bothered by the fact that she had allergies and sneezes all through the video. she also almost sneezes and sniffles frequently. anyway, i just found out that there is a fetish for sneezing. very cool. so i made a tiny gallery, with a few pix, an audio clip of one of her sneezing fits, and links to order or download the video.here is the link:  urlLink FREE SAMPLES FROM AMATEUR PORN WITH SNEEZING GIRL i hope you find it entertaining. :)”   Ch2 said  “those are incredible sounding sneezes!! wish there were more!! Thanx for the tip. :yes:”   My Notes:  Dear god… I’m speechless… ----   ON HOW TO PROVOKE SNEEZING     Skada said  “This is a comprehensive list of how to induce sneezes. Not every method will work for every person. Thank you to everyone who contributed ideas.     1. Pepper     Finely ground pepper works the best, and white pepper works even better. Don't put it up your nose, or inhale it in large amounts; it will sting and hurt. If you just lightly sniff the air near the pepper, it should give you the tickle. If this still doesn't work, there are a few other ways.     2. Q-tips     Someone recently pointed out that it is dangerous to take the cotton off of the end, because it can cause bleeding if you scrape a membrane. So, it's much better to keep the cotton on. It's also recommended to use the kind with the paper/cardboard middle, instead of the plastic middle. There is less chance of being hurt. With the q-tip method, you insert the end of the q-tip into one nostril, and lightly move it around, until you find the most sneezy spot.    3. Toothpicks     This one is tricky. It's a good idea to start out with q-tips until you get good at not hurting your nose. Once you've mastered the art of tickling without hurting, then you can try something like toothpicks. Some people use them instead of q-tips because the end is more stimulating, as opposed to the cotton on q-tips. Remove the toothpick before you sneeze, so you don't end up hurting your nose. Just remember that safety is the most important thing.     4. The Tissue Method     This is probably the most common method, after pepper. To use this, you get a tissue (or some people use papertowels, because they're more durable) and roll one corner into a point (like the shape of a unicorn's horn). You use the point to tickle the inside of your nose (like with the q-tip and toothpick methods). This method is different, though, because you can leave the tissue (or paper towel) inside your nose when you sneeze, because it's too soft to hurt. Sometimes this can trigger multiple sneezes.     5. Dental Floss Threaders  Use the pointed tip of the threader to lightly tickle the inside of your nose. Because the plastic is thin and bendable, it shouldn't hurt, and you should be able to leave it in your nose to try for multiple sneezes. You can find these on the toothpaste/dental floss aisle in your grocery store.     6. Broom Brush Bristles (or Paint Brush Bristles)     This is much like the Dental Floss option. Use the tip of the bristle to tickle the inside of your nose. Since it is firmer than a tissue, it won't get all soggy. However, it's soft enough not to hurt. You can also keep it in for multiple sneezes.     7. Paperclips     This can be rather dangerous, so be careful. Unfold the paperclip until it is mostly straight, then use the tip to tickle the inside of your nose. Don't leave it in when you sneeze because it can damage your nose. This is about as dangerous as the toothpick method; remember to be safe.     8. Light     This is called photic sneezing, and it does not work for everyone. For some people, staring into a bright light (or sometimes only sunlight works) can either cause sneezes, or help to un-stick a stuck sneeze. However, this doesn't always work for everyone.     9. Spicy Foods     This does not work for very many people. For a select few, inhaling the aroma of spicy foods, or eating spicy foods can induce a sneeze. This results in singles or multiples, depending on the person.     10. Blades of Grass     Using a tall blade of grass, tickle the inside of your nose very gently. Because it is soft and pliant, it will bend to your nose and you can leave it in for multiple sneezes. Allergy sufferers might find this particularly effective.     11. Feathers    Another classic method, feathers can be used much like the blades of grass. Just gently insert the tip of the feather into your nose, or run the tip of the feather along the edges of your nostrils. The feather can also be left in your nose for multiple sneezes.     That is about everything. If you think of something else, send me a PM and I might add it to the list. I hope this helps people.     SK”   My Notes:  Thanks to Skada, I can now induce sneezes in the most unwilling of women. I am now the sneeze master, SNEEZE BEFORE ME. ---- Look, go see for yourself, I can’t fathom how anybody would find sneezing erotic.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Because she so kindly asked for a pic of her... 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Annisa said... " While I do agree that those forum posts are extremely disturbing (I got goosebumps...to think that people like that truly exist...the horror! The horror!), however...I must ask...what the hell were you doing at the forum in the first place? Why would you go to a site called www.gamefags.com?? In a way, I find it even more frightening that you actually took the time to read through them and then copy and paste them on here. I guess that's what happens when you have too much free time. By the way, how long are you going to be sick for anyway? Zio misses his bitch. :) "  With great power, comes great responsibility. I made it my job long ago to try and help the world and rid it of stupidity. By correcting grammar and spelling in MSN conversations, by sarcastically commenting on everything that breathed and even things that didn't.  With this new knowledge, you should become wary on how stupid people can become from using net lingo. If you had never seen this, would you have believed such idiocy exists?  And besides, I didn't take that long to find the more stupid comments on the site xD I would just click one link, then another, and the first post i'd see would be a sufficient example. Try it yourself, you'll find that the effort I took wasn't very high.  And I should be back tomorrow, despite my doctor saying I should get a three day rest. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      TOPIC: Gamer Idiocy  Some people think games are the cause of violence and numerous other sins. I think it’s because of stupidity coupled with gaming. But then again, stupidity coupled with anything results in dire results. When will people understand this? If they spent more of their time taking care of their child instead of just banning shit from them, there would be less violence in youths. Or at least I think it would.  ANYWAY, despite being a gamer, there is a certain kind of gamer that I abhor, because they make perfect scapegoats to prove how games are bad for you. Not that I blame those lying the blame on these idiotic individuals, I more blame it on the parents of these people. I believe some people should never have sex, and you get these kinds of people as a result.  All quotes after this message are from the forums of  urlLink www.gamefaqs.com  , and are unedited. WARNING- STUPIDITY AHEAD    On a topic on hookers in Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas    smithi3 said ... "Man I hope you can see hookers like doing stuff to you in the game maybe just there head bobbing up and own in your lap wud b good and you feeling their boobs man that would rool this game wud b the best game 4eva"    In reply to the statement of "You are a very lonely man, aren't you?"    smithi3 said ... "yeh but it would be cool like they were doing it to you in real life  uhh uhhhhhh unghhhhhh unghhhhh"   My Notes : See? All women reading this should go date a nerd right now, to prevent serial rapists from arising later on in life. Lack of sex and physical contact creates sad people such as the wise smithi3 above.    On “what you will do when you pick up GTA San Andreas for the first time?”    Solid-Steve(gs) said ... " 1.KILL  2.KILL  3.KILL"        My Notes : Regular Charlie Manson this fellow, he will go far in life. Or he’ll get bum-raped in jail. EITHER WAY…    On “What is the funniest thing you have said about Ragnarok Online in real life?”    ShinyKirby said … “About RO in real life?I tried to say to my sister, "I killed the MvP!"Instead, it came out as "I killed the NPC!"   My Notes : Oh, ShinyKirby, how you make me blush. Your wit is ever so droll! Please, I don’t even think a person with an emotional IQ of 200 would laugh at that.    On “What WWE Diva You Like The Most”    ssjgamer said … “Torrie Willson... I love the part of her intro where it shows her live-action and she bends over and pulls down her...Yeah.”   My Notes : Oh yes, I love pixelated boobs as much as the next bloke.    On “Stat of Lib in Spider-Man 2”    spike17spiegel said … “WTF is "Stat of Lib"? Was it extreamly hard to add y to that Stat of your and to add erty to Lib. Lazy fool”   My Notes : *giggles* Staty of Liberty. He didn’t spell extremely right either.    On “Rikku’s (from Final Fantasy X and X-2) Cup Size”    Tidus is cool said … “By The Looks Of It...Its Definitely Smaller Then a "A" cup. lol...she barely has anything.”   Smokingfrog2 said … “Maybe she should wear a wonderbra, or maybe she just got a reduction, because auron said he was going to feel her...”   My Notes : Why the fuck do you care? I mean honestly!    On “Where to find Dear or Alive hentai pictures in ‘compromising’ positions”    Ssj2joe said … “go to hentaiparadise.com (check the spelling). There are some nice DOA doujins there. Also try e-hentai.net. OR, search the name of a doa char on google image search. (like "kasumi") ENJOY.”   My Notes : Which is sadder, the fact that somebody asked for the pics, or that somebody had already voyaged for them before?  ANYWAY, that concludes this session for today… I’ve seen enough for one day.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Quotation of the Night : I do not feel obliged to believe that the same God who has endowed us with sense, reason, and intellect has intended us to forgo their use- Galileo Galilei   Rambles : It’s strange that I found a quote which relates exactly to what I was saying last night xD Oh well x)  I’m STILL SICK, and it’s starting to get on my nerves. Whenever I try to work on anything proper I have to stop because I’m violently coughing. Bitching.  So rather than risk my own health, I’ll just post some crap I wrote for tga, some website I decided to re-join simply because I’m not famous there… Yet xD ----- Name: Decanus Tafford Age: Twenty   Race: Human Sex: Male Kingdom: Libaterra Class: Swashbuckler Weapons: A cutlass called Poonany, and a knife called Mang. They be sharp weapons, ai. Innate magic ability: Decanus has the shrewdly devious ability to mimic the voice of anybody he has heard talking. Some people say it isn’t magic, but simply a bloody ace connection between his ear and vocal chords. But hey, it’s a kind of magic, and you should all listen to Queen if you don’t agree. Physical description: Decanus is the bomb with the woman, and it isn’t just because he’s well endowed in a certain area down under, but because he looks like a man. A real man, not some metrosexual bastard at that. From the sophisticated, yet masculine, eye patch over his left eye, to the black soul patch under his lip. His eyes are a riveting brown, and with them he unclothes women without their consent. Arrrrrrr  Decanus is the stylish pirate you only wish you could be. His choice of a dashing pirate hat, an unfastened cotton shirt with bloody long sleeves, and black cotton pants with those ingenious laces up the groin area all indicate he is trendy. The shirt is rarely buttoned up, thus revealing the masculine, meaning hairy and muscular, body of Decanus. He also has leather boots that could easily pulverise your ‘valuables’ into useless muscle. So watch what you say. Character description: Decanus is a player, and like Hugh Heffner he is idolised for following the dream. He is also a drunkard, a presumptuous cunt, and an all-around loveable guy. He isn’t “take-home-to-your-parents” presentable but hey, you can’t have everything, whelp. He also has a natural, groovy pirate accent. So he says “Ai” a lot. Background info: Decanus was born to a working girl, a very attractive whore. Who his father was exactly, the mother could not remember. She had screwed way too many people, and had continued well into her eight months of pregnancy. Which just goes to show, people have strange fetishes.  As soon as Decanus turned six, he became a stowaway on a ship called “The Bloody Heathen”. The captain of the ship was, unfortunately, a paedophile. So when Decanus was found, he was immediately brought into the captain’s room. Luckily, before anything could happen to our young hero, a saucy vixen appeared out of nowhere (deus ex machine) and saved him by cutting off the captain’s wang, who died a second later because he had been thinking with his dick at the time, and we all know that by chopping off our thinking mechanism we cease to exist. Then she stripped, made the young Decanus get a hard on, and they made passionate love beside the corpse of ol’paedophile.  Only after she turned into water did Decanus realise he had been seduced by a water maiden. Like it really mattered! HE GOT LAID AT SIX! Anyways, it was only a day later did he notice that he seemed to sparkle with magical energy, when a bloke came to check upon the old captain. Though he had never held a sword before in his life, he took up the cap’n’s cutlass and turned the dude into shish kebab.  Yes, Decanus Tafford’s life has been truly inspiring. To make a long story short, for the next fourteen years of his life, Tafford spent his time plundering and shagging and drinking, drinking and shagging and plundering, and did this all at sea. So when he finally crashed into land because of drunk driving and was forced to get off the ship he so loved, he realised something. There isn’t more to life than drinking or shagging or plundering. So now he does these things in local pubs. He lives in Trinity Gask a happy man, with hardly a worry as to the whole rebel vs other foreign bastards conflict. Yet. ----- Yes, I got lazy near the end xD Now, his theme song is played to the tune of the theme song from Shaft, but with some changes… ----- Decanus Who's the white pirate dick that's a sex machine to all the chicks? (Decanus!) You're damn right Who is the man that would risk his neck for his brother man? (Decanus!) Can ya dig it? Who's the cat that won't cop out when there's danger all about (Decanus!) Right on You see this cat Decanus is a bad mother-- (Shut your mouth) But I'm talkin' about Decanus (Then we can dig it) He's a complicated man but no one understands him but his women (Decanus Tafford) ----- Do you dig it? Of course you do.     Well, i've been collecting some records of my ownage of others on msn, and all will be revealed soon... As soon as I collect two more, that is.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "You can only be young once. But you can always be immature" 
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Pepsi, it's not only for straight men. Great tagline eh? 
     

    
</post>


<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Because Alec is a lazy fuck, this article doesn’t have the Sean Connery praise it should xD But hey, read on anyway.  Men everywhere look up to James Bond as an idol. More importantly, however, they look up to Sean Connery AS James Bond as an idol. Now bona fide men (not the sherry sipping, cane twirling, metrosexuals women call men these days, take  urlLink Gackt  for example) rejoiced when they heard Pierce Brosnan was finally giving up the seat of glory. Then they hit themselves in their genitals, because it was yet another blow to manhood, when it was announced that Eric Bana was the most likely candidate to be the new James Bond. I mean honestly, it’s not that he isn’t a decent actor, he’s just not Bond.  So, without further ado, I bring to you the candidates for the new James Bond. -----    Candidate Number 1:  Sean Connery    What? Did I just make a blunder? FUCK NO, DAMMO BLUNDERS NOT. After talking with a friend of mine I decided that the most fitting substitute for Sean Connery would be Sean Connery. And yes, I know he’s not getting any younger, but that could be the new Bond edge we’re looking for! Picture this…  ----- The wheels sped down the road; Bond was being chased yet again.  In that thick sexy accent of his, he said “I crapped me pants, AI!”  He put his hands to the brakes, and the vehicle came to a sliding halt. Slowly, Bond reached into his super chic jacket, and removed his latest Q invention.  The inhaler.  “Breathe in Booond, Breate out Boooond” The spy told himself.  He slowly removed himself from his Aston Martin wheelchair, and turned to face his pursuer.  “Ach, ye have a fine set of wheels, ye do!”  The woman got out, yer breasts reaching her toes as she did. Her Italian accent was cracked. “Ferrari…” She hobbled over to the man with the golden gun. “Should we go for a martini? Shakeeeeen, not stiiiiirrrrrred?”  Before Bond could say “AYE!” a voice from his jacket, that of Q, said “Remember Bond, no more martinis.” Before Bond could ask, Q’s voice came back. “And remember, if you’re going to have sex with her, you must, and I stress MUST, take your medication five hours before the Viagra. Q out.”  -----       Alright, so that would only appeal to people with Old People Fetishes, but it’s the best I could think of without the use of a time machine. And the best I can do at 12 at night. -----    Candidate Number 2: Bruce Willis    Now, I know what you’re thinking, he’s not English, he’s American. But DAMN, there are few men who can be the tough guy and still be charming. Ever seen Hudson Hawk? Fabulous movie, despite bombing in the box office, but then again, LOTR did well in the box office. So I don’t have very much trust for “the system”. ANYWAY, if you gave Bruce Willis an English accent, and put him in a suit, he’d be perfect for the part. Sure he’s getting old, but he’s still not THAT old.  -----    Candidate Number 3: Steve Irwin     No, sorry, I just couldn’t help myself xD But the stupidity in selecting ol Irwin is just as high as selecting Bana boy. They’re both prisoners of Mother England.  -----    Candidate Number 4: Bruce Campbell    Bruce Campbell would be an amazing choice if it wasn’t for the fact that he’s generally a B-rated actor, with the exception of his work in Army of Darkness. He’s one of the few people men will admit was The Man at some point or the other. As opposed to Sean Connery who still is. -----    Candidate Number 5: Dammo    That says it all really.    -----  Feel free to vote. And remember this classic moment from Monty Python’s  Life of Brian .   Brian: You are all individuals! Crowd: Yes!Yes, we are all individuals! Lone voice in crowd: I’m not Person next to him: Shh!   The moral of that situation? Err, vote me you cunts.    Link of the Moment  :  urlLink The Truth About George , the 43rd President of the USA. My favoured Bushisms  are    "And out of the evil done to America is going to come a more peaceful world, and a more better America..."   I mean honestly, what a tart xD    "What is your ambitions?"   Too not learn English and become president of the USA. I mean even Microsoft Word recognises that error.    "I'm honored to shake the hand of a brave Iraqi citizen who had his hand cut off by Saddam Hussein."   … Right, I don’t know what to make of this one.   "We want results in every single classroom so that one single child is left behind."   Ah well, want more, go to the aforementioned site.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Bah, I noticed the google ads had Doom 3 on them, so I wanted to see if any cool porno links would come up xD  This should make it Dammo's turn to post, as long as the word 'homosexual' isn't ridden throughout it (funnily enough i've been working on the Heterosexual male commandments- Dammo), then the google ads should be fine.  Oh, this is a blog, that's right. Today I played DDR for two hours straight (... You sick fuck-Dammo) , and I'm buggered.  Hmm, note to self, post when I have energy.    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Doom 3, to Hell and Back.   Well Dammo went with a game preview, so I will too.  Ever wanted to stay up all night, scared shitless, wondering what the hell is outside waiting for you?  No neither have I, but that's not the point.  The point is that Doom 3 has set the new standerd for FPS games. Besides ID Software creating the bloody catagory in the first place, ID are known for releasing rock solid game engines which define the gaming industry.  Anyone who is anyone has played the original Doom. If someone told me they have never played it before, I wouldn't hesitate in punching them in the face right on the spot. Who can forget the crappy MIDI music, the growling as you walk down a lonley corridor, or blasting the shit out of a monster at point blank range with the beloved shotgun?  The next installment of the Doom series is nothing short of an visual experience. Nvidia have pumped out thier 6800 ultra that supports engines for Doom 3 for christ's sake. You know it must be good.  And it couldn't come soon enough. ID software have put a lot of time and effort, with development starting right after Quake 3 was released. Level design looks nothing short of amazing. Shadows are catsed on models themselves, with distinct realism never seen before. Animation is fluid and flows together perfectly and gameplay was designed to be done alone in the dark...  Of course, with detail comes lack of quantity, as there is no way, with the amount of detail in each model, that you can have too many models at one. This means that the shit load of monsters that Doom was known for, will not be as present. Small price to pay, but still.  You will want a damn good computer though. About 2.4 ghz with that beloved 6800 ultra and a shit load of RAM should do you. Pity I'm still on a Pentium 3 huh. (Fuck up Dammo xD)  So relive your childhood. Buy me a new computer, and let the walk to hell and back begin!    Source From: Me reading Hyper Magazine in the newsagent this afternoon.    Dammo's Notes: On those graphics, Alec neglects to mention that some of the graphics are still 2D. He also neglects to mention that Doom 3 is still shit compared to Far Cry, with only one advantage over it, and that's character models xD  Dammo's Notes by Alec: Also, I'm a smelly bitch who has to do a 10 minute presentation by tomorrow. This is because I am stupid. After giving shit about Alec doing the same, I have stupidly gone off and left it to the last minute. (You stupid cunt xD I just have to give in the papers, not actually do the presentation- Dammo)     
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There comes a time on ones life where you just sit back and wonder 'why don't I go out and jump on some crocodiles?'  Well of course you do, it's a turning point and everyones life. You know you have grown up once you have thought about this.  Now although everyone thinks this, one man acted on it, and hence became an idol. A ambassader, if you will, to the rest of the world, that now represents a little speck of dust known as Australia.  His name, is Steve. Steve bloody Irwin.  Now don't get me wrong, great bloke, done a lot for the wildlife and whatnot. Sure he nearly got his kid eaten, but that little incident can be overlooked. I mean look at all the great stuff he's done. I've been to his zoo, and although I didn't see him, although the lines were ridiculously long and full of tourists, although the poor structure of his zoo outlines the rushed buildings and extensions put forward due to a sudden rise in fame, and although it is just a little bit on the expensive side, it's worth it to see crocodiles being raised away from their natural environment.  I mean seriously, who wouldn't want to be fed in front of a thousand visitors, cheering and taking photos of you? I sure wouldn't mind it. If I had a choice between living in a river, or living in a small pen being looked at all day even when I take a shit, I would take the latter in a second.  Onto the next point. Who the hell talks like Steeve bloody Irwin? Apparently, according to those oh so smart Americans, we all do. And why shouldn't one person represent the way in which a whole country? You know it makes sense. ( I can't imagine you people speaking otherwise- Dammo )  'Crikey! Look at this beauty!'  I got another idea, Steve darling. Shoot yourself in the head, or at least stop talking like a  over crazed orgasming pigmy.  'Have a go at this!'  How about no, friend.  Don't get me started on the movie. The only good thing coming out of that movie was the perve. And no, not on Steve's wife, the other chick. We know a lot of that film was in your park Steve, nice try buddy. The overly used sterotypes were second only to the terrible dialogue, and to top it all off - the ending was as good as my maths ability (which is honestly quite bad) [ Don't forget your English- Dammo ].  I guess you could say I'm not his biggest fan.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
           urlLink Yoshi..  said...                    We're gonna be black??!!! Euhh... that's the last thing i want.. seeing my character as an ugly fat black dude in a game.. well, come on y cant rockstar let us to create our own character before we play.. so we can choose whether we want to be black.. chings.. white trash.. pakis.. italian.. or arabs. it gonna be more fun if rockstar can also allow us to choose our own sex.. whether we want to be a male, a female, or both :P.. it's gonna be cool to play as a sexy seductive dangerous blood-thirst chineese whore. :P (my fantasy)   -----       In response to  "We're gonna be black??!!! Euhh... that's the last thing i want.. seeing my character as an ugly fat black dude in a game"  As opposed to being a ugly, skinny, brown dude in real life? xD   In response to  "well, come on y cant rockstar let us to create our own character before we play.. so we can choose whether we want to be black.. chings.. white trash.. pakis.. italian.. or arabs"  Well they could do that, but it would make the voice acting and such harder. If you don't mind your character not talking, then sure, hey, why not make your own? But with GTA: VC Tommy Vercetti had a voice, and it was a sexy one. And don't even think about adding voices for all those races, it would be too hard. And it would take up even more space, space that I honestly don't think there is. (Note: GTA SA runs on a dual layered dvd disc, unlike it's elders)   In response to  "it gonna be more fun if rockstar can also allow us to choose our own sex.. whether we want to be a male, a female, or both :P"  Ummm, how would that lend to the gameplay? Pick a female and you can whore yourself perhaps? Or even as a man you could sell your body. And I'm not going to say ANYTHING about the both comment.  (I don't know, I think it would be kinda cool xD -Alec)    In response to  "it's gonna be cool to play as a sexy seductive dangerous blood-thirst chineese whore. :P (my fantasy)"  ... I can't give you that fantasy, but I can give you something pretty close. A Japanese (the country near China) review of female vampires (blood thirsty!) and the girl with the brown hair in the first pic doesn't look half bad. Bewareeeeeee, MATURE CONTENT.  urlLink Click Here   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas      Designed By: Rockstar North    Instead of starting off with something totally silly and retarded (Which I’ll leave to Alec) I decided to do a game preview type thing. Anyway, let’s start, shall we?  The  Grand Theft Auto  series has pleased many a gamer with its freeform game play and general ability to knock whoever you liked off. This was what made it an appealing game, but it never really made it big with the mainstream. Maybe it was the crappy graphics, maybe it was that it was a little ahead for it’s time in terms of violence, but whatever it was, the game didn’t hit it big.  That is until  Grand Theft Auto 3  came out in 2001 for the PS2, and boy was it unexpected. It practically came out of the blue, and it shocked the pants off of gamers, because it allowed them to do even more devious acts. Not only could they steal cars and shoot the shit out of people, but they could also hire whores for ‘health benefits’. And all this in stunning 3D graphics! This game was, for the average male gamer, the equivalent of multiple orgasms to female.  Of course, parents took up their pickets and protested against the violence and shit, because that’s what parents do. And then the  GTA3  thing died down. Why? Because  GTA: Vice City  was coming out. They obviously didn’t want to make it look like they were remodelling the  GTA3  engine, so they made it look like an expansion pack. Anyway, this took place in the 80’s, and once again gamers pleasured themselves, but this time to Michael Jackson tunes (Alec pleasures himself to MJ tunes daily).  And then there comes  GTA4 . Now, don’t get me wrong, I’m looking forward to this game as much as the next nerd, but for Christ’s sakes, I feel like I’m going to be disappointed. Call it a sixth sense, but I feel like I’m looking at what will be an empty carcass of a game.  Let’s start off with something that really bugs me about this game. The size. It makes the bold statement of saying it will be three cities large and will be “somewhere between five and six times bigger than Vice City”. I find it hard to believe that the PS2 engine can handle this. Even with  Vice City , the machine seemed to have essential troubles keeping up with the flow of the game, and you’d sometimes see through roads etc. And with the enhanced graphics in  San Andreas , how the fuck can Rockstar even HOPE to keep the game running smoothly?   Now ok, let’s say they manage to pull the impossible off, there are concerns I have to do with the actual play engine. Let me start this paragraph off like a blunt cunt. I hate realism. I feel that gaming should let you do whatever the hell you like, whether it be racing through a forest as a blue hedgehog or stomping on mushrooms as an Italian plumber. With this said, I think the Weight and Exercise system in  San Andreas  is bollocks. The whole idea of you actually having to eat to not look like an Ethiopian bugs me. And the fact that if you eat too much and don’t exercise you’ll look like Anna Nicole Smith did a while ago. WHY BOTHER?  Finally, because I’m getting tired, the music. Since this game is set in the early 90’s, this means AC/DC, Ice Cube, and the Beach Boys. Now, don’t get me wrong, the Beach Boys is great, if you’re making a  Pee Wee Herman Driving Simulator  but otherwise I just can’t imagine myself killing people to that brand of music.    Image One :  urlLink The  Amazing  BMX Bike ! Ooooo, aaaaaaaa, bleh.  Image Two :  urlLink The Big Beach Boy    Bibliography :  urlLink IGN   Pictures (Edited by Dammo):   urlLink Gamespot   Bicycle Race Lyrics :  urlLink Queen        So with all that written down, I will stop. Leave your thoughts if you’d like.   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       American Culture (Click to Enlarge)    urlLink     What a statement xD I thought this would be a nice way to start this blog off  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>