<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't help but wonder; why are we in such a rush to dash headlong into the future?  For a while it seemed that people had a problem with living in the past.  It's not so true anymore, but people still fail to live in the right time; the present.  Now it's all about that which has not yet even come.  Why are people so worried about tomorrow, to the point of forgetting today alltogether?  Everything is too serious, nobody seems to want to leave anybody else room to laugh anymore.  By the time eighth grade rolls around, students are already getting the big decisions shoved down their throats; what they're going to study, what they're going to do with the rest of their lives, what they're going to be in the world, when they grow up.  The problem is, people these days are forgetting those last four words.  Did anyone ever stop to think that childhood and adolescence are indeed equally important parts of life?  One cannot simply skip ahead of these neglected years of life.  These years are what define what kind of people we're going to be for the rest of out lives.  When these years are gone, they're gone.  That's it.  Welcome to life, nobody cares you forgot to do the preliminary chapters.  If you waste these years, if you waste these formative years, you might as well cast off the other decades that will follow, too.  So what's the rush?  You're sixteen, you're not supposed to be worrying about post-secondary for another three years.  So start living the life you heave directly in front of your face.  The future can wait.  That's why they call it the future.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so now I have this "blog" thing.  Guess I'll make use of it soon enough...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've noticed a certain trend with people in general.  Some of my closest, dearest friends are posessed of a powerful inner wisdom with regard to life in general.  This gift allows them to offer great advice when somebody comes to them with a problem, for example, a fight between friends, or a breakup.  I am told that I myself posess a particularly potent wisdom, and apparently can offer very good advice when asked for it.  So why can't anybody use their own wisdom to guide themselves, myself included?  The same people that did such a good job of helping me one one day find themselves helpless the next day, and come to me with a similar problem, which I in turn have no problem answering.  So why don't they already know what to do?  Maybe it's the fact that being the third person gives you a more levelheaded perspective of events.  Furthermore, it's not without reason that the fact that you're not going to get burned telling somebody ELSE what to do compells you to advise things that you would never dare consider for yourself, but perhaps are indeed the correct answers.  Or maybe actually having the problem simply throws the mind off track, blinding it to otherwise simple and painless solutions.  Perhaps it's a mystery that simple isn't meant to be solved.  Maybe that's one of the reasons we have friends in the first place; a second opinion never hurts, and a third can go a long way, too.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Give a person an important task to complete, tie it to an immovable and inevitable deadline (say, two weeks for now), and put lots of pressure on said person to get it done.  If our friend is remotely average, chance is in favor of this person making beginning efforts toward getting the job done a few short days prior to the deadline.  I am surely no exception to this rule; procrastination is a looming evil in my life, as well.  The question is this; why?  Why do we as people allow ourselves to dig these holes when we know from the start that putting our duties off will just make life harder in the end run.  Perhaps it can be attributed to an overwhelming obsession; that is, of the short term picture.  It will be more comfortable to goof off now and do nothing, as opposed to doing actual work, since there is time to spare.  Ergo, nothing gets done, and the vicious cycle keeps up until it's almost make or break time.  This is indeed a fine example of doing the exact opposite of my previous post's theme, that is; worrying wholly about the future and forgetting the present.  Instead, the problem is inverted, and the future is altogether forsaken for the past.  Once again, the happy medium prevails!  It's rather unfortunate, really.  The answer is laid right in front of one's face, and one needs only to reach out and take it.  But lethargy's powerful influence deadens the hand, and no effort is made.  It's something that we all have to come to terms with, and I myself am admittedly far more adept at overcoming procrastination than many unfortunate people.  It's simply a matter of what's more powerful; your conscience, or your desire.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>