<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay, I have finally posted my first weblog. Go figure, been on the web since it's inception in 93/94 and on the Internet before that, and only now do I catch up to blogging. Oh well, better late than never. We'll see where this goes...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally the game that I have been working on for the Rubbermaid Commercial Products division of Rubbermaid Corp. is done. It's an isometic tile-based game done completely in Macromedia Flash. Although it was one of my more fun projects it was a challenge. I can understand why game developers are a different breed. Give it a try if you have the time, let me know what you think.   urlLink The Adventures of Safety Man!   Codes:  During gameplay - "andyg" my head; "chris" the designers head; "handy" my friend Darryl's head  Have Fun!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday the pastor of my church quoted the Roosevelt Panama Canal dedication speech during his message. Sometimes I get so frustrated with people today when they voice their short-sighted opinions of the Iraq war and Bush administration. This is a good truth to remember... "They will have their say and they will go downstream like bubbles; but the work you have done will remain for the ages". In the years to come we will see the good brought about and the evil prevented by the Bush administration... and the opponents will be forgotten.  November 16, 1906 - "Why, gentlemen, there never was a great feat done yet that there were not some men evil enough, small enough, or foolish enough, to wish to try to interfere with it and to sneer at those who are actually doing the work.  From time to time, little men will come along to find fault with what you have done; to say that something could have been done better; that there has been some mistake, some shortcoming; that things are not really managed in the best of all possible manners, in the best of all possible worlds.   They will have their say and they will go downstream like bubbles; they will vanish; but the work you have done will remain for the ages.  It is the man who does the job who counts, not the little scolding critic who thinks how it ought to have been done."  --Theodore Roosevelt 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Gaming PC Makers Take Aim at Lucrative Niche   Very cool. This is a business I'd love to pursue. Be creative, hands-on, and technical all at the same time. I've started a business plan and I can see why companies like Dell and HP are pursuing it. We'll see what the future holds. Right now I don't think it's stable enough, but maybe if I had some stable income with freedom this is something I would explore.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Memorial Day 2004  Ah, a good day and a good story. Where would America be without the people that dared to give their lives for what they believed in. We owe these people the freedom that we enjoy today. The freedom to write this post and not have to worry about what other people think, much less worry for my life. Too many people today whine and complain about what we are doing in Iraq, but that's all they ever do, no action. Hopefully today they remember, stop complaining and do something about it.  We need more people like  urlLink Nathan Hale  and those would would actually stand behind words like, "I do not agree with a word you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it. --Voltaire"
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw an advertisement while I was watching VH1. It was about how AIDS and HIV was an epidemic that we had to do something about. There has been so much money and so much press dedicated to how to prevent this disease when the solution is so simple. Stop spreading it people!  Not to be insensitive, HIV is a terrible, horrible thing. I wouldn't wish it on anyone. However seeing the ad did make me think. The ad mentioned how 20+ million people had died from HIV, I assume it was placed in there for shock value. It failed to shock me. Only because I know that 41+ million people have died because they have been aborted.  Why should we worry about this disease called HIV when we are killing ourselves without the need for any disease at double the rate? Think about it, which is the worse epidemic???   urlLink AIDS.com: AIDS/HIV Facts    urlLink US Abortions Statistics  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently the company I work for,  urlLink StudioNorth  lost one of it's best developers, John Daharsh, to Colorado. That's the third developer in my career I've lost to that stinkin' state. I guess it's only a matter of time before all developers either migrate to CO or CA. We'll see how long it takes me to get to one or the other.  In John's career at  urlLink StudioNorth  he has taken ownership of many large name clients like  urlLink BP ,  urlLink Hewitt , and  urlLink Cardinal Health . His last project at the Studio was the site you now see when you visit the  urlLink Addison Public Library . He will be missed.  Anyway, if you are looking for an excellent independent web developer/designer give  urlLink John  a  urlLink buzz . Otherwise check out  urlLink StudioNorth .
     
    
</post>


</Blog>