<Blog>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       check this out>>  urlLink stickdeath.com  lots of vulgar language :)  or how bout my favourite game website  urlLink miniclip.com  lots of game   try hip hop website why don't you become a member of it  urlLink b-boys.com   rest of the web not interested only in this or maybe try playin diablo2 fun siah    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Usher  Linkin Park Limp Bizkit NSyNC Jay-Z Backstreet Boys Westlife Five.... some more donno eh  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       During June holidays the school have a sec2 camp...at first it was very very boring, not interested at it. I'm going to tell a stories what happen when i was in camp.Its somthing like a diary but i really miss it feel like going again.  Day 1  Tuesday/May/2004     Haha just started getting the list of camp what to bring and all those rules for the camp.The teacher in charge was Mr Desmond Eng and Mr Mahmood.They will tell what to bring and all those thing what to there.   Day 2  Thursday/May/2004     Just started packing up the bag for the camp on Satuday,finding out what clothes or anything to bring.Steven is one of the experince in camp i always call him.It was so tired pack bag...last day which is Friday must be ready before Saturday early morning.  Day 3  Saturday/May/2004       First day of camp was so damm boring..feeling like going home even not in the camp centre it was in school we get to know the student leader first then we play ice breaker.Just to know the friends which I don't know.The group is called 'Panther C'soon after that we wait till the bus come to the school to bring us to the camp.It is called somthin adventure camp can't remember what is it.       First day we went to the hall to learn the school cheers and my group cheers.After that we went to the domitories which they called it a bunk, a place where we sleep.So first activity was one of the low element.We have to do all the activity which is Broken Bridge and some more...I only do the broken bridge cause i was force i hide the rest of the element. Then its lunch time we had papadom think so which is an indian food, no using fork and spoon only using hand.       Soon after that there is another activity which is can't remember anymore but i only know before dinner there is an activity to paint a paper which everybody must participate,we have to try to fill all the papers with colours and in the end it was a mess.Our track pants have some stain and the shirt haha and some more what Zulaiha want of my closest friend which is a stundent leader disturb sial...my PE shirt dirty lucky not all wait go back mother scold haha...then after that we have our dinner can't remember what i have...soon after that we go for the night walk at the park.So damm boring walk walk at night see nothing at the park soon after that go back to the camp.So tired then we have to do a reflection in the hall.          Then after the reflection we have our snack which we eat bread and hot milo.The hot milo so hot never drink like that before than after that it is bed time.After he have bathe i see my friend which is Rasrizan at the next room...we went to the canteen to drink milo together then i saw Zulaiha again haha...so nearly 12:30 am time to sleep in the room we went back to the room we sleep peacefully untill the next day...  Day 4 Sunday/May/2004      Early morning i wake up around 5am but i see some people walking to the toilet but i think it still early i went back to sleep then wake up at 5:30 and i think its better to go and bathe before i have to rush and the toilet have many people.Then we went to the Hall to do the morning exercise so hard...haven't even have breakfast must run and do push up and sits up....after that we went for breakfast we have mee and I only do one of the activity on Sunday.     Rock climbing wahh...first time im doing it,when i was pri5 i run away hide from all the teachers but this time cannot run away. So bored till lunch time eat rice with chopstick...i don even know how to eat rice with chopstick...before dinner time the art that we do on Saturday must cut out the favourite part which i like...then tell why i choose this colour...Dinner we have porridge wahh!! so delicious..then we went for the camp fire...all the house group must at least act...so bored untill the teachers have to do the banana dance...so nice seh...especially Mr Tony Fernadenz so cute. then snack we have half cake for snack with hot milo....time to bathe only 1 hour before lights out we must also do the reflection before the snack and bathing time...quite long the reflections on Sunday was the tiring day of the rest.    Day 5 Monday/May/2004     In the early morning i wake up same time 5:30am go and bath as usual then the morning exercise so tiring then the previous one...during breakfast we have Nasi Lemak so delicious....first time the camp give good food.Then we do the last activity which is the challenging pole 2 i was afraid of height but i don't know how i can do it...so scary like want to commit suicide.then we have lunch which is the last meal before we go back to school.Before boarding the bus we say goodbye to the student leader..haha thats it for the sec2 camp                                       THE END   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hakim Aliff Effendi Ruzaini Fakruh Salahudin... some more can't remember   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>