<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We didn't do much, we just talked about costumes and stage sets and lighting and stuff. We came to no real conclusion.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This went better, Mr Piercy was there. It was quite funny. We did a lot on a bit where Jenny has to shoot a 'gun' around, but everyone does it now, and Jo dies and falls over, and then I catch her, and realise it's a guy (the character), and then drop her (not too far).  I think the rehearsal went well.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This went badly. When everyone had finished eating and we started doing stuff, everyone couldn't really be bothered to do anything. I think it was everyone's fault, not just one person.  Me and Alice left.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not much to say, we practised through the play. Kim and Jo did their bit as well. It went OK.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Who was present:  Everyone execept Kim and Laura. Kim was seeing her man, and it was Laura's cousin's birthday.  We went through the scene again, Kayley spoke Laura's lines, and Kim is Donald Duck so we just didn't do that bit.  We decided that instead of Raymond being about the "stand on his head", he can now "stand on one leg". What a hero.  Uh, yeah, we just made it better, and we could make as much noise as we wanted. The bliss of it all...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Who was present:  Uh... Me, Alice, Jenny, Kayley, Laura, Jo, and I can't remember whether Kim was. I think so...  We just went through the play again. It's slowly coming into shape.  Kim and Jo went through their bit too.  We worked on the fight scene, to make it more realistic/better, and then the savvy exam officer with the hands-free walkie-talkie earpeice came in and told us off, "Offence ref.2342, 'Decibel count excessive of limits'".  Poor us.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Who was present:  Everyone  We just went through the play, not the bit with just Donald Duck and Peter, but the rest of it. We half acted it, but with scripts. It went quite well, I don't have anything much the report about it though. Not sure if I can remember a whole lot >_ 

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, first entry...  I'll say who is playing who first, if I can remember...  Me:  John  Alice:  Willie  Jenny:  Raymond  Jo:  Peter  Kim:  Donald Duck  Laura:  Angela  Kayley:  Audrey  We had an in-lesson rehearsal type thing today.  Members Present:  Me, Alice, Laura, Jenny and Jo.  We only had half an hour, not a full lesson.  All we did was half-read through the script, doing our best to remember the lines. I can sort of remember mine, at least at the beginning, which I'm more familiar with.  Oh yeah and we practised the bit where there are two different groups of people counting to 100 at different paces, which seems to me to be the hardest part of it to look realistic. You have to time it just right.  Nothing more to say.
     

    
</post>



</Blog>