<Blog>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here it goes.. Haven't been updating my blog for several days le.. Though added a poem yesterday.. which was quite insignificant.. But its meaningful though.. Well, woke up at 615 this morning(the usual school day time) and was quite sleepy.. Perhaps had a late night ehz? Well, had a conference with weixian and joycelyn for two and a half hours according to weixian.. It was fun and interesting though.. Weixian played the guitar at 1st, then joycelyn took out hers to play as well.. As I don't have a guitar and didn't know how to play, I became the audience haha.. Joycelyn sang too and her voice was very sweet.. And well if ya had read weixian's blog, you would know that something had happened.. Well, there are obstacles in our life which are meant to be overcomed and we grow and learn from them.. So we should just take things in our own stride.. and be happy always(though it may seem impossible).. However, no harm trying it as well right? Why torment yourself when you can enjoy yourself instead? These philosophies may seem too exaggerated, but it can be attained.. though not always.. Well, today stayed back after school to do my "O" levels art final piece as the deadline is closing in soon.. And oh yeah.. weiqiang today don't know why came to my school and joined me in the art room.. haha but there was amyrul and me in my class and the rest were sec 4s.. Yeah.. and after that went back home, ate my dinner.. Then around 8+ weixian came to my house use com bahx.. Use until 10pm den we go for our usual running and exercise.. haha must maintain and be constant.. if not waste our previous efforts le.. hehe.. overall quite a jubilant day today for me bahx.. nothing bad happened.. :) haha oh well, good night and rest.. my soul mate.. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am a rose, you are my thorns,
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Strangely, things have been going on smoothly for me today.. Well, lets beat around the bush again.. Start from the morning ok? You have no choice anyway :P Hmm.. woke up earlier den usual by 15 minutes.. yeah.. cos my younger brother need to go school early.. so implicate until my sleep also sia.. haha but whats a 15 minutes sleep compared to exceptionally good luck today? My dad drove me and weixian(he go see see) to northland early in the morning.. Well, reach school bout.. ehz.. 650 a.m. bahz.. There was only a handful of students seated on the parade ground.. well.. and out of the few,    it seems to be.. fate?  Our uniform groups' standards getting lower nowadays ehz? See them march hor.. dun wan to say la haha.. Then had the lame singing session which the student leaders showed their imcompentency, cannot control us and make us sing.. After that the upper sec (including me) was supposed to go to the field and be audience to some telematch.. Never let me play I dun wan see lehx.. :P So me, amyrul, suresh, christopher and osc went to the art room.. But unfortunately only me and amyrul can enter, as we are the art students whereas they are not.. Well, too bad then.. they have to bear with the boring show.. haha.. Today at art room so few people, initially me and amyrul only.. den some sec 4 girls came, followed by salini and pavitra.. Then I did some of my art bahz.. haha but quite lazy..   And   the presence of.. was not available..   10 a.m. John, our monitor came up and gave us our souvenirs, which was a water bottle larhz.. haha.. Then osc came to my house with me and changed for the lunch.. Hmm what lunch? wait la.. relax.. :P Our former chinese teacher last year wants to treat us(last year 4nb chinese students) to Seoul Garden at Marina :) Ate quite some food there, and the group, 14 of us dicussed where to go next.. haha our teacher went back, well she needed to rest i guess, as she is pregnant.. haha congrats to her.. Then out group sorta splited up.. I went with weixian, bingru, pengxiong and siangcher.. Went to Cine Leisure and played the arcade for awhile.. After that went play 1 hour of lan game at duno what shop la.. haha.. Hmm the game i played, named "Sacred" quite nice lehz.. haha maybe go buy, cos still have some popular vouchers left.. But I wonder whether they have this game.. Well, just wait and see bahz.. Then bingru came to my house, burn song lorz.. and put picture at his friendster la.. haha.. Then he go home, i accompany him wait for bus lehz.. see I sho good 1 :P Hmm.. duno why lehz.. The hatred and fury seemed to subsidised a lot..    Perhaps my stained soul have been cleansed, and the dying flame in me relighted.. by her..  Wah.. what am I saying? I don't even know why.. haha.. Well.. anyway, good night my lonesome diary.. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, had a long day today.. the usual lessons passed slowly till a math mock test.. Then chinese lesson we watched a video.. After that went to canteen had something with christopher to substain my greedy stomach.. Went to the gents, washed my face and went back to class for the english paper 1 prep exam lorz.. Lasted 1.5 hrs.. slept for 15mins in the exam bahx.. cos finish before the time given mahz.. Then test finish le go art room do my "O" level de art coursework lorz.. + final piece.. Stayed there until 6+ bahx.. Hmm.. actually stay there also quite fun.. haha guess why? Nahx.. keep you in suspense lehx :P Hmm.. den after tat go home lorz.. Weird.. today go home not sleepy lehx.. instead more perked up sia.. Last few days so sleepy sia.. Cos i every night so late sleep de.. Almost every night go running with weixian.. train for ns mahz.. haha but sometimes lazy or busy never run lorz.. Tonight dunno got run anot.. About time le.. our run starts at 10pm de mahz.. haha.. Well anyway.. sorta great day today.. but don't quite get the reason why lehz.. haha.. Okie bahz.. Good night :) 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been burying myself into all sorts of activities going on.. Trying to forget.. But my efforts were in vain.. Well, thats the consequence.. and life still goes on.. All I could do now is to give her my regards and wish her the best.. We have to learn to let go sometimes, though it may inflict pain on ourselves.. Thats the way of life.. My previous entries were deleted.. for my new lease of life perhaps.. I couldn't even fathom my own thoughts sometimes, which may seem a little too distorted.. The winds of change do alter us.. and I have changed too.. Nobody is perfect, though perfection is wonderful.. So, we have to live with what we got, and cherish them well.. I used to take things lightly and I was able to forgive and forget easily.. But perhaps the revolving of the universe have evolved me.. Revenge is sweet, and I would like to taste it.. He incurred my wrath and now he shall face the dreadful consequences.. However, I do forgive and forget, depends on who that person is.. and the degree of his wrongdoing.. Well, 1st post since I deleted my entries.. Fall into deep slumber, my confiding soul.. 
    
</post>


</Blog>