<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dont feel well @ all today, feeling sick & cant stop going the loo (TMI). Havnt had much sleep either coz of my stomach :-( Also got told last night that my dog might be put down, just thinkin about it Im fillin up :'( He's only just over 1 years old & he's dyin, he's livin with my mum & bro's & my bro's think it's better if he gets put down, put him out of his misery. Even tho I shout @ him I love him to bits, when he got back from the vet's last week I nearly cried coz he was still tryin to wake up from the anasthetic, fallin over & droolin everywhere. He's only a baby really, he shouldnt be like this :-(
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I spent the weekend with my lovely gf but she had to go home on Sunday :-( Sometimes I feel Im horrible tho towards her coz Im a moody cow, probably coz its that time of the month but then again Im a moody cow anyway. I felt like I was constantly havin a go or tellin her not to do stuff, like a bloody mum or somethin, god knows how she's gona cope with me when she moves here!! The weekend was lovely tho, as long as I get to spend time with her I dont care. Baby I love u & Im so happy ur my fiancee xxxx   Im really lookin forward to August tho coz Im gona see her 3 times that month, normally we only see each other every 4-6 weeks :-( So August will be gr8 :-) Lookin forward to Manc Pride, havnt been before & also Brighton Pride, gona meet people I havnt met yet @ both places so be gr8 :-) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I cant wait til Friday, my gf is coming up from Croydon (its been too long since I saw her).  We'v been together nearly 6 months & we'r still goin strong, I never thought it could last but it has :-) I cant wait til we'r together properly & livin together. This must sound horrible & mushy but I dont care, it's all good for me & lways will be while Im with my beautiful future wife 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Went out last night with my m8 & her m8 & my poor body is shoutin @ me now :( I can tell I havnt danced for a while coz now my poor old bones are achin & screamin @ me. Think I'll be restin tonight before I go out tomorrow night :D Had a great night tho, met people from work as well so we all stayed together. Im surprised I didnt get drunk really the amount of alcohol I drank speshly shots but Im glad I didnt have a hangover wouldnt have been able to cope with it today otherwise!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dont know why but today I feel really teary, maybe its coz its comin close to the "time of the month". Then again I get like this even when its not & its gettin on my nerves. Im sittin in the office wantin to cry, think I should smack myself for a bit might stop me from cryin anyway. I remember when I used to feel like this & I would hurt myself, get the razor & jus cut away until I felt better but now Im happy to say I dont do that any more :-) But there are times when I feel so close to doin it but I wont let myself. I wish I could get rid of these feelings coz its makin me feel low, sometimes I think Im beeter off without my gf that she deserves someone who isnt as moody as me or gets the way I do a lot. It takes me ages to get out of this & I hope I'll be feelin better by next week when the gf is here for the weekend.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Im so glad its Friday today, Im so tired. Its been a long time were Iv actually been busy in work, makes a change I normally dont work LOL :-)  As well as work I did some volunteer work the other day, bein a steward in Southport for the yearly outin for young people with disabilities. Didnt realise it would be so tirin then as soon as we got back I had to go str8 to my other job. My aunt said I was snorin that night, went bright red when she took the piss *blush*  Had a gr8 day yesterday, took a group of young women out for an activity day. Did climbin & in the afternoon did rafty buildin, had a laugh & we (the workers) sank their rafts :-)  Now Friday is here so cant wait to go home. My bro's 21st tomoro so should be a good day :-)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today the weather is gorgeous & Im stuck in work like everyone else, whoever invented work should be shot!!!!  Not sure if it's the weather but Im feelin bit funny today. Keep think about me & g/f & how things will be. She's movin to Liverpool to be with me but Im scared in case it all goes wrong, never know til I try I know but I cant help thinkin (probably why my head hurts)  Cant write much am in work so hopefully write more next time
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the first time Iv ever done one of these, thought it would be good to get things out for myself. Be interestin to see what I put anyway
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know yesterday I was in a great mood, feeling good & takin the piss outa my boss but things just change so quickly dont they? On my way to my other job last night when my aunt called me to tell me my mum had had a huge panic attack &amp; that my mum was cryin for me. I'm such a horrible person coz I didnt want to go see her & I didnt feel anythin when my aunt told me about my mum. I have no feelings for my mum &amp; I dont think I ever will, I cant stand bein near her. When I got to her house I had to sit next to her, she was clearly upset but I just couldnt be bothered but I had to put my arm around her & she just clung to me like a little child. I cant be doin with her cryin coz when I hugged her I had no feelings there for her, I hate bein her daughter, she deserves better than me. She's goin the docs this mornin, my aunt is takin her but my aunt was waitin for me to ask about my mum so I just said to her to call me later to let me know what happened. How can anyone have no feelings for her mother? I just cant let go of what happened years ago &amp; it'll always be there with me, I never thought I could dislike someone so much especially my mum!!!!   I also hate it when I feel like shit, it makes me feel worse today coz of what Im like with HER. I didnt want to come into work today, took me ages to get out of bed, I need to go away somewhere get away from it all. I need space &amp; I cant get it, if I had the money I'd go away. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I just had a lovely weekend with the wife, she came on Friday &amp; went home on the Monday. The only downside was that she had to do a lot of drivin thru the weekend, Iv so gota pass my test that way we can both take turns. She was so tired (((((((((((((baby))))))))))))    &nbsp;  Not gona see her now til 6th August for Brighton Pride, I hate not see'in&nbsp; her for ages gets on my nerves but it'll be nice for when we r together, love u baby xxxxxxxx    &nbsp;  God Im all soppy today, must be the hormones or somethin!!!!  
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>