<Blog>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night I went to go watch a friend of mine from my writing workshop read at the  urlLink KGB bar .  Both this friend of mine and the other woman she read with (originally from Trinidad; see: coolest accent ever) are incredibly talented, and it was a joy to sit and listen to them and drink some Rolling Rock.  We also met up with another friend of ours from the workshop who, randomly enough, works in the field of horseracing.  For the months of July and August, he will be living in  urlLink Saratoga Springs , which is, of course, the mecca of horseracing in the US.  Because there are suspicions of terrorist attacks on the Republican convention (which takes place right next to my 54-story building, built right over Penn Station), I will be taking the first week of August off.  Our friend invited us to come stay with him for a few days and live it up in Saratoga, and so that's just what we're doing!  Apparently there are great bars there and I've never been to a horse race before, so I'm excited to see what it's all about.  As we walked out of the bar, some British bloke came up to my friend and I and just started jabbering away, arms clasped tightly around our shoulders, about this bar that he works at and about London and George W. and though clearly drunk, he was, I admit, entirely amusing. (You can't get too annoyed with someone who has a British accent.)  Anyway, there were a few other people with us at the time, one of whom tried to join in the conversation, at which point one of my friend's friends yelled, "Hey! Get your own British person!"  Which made me think, 'Hey, if I could have my own British person, who would I choose?' And I think the answer would have to be  urlLink Rupert Grint .  That's right, little Ron Weasley - and I'd just walk around with him and tell everyone he was my little brother, cute as a button, even when he's burping up giant slugs.  The coolest thing is that I actually have a picture of him.  I was at the premiere of the first Harry Potter movie (which is called Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone in Britain) at the  urlLink Leicester Square Odeon  and got to watch all the cute little Hogwarts students tasting their first slice of fame.  I couldn't have cared less about the Potter series at that point, but I had the sense, even then, that I was in the midst of greatness.  Or maybe it was just because Cher was there.  Just joshing folks.  Although Cher really was there, and she's a pretty scary lady.  Tyronne Biggums and I have just decided to go to Amsterdam.  Aforementioned friend who read at the bar last night will be going to the U. of Sussex next year and we will be visiting her and then the three of us will be flying off to the land of milk and honey.  (And by milk and honey, I mean  urlLink milk  and  urlLink honey .)  Anyway, I'm excited.  I'm also excited because tonite is the Filberg Edelweiss summer party at the  urlLink Intrepid Museum .  And no function in the field of law would be complete without an open bar, a palm reader, face painting and sand art.  Look out folks, this one should be a doozie.  See: Natalie Wood.  Ouch, keep the gloves up Sister.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sue-- I know you work in production stuff but I don't know exactly what it is you do; in any case, i just had a presentation to our company from On The Scene Productions, Inc. and they are responsible for broadcast publicity, basically.  they do a ton of stuff, and I grabbed some info,in case you are still wanting a full time job.  it sounds really interesting, they are really well known and respected in the industry--my old agency used them, they're nationwide, blah blah.  They do projects for major music bands and labels; sports; movies, soundtracks, etc.  their client list is really impressive.  thought u might be interested.  if so, www.onthescene.com may give you more info.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.thepetitionsite.com/takeaction/679035073  I stumbled across this on a live journal community yesterday and thought you peoples would be interested in signing and passing it along.        My allergies are so SHITTY today!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has come to my all-too-fleeting attention that a 9 to 5 job just can't suit me for the rest of my working days.  I've only been in the occupational alt world since late august, and already i'm about to tear my hair out.  well, at least if i was hairless, i could plead illness and somehow wiggle my way out of working like a proletariat slave.   i welcome and encourage any ideas to get me out of this slump!  the only jobs that don't necessarily follow a 9-5 schedule (that i can think of) are stripping, waiting tables and construction.  I'm too fat, too elitist and too lazy to do any of those.  so help!  SOS...  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to say, I heard one of the funniest jokes today.    What's the difference between and onion and a hooker? Noone cries when a hooker is cut up.  hahaha.  sick sick sick sick, i know.  but damn if that isn't funny.  kids, there's something you might not know about me.  i smoke rocks.  that's right,  urlLink tyronne  smokes rocks.  but a word to the wise:  it's impossible to sleep when you high on crack.  you benedict arnolds, you!    i've said it before, and i'll say it again.  "Remember what the Bible says: He who is without sin, cast the first rock. And I shall smoketh it."
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I broke it off with my minion-of-the-Anti-Christ boyfriend.  I actually thought that I'd be wallowing navel deep in emotional diarrhea at this point, but I think what I feel is more along the lines of relief, freedom and social prowess.  I have Tyronne Biggums (my beautiful roomie) and Don Fiedler to thank for pre-gametime pep talks, locker room ass-smacking and the like.  I wouldn't have had the guts to end the relationship without their capacity for rational thought and logical reasoning.  Although  urlLink Xanax  and  urlLink Captain and Cokes  (made with love by Tyronne) definitely helped ease the raw physical and emotional pain.   urlLink And just for a giggle... 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find it immediately necessary to give props to my girl for breaking free from the ties that bound her!  While Xanax and Captin make for tasty treats, there's nothing more refreshing than self-empowerment.    Now, let the real celebration begin!  We shall overcome and overpower men with our sexual prowess.  I think that perhaps the following lines may adapt to our situation quite well.  Let's give them a go, shall we?!  * If you were a booger I'd pick you first. * Roses are red, violets are blue, I have warts, so will you.  * I'd suck a fart out of your ass and hold it like a bong hit. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WARNING: I have had nitrus today because I got two cavities filled but an hour ago. DO NOT, I repeat, DO NOT ask me for money that I owe you because I will be extremely confused although it may make for an amusing story. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Speaking of normal foods in the context of sex, one of the restaurants my firm orders from has some sexually explicit sounding lunch sandwiches, i.e. "The Cockrobin" and "The Porker Corker."  Now, "The Cockrobin" is pretty much just a chicken sandwich, which I of course had to order just so I could say I ate a Cockrobin.  But "The Porker Corker" is actually made with sausage, thus living up to its disturbing euphemism.  However, the term "porker corker" makes me think of shoving something specific up one (or two) specific orifices, and let's face it, while I'm not entirely adverse to the "shoving" I refer to, I am rather adverse to eating something thats name implies the aformentioned shoving.  That's all I'm trying to say.  In other news, Happy Birthday to my Filberg Edelweiss partner-in-crime,  urlLink Don Fiedler !  Along with myself, Don is the co-founder of " urlLink Flingers " and part-time lounge singer, with such hits as "Mandy (You Came and You Gave Me a Boner)" and "Penis Colossus."  Happy 25th Don, and eat a dick.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came to the disturbing conclusion today that novelty mints shaped like penises should not have faces on them. It just makes it that much weirder! Who was in that boardroom meeting and thought that would be a good idea??? TELL ME!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently became aware that I am part Norwish.  My grandmother--god rest her soul--hails from the great country of Norway, making me 1/10 Norwish.  Now, I understand that "norwish" isn't NECESSARILY the correct term, but I think it makes a hell of a lot more sense than "norwegian."  I mean, it should definitely follow the UK pattern that has already been established...for example, britISH, irISH, scottISH, and so forth.    "what about the '--an' souding suffixes" you might be axkin.  and my answer is this: i dont know and i don't care.  as far as i'm concerned, Norwish tops the nationality-suffix cake.  one day, the vocabulary will change, thanks to my invention.    which brings me to another point.  that being, my intelligence.  my genius IQ should make others falter in my presence.  and it does.  let's face it--most people are stupid, when compared to me, and of course, my lovely roomate.  so please, people!  pick up a book!  corinne and i can only take so much stupidity each day.  that is all.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to Rewind and Quicksand.  This blog is brought to you in part by  urlLink Slack LaLane  and utter boredom at the law firm of Filberg Edelweiss.  Some jackass in the IT department must have just discovered my internet freedom to shop, play games, and repeatedly view the Teen Girl Squad cartoons at HomestarRunner.com.  I'm blocked from everything remotely interesting except between the hours of 12-2.  (Those bastards must have missed the Nine West site though, muah ha ha ha!)  Joining me shortly will be an elite handful of some Freaky McNerd cronies, with possible guest appearances by my officemate,  urlLink Don Fiedler .  Thanks for playing, and go fuck yourself.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>