<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No, not really :) I had a good day today. The day went by very quickly. Maybe that was because I slept until 4pm. I woke up, looked at the clock and said "Holy crap!! I have to be at rehearsal in 3 hours." I've never slept that late before without having been awake until 8am in the morning(which I've done many times before :). It's probably the reason why I'm awake now :) Anyway, rehearsal was great. We were supposed to run all the blocking for Act 1 but only got through the first scene because we were polishing everything. It's looking great. Ro and I have done a good job so far, if I do say so myself :) After rehearsal, I hung out with Ro and we watched a couple episodes of "Dead Like Me", which is an awesome show. I watched it a couple of weeks ago on Showtime On Demand and I told Ro "You so will love this show. You've got to watch it." Do I have good taste or what? Of course, it's easy for Ro to like something. He's a loser!!! I'm writing all this because I know he's going to read it :p Anyway, I have to get up in 4 1/2 hours so I'm heading for bed. Ben Folds in 17 hours. Report after the concert tomorrow!!!!!! Yes!!!!!! More later..........
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tonight I went with my family to my dad's cousin's house. We went to do some visiting and some swimming. The water was too cold for me which sucks because I wanted to try out my new bathing suit. Ah, well.  My niece, Shaylee, went into the pool for the first time. She loved it. She had an absolute blast. We had a good time. Grilled some burgers, listened to her husband talk about Farenheit 9/11, recalled good old times with my sister. I had a good time but then I started thinking about things that have been getting me down lately and I kind of brought myself down, so I called it a early night. I came home and watched Road Rules and then Seven Brides for Seven Brothers. I really think I'm getting better at picking myself up when I'm down. I was watching RR and started feeling better right away. Either that or I'm just getting over being hurt....finally. It only took me a month after the fact to start getting better. That's something my sister and I were talking about. She said to me "f your ex was here, he'd probably be sitting next to you instead of being with the guys talking about that movie because it would still be early in the relationship. What, like a month and a half, right?" . "Yes" I told her. "Can we drop it please? It's already hard enough for me without you bringing it up." I've figured it out with the help of my sister that since I'm not sure exactly what ended the whole thing, that is the reason I've been so down. I've just been racking my brain with what I could have done wrong. It doesn't help the fact that everyone I know still asks me about him and says that(even though we dated for like three weeks) we were a cute couple and seemed to be happy together. The one thing that kills me is when people who think they're being helpful say "You're both so sad lately, ever since you decided to not see each other anymore."  Okay people. Not my decision. Totally his. I just didn't want to ruin any fragment of feeling he might have for me by being a bitch. I have a feeling I was, though. I also feel that all my stress from theatre stuff didn't help it any either. He probably won't talk to me again. I'm dealing with it. I know now that he just didn't feel the same about the relationship situation as I did. It's a part of life. We deal with the cards we're dealt. I know that, hopefully , in a few months, I'll be able to watch Family Guy, look at the sofas at the theatre, and sit on Ro's futon without feeling sad. I digress. If I don't get better, I'm moving to Boston to live with my dad's family :) Move away and on from everything. I'm talking about this because it's better out than in. On a happier note, Ben Folds on Wed!!!!!!! Hooray!!!!  More later!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I've been offline for over a week because our computer had several viruses on it. Being the lazy, busy person I am, I had no time to find a computer to do anything on. I am now typing on our brand new computer. I was told that I could have the old one if we can get it cleaned up and running again. Some weird, kind of sad news: I have been diagnosed with having depression. I'm not all that surprised. I've been rundown lately and not in the mood for much of anything. My parents are concerned about me being like this. There are certain things that would perk me up but alas, I won't be receiving my wish anytime soon. I knew there was something wrong when I was watching Adam Sandler movies last week and not laughing at all. Well, that's not entirely true. I watched Billy Madison(my favorite) and laughed my ass off. I've never watched that movie with anyone else, just by myself. There are only a few people that are allowed to watch that movie with me. They can probably guess who they are, but I won't reveal names :P Anyway, the depression thing. Even theatre hasn't picked me up. Cuckoo's Nest opened on Friday. I got depressed thinking that I won't get any flowers during this show because I never get flowers from anybody. Not even when I was directing Birdie last year. Silly things like that get me near tears. I was out with my family and we were talking about going to my cousin's house to visit and use the pool tomorrow and I was sad because I'm odd man out again, as I always am. My sister and her boyfriend, Mom and Dad, the baby and the dog. And me, by myself. Things like that are so stupid, I can't believe they make me upset. I've been thinking about getting away for a while but I can't because of my committments to rehearsal for Stage Door and then performances for Cuckoo's Nest. I would go somewhere quiet with the one person who means a lot to me, but, of course, I don't even have that anymore.... See, I depress myself and now others. Argh!!!! :) Sorry for being this way. I think a lot of events have led up to me being this way. Running myself ragged with Ride The Winds, board stuff, having been hurt by so many people in the past three months, being hurt by someone I didn't think would hurt me, having my heart broken not once but twice in four months.....So many things. People tell me that I have to move up and on. Well, I would love to be able to freeze my feelings but it's not possible. As I told someone last week who also dealing with a lot of crap "Well, at least the person you care about is still there to listen. And you have someone willing to love you and listen no matter what".  I hate to admit it but it's true. My friends love me but they are so tired of my crap, they've stopped listening. I have no one who cares enough to listen. I hopefully can go see a therapist to help me with deal with everything. No, I'm not suicidal. My friends seem to think I'll be back to my normal self when I'm done being hung up on things. My outlook on life has changed so much. I don't think I'll ever be the wonderful person I was a year ago. I meet people now who think I'm crazy bitch and I think to myself "I would love for them to have met me last year when my life made sense." Well, I'm off to bed. I'm not crazy, I swear. Just a little blue...... but then, who isn't, once in a while? :) More later.........
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Shaylster's 1st chocolate cake. We're not sure she liked it :)
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Ride The Winds cast
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, with nothing to do since my best friend ditched me, I stayed home tonight and watched the rest of "Say Anything". I love this movie and not just because it has John Cusack :) I think the movie tells a wonderful story about how love will hit you when you're not expecting it. It also shows how love can conquer all and how it's always nice to have someone there to support you when everything blows up in your face. Every girl should have a boyfriend like Lloyd Dobler. He's persistent and doesn't give up easily in the pursuit of love..... Why aren't there more men like him? :) I was hoping I had someone like him but I was sadly mistaken. Que sera, sera. More later.........  P.S. I MISS YOU!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, lately, I've been on a Hoobastank kick. Their music is sooo awesome. The words are heartfelt. You can really hear his pain and joy in every word he sings. Plus, right now, the songs express how I feel recently. Hopefully, some people can take hints from that. On another note, our first rehearsal for Stage Door went very well. Our cast is amazing and they will all be so much fun to work with. Cuckoo's Nest is going well also. Tonight Ro was bitching at me onstage about my entrance in the beginning of the 2nd act. "Why are you coming in? What's your purpose?" I told him to leave me alone and that I was coming to work. Kathe backed me up on that one. After a few minutes, Ro was his normally, sort of sane person. "What's happening, hot stuff?" Yada, yada, yada :) Dodgeball(the movie) tomorrow night, I hope....... More later.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My family at my parents' 25th anniversary party!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Shaylster, me,and Mickey!!! I look like crap!!! Hey, that's on like 4 hours of sleep!!!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Can't sleep again so I ended up watching Punch Drunk Love which was a very interesting movie. I love Adam Sandler and he never ceases to amaze me with the characters he plays. So right now, I'm on an Adam Sandler kick. I'm finding which of his movies I haven't seen and setting out to see them. The only ones I haven't seen are: Going Overboard, Airheads, Bulletproof, Little Nicky, and Eight Crazy Nights. Yes, I've seen all the others. I own most of them with the exception of Big Daddy, The Waterboy, and 50 First Dates. The last one I'm getting soon. It's my favorite AS movie so far. I say that about all his new movies though. They continually get better. I have to watch all of Big Daddy and The Waterboy and determine whether I want to buy them. Word of advice to anyone: Check out "Mixed Nuts". It's one of his earlier movies. It actually stars Steve Martin but he's in it and he's hilarious. It's one of my all time favorite movies. Goodness, I must be really tired. I keep going on about Adam Sandler :) Well, he is good........ More later!!!!  P.S. I STILL MISS YOU :p
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here it is, 4 o' clock in the fricking morning and I can't get to sleep. Good lord, someone hit me over the head with a frying pan, please :) In my insomnia, I put all my laundry away and watched 'Love, Actually' which was actually very good and very cute and oh so sweet in some places. Today I had my niece's birthday party which I was late to since I didn't get to sleep until 6:30 am yesterday(Sunday morning). It was fun especially for the baby. The party was at a park so we played on the playground, swung on the swings, and seed on the sawed. I, seriously, don't know what I just said :) It was great. I got some pictures with my sweetie of a niece, Shaylee, who is 1 year old today(June 14th). That's all I did. Pretty boring day. I was supposed to go to a line run but I didn't since it wasn't mandatory. I've been at the theatre a lot lately and will continue to be there much, much more in the two weeks to come, since I have Cuckoo's Nest and Stage Door rehearsals to handle. Plus, I found out that I might have to handle our first rehearsal by myself on Wednesday if Cuckoo's Nest isn't halfway decent tomorrow night. If we're not so good, we have rehearsal on Wednesday and Kathe needs Ro since he's the lead. Oh, well. If I have to run it myself, I can do it. I've directed before. Piece of cake....... I think :) Now, I'm tired. The plumber is coming to fix our sink in like 4 hours. Drat!!! No sleep til Brooklyn, I guess :) More later...... Happy Birthday to the Shaylster!!!!! 
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Everything is a blur to me. All I know is that I had a lot of fun tonight. It kills me because I tattled on Mark for drinking during intermission and I was drinking with him after we left Silver Diner. I saw my friend Steve tonight. Haven't seen him since about a month ago. Some people thought he was my boyfriend because he was super friendly with me. No way. I love Steve but not like that. It would take a lot more for me to love someone like that. I hope Martin got home okay, as well as Mark and Ryan. I had an awesome time. Lot of fun, lots of laughs. I wish I had known how much fun Martin and Mark were like two weeks ago. We could have done this sooner :) More later........
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I can't think of titles so I'll jsut use random words. I decided insanity would be a good word because of "Cuckoo's Nest". Friday night it was and our second to last performance of RTW. Afterwards, we went to Rocky Run in Columbia. I was doing good until "he" walked in. He had said he was coming but it was like an hour after we got there, I figured he wasn't coming. My heart jumped in my throat, as it normally does. It's silly for me to feel like that when 6 weeks ago I thought it was a bad idea to get involved with him. I should have listened to my gut instinct but I felt something special about him, so I gave him a chance. Where does it leave me? He's fine and happy-go-lucky and I'm depressed and wishing I hadn't listened to my best friend. I'm going to be so sad when the show ends tomorrow night. I know I won't be able to give him a hug or I'll start crying. Ah, well. He probably wouldn't want to hug me anyway, seeing as he treats me like I have lepercy or something. 'Tis my life. Sad, ain't it? :) More tomorrow.....Will she cry or not? Stay tuned........
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Saw Harry Potter with Ro, Ryan, Tim, and Robin last night. I can actually remember some things from the movie now. I really liked the dementias. They were very creepy. The movie had it's funny moments. Emma Thompson was funny as the Divinations teacher and I especially liked the actor who played Professor Lupin, though I can't remember his name. Saw some ads for some interesting movies also. A Cinderella Story looks very good. Hilary Duff and Chad Michael Murray in a modern day Cinderella Story, natch. After the movie was over, we stood outside and talked for a while about all the theatre crap that's going on. It's driving Ro and myself to the edge, nuff said. We were going to go and hang somewhere else but Ryan has a new job I'm sure he doesn't want to be fired from and Robin also had to work today, so Tim naturally had to go with her since he came with her. That's all I can remember. I have to email my bio for "One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest" to Maureen. Tim asked me to write his bio last night. I'm not sure if he was serious or not, so I'm going to write it and see if he likes it. More later..........
      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another great performance of Ride the Winds yesterday afternoon. Albeit I heard some stuff I didn't want to hear but since I didn't hear it from the person who supposedly said it, I'm going to give that person the benefit of the doubt and hope they didn't say it :) Are you following me yet? Anyway, after the show, I wasn't planning on going to the cast party since I was in a crappy mood(when am I ever not lately :). Ro and Kathe convinced me to go and it was nice. I swung on the swings and I felt the best I've felt in two weeks. After that, auditions. We were hoping to hopefully get more kids than we did on Saturday. Our wish came true. It was 6:50 and we already had 20 kids. I turned to Ro and said "It's only 6:50". When we started auditions at 7:15, we had 92 people in the building. Our auditions took over 3 hours and we've only so far cast the guy parts. We'll work on the girls tomorrow, hopefully. After auditions, we went back to my house to drop off the dog and pick up the tape I taped the Tonys on for my dear friend, Ro. Then back to Ro's for Tony time. Shhhh! No talking :) For those of you who don't know, Ro is my best friend. He's like a brother and one of the only people who doesn't treat me like shit. Anyway, it took forever to get the tape to rewind because the tape was crappy. We finally got the idea to run the tape and rewind it while it was playing. Tony night is like Oscar night, in the fact that there's no talking when the awards are on. The opening number was great. For those of you who care, more highlights: Fiddler #-Tradition; Tony Bennett sang "Lullaby of Broadway"; number from Caroline, or Change-Wow; Wicked # was good; Carol Channing did a rap with LL Cool J and she still has it; Wonderful Town #-loved it, wanna see it; Assassins was good; Best Director of a Musical went to Assassins; Popular Comic Actor Jimmy Fallon was funny; Avenue Q # awesome gotta see it; Phylicia Rashad won for her role in "Raisin in the Sun" what a wonderful woman, totally deserved it; The Boy From Oz # was cool, Hugh Jackman was great; Best Revival of a Play went to Henry IV; Best Revival of a Musical went to Assassins; Best Play went to I Am My Own Wife which is one guy playing over 40 roles; Best Actress in a Musical went to Idina Menzel from Wicked; Hugh Jackman won Best Actor in a Musical; and then Best Musical went to Avenue Q, whose producers were very very surprised. I think it was totally deservant of the Tony. I've never watched the Tonys before. They were great. Being a big fan of plays and musicals, I loved the musical numbers and will def. watch the Tonys again!!!!! More tomorrow night after I get back from Gavin!!!!!!!!! Yes!!!!! Gavin DeGraw...........
      
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today we had auditions for Stage Door, the summer youth production we're doing this year. We had a pretty decent turnout for the first day of auditions. I think we'll have an excellent cast. Ro and I are very excited about doing the show. I'm excited because the last show I directed was "Bye Bye Birdie" over a year ago. I'm also excited because directing a show takes up much of my time and that'll be nice. I've been lonely and a little blue and feeling like I haven't had much to do in the past two weeks since the "incident". If you know me, you'll know what the "incident" is :) Tonight we had an excellent performance of Ride The Winds. Tomorrow is our last matinee and also a cast party at Susan's. Fun,fun!!!!!!More later........   P.S. I MISS YOU :(
      
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay. I've seen this movie twice now. I think I can fairly remember all the gory details. Actually, I can't :) Steve asked me today what my favorite part was and I couldn't think of anything that stood out. I can remember the people I saw it with(Michelle on Thursday and Ryan on Friday)but nothing else :) I remember someone saying they didn't get the end. It was very understandable, I thought. I can't explain it without giving stuff away. Oh well. I'm probably going to dragged along next week when Ro and Tim go to see it. Maybe I can post about it then. For now, I must sleep because I have auditions tomorrow or later today rather. TTFN
      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I woke up and went to a job interview, which went pretty well. Then I went home and fell asleep again(I've been doing that alot lately) until it was time for me to drive Ro back to Bel- Air. Yes, I am an extremely nice friend. Normally, i wouldn't have driven him but I have no life and he was giving me gas money. We talked about all the theatre crap on the way up there(1 1/2 hours because of traffic!!!) and about auditions. The "Board" came up with the brilliant idea of charging the actors to be in the summer show. It ain't happening. That's all I have to say. Anyway, we dropped Simon off and came back. Ro went on his merry way with Kathe and I went home. Surprise, surprise. There was no one home so I went to pick up my tickets for Harry Potter tomorrow night at Muvico. I figured since I was there and had nothing else to do, I'd go see a movie. Shrek 2 it was. Maybe I'm just in a funky mood but I didn't find it that funny. I'm sure when I'm in a better mood, it'll be hysterical to me. The story was good and there were lots of pop culture references. I will probably see it again, I'm sure. After I stopped at Ro's to just chill, I came home. I was going to stay at Ro's since he's out of town and has no problem with me being there but I decided to come home and sleep in my own bed. I'll probably stay there tomorrow night since the movie won't end until like 3am. That way I don't have to drive home. I still don't have anyone to go with me to the movie. These are the problems of a crazy person!!!!!!! :) More later.........
      
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey. Thanks to all who have decided to come and visit my blog. I know several people that have one and decided that I'd like to have one too :) Don't worry. Mine will not have the nastiness that certain people's blogs do. I'm going to use my blog to keep people updated on my life, theatre and otherwise. Mostly theatre, I'm sure, since that's mainly what my life consists of :) I chose Kenzo's World because it's a nickname of mine that I actually like. My "brother" Ro gave it to me right after I started calling him Rory. For those of you that only slightly know me, let me tell you some more :) 24, single, love theatre, tv, and movies. Best TV shows: Simpsons, Taxi, Futurama, Family Guy, That 70's show, Cheers, and Wings. Also Monty Python and anything British comedy. Great movies include anything done by Mel Brooks or Kevin Smith. Also Sixteen Candles, Goodfellas, Say Anything, Tombstone, Bridget Jones' Diary, and anything with Adam Sandler. I love to laugh, though I haven't been doing much of it lately :( Long story. Send me something if you want to know. I'm a very kooky person and my life goal is to be happy with the right things and the right someone, who I'm waiting to be ready for me. Actually, if I have the right person, when he's right, I don't need a lot of stuff. That's all for now. I have rehearsal shortly and must get ready.  TTFN!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wow. What an awesome show. I've never seen the show before nor did I know what it was about. It was sensational. I hope that Stage Door is just as good. When I dropped Ro off at his apartment, Ro, Kathe, and myself were all talking about musicals. I argued that musicals do have their place. Kathe disagreed. She's not a big fan of the musical. Ro, of course, loves them. I like ones that make sense. You know, things that could actually happen or have happened. This is why I despise CATS. Never could happen. My three cats don't sing and dance. Now, maybe, if the actors portraying the cats had more cat-like things. Like licking themselves whenever the spirit moved them or maybe plopping down in the middle of a number or leaving a dead small animal at your feet. Maybe then I'd see it. Ragtime was great!!! Set constrution tomorrow(Saturday) and Sunday all day. Well, tomorrow, Ro and I have my Daddo's 50th birthday party. Kathe is meeting us there. Ro and I are leaving the theatre about 2:30, 2:45. But then it's back there at 11 am on Sunday for finishing up on the set, cleaning the theatre, and Q 2 Q. If anyone wants to stop by and help, you're more than welcome. We can always use extra hands. I feel like a total goober right about now. I was on my way home tonight after dropping off Ro, and I started thinking about an ex-boyfriend(not saying which one) and about how he always made me so sexually aware of myself. I never slept with any of my boyfriends. Well, I slept with them but not in "that" way :) Now I'm making myself sound like a tramp. Well, those of you that know me, know that I'm not. You also know how many person I've slept with and how dreadful that was :) The boyfriend I was thinking of I never got a chance to "sleep" with, though, I wish I had. I regret it a lot sometimes. Like I say, que sera sera. Whatever will be, will be. More later......  
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       God, some the stuff at the theatre is ridiculous. Everyone is fighting about petty things. Doesn't anyone understand the real reason we're all here? It's because of our love for this theatre. I would hate to see this theatre not work and have to shut down. It seems like everyone in this fight has forgotten that reason. People ask me if I want to act. The answer is "No". Yes, I like to be on stage. It's fun. My favorite thing to do is stage manage. Running lights isn't bad either. If I could, I would like to be a stage manager for a professional company if the teacher thing didn't work out.&nbsp; I live for working backstage. It's great, wonderful, and fun. You get to boss people around. That's always fun :) Tonight, the s**t hit the fan. Ro and I were getting yelled at by both sides about the program. It pisses me off how certain people want us on their side but they don't trust that we'll do the right thing. I know that they don't trust me at all and also for a fact that I am talked about behind my back. "Well, if she did that, how do we know she won't do it again?" I don't want to be a board member. I just want to do my artistic thing and be done with it.&nbsp; If I'm not trusted by them, why should I stay on their side? I won't go over to the other side either. I'd like to be neutral but it's too late for that. It's all bullshit. Nobody is doing what's in the best interest of the theatre. They all think they are but it's not true. Ro and I are screwed where this show is concerned. Both sides expect us to do what they say. We have personal ties on one side, veiled threats on the other. IT'S ALL CRAP!!! Just let us do what we came to do: Direct. I'm doing this for those kids. I'm not directing this show for anybody else. And I'll be damned if I let someone tell me how to cast my show. If you wanted a certain cast, you should have volunteered to direct it!!!! I also don't need or want directing notes from someone that doesn't know what they're doing in the first place and let's their actors dictate the blocking to them. I just had to get that off my chest. I feel so alone when it comes to this theatre stuff. I wish I had someone to vent to. Bad thing about not being in a relationship: No one to talk to about stupid things. Well, I can talk to my friends but we always argue.&nbsp; Anyway, the theatre is not the best thing for me all the time. It's ruined relationships with family members, friends, and boyfriends. In the past 8 months, I have had some much stuff thrown at me that my attitude has become worst and has made me a bitch at times. Ride the Winds was a show that I loved doing but working with Bill, who is on the other side, wasn't the easy thing. He would get on my case about choosing sides and a lot of other nonsense. Then I would take it out on actors who were my friends and who only want the best for me. My being a bitch ruined something good that I had going. I'm glad that I learned through that experience not to let theatre enter my personal relationships with my family and friends. I leave my problems at the door. So far, Stage Door has been wonderful. I don't let any of that bullcrap affect my rappaport with the actors. As does Ro. We treat those kids with the utmost respect. I love each and every one of them. I wish I could back and fix anything that was ruined during Ride the Winds but I can't. What's done is done. Anyway, my questions from yesterday. Bobby Eddowes was my first boyfriend and like I said, the sweetest guy I ever knew until my last boyfriend, who was as sweet as honey and just as cute as a teddy bear. Fave beer? Either Molson or Heiniken(sp?). Two favorite bands? Well, I have many faves. Let's see Barenaked Ladies, Foo Fighters, Mighty Mighty Bosstones, Weezer, The Strokes, Green Day, to name a few. Movie posters on my wall? Sixteen Candles, Say Anything, Tombstone, Empire Records, Mallrats, Happy Gilmore, Billy Madison, Mixed Nuts. New questions for today. Only a few will know this. First show I ever was in at Burtonsville Players/ Laurel Mill Playhouse? First show I directed? Where am I ticklish?My first crush on a celebrity/sports figure? What color is my car? Okay. Bed. Ro and I are going to see Rameen in Ragtime tomorrow night. That should be fun!!!!! More later........   
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Nothing exciting or of any interest happened today. I just went to the Dining Room read through and that's about it. I will answer my questions from yesterday. Fave hockey team? New Jersey Devils. Fave baseball: New York Mets. Fave football: New England Pats. I liked the Pats before they won the Super Bowl. I'm not jumping on the bandwagon. Hopefully, I can go to my first pro football game this fall. Did I graduate high school? Well I got my GED. It's a long story, better for in person. Any other schooling? No. Didn't have the money. Three animated shows I live for? Family Guy, Futurama, and the Simpsons. New questions: The name of my first boyfriend and the 11 year old boy I compare all guys to? J/K. I don't do that, though he was the sweetest guy I ever knew until my third boyfriend came along :) Favorite beer? Name two of my favorite bands?&nbsp;Name two movie posters I have on my wall (sorry, if you've never been to my house :) . I'll answer all the questions tomorrow. Now, I'm going to eat some pizza and watch porn :) No, I'm going to watch Serendipity.&nbsp;I'm looking for something to do Friday and Saturday nights. Any suggestions?&nbsp;More later.........   
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Don't you hate when that happens? Real quick post because it's raining outside and I want to go get cozy under my comforter and watch Happy Gilmore :) Rehearsal went pretty good tonight until the damn roof started leaking when the rain started. Hopefully, it won't be pouring tomorrow during rehearsal. I'll keep my fingers crossed. We have a&nbsp;costume parade tomorrow night plus we have to clean Act 3, Scene 1. It looked awful tonight. We'll take it slowly tomorrow and get everything&nbsp;fixed that needs to be. Rameen is&nbsp;doing a wonderful job. He's already off book.&nbsp;I hope we can get someone like that for&nbsp;Jimmy :) Anyway, rehearsal tomorrow night. If anyone's ever in the area, you're more than welcome to stop by. It's always nice to see an adult face :)There is also a rehearsal&nbsp;for the Dining Room(which&nbsp;I'm stage managing) but obviously, Stage Door rehearsal comes first. I&nbsp;have to get something off my chest right now. There's alot of crap going at the theatre. Unfortunately, my parents and I are all involved at the theatre. We're all on Kathe's side but sometimes my dad will get on my case about something that I know nothing about. It's just all crazy. I'm still at the theatre because without it, I would be nothing. The theatre made me who I am today. Seven years ago, I was the shyest, quietest person ever. Now I'm still shy and quiet but I will be more bold in doing things.&nbsp; I'm going to watch Happy Gilmore. Before I do, the answers to yesterday's questions: Rory and The Real World: San Diego. I miss it on Tuesdays now. I&nbsp;feel like a goober&nbsp;because I always used to say you wouldn't catch me watching that show but it's so addictive :) Questions for today: Favorite sports team in hockey? Baseball? Football? No basketball. I'm not a big fan of b-ball. Second question: Did I graduate from high school? If so,&nbsp;did&nbsp;I get any schooling afterwards? Third question :&nbsp;Three animated shows that I live for? Answers tomorrow!!!! Until then, Happy Gilmore here I come. More later....... &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Stage Door rehearsal went great tonight. We had a reporter and photographer from the Gazette there. She asked the kids lots of questions and they all had a good time answering them and being silly. Unfortunately, we've lost another male actor due to sports. Does anyone out there want to act? It's real easy. One little scene in the 1st act. That's it. Anyway, let me know if you know of anyone. We only made it to the middle of Act 2 due to the late start. Ro is going to Pennsylvania with Timmy tomorrow so I'm running rehearsal by myself. Well, I'll have Stu. I know we can get through the whole show in 2 1/2 hours. We just need to pick up the pace a little. Wed, we have a costume parade and individual work. I'm working with someone and Ro's working with someone. One-on-one. The actress I'm working with just needs more of a shy, kind of sensitive touch to the character. I'm trying to decide how to approach this in a way she'll understand. On a happy note, Rameen and Tim have joined our cast as Sam Hastings. Rameen is doing the first three weekends, Tim the last weekend. We have a week and a half to get someone in who can learn the lines and blocking of Jimmy Deveraux. I'm praying it happens. Keeping my fingers crossed :) My questions last night in the blog were a little weird and maybe too personal. Only my best friend would know when I lost my virginity. Fave Kevin Smith movie? Mallrats!!!! Better questions : My best friend is who? MTV show I've hated to miss this season? How boyfriends have I had? I'll answer that last one right now since it's easy. The answer is 3. Have I ever had a serious relationship? No, not really. By serious I mean long term. My longest&nbsp;relationship was 3 months long and that's when I was 11. Seriously!!!! In one relationship I wasn't ready for seriousness; the other realtionship, he wasn't ready for seriousness.&nbsp;I always used to find that I thought I didn't have the time for serious relationships.&nbsp;Then I discovered that if someone is special enough to you, you make time for them. I've had (and still&nbsp;do have) a&nbsp;lot of guy friends that never&nbsp;panned out to relationships.&nbsp;My closest friends are my guy friends. My whole life has been like that. Some people get the wrong impression of me. I'm hanging around, talking and laughing with guys, I come off as a flirt. I'm totally&nbsp;the world's worst&nbsp;flirt. I suck at it. Ask any of my friends. I think I'm bad because I grew up with the understanding that the guy should make the first move. Well, that and the&nbsp;fact that I'm a little shy and I don't think&nbsp;I'm very&nbsp;pretty to get most guys' attention. Whatever!! I've just gone on a&nbsp;long tangent. Crazy or what? Crazy!!!! I'm going to watch my Billy Madison DVD that I got today and hopefully fall asleep at a decent hour. Yeah, right!!! Normal sleep has escaped me for the past two months ever since all this crap started happening to me. Oh well!!! More later.......... &nbsp;&nbsp;     
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     Love Gavin. Don't care much for the hat. I bet he took the&nbsp;stickers off of it, though : )&nbsp; urlLink      
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Gavin "Call me Yummy" DeGraw&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       No, not really. Just seems like it. Friday night, before the show, Michelle and I went to Baltimore to see Gavin DeGraw(an amazing singer) perform at the Baltimore Orioles summer concert series. He was so good as he always is. He does an amazing cover of Marvin Gaye's "Let's Get It On.". I wanted to take Rory to see Gavin but he didn't want to risk being late to get his black eye makeup and everything done. My makeup is regular makeup so it was no problem for me. Anyway, Rory loves Gavin too. He would have had a blast. Michelle had a good time. We left at 7 and made it to the theatre at 7:35. I had plenty of time to get into makeup and costume. After the show, we went to Bennigan's where I discovered that by alternating drinking soda and liquor, you won't get much of a buzz. Either that or my tolerance level is lower than it used to be. Saturday, had rehearsal at 2pm, hung around with Rory for a bit, went home to take a shower, went back to the theatre for the final performance of Cuckoo's. Kind of sad. In my first scene, I was talking to Omar who sits in the "Station" with me. Neither of us could believe that it was the last show. We both agreed that it seemed like the show had been going on for like 4 months. It was the first(and probably last) time I've ever had a really long convo with Omar. Usually, we would tease each other. He started calling me "Cupcake" after I wore a shirt that said that on it. After the show, we struck the set. Everyone had a couple of beers while doing it so it was a very loose set strike. The thing I will miss most about Cuckoo's is the cast. What an awesome group of guys!!!!! I love each and every one of them. I'm glad to have met these guys, especially Tim, Robin, and Jack. Tim is one of the funniest people I've ever met. He can totally distract you from your problems. Jack is very cool and interesting person. Robin is so sweet. Always a nice word. He called me sweetheart and at one point, was trying to set me up with his son, who's the same age as me. I hope I can work with all those guys again. After strike, we headed to Rocky Run. Kathe said she would buy us all dinner, which makes her an equally awesome director. I missed her getting her cast gift because I had to run home before going to Rocky Run. They knew I was on my way. Why they couldn't wait for me? I don't know. Anyway, today, set construction for Stage Door. We built half of the set and have the primer coat of paint and everything. The upstairs is all clean and we organized a boy's side and a girl's side. After set construction and some pizza(thanks to Stu), Ro, Tim, and I went to Ro's to watch "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest" on DVD. I had never seen the whole movie. Ro tried to get Kathe to watch it with us but she refused. The movie was great. Ro and Tim didn't like the fact that they filmed parts right out of the play but those parts didn't make the final cut of the movie. I love watching movies at Ro's. He only has a TV in his bedroom so you're forced to get comfortable. I had to share the bed with Tim because Ro has this chair that only he can sit in. News flash, Rory!!! No one wants to sit in your stinky chair anyway : p Afterwards, we chatted for bit about theatre crap and then bid goodnight. I went home and managed to squeeze in some time with my niece, who was visiting. Luckily it's summer so my sis and her family goes home later on Sundays. I miss seeing my Shaylee. After Stage Door, I'll have more time to see her. Okay. I have paint all over my arms and legs but I'm exhausted. I'm torn between shower or bed. I'll decide eventually :) Oh, the answers to the questions I asked in my blog last week(See? I said that I would forget). Anyway, my middle name is Michelle and my eyes are grayish blue. Two other questions: Favorite Kevin Smith movie? How old was I when I was no longer a virgin? Rehearsal tomorrow night for Stage Door. We have to block in Rameen and Tim, who are replacing an actor we lost last week. Hooray!!!!! More later........      
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       What a boring day!!! Got up about 11:30, did some laundry, washed my costume for Cuckoo's Nest(hey, those nurses uniforms get hot and icky under those lights), listened to some music, and spent a good 2 hours on the comp. typing in the bios of Stage Door. I said that I would do the program because I want to make sure none of the kid's bios get cut. They've all worked really hard. They deserve all the bio space they want. That reminds me of a story from rehearsal on Wed. A reporter from the Laurel Leader was there. Ro was talking to her and Mary asked if I was going to talk to her. I said "Mary, I don't do this to get my name mentioned anywhere. I do this summer program for you guys. That's the most important thing." When I said that, I realized that the Summer Youth Program is my one greatest accomplishment so far. I started the program in 1998 and with the exception of last year, I 've directed every production. I live for the summer program. Not many directors enjoy working with young people. I like it better than working with adults sometimes. Young actors are still learning their craft. They don't get big heads real easily, they also don't get all pompous. They will, I've learned, complain about their costumes. I think every actor hates at least one costume piece they have to wear. I know I have. I dislike the cap I wear in Cuckoo's, I despised the habit I wore in Blue Leaves, I barely tolerated the&nbsp;strectchy head band&nbsp;in Deadwood Dick. The one show I've done that I've loved my costumes was Betty's Summer Vacation. Since we went with product placement in that show, I wore my own Old Navy clothes. Plus, I got to wear my two piece on stage. When I first found out,&nbsp;I wasn't thrilled but it was so much cooler on stage in a bathing suit. Anyway, I love my kids in the summer program. People keep telling me to go and direct adults. I have. I directed Birdie last year. It was great but I work best with younger actors. That's why I'm going to be a teacher, people!!!!!    --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------    Tonight we had brush up for Cuckoo's Nest. Since Cecily was missing,&nbsp;I filled in for her. Mary and I decided it would be fun to&nbsp;put on long ball gowns and be very high class hookers. Mary(for those who don't know) is a young actress I met in the fall. I cast her as the lead in the one act "Meet Virginia". Mary has an attitude that was very much the character. Mary is a great, great girl. We get along so well. She's like a younger sister. I love her to death. I have told her that I would cast in one of my shows in a heart beat. She's in Stage Door and she's amazing!!! Anyway, Mary and I were upstairs trying on dresses and giggling like 7&nbsp; year olds. When our cue came, we climbed through the window on stage and had a ball :)&nbsp; There had been a rumor about going for cheesesteaks but we decided maybe another time. Instead, we went to Oliver's. Let me say that Tim is one crazy, hilarious guy. Whenever we go out, Tim is the life of the party. He has funny stories and crazy songs he sings. I hope that Tim and I get cast opposite each other in Our Town. I think we'd work very well together.&nbsp; I can only hope.&nbsp; Last two shows of Cuckoo's Nest this weekend. Come and see it if you haven't. We strike the set Saturday and that's always a blast. We usually party afterwards. Anyway, I've got stuff to do tomorrow. Supposed to see Gavin DeGraw in the summer concert series the Orioles have. He's supposed to perform before the O's game. Don't know if that's going to happen. I'd have to drag ass to the theatre for the show. Kathe says she's not starting without us. But it's supposedly going to rain and I hate trying to park in downtown Baltimore. Expensive!!!!! We'll see. Oh, since I'm so nice, Happy Birthday to Ryan!!!!!!!!!!!!! More later..........    
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm keeping this short since I feel kind of blah. Stage Door rehearsal tonight. Ro and I were able to fine tune a couple of scenes that we felt needed work. Rehearsal ended at 9 (our earliest end time so far this summer). I worked&nbsp;out some costumes for different people. Ro and I went to Friday's to meet up with his girlfriend. She got there and then I had to listen to them argue for a good 15 minutes. One thing I don't miss about a relationship? The fighting!!!! Ro is my best friend and I love his girlfriend too. But geez!! Luckily, they make up more than they fight so..... I decided to leave early. I came home, ate my late dinner, and played a little NHL 2002 on my PS2. It was relaxing but then I got so bored. Now, I'm going to my room, putting on some music, and trying to go to sleep. Will I get to sleep? No, probably not until like 3am. Too much stuff going on in my head!!!! Usually if the music doesn't work, I'll fall asleep watching TV. Tomorrow night, we have Cuckoo's rehearsal and then a possible road trip to Philly for some cheesesteaks. It was Tim's idea. He says it'll take like 2 hours to get up there. We'll see......  
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       No, nothing bad happened. That was just the first thing to pop into my mind right at that moment. Tonight I went to Columbia Mall with a friend. It kills me how packed the mall is on the weekends but even in summer, it practically deserted on a weeknight. We're going up Route 29 to the Columbia Town Center exit and come up on all this traffic. Whoops!! Concert at Merriweather. So we go a different, less crowded way to get to the mall. We're passing all the traffic for MP and trying to remember who was playing tonight. I ask my friend to look and see what kind of age range there is, maybe we can figure out that way. Well, there's people from 15-60.&nbsp; It's driving us crazy so finally we call information, get the number for MP, and call and ask. It's Nickelback and 3 Doors Down. How could I have forgotten that? I&nbsp;heard the announcement the other day when a radio station was giving away tickets. Duh!!! Anyway, we go to the mall, get something to eat and then walk around. We hit the Disney Store, Sam Goody, B&B Works, Nordstrom(where there was the cutest plaid mini for $23 and also the cutest salesman :) . I didn't get either. Couldn't afford the mini, didn't really want the salesman. I have other people on my mind right now. After Columbia, it was still early, so we decided to hit Arundel Mills. I never really buy anything. I just like to walk around the mall and observe people and things. It's fun. More fun when you have someone to walk with. We leave Arundel Mills passing Bass Outside World contemplating how hard it would be to steal one of those boats they leave outside. We have nothing to do so we decide to just drive around. Since my brain wasn't properly working on Monday, I remember that I have to get the bios I left at the theatre so I can start doing the program. We're there looking for the bios when I get a call on my cell from my friend a.k.a "little brother" Collin. He had just driven by the theatre and seen my car. He was parked outside. He comes in and we all chat for a bit.&nbsp; I can't believe that Collin is driving now. I met Collin in 2000 during "The Music Man". He was 12 at the time. Now he's 16 and looks all of 22. When we hang out, people think we're dating. No thanks!!! A little too illegal for my tastes :) Anyway, Collin is one of my favorite people in the whole world. I haven't seen him since the Main Street Festival. I got on his case about not keeping in touch more. I tried to convince him to be in Stage Door, since we lost an male actor on Monday. He can't do all the dates. He asked me about my love life. My friend said "Better not to touch that subject." Collin has been my friend through many numerous crushes and flirting games. He understands me very well. He was one of the first to know about my crush on Steve B. during Music Man. He also knows about the not so hot January and Februrary I had with Erin. For someone a good 8 years younger than me, he reads me like a book. That's what "little bros" are for, I guess. Anyway, he had to leave to be home for curfew or his mom would have his hide. I found my bios and drove my friend home. Came home myself, put away laundry, and watched TV. Now I'm writing in the blog. What an exciting day!!!! Can't wait for Friday!!!! Gavin DeGraw concert before the O's game. I will make Cuckoo's in time. They can't start without Michelle and I. The concert will be over in plenty of time. Here's hoping anyway :) To bed, to bed. Have to clean the bathroom tomorrow. Yuck!!!! Other than that, a day of sitting on my butt typing bios into my comp. I can hardly contain my excitement. Rehearsal tomorrow night for Stage Door. More later......      
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Cleaned up the old homestead today and while I was doing that, I watched Dazed and Confused. I love, love this movie. Now it's not my favorite movie but it's high up there. I mean it has an sweet soundtrack plus a London brother. I love the London brothers, Jeremy and Jason. Why? I'm not sure. I think it goes back to when I saw The Man in The Moon with Reese Witherspoon and Jason London. So now, I'll deem a movie watchable if there's a London brother in it. Mallrats-Jeremy; Out Cold-Jason; Dazed-Jason; To Wong Foo-Jason. Jason is my more favorite of the two. He is the better actor and the one who's in movies. Jeremy does a lot of TV.&nbsp; Wow!!! Look at me go on about the London brothers. I'm sorry. They're just really nice guys : ) Anyway, after I cleaned my room, I was bored so I decided to take some pictures of it. To see what my humble abode looks like, you can go to:   urlLink  http://www.msnusers.com/3o910moa7koq6jogh656aiaic6/documents.msnw?fc_a=0&amp;fc_p=%2FPictures%2FKendra%27s%20Room     &nbsp;  Yes, I'm kooky. I'm usually very bored all day. If anybody ever wants to come over and hang, that's cool. I have lots of movies and digital cable : ) Anyway, I'm taking a shower before heading off to the mall. More later......  
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       when I can't think of a title for a post :) I'm usually more creative than this. Whatever!!!! My brain cells are going down. It's from hanging around all the smokers that I do. Well, that and the alcohol. Of course, I don't drink that much so maybe it's not that :) We had Stage Door rehearsal tonight. We were supposed to run the whole show but since we got started late due to a parents meeting we only got to Act 3, Scene 1. But we did the curtain call so that's one less thing to worry about. Whew!!! I also saw some Ride the Winds people tonight(Susan and Ryan), which I wasn't expecting. If you guys read this, sorry I wasn't more talkative but it was a little crazy tonight : ) After rehearsal and after arguing with Ro about something (he thought something that I thought was wrong and could never happen because wishes don't come true), I drove Ro home but then I had to go back to the theatre because I forgot some papers that we needed. So I'm leaving the theatre and I get a phone call from a friend. I'm sitting in front of the theatre chatting on my cell phone for a good 20 minutes. Yes, I could have driven and talked at the same time but I wasn't in a hurry to get anywhere. I was on my way home when I realized I forgot something else so I headed back to the theatre. Then I had to stop at the store and get some food. Now, I'm going to eat and call it a night. A lot of stuff is running through my mind right now so hopefully I can sleep. I'll just let the sounds of Route 29 lull me to sleep :)&nbsp; If anybody reading this is free the weekend of July 31st and August 1st, we could use some help building the set. Thanks!!!! Tomorrow night, I have nothing so I'm hitting Columbia Mall with a friend. More later......    
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       or so I'm told. Last matinee for "Cuckoo's" today. It went surprisingly smooth except for Steve putting his hands all over me on the "Sweet thing" line. Total surprise!!!! After the matinee, there was a little cocktail party at Cafe de Paris in Columbia. The whole cast was there, well, except Gary and Ken. It was great fun. I had a Bass Ale and then&nbsp; a screwdriver. I had a bit of a buzz when we sat down to eat dinner. I didn't have anything because that place is expensive. Anyway, after that, we kind of hung around and chatted theatre stuff.&nbsp; Kathe and Michelle were discussing casting for the Dining Room. Ro suggested we all go to his place and discuss it. While Kathe and Michelle discussed, Ro and I watched "Viva La Bam". That show is crazy, but so fricking hilarious!!!!!! Afterwards, I went home but couldn't sleep so I went out and drove around for a while. I was in Laurel and stopped at the theatre. I tried to sleep on one of the couches upstairs but those things are uncomfortable even for a 5'5" person like myself. I knew this already from a past experience but I figured since I couldn't sleep in my bed, maybe an uncomfortable couch was the answer. It wasn't. I was tired of driving around so I got one of the many decks of cards from Cuckoo's and played some solitaire. I hate that game. I totally suck at it. Blackjack, WAR, Asshole, and Go Fish are more my games. That way you can accuse people of cheating : p Even Uno is a better game than solitaire. Anyway, long story short (too late), I got bored and came home. I'm now writing in this blog and I'm exhausted, finally. I've decided to make my blog more interesting. I'm going to ask questions about myself to see how well my friends(which hopefully all of you are) know me. First question, what's my middle name? Second question, what color are my eyes? I'll post the answers in the next blog and when you read it, you can say "Now there's something I didn't know". It sounds like a good idea now but I know it'll never work. I'll forget to do it. But let us pretend like it will work and answer the fricking questions : ) More later.............  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I haven't had a drink in like two weeks, mostly because I've been fighting a cold. Tonight after the show, we went to Bennigan's. I ordered a screwdriver. Maybe it's because I didn't really eat anything all day but I got really weird. I can honestly say that I love drunk Kendra. It's the usual me, just a little more uninhibited. So word of advice : You want me to do something crazy, get me a drink. I love being crazy. I'm just less shy when I've been drinking. I also tend to run my mouth off more and I'll say things I didn't mean to let slip out, like most drunk people.&nbsp; I was fine to drive home as I usually am.&nbsp; I took my drunken time to go over some odd things that have happened to me in the past few days. A drunken reflection if you will. I'm a little sad my buzz is wearing off. I wish I had a party to go to or something but I have a matinee tomorrow. Aw, crap. But on the bright side, cocktail party afterwards. Hooray!!!!!!! I'm still in search of a "Parchessi" partner. More later.......  
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Why do I keep hitting my knee on this stupid desk? I just did it again. God, I'm getting retarded :) Either that or senile. Do you ever have one of those days where you get nothing done that you wanted to do? Well, that was my day. I sat at home and watched "I love the 90's" on Vh1. It's pretty funny. Then, of course,&nbsp; I took a shower and headed to the theatre for what seems like the 18th week of Cuckoo's Nest. I love the show, don't get me wrong, but it seems like it's been going on forever. Maybe it's because I'm usually hanging by myself upstairs when I'm not on. I wish Ride the Winds was still going on. At least then, I was always doing something. We have a matinee this Sunday. If there was no matinee, I might have gone to OzzFest. They have some good bands this year. My only problem is that it's at Nissan and I hear traffic is a nightmare. Ah, whatever, I can't go anyway.&nbsp; A side note, a lot of my friends have been odd lately. I feel like a lot of people around me are treating me like garbage. I hope I didn't do something mean or nasty. It bothers me when people don't tell me what their problem with me is exactly. It'll drive me crazy for days :) Oh, I have to get up to get costumes out of storage and other fun stuff before rehearsal at 2 tomorrow. I better get to sleep. More later........  
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I got a response&nbsp;about my post the other day about my needing a "Parchessi" partner.&nbsp; Person who responded: All I have to say to you is "Okay". You know where to find me if you're serious ; p I dare you&nbsp;    
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Jen and me at the wave pool. We're bathing beauties. I can see how people think she's my older sister.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My sweetie, Shaylee. You can't see but that's a Red Sox hat she's wearing. She has good taste :)&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yesterday I went to Six Flags with my sister, Rob, Shaylee(my niece), and my mom. A great time was had by all. We got there about 10:30, right when the park opened. Rob decided to hit the roller coasters in gotten City first(Superman and The Joker). He had to go by himself because the rest of us aren't big roller coaster fans. Meanwhile, my mom watched the baby and Jenny&nbsp;and&nbsp;I went on the Alpine&nbsp;Bobs. What an awesome ride.&nbsp;It goes forwards and backwards. When it started going backwards, we're like "This isn't so bad." and then the ride started picking up speed. Suddenly we're like "Tell us when it's over.":) After that,&nbsp;we rode the Blizzard River ride, which is basically a tube down a long water slide. You don't get very wet but like most water slides, it's lots of fun. Then for the baby we went to Looney Toons land, or whatever&nbsp;it's called. We rode the carousel because Shaylee was too short for all the other rides. Oh, well, there's always next year when she's 2. Rob said they would bring her back for her 36" anniversary. We then decided to take a break for lunch. After that, water rides. We hit the wave pool with Shaylee. She had a great time trying to bend down and drink the water. When the wave pool closed for a 15 minute break, we went over the Kiddie's Cove so Shay could play in the water with people her own height :) Jen put her down in the water, Shay lost her balance, and fell face first into the water, but no tears. She was okay. After Kiddie's Cove, we went on the Lazy River. What a good way to get some sun. You can lie there and think about getting tan. After Lazy River, Rob decided to hit the wave pool while the rest of us dried off by lying in the sun. Shay took a little nap and when Rob came back, he , Jenny ,and I decided to go to the waterslides. We went on the colored ones(red and blue). Those slides have been there since the park was called Wild World. We went down those about four times and went back to the chairs where Shay had woken up. Jenny took Shay into the pool with her and then her and Rob went down a couple more waterslides. It was almost time for me to go so Jenny and I went on the tilt-a-whirl. Then unfortunately, I had to leave to go to rehearsal. We had a final blocking rehearsal last night. Originally, I was supposed to stay at Six Flags a lot later but then I won tickets to a concert at the 9:30 Club. Then I was reminded about rehearsal, which I needed to be at, so I had to find someone to give my tickets to. Luckily, Ro helped me out and found someone. I was looking forward to going to that concert too. Ah, well. What are you going to do? Anyway, my day at Six Flags yesterday was a lot of fun. If I could go every day,&nbsp;I would. Look for pictures I post from my fun day. More later......      
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just my knee on the stupid computer desk. Cuckoo's rehearsal tonight. Best rehearsal ever. It was hilarious. Brush-ups can be. Someone made a comment about Tim not being suicidal enough in his portrayal as Billy Bibbit, so tonight we made him a sign to wear that said "I'm suicidal." Anyway, fun, fun. We went to Oliver's afterwards. Steve B. (a friend of mine) came with us since he's going to be filling in on Sunday for someone. I love Steve and we've been friends for years but I always feel like he might be hitting on me. He's nice but I don't think so. Maybe 2 years ago or even a year ago but not now.  Tomorrow night we have Stage Door rehearsal and the people from MPT are supposed to be coming to tape. We'll see what happens there. On another note, I'm going to Six Flags tomorrow. Hooray. More later......
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My best friend keeps telling me that I need to "get some action" as he so lovingly puts it. Any takers? :) Seriously........anyone willing to play Parchessi(as we call it) with me? I'm not the champ but I'm not a beginner either ;0) Okay....What an odd message. Aw, whatever....... More later......
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now that I have your attention :) What a long fricking weekend. Performances Friday and Saturday and Sunday afternoon. Rehearsal Saturday afternoon. Auditions Sunday evening. It's crazy, right? Well, yeah, but what fun!!!! I'm only on stage for a short amount of time as are two other female roles. The three of us will just sit and talk outside while we're waiting to go on. It was especially great this weekend since Kathryn was filling in for Diana. Mary and I were so glad it was Kathryn, who is loads of fun!!!!! Saturday after the show, we went to Rocky Run with some people from the Ride the Winds cast, who had come and seen the show. It was Steve's birthday and the restaurant staff sang "Happy Birthday". Nik, somehow, knocked over and broke a bottle of hot sauce. Ro was making friends with people at the next table, who had come from the Kenny Chesney concert. It was great. I haven't had such a good time in weeks....But I wake up Sunday morning to discover that I am developing a cold. So through Sunday's performance, I'm sniffling and I'm also overly warm on stage. Then we all go and eat at C.J. Ferrari's, an Italian restaurant,which makes one of the best steak sandwiches in the tri-county area. It was nice to sit down and talk to Robin, who plays Scanlon. He lives in Germantown so he doesn't usually come out with us. He was sticking around to audition, so we dragged him along. Auditions went very well. I think Kathe (the director) wasn't expecting so many guys. There are more auditions tonight so we'll see how she decides to cast the show. If not cast, I'm going to stage manage. I was asked to do "An Amercian Daughter" at GAC but have decided to not. I love working at Greenbelt but I'm just not sure about the show. I've also been asked to audition at PGLT for "Lady Wyndemre's Fan" which opens in October. I might and then go into "Our Town". Yes, I'm keeping busy but I know where my priorites(sp?) lie. Work, family and any relationships I might have in the near future always come first, before theatre. We were just finishing rehearsal last night and we were turning the lights off. Ro left the stage lights on and then turned to me and said "Isn't it beautiful? The stage. She's always faithful. Sometimes cruel but always faithful." Spoken like a true theatre person, Rory!!!!!! :) Well, blah, blah, blah. Yadda, yadda, yadda. More later....... 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so sick of liars and assholes. Quite simply, men. I don't mean to offend since I know women do the same things that guys do but why do guys say one thing and then turn around and do the complete opposite of what they've said. It makes me sick. Maybe I should take my mom's advice and become a nun. Arrgh!!! There are some things I thought I could deal with but I'm wrong. I know everything happens for a reason but why does alot of the bad stuff happen to me? :)On a different note, my ex-shag buddy(or as he has been called by some people : Tool) is coming to see the show next weekend. Whoop-de-do.I used to have this big thing for him. I'm so glad those feelings are gone. He could be a prick sometimes....More later.......  
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey. I made a incredibly retarded film. Check it out.   http://mm.dfilm.com/mm2s/mm_route.php?id=1881972 
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "It's time to take out the trash -- dump whomever needs dumping, clear out your emotional baggage and get ready for new love coming your way." This is what my horoscope said today. I'm going to ignore the whole love thing but I take everything else to be a sign. I'm going to clear all my emotional baggage away. Be gone, big suitcases of woe!!!! Shove off, duffel bag of despair!!! God, I'm such a goober :) Anyway, rehearsal tonight for Stage Door. Good as it usually is. We're blocking the rest of Act 2 on Wednesday. We're getting closer to the end of the blocking. Yes!!!!! Now, I can finally begin to watch what the actors are doing with their facial expressions and body language. After rehearsal, Ro and I watched Road Rules Xtreme while going over the bios and character studys our actors turned in. Road Rules was kind of ho-hum. The character studys, however, were very interesting. Some of these kids can really write. Speaking of which, a dear friend of mine told me that they read my blog and gave me some advice. "Don't let your life go to shit. You are extremely talented." Well, duh, the talented part I know :) Just joking :) But I know that they're right. I graduated high school 6 years ago and I haven't really done anything with my life since then., Except join up in community theatre. Hopefully, when I get some money, I can get some schooling done. I'm going to apply to Simmons College in Boston for the 2005-2006 semester. They have a great liberal arts program there and since I want to be a teacher, that's a good program to get into. More later......
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HAPPY JULY 4TH!!!!! Normally, I'm not all that big on July 4th. This year, however, was my niece's first 4th with fireworks. Last year, she had been born but my sister wasn't real big on bringing a 3 week old baby to a fireworks display. This year, we hit Fort Meade for some good family fun. We hung out for a bit at the carnival they have at MeadeFest, I freaked when I thought I saw an ex of mine, calmed down when I realized it was only a remarkable double (just missing the glasses).Then we settled back to watch the fireworks with some drunks near us adding the usual ohhhs and ahhs. And of course, every year, I have to sit near someone who starts singing(badly, I might add) "Proud to be An American". It's usually a drunk doing the singing. On the drunk note, I just want to say that all my friends who drink,(whether it be legally or not ;) I just hope you all got home safely. Some of you I know were okay, others I worry about alot(you know who you are). My niece, Shaylee, had a blast at the fireworks. She sat very nicely for all 25 minutes of the fireworks. Then I sat in traffic for a half an hour with Michelle, waiting to get off the base. But it's okay. We sang along with Hoobastank the whole way home :) HAPPY 4TH!!!!! 
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm feeling sooo wonderful. I had a long talk with one of my closest friends tonight. We talked about all sorts of things that have been going on and we rehashed some old memories. She made me remember things that were kind of painful but also special. I'm glad to have found someone to sit down and listen to me blab on for 20 minutes at a time :) Thanks Mickey!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had another great performance tonight. After I did my scenes in the first act, I went and sat on the roof and looked at the stars. It's my new calming technique. Not that I really needed any calming :) It was just so beautiful outside. I just wish I had someone to sit with me on the roof. I love my friends but I have no one fun to talk to. I enjoy talking with my friends but I miss talking with a great sense of humor. My friends always talk about the same things. I miss the good talks I used to have with .... Oops, forgot that I'm trying not to mention old hurts anymore. Trying to keep myself sane :) Ha!!!!!!! Cuckoo's Nest is fun. Not as much fun as it was in the beginning but still fun!!!!! We're missing an actor all next weekend and then we're missing an actor for our second matinee. We have a replacement for next weekend. We're trying to find a replacement for the 18th. It's a small guy part. If anyone knows of somebody, let me know. Thanks!!!!! I'm supposed to go with Eric to the movies tomorrow, or rather, today. Don't know if I will. Not the brightest idea right now. I'm worried that I'm too suspectible to anything right now and that I might do something I shouldn't with him, when there's only one person I want to do that sort of thing with and, no it's not Ro!!!!! Never in a million years!!!!! He's my brother for god sakes.  More later..... I hope you checked out my pictures from after the concert the other night!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    All together say "We love Ben Folds!!!" No bunny ears this time.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Hey. No smoking in the elevator, Ro!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    "I hope you're not giving me bunny ears" is exactly what I'm thinking.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Went to the Pier 6 Pavilion with Rory on Wednesday and saw Rufus Wainwright, Ben Folds, and Guster. It was a great show. Very well done!!!!! Ben Folds, you are still the piano god. Guster was excellent. I saw them open for BNL a couple of years ago. I have a couple of their CDs. They went on last after Ben, so by then, I was all yelled out :) Ben rocked as he always does. He did many amazing songs from his new EP, which will be very welcome by yours truly :) Rufus Wainwright has a beautful voice and I'm going to see again as soon as I can. All in all, the concert was great. More later!!!!!!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I have nothing to report. Boring, boring, boring!!!! Oh, well, my 'rents are headed up to Boston tomorrow evening for a week. Some alone time. Hooray!!! Not like I see my parents every minute of every day but you know, I love having the house to myself. Ahhh. Now I can walk around naked : ) Tomorrow starts another fun weekend of performances. I hope they go as well as last week's. More later........  
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Wow!! The BNL concert was awesome on Tuesday. I met lots of people I've only talked to online before and I had a great time. Got to Merriweather about 6:15. Parked at the mall and then went to MP to meet up with Katie. She informs me that the seats we got aren't that great. I said it was fine. I'm not picky. Anything is better than the lawn, though lawn seats have their moments : ) We walk around for a bit and then find our seats. The opening act is some guy named Mark McAdam. He was pretty decent. No Gavin DeGraw, but still fairly good. After he was done, we waited a good 40 minutes for Alanis to come on. I was worried her set would run into the Ladies' set but she finished when she was supposed to after a rocking encore with BNL. Having never seen Alanis in concert before, I didn't know what to expect. I thought she might suck but she was great. Not much acknowledgement of the audience but some artists are like that. The guys came out during her last song and started rocking out and then they all started grinding with the guitarist. Funniest thing all night. After 20 minutes for set up, it was BNL's turn. They opened with Brian Wilson. Some Fantastic next and then banter and a rap about the eye makeup Steve was wearing. The reason I love BNL is the banter they have between themselves and how they manage to include every single person in the audience into their talks. They're just awesome. They played for about an hour and 20 minutes, closing with Shopping, which is a great song that features choreography with shopping carts. Yes, shopping carts. They left the stage. Came back on for an encore of Break Your Heart(beautiful song) and It's All Been Done. Left the stage again. Came back for a second encore with Too Little, Too Late. They usually only do two encores, so after that the concert was officially over. Katie and I decided to go and try to meet the band back by the buses. While we were contemplating this, a guy walks up to me and starts talking to me about the band and how he can't believe he's meeting me. I have no idea who this guy is. Turns out he's from barenaked.net, which is a fan board I belong to. I've talked to him a couple times and he turns out to be very sweet and kind of cute. He talks to us for another minute, then goes back to his friends. Katie, myself, and several others wait outside the back gates for an hour before being told that the band won't be coming out because it's a crew member's birthday. Having met the band, I wasn't too disappointed. I had a good time hanging with all the other crazy BNL fans. We walked back to our cars, Katie dropped me off at mine, I came home and dropped. My legs still hurt. I could barely stand up at rehearsal tonight : ) I was dancing all over the place at the concert. That's what concerts are for!!!!! Anyway, I had a marvelous time and can't wait for my next BNL concert. This weekend is looking to be pretty boring. My 'rents are going on vacation starting Friday and I'll have the house to myself. Snooze-fest!!! I'm going to be so bored. Thank goodness for the show!!!!! More later.......    
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       is what the concert was !!!! Alanis was supposed to close but the Ladies did instead. It was amazing as always. I just got back and I'm exhausted from standing so much and screaming. I'll post more tomorrow before Stage Door rehearsal. My new friend, Katie, and I were talking about Green Day and how we can't wait to see them this fall. Anyone want to come with us? It's going to be a rocking time. More later......  
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I changed the way my blog looks. I hope it doesn't confuse people. I don't want anyone to think "Oh, this isn't it." and leave. I'm very excited. I'm seeing Barenaked Ladies tomorrow. i haven't seen them since Februray. I'm sure they'll be great. Tomorrow would have been concert day anyway. If not BNL, I would have headed down to Virginia and the Project Revolution Tour with Korn, Snoop Dogg, and many more.  I'm going to see BNL with a new friend tomorrow, Katie. We met through the fanclub. She has an extra fanclub seat and asked if there were any takers. I took it. It's going to be a little weird. I usually go to BNL concerts with my friends. Katie is a HUGE BNL fan so I'm sure we'll get along very well. I have to hit the shower and then I have Dining Room rehearsal at 7:30 at the theatre. More later.......  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Matinee today. Very good. We did nothing afterwards, so I am now sitting at home bored out of my mind!!!!! What to do?!?! I could play Parchessi but, alas, I have no partner!!!!! The answers to my two other questions: Where am I ticklish? Def. the sides and I'm been told I'm ticklish behind the knees and on my neck. I don't agree fully with that. First celebrity/sprots figure I had a crush on? Scott Stevens. He played for the Washington Capitals years ago and he is the reason I love th NJ Devils. He is the most awesome hockey player in the world!!!!!! More later.......  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Real quick. Show went very well. No one called me any names. We all had a great time at Bennigan's. I love these kids!!!!!! My parents are flying up to Boston this morning and will be back Monday night. Party!!!! No, I'm kidding. My great aunt passed away Thursday night. She was a great woman. She will be sorely missed. My parents are flying up there today, but then driving up there on Friday for vacation and to stay a week. Too bad they couldn't figure out some way to stay. It would make it easier, I think. Okay. That made no sense :) Matinee tomorrow afternoon and then possibly supper with the cast of crazies we have. Someone call me if you want to hang with my lonesome self!!!!!!! More later.......  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well, tonight went great!!!! We had a sold out house, the audience loved it, and the cast was awesome!!!!! It would have been great except that somebody(not a cast member!!!) called me a bitch. I've actually never been called one to my face, especially not by someone who is a good 25 years older than me. Very mature!!!! I was confused because I wasn't sure that he really said it and then he said" That's what you are.". It's all this theatre crap again!! The person in question is on the other side, majorly. I wasn't mad until I realized that he actually said that to me. I then got really pissed because I've never been anything but nice to that family. I know that that's the way of the world. To add to all the crap, we went to Friday's afterwards and everyone(practically!!) was coupled up. I hate when that happens. I've come to the conclusion that I'm not meant to be relationship material for anybody. My friends are always telling me "You're so sweet, pretty, and funny. You'll meet that right someone." I'm at that point in life where I feel like I might have already met that person and I let them slip away. Do you ever get that feeling? I also feel like I'm never going to play "Parchessi" again!!! I had an offer but I guess he chickened out. Aw well!You know where I am.Come and get me : p Blah, blah, blah. I'm tired and confused!!!!! Goodnight, Montreal!!!!!! BNL in 4 days!!!!!! Hooray!!!! More later.......  
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I've decided that since I'm so bad of thinking of titles for my posts, that I would just use Barenaked Ladies song titles. Creative, eh? It means I won't run out of titles for a good 3 to 4 weeks : ) On to the post. We are in Hell Week for Stage Door. Everything is looking great except for the middle of Act 3, Scene 1. Hopefully, we can get it running right by Friday. I've also discovered last night that I have to do the whole program myself since my print program won't allow me to send it to the person who was going to put the bios and graphics together. Mo's going to be upset but oh well. There's nothing I can do about it. Tonight Ro informed me that Dining Room was going to be rehearsing upstairs so we needed all the kids to stay in the back yard. Ordinarily, I wouldn't have a problem with this except when we started the show tonight, it was a good 85 degrees outside and these kids are wearing suits and long dresses. I also was informed from a couple of parents that someone from DR was very rude when one or two of the kids were trying to get their shoes or costumes from the side where they were rehearsing. I have a good idea of who it was. I told Ro that they cannot rehearse up there on Thursday. I am planning to run it like a real performance and we wouldn't be running a rehearsal during a performance. I respect their right to rehearse but we were not informed ahead of time that they would be rehearsing up there. Also, our kids need to get changed and several other things too. I'm going to really miss Stage Door rehearsal. It's been keeping me upbeat and happy. I haven't been in a good mood like this since hell week for Ride the Winds. That was one of the best weeks of my life. I just had fun working lights and stage managing that show. I was in much happier place then, lifewise. Cuckoo's Nest hell week was blah. Never looked forward to it at all. I won't have anything to do now. Not many Dining Room rehearsals I have to attend since I could stage manage in my sleep. I'll have to ponder over what to do while I'm working on the program all night!!!! Oh, answers to questions. 1st show I ever directed? You Can't Take It With You.1st show I was ever in? Little Women, I played Meg. My car is dark blue. I can't remember the other question, if there was another question : ) More later........   Please come and visit if you're in the area this week. My job is basically done!!!!  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       In thinking about the Eric situation, I know that I would definitely not date him. He's great and all but there are only about 3 guys I would want to date right about now. No fair guessing who!!! More later.......  HAPPY BIRTHDAY DADDO!!!!! 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I was awoken at 3am because, stupid me, I didn't put my phone in silent mode as I normally do. I looked at the display and saw that it was my "buddy" Eric. I was half asleep and didn't feel like talking since we usually talk for about 2 or 3 hours, so I didn't answer. I love Eric(or Eazy E, as he's sometimes called). He's been there for me when I've been dealing with some bad stuff. He was there after my last relationship and he felt bad for me. He told me that he thought it might be something really special since I seemed to really like this guy. Then he asked me if I wanted him to kick his butt. I said "No!!". Eric is someone I sometimes consider dating. He's a good listener, funny, and cute. He can be very goofy!! We talked on the phone a couple of months ago on the night Ride the Winds closed. I remember because I was in a funky mood. He asked me if I would ever date him. I said"I guess." "So, that's a yes?" "It's an I guess!" I'm really not in the mood to get hurt for a 3rd time this year. And I think Eric would hurt me. This is someone I almost dated 3 years ago but didn't for good reasons. I don't know. Eric is a unsolvable mystery, much like another guy I know. You think you have figured what they might do and then they turn around and do the complete opposite. Yes, I know a lot of people are like that. That's life. I'm exhausted so here's a weird fact. Thinking about Eric reminded me of this fact. Guys that wear glasses, I find really sexy. It's not because I wear them. It's usually guys that wear the glasses for reading or driving. I don't why but it's really sexy when they wear those glasses. This is the case with a lot of guys I've been attracted to in the past. Eric, Steve, others.... Call me crazy and get it over with : ) I just love it : ) More later......  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       That's me : p No, really. I had a nice weekend, albeit a little crazy. Friday I went with Rory to see my friend Rameen in Ragtime. I've already posted about that. Saturday, set construction for Stage Door and a little rehearsal. We've gotten Act 3 , Scene 1 down to 23 minutes which is decent. Hopefully it'll be less than that tomorrow night. I stayed at the theatre until about 3:15 on Saturday. Then I went to my Daddo's 50th birthday party. We had it at my cousin's house. It was great. She has a pool and it was such a beautiful day. Lots of theatre folks were there and everyone had a great time. Ro and I then went back to the theatre to help put in the steps. Well, since neither of us are very good carpenters, we ended up writing Ro's bio and the directors' notes, finally!!!! The directors' notes are very good. A little sappy but we feel very strongly about this show and the young actors involved. Anyway, then I drove Ro home and we watched Road Rules and waited for Kathe to come home. When she got there, we read her Ro's bio which she thought was very high and mighty even for him : ) I went home and fell asleep late.  Then this morning I had to get up and try to get to the theatre on time. Of course, I didn't get there until about 12:30. There was lots of stuff to do, though. Finish painting the floor, clean the risers off, put another rack for costumes upstairs, put a railing on the steps onstage. Much, much stuff. And it all got done. At 7pm, we had a Q 2 Q and it was long. We got out of there about 10:15 or maybe even after that. I was so exhausted that I came straight home. Did I go to sleep? No, of course not. I have to finish the program and send it to the woman who is printing our programs. I better check my bio. I might be sending an old one. I hope that I'm with it enough to make sure I send the right one :) Rehearsal every night this week and we open on Friday!!!!! Oh my goodness. Are we ready? I sure as hell hope so. More later........  
      
</post>


</Blog>