<Blog>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey ya'll! Today was MUCH better than yesterday! Well, I didn't let things get to me as much as I did yesterday! Anyway, its kinda funny. Well the other day, Monday I think, me and Ryan Larson were throwing a plastic bottle on the bus and I threw it at him and it went out the window instead cause I missed. the bus driver didn't turn it in till today, and I got called up to the office during first period. I dont care though, I only got a hour of ASD. Its my first time too so its not that big of a deal. But the thing that pisses me off is that Ryan didn't get ANYTHING! He was flicking me with a rubber band! Hmmm...well what else happened? I had the oral in spanish today, it was easy. After school Ashley came over. It was so funny, we were wired! She's the best friend ever! I can't wait till the weekend. I'm not sure what I'm doing on Friday night, but Saturday I haveta go to a cousins wedding in South Carolina. It'll be fun! Sunday is Ashleys birthday so hopefully we can hang out.    Well I hope ya'll had a good way too! Just think...6 more days left of school! YAY! I'm excited! Love ya'll! MWAH :-*     
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hey! this is the first time that i've had an online journal...i think its gonna be cool, if only people will remind me to post stuff pretty often... today was how i thought it was going to be: long, boring, and AWFUL! it's like everything i do is wrong, i hate it...:-\ there are some good things, i have this guy that i REALLY like and i have the best friend EVER! so whenever i see or talk to them, its like all my problems go away. anways, right after school today there was a spanish picnic thing i hadta go to cause i needed that good grade...the only good thing that came out of going was ice cream...hehe...then after the picnic i came home and went to the pool while my sister had practice...that was about the highlight of my day! then i came home, studied for that stupid spanish oral i have tomorrow...and now i'm talking to the best friends ever and waiting for the new Real World to come on...yay! well..i hope everyone has a great night...hopefully tomorrow will be a better day! :-D ONLY 7  MORE DAYS OF SCHOOL till summer '04! YEAH!!  Kim :-D 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>