<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, sorry...but in this post...i will not be using my good grammar. ugh...i just need a break from perfection >. well...i was reading tae's blog...and yeh..the guy just makes me smile...alot. hmm...he is one of the few nice people i've met online...i think i was like...by luck or whatever™...i dont know...i had just got a new computer...with internet and all that crap...i joined this group...Gothic Haven...and, well i first noticed tae...hmm...i didn't actually think twice when it came to adding him to my MSN messenger..not knowing that some people hate it when you do it randomly...(sorry!) well anyway..he added me, and told me that i caught him on a good day...well, yeh...thats always good. now, i would consider him one of my really good friends...like, really. i dont know much about the guy..but..its always great to talk to him...anyway yeh... im in a horrible mood today...kind of like...fuck all..eh...its cold and wet right now...ugh...thunder storms...i hate them i love looking at the lightning though...hmm..yeh...Lee got me a new charm for my charm bracelet...it says "class of 2004" on it, way awesome...ok, some people might find it gay, but whatever™... oh, will and grace is almost on...cant wait...i love will and grace...jack is mah fave. he makes me laugh so hard..so, its like, if i have a horrible day [which i am] i can watch that show...and all my problems go away for half an hour...great. hmm..i'm really lonely...i DO know why though...i've been alone almost everyday for the past 2 weeks. i dont mind getting some alone time..but...im getting to much of it...with Taryn gone..i'm lost...she moved to quebec city last weekend...hard to imagine that i wont see her at school no more..ouch. it sucks.reality is to hard to face..oh well, she might be coming down for the first of july...hmmm..she can hang out with Wicky and me...*laughs* anyway...i dont feel like writing anymore...i have no more randomness in me...ugh...if i do...you'll see me post...[miss ya taryn] ~Slowly getting over Jenn and Dave...~
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            *HUGS* TOTAL!  urlLink give The_Surreal_Sin more *HUGS*     urlLink Get hugs of your own     Oh No! I have no hugs...please hug me...pwease!    
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       align=left> urlLink  I adopted a cute lil' poison fetus from Fetusmart! Hooray fetus!     hehehe, welcome my little fetus...:P
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It sickens me to know that I am afraid of food. I can be so shallow. Lets see. Yesterday...I woke up at around noon...had a glass of water...then at around three...I had a glass of grape juice...at five...everyone was having supper so, I joined in like a huge pig...and had a salad...ugh! I went to bed at around 1:00AM. One of my aunts who is close to my "new" family came over for supper..so I really had to force myself to eat...though, the feeling of food being stuffed in your mouth, isn't really a desired one...well anyway..about that aunt of mine...can anybody say -huge-son-of-a-bitch- 10 times real fast?! She was talking to my erm "dad" since my "mum" is nowhere to be found...[though she did call me and tell me that everything was alright, and that - no she wasn't coming back...ok. I'm heart broken...and it sucks to know that you miss your own replacement mom...I'm not supossed to hate her?! Oh well...she was there for me and I am thankful for everything she and "dad" have done.] UGH! I keep going back to another subject... *coughs*becauseIdontWantToTalkAboutIT*coughs* Anyway, she was like "Tim, dear. You have to watch that freak show, you know shes going to be 6 feet under if you dont watch her...Just like that mother of hers! She calls herself a mother, she was clearly knocked up with her first child, what was it again..Michael his name was...where is he anyway Tim?! Dont tell me you dont know!" I was in such a rage, that I got up from the table, jai toute sacré on the floor and I was just fed up of her and her antics...she cant go spread bullshit somewhere else but here!? The wacko...shes such a dumbass!! Dont ask, just dont...*cries* WTF am I doing... Ugh, I called nat today...only too find out she was gone to Montreal for the week. too bad, I'm not headed there for about another couple of days. By the time I get there, she'll be back here...meh. whatever...I need someone too talk to...and, well...apart from Dee or Billy...All I have friends I've met online...But - I would only talk to one of them...and thats only if THEY started the convo...I dont want to have some kind of pity party going on..It's just the guy, he understands so much...I dont know...I just, like him alot..My dad wont stop it with the phone calls..he always says the same thing "I never meant to hit you Em. You know you're an amazing person...blah blah blah..."then the moment came..he said IT..."im sorry"...this was the perfect moment to show him how much I really didn't care and that he had lost me forever...I just said..."If only sorry could heal all the scars...If only you hadn't hit me all those times...If only..." and I hung up...and I cried for awhile...I just wanted a normal family..for once..just for once..try to see what its like...I called BELL© Telephone a little later and blocked his cell phone number...his home phone..everything... SHAY- RIP JENN &amp; DAVID...J'vous Aiment! 
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I haven't updated lately...but...meh, things happen. Ok, so some poeple want some GRAD 2004 reviews!    Grad Day  Jess, Nat, Lucie and I all went to Jess's to go swim. Of course...I had to get all "body-consious" and not go...but whatever™...After that, Jess and Lucie went to get their hair done. fun fun. Meh...I didn't get mine done...I did it myself. :D During that time. Me and Nat walked the streets and just were plain bored. Thats us though. At around 3:00 PM we went and got Nat's hair done. Her hair was nice. Great actually. But, I just went home,and was like fuck all. Der...I'm always like that...   Grad Night  Ok, supper was horrible. But I didn't mind. I had a glass of juice and some bread sticks. Ok, yes..my eating problems must stop and I know it...>. Grad Party  I couldn't stay the night at Alex's. But who cares. Nat either. So there. I went to his house. He has a pool, a dog...had a campfire going. (which was awesome) Frank was there filming everyone as they came in. AWESOMENESS! I had a wonderful time then. Just to be with my class, was enough.   The Morning After  Well, I was the first to get to school I got like 1 hour of HIGH-speed internet. Which is always great for music transfers and IMing. Chatted with Karley..*I LOVE YA GAL* That day wasn't emotinal. But ok.   Last Day :'(  Ok. EMOTINAL! CRYING CITY!! I cant belive it I even cried. Especially when they did "Le Pont" Long story...It's a tearjerker. Awww. I'm crying. Just replaying it in my head. Had a hard time leaving school. Really hard. To imagine...next year, alone...in a new school...ENGLISH school. Eep. Scary. Dad is like "Ifya dont like the fucking school, change!" No, mom isn't home yet..*cries*   Well, lets get to my regular rants...>:]   Yeh, today went out...skateboarded..with some friends. most of the day. After went out and bought two new CD's "The Darkeness" and "The Rasmus" (Rasmus ROCKS!!) [did you notice. I got my keyboard to work again..:P] My caps was jammed. Darn it...Angry at chain e-mails again I guess..heh. I haven't talked to Tae for awhile. I dont know whats up with him anymore... oh well. Someone else joined Scrrap the other day...I have no clue who he is...he seems nice enough though... I added him to MSN messenger, hoping maybe we could chat. But I guess not..its been like acouple of days and he hasn't added me...Aww well..   Fathers Day   You see, long ago...my dad did something..he hit me...and his ring got caught in my skin. so I have this scar on my face...I nevre went back to see him...I dont know...I'm scared now...I fear him...Well, his new wife Linda wants me to go to see him this weekend...its like do you think I am fucked?! Anyway...I dont want to be a part of that family..even though what I have now is falling apart...I'm offically dying...and no-one in my class knowes yet...please help...   Offically Dying  Yes...Sad But True...I suffer from S.A.D  Oh joy! More Pills to pop...*rolls eyes* I have an eating disorder...Nat told her mom. her mom told my mom [when she was still around] I guess it scared her away...bah...fuck her. I cant believe it...its all falling apart..for real...I have so many problems according to my Social Worker...lets make a list he said...then smiled in a really cheesy way...*ugh* 1. Self Harm issues 2. Eating Disorder 3. S.A.D 4. Massive Depression 5. Huge Mood Swings...its like, not normal  ugh...fuck it...I'm too embaressed to go on..  Like I said..I love the Rasmus..well..one song in particular...called Guilty...here are the lyrics...   I feel guilty my words are empty no signs to give you i don't have the time for you  you say i'm heartless and you say i don't care i used to be there for you and you've said i seem so dead, that i have changed but so have you  guilty, guilty i feel so empty, empty you know how to make me feel  i put a shield upon you i didn't mean to hurt you i would have only poisoned your mind never meant to make you cry  you've been so toughtless i can see right through you you used to be there for me so don't you leave say goodbye cause you have changed but so have i  i never though that the time and the distance between us made you so much colder i'll carry the world on my shoulders   I never put any quizzy thingys about myself on this..*you must be relieved...eh?!* Well...I have the time...why not..I borrowed it from Tae ;) I hope he wont mind...  -Full Name: Shannon Emily Jean-Louis Beaulne -Nickname(s): Shay, Shann, Em, Emo -Are you named after anyone?: Nope. -Pets: Cats; Lucifer/Goggles - Dog;Blue -Birthday: March 26th 1988 -Time of birth: 20h34 -Zodiac sign: Aries -Age: 16 -Height: 5 feet 9 inches -Eye color: Green. -Hair color: Erm it changes monthly right now its dark dark brown -Current residence: My house -Where were you born?: Ottawa -Where did you grow up?: here -Email address: god_is_worthless@hotmail.com -Homepages: This one -Computer(s): Erm, this one?! -School: The only one here -Grade: 10 -What kind of student are/were you?: Very smart, yet not nerdy. My average is in between the 85's and 90's. I tend to stand out. Yet, very anti-social - I am in almost all the comities.. -What do you want to be?: Lawyer. Either that, or a musician -Fears: Dad -Medical issues: Eating disorder, self-harm issues -Where do you work?: ... -What do you want to be in the future?: I really want to go back to Ireland and live there...  *Opinions and Questions*  -Best movie of 2003: I dont do the whole, "Let's-sit-down-and-watch-a-movie" Kind of thing -Best TV show of 2003: CSI, Law and Order. -Best new music artist of 2003: many -Best songs of 2003: many -Best kind of music: Whatever™ the people like... -Who do you have a crush on: This guy, but he's gay :( -Do you like someone famous: No. -Who do you have for best friend of opposite gender: Billy -Do you like pickles?: ...pickle weasels... -What are you wearing?: jeans I got at a thrift store, a metallica concert tee, like a million bracelets -What time is it?: 23h38 pm -What is your idea of a perfect date?: ...must we go over this? -What is your idea of a perfect honeymoon?: Not getting married -What is your idea of a perfect wedding?: *rolls eyes* and again...no plans -What song reflects your life the most?: Ooh, many..."Hold On" Good Charlotte -What hospital were you born in?: Erm, the one in Ottawa... -Which celebrity has the best hair?: Amy Lee* -What do you wear to bed?: scooby doo boxers *thanks Billy* -What kind of socks do you wear?: ugh, I hate socks -What kind of toothpaste do you use?: anything -What kind of shampoo?: erm, whatever™ -What brand is your TV?: Well, its a TV -Have you ever done any extreme sports?: BMX and Skateboarding are regular...but, are those that extreme?  *Favorites*  -Books: Too many... -Relative: Mookie -College: meh... -Stores: Chapters, any thrift store, -Kind of chainletters: NONE. -Poems: poems that, someone* wrote... -News channel: Meh...whatever™ -TV shows: CSI, Law & Order -Five girl names: Gawd...erm. Blair, Connor, Cooper, Sam, Emma -Five boy names: Ben, Xavier CANT THINK -Top 5 Actresses you like:...eh, they all seem fake to me.. -Top 5 actors you like: Johnny Depp! -Male singer: Ville Valo -Female singer: Amy Lee -CD: Too many -Bands: Nirvana, H.I.M, Our Lady peace, Sisters of Mercy, Jet, more... -Website: http://www.blogger.com ;) -Music Award Show: Meh, whatever™ -Music Video: Everytime (Britney!! ACK!) -Vegetable: Onion, Carots, Green pepper, cucumber -Meal: ... -Drink in general: Rasberry Slush...I'm addicted -Cheese: Cheddar -Ethnic food: Italian -Fast Food Place: Subway -What do you get there: Any kind of salad -Eat-in: Pizza-Pizza (Good times eh Billy?) -What do you get there: I think the name says it all... -Snack to munch on: popcorn -Kind of pizza: cheese -Ice cream: chocolate chip cookie dough -Bread: White -Pastry: That makes me vomit -Cereal: I dont really like cereal... -Meat: Uh? -Holiday: Halloween or Christmas, only for the presents (selfish...I know) -Sport to play: My Passion! Basketball -Sport to watch: Hockey -Thing to do in winter: Snow Angels! -Thing to do in summer: Erm,complain of intense heat! -Thing to do on weekends: Write -Vacation spot: meh...Les Iles de St-Martin! -Dream vacation spot: Ireland -Place to shop: Thrift store -Thing to do on a rainy day: Sit outside, and let it rain on me... -Thing to do on a sunny day: Play baskeball... -Color: Black -Magazine: Oh - Hit Parader -Gum: Juicy Fruit -Outfit to wear: Whatever™ I get out of the dryer first... -Pair of shoes: Vans. -Kind of car: meh... -Stuffed Animal: Boo Boo...stuffed animal...>. . [something screams GET OVER IT BITCH!  
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OH WELL, NOW THAT MY KEYBOARD IS SERIOUSLY FUCKED UP. I CANT TYPE IN SMALL LETTERS...OUCH >.  ANYWAY, HAD A PRETTY GOOD DAY TODAY. MUM ISN'T HOME. I DOUBT SHE'LL COME BACK. *SHOUTS : MOM, WHY? WHY? WHY? WHY? WHY?* DAD IS BEING TOTALLY GOOD WITH THIS SITUATION. CAN YOU BELIEVE GRAD IS IN ONE DAY, AND MY MUM WONT BE THERE!? SUCKS, EH? BUT HEY, AT LEAST I'M GOING TO GRADUATE...MEH, ITS NOT EVEN GRADUATING REALLY. MORE LIKE, A NERD GRAD...>.  I DONT THINK MEGGIEZ IS COMING TODAY, SHE WAS HERE YESTERDAY AND THE DAY BEFORE WITH MOOKIE, THEY'RE STUDYING FOR EXAMS. YUCKY. AWW WELL, PART OF HIGHSCHOOL EH...(THE ONLY BAD PART) FRIENDS ARE COOL, PROJECTS ARE AWESOME, MUSIC CLASS ROCKS AS DOES ART CLASS...ALOT OF THINGS ARE GREAT. OH, AND NON-CATHOLIC SCHOOLS ROCK TOO...YAY, I CAN BE WHATEVER™ I WANT...PUNK/GOTH/METALHEAD WHATEVER™ THE FUCK I PLEASE...MEH. I ROCK...>.  BUT OF COURSE, TODAY WE GOT THE CHANCE TO DECORATE THE GYM...IT'S BIGGER THAN IT LOOKS, ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE ON A 12 FOOT HIGH LADDER. YIKES...I HATE HEIGHTS >.  I THINK I AM OVERREACTING. I AM NOT GOING TO BE MOVING AFTER ALL. I MIGHT STAY IN VKH AFTER ALL...YAYNESS. NOT GONNA MISS ANYONE. EXCEPT FOR THE FACT I AM CHANGING SCHOOLS. MIGHT TAKE A LONGER BUS RIDE, BUT WHATEVER™.  I HOPE THAT MAYBE MUM WILL HAVE THE SENSE TO CALL. AFTER LIKE ALMOST A WEEK. DAD NEEDS TO LEARN HOW TO WORK THE WASHING MACHINE. HA. MUM HAS TO BE OUT OF HER MIND LEAVING, JUST LIKE THAT. BUT WHATEVER™  ARG. THIS CAP LOCKS THINGY IS ANNOYING...SORRY TALKING TO MYSELF AGAIN.   HAS ANYONE NOTICED HOW HOTT SAM IS?! OUCH. CRUSHED! ALEXZANDRA IS GOING OUT WITH HIM...AWW, SHES SO LUCKY... ANYWAY, I COULD ONLY DAYDREAM ABOUT HIM. HE IS WAY OUT OF MY LEAGUE. :| BAH, WHATEVER™  I JUST REALIZED SOMETHING. I HAVE SO MUCH STUDYING TO DO. *SIGHS* NO NO NO NO! BAH, I'LL DO IT LATER.   TAE IS MAD AT ME AGAIN. WELL, I'M NOT SURE. ANYWAY - HE JUST TALKS TO ME LIKE ONCE A WEEK. I SHOULD REALLY BE POSTING ON HIS THING AGAIN... I DONT THINK I WAS THAT MUCH TIME. NOW IT FEELS LIKE WE ARE PRESSURED INTO DOING IT...GAWD SOMEMORE OF THAT USELESS SHIT. I MEAN, FOR SURE, HE CAN DELETE THE THING...BUT I WOULD FEEL SO GUILTY...IT WOULD BE MY FAULT I THINK. I THINK HES PISSED AT LAURA...IT SEEMS THAT WAY ANYWAY..>.  I DONT THINK I SHOULD BE TALKING LIKE, SO FREELY...AS IF HES READING THIS ANYWAY...I GIVE UP..~SHAY RIP JENN & DAVID   
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      FUCK YOU, YOU, AND YES...YOU! ALL OF YOU!  You know, people at school are mean...Idiots. You can't even wear what you want. I got this wicked roxy™ tee shirt...and I cant wear it, because the mf-ing bitchy preps will kill me. Either that or eat me alive. Ouch.  My dad is corny. I come in from school and ask him, as always "Hey, has mom came back home? or, did she call?" He always just smiles, and says no. Whatthefuck?!  Where is she? Why did she leave? Just like anything I ever had that was good. it either dies, or leaves.  cries  Why?! I just want an answer..she doesn't HAVE to come back if she doesn't care..right?  Definetly Right. Just...I dont feel like doing this long update...I'm to busy eating everything I can find! RIP Jenn and David! - Shay
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ..::Billy! Thanks a bunch...::...  Aww, he had his mobile on! What-a-sweetheart...I know, I know, I shouldn't be SO dependante on him...but. When I need him, {which is almost always, hes there}!  Mum isn't back...suprise suprise...Grad is this week. Shes not going to be there...so what? Why should I give a shit?! *groans*  Meggiez gave me a new nickname..hehehe...My name is now Shay. I dont know...I like the sound of it...Its cool ;)  I just thought I would tell everyone that thanks to Billy...I feel a lot better...   ..::LOVE YOU BILLY BOB >.  Oh, and tomorrow is exams...Ouch, "Hi. I'm failing!" Oh well...we live, we learn. RIP Jenn and David! ~Shay, SEM, Whatever™ you want to call me!
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       *cries*  Why? What is fake is falling apart. Help! Look, I know I dont live a fairytale life. But...why? Why do I always have to go and make up this fantasies for myself. Act as if everything is alright, when obviously it isn't. Ok, just to get all my fantasy readers into my real world here is how the story goes...  My mom, is dead. Nothing much to say here. Thats it. My dad, wants nothing to do with me because I'm a girl. So what?!. Meh, I live with the people I call "Mum & Pop". They never tell me anything. at all. I know they dont love each other like they used to but, please when something goes wrong...just tell me. I hate finding things out on my own. Its just wrong. Yeh. Wrong. Bah, Fuck it  I mean, nothing in my life has ever been remarkably "fun". I'm the one everyone hates to love. I'm sweet, caring...blah blah blah. Ok maybe not. I am anti social, a bitch to some extent, nosey, stuck-up and hot headed. If I was to go on...There would be no more room left...lol... I always get the pity...when someone finds out what happend...I'll try to lie..so that they treat me the same...but they  ALWAYS  find out!! WHY!? Bah. Fuck it.  But now...things with Mum and Pop aren't going so well...Its like I dont exist. They never tell me anything they always make it seem as if I am too much trouble for them. FUCK IT..!!  Well they tore it apart my  "family"  Are a bunch of nitwits and all hate each other. I came back from something with a special friend of mine, to find that  mum  wasn't home. I asked  pop  where she was...and he said she had left...To wherE? he will not tell me...Oh Goddammit! She still isn't back...and I came back last night!  *cries*   You see...everything is gone. All my illusions they are actually FAKE!   I wish I could talk to someone...but Meggiez and Mookie are up stairs and I dont want to bother them...{NO...THEY AREN'T DOING  THAT !!} Even someone online would be great..I talked to Joel...but that dont help me any...I dont know why I dont talk to Tae anymore...I guess its because he is annoyed with me...for not posting in Scrrap...Meh.   I cant talk to Billy..hes moving all day today. Joey was here...but its no use...I want to talk to Billy...Alot. Lets go see if his mobile is on...RIP Jenn~ SEM  
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh Gawd. What has happened to innocent Sem?!She left...shes gone! Ok, so...Rick. Problem number one! Why Rick? He is so, nice...but he seems to forget that I have my own life. I can't always be "there". Right?  He has called me over six times. Always asking me if I can go out with him. I always say no. BEcause, I am not "into" him that way. I've told him SO many times...but he keeps going at me...:( He is now mad at Billy, he says its all Billys fault that I am not "into" him that way! Huh? He doesn't know apparently...Eep.   Went to the brige today. Seen where those two people were killed. So sad. There are flowers everywhere around the water...poor dude will be missed, Big Time. He died with his mom. Poor soul. How hard can it get?  I'm really tired. Tired of school mostly. Exams and all. >.  Ok, currently...I'm in love with "Misfits" Oh yeah! Love em! TIGHT...I listen to them like 24/7...Aww...moi et la musique...inséparable...;)  I cut my, my own hair. :| Erm like 6 inches off by myself. Heh, mom wasn't to happy. Meh. The hair is ok though, I think. I cut it right before grad. Hehehe...Fuck the hair. the dress the shoes. Every FUCKING DETAIL must DIE or BURN TO FUCKIN' HELL! Ack. That makes me feel a whole lot better...  I love this song...    HIM - Gone With The Sin    I love your skin, oh so white I love your touch cold as ice and I love every single tear you cry I just love the way you're losing your life  Oh, my baby how beautiful you are oh, my darling completely torn apart You're gone with the sin my baby and beautiful you are so, gone with the sin  I adore the despare in your eyes I worship your lips once red as wine and I crave for your scent sending shivers down my spine I just love the way you're running out of life  I'll post more tomorrow...right now I feel sick...ewW...RIP Jenn..~On t'aime toute! SEM
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No No No No! This cant be happening! No! There is only 6 days of school left. I usually dont care, like before there was always next year to talk to my friends...but now, there is no more "next year" And there is no more friends to talk to. I'm moving, so I am automatically changing schools. Dammit. Billy is moving to, but only two streets down. Meh. Lucy ass, gets his old friends back, he gets Joey, and the same town. Here I am, no Billy, no friends, no same town. Bah, I should just fuck it I guess...But I want a good chance,more like a fair chance a being sucessful at life and school...stuff like that.  I guess I'll have to get throught next year alone.  I will survive. I mean, new school chance of change..right? I dont want to change..but whatever™ Hopefully they aren't a bunch of stuck up losers who they think they know it all...:P My choice of french to english is a bit drastic. I know. But hey, a highschool is a highschool is a highschool. *duh* Just a diffrent shit load of preps, right? :P Oh no, major factor: Preps. Yikes. They scare me. Uh-huh, yes they do :'( Maybe they'll belong to a nice society of preps. *Meh, dream on loser*  I dont know. The fact that I'll probably only be spending two years there makes me feel ALOT better. I wont be a prisonner in my own school. Just turned 16 in grade 11. Is that normal. I think so. I'm supossed to be in 12th because I was offered to take summer classes to get over 79 in math so I could boost up, but nah. Enough that I'm going to be new there, I dont want them to think I'm a french brainball...yucky.  I'm leaning towards their sports team. Basketball? Oh, hiya...it's my passion. ;) I hear at my new school they have "LAW" courses. Yayness. Oh, hiya...it's Law, my other passion. When Basketball and Law meet. ;)  *It's weird, Jenn wouldhave loved it..RIP Jenn :'(*  You know. I'm in love with this blogging thing. Like totally. No one reads it...but just to write and spread my thoughts. It feels awesome.   Oh, I joined a contest today at http://www.peta2.com "I am not a nugget" Yeh, you guessed it , I'm a vegatarien. :P I'm getting some stickers...YAY! :) So fun, so fun.  I just cut my hair, by myself...free hand. About 3 inches off the back. >. .  Ha, 6 days. Just 6...please help me make a countdown.  RIP Jenn * Love ya Hun!
      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ugh. The heat is unbearable! I'm dying here man! The fact that I am wearing jeans, tee shirt and a sweat shirt is getting to me now. o.O  Grad is soon. :( I dont want to leave at the end of this year! No! I can't. Billy is moving this year too! :( Aww well, I'm moving he's moving. We have e-mail, and then the phone. I'll be missing him SO much. Hopefully he will get things straightened out with Joey. Nah, I they will. For sure. *whispers* They're perfect for each other!  *dies* The Heeeeeat! Ack. Ooh, I'm multi-tasking! I'm talking to Billy on the phone, writing this, chatting with various people, sending out invites to the grad party...  I have so many projects for tomorrow..*dies* Someone help me finish all this BULLSHIT! >Religions of the World> 5 to 6 pages >Jeu Questionnaire > 50 Questions  >CrossWord...dont ask. Just dont.  I'm just sitting here, waiting for something to happen...actually, I'm busy, projects and stuff...:S  I hate Alex. I hate him! I hate him! I hate him! *goes crazy* I cant believe I actually talked to him at one point. He sickens me. He got into a fight with Big Brun, and Alex *this other guy, hes a good friend...Ack! Howard!* And I ask him whats going on with that...he goes off at me, as if I had like slapped him. Gawd. Some people at school need Anger Management! He like, its none of your fucking business! get the fuck away from me...BLAH BLAH BLAH!! :( JENN! WE MISS YA! BIG TIME!! :'(  I hava no idea at all of how I am living right now. I havent eaten a "meal" for about a week. I could count on one hand all the things I've eaten from last monday...yuck. Like chocolate milk, 2 pop cicles, some cotton candy, and like half a bad of pop corn. Which I threw up on sunday - I went and drank on saturday...*read previous posts*   I ran track again today...yucky, now I know why I am NOT on the track team...HA! LOL. Gym is hell this year. Hopefully, I can get away with just NOT getting it next year. Hoo Hoo Waa! No track, no running, no PaIn!   Julie hasn't been at school for awhile...because of Jenn...*cries* THIS IS SERIOUSLY FUCKED UP! I can't live like I used to...Bah, fuck it...meh...  Problem...my social worker thinks I'm totally suicidal..or fucked up, or whatever™...He's fucked...totally! I hate him...FUCK YOU FUCK YOU FUCK YOU!  Mookie wants the phone bad...just so Van can call him...then after April..Those girls are SO annoying...Well, I dont mind April. Shes alright...But I hate that Van girl...*yuck*  Right now, I'm talking to Nat's boyfriend, and his friend "pat" Ugh...they're idiots. I hate them. Yet, I talk to them *it kinda makes me wonder* I mean, if you hate someone...why bother wasting your time talking to them...it's pointless...right? I dont know. I guess its just to pass time off...  RIP Jenn* :'( ~Sem 
      
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Billy wants to appear on my blog {bless his soul}. I told him that he already has. Then, he said he wanted to have something happy. So, Billy here we go :P  ..::Billy, I love ya! So so much! I hope that I will see ya more often since I am changing school's this year! You said we'd be friends forever! Keep that promise, I can't live without you. (I dont think anyone could.:D)::..  Anyway. *shrugs* Today, I had P.E. Dammit. We ran 600meters, then went on to the Long jumping. >.  >>Listens to H.I.M Funeral of Hearts It's really awesome. The words make me think. Like, after me and Benn broke up, I dont know how many times I listened to THAT song and just cried. (With Billy of course) He didn't cry as much as me. I dont recall him crying. I recall going shopping and buying some sweats at Roots. With him. Aww, he was with me...Pity Shopping. He bought me a charm bracelet that day too...He got me like four charms. The Irish flag, the french flag, a basketball and a volleyball. So sweet. Now I have a customized one that says Billy & Em BFF. Aww...;)  Another thing to consider...BFF...Best Friends Forever. I doubt it with some people who say it. But Billy and me ARE best friends. :S We shop together, we eat together, we cry together (in times of need) *duh*, he's like my best Gal friend. :D  Alot of noise here. Alex is playing Tony Hawk 4, I'm listening to H.I.M, the phone is ringing, I can hear James and Kaddie {friends of mine} practicing our new song, my mom is shouting at me...Hurrah, I'm talking to like 7 people online, and they are all talking at the same time...*doodleedee*! Arg! I'm trying to work here! *screams*  Nat is at soccer. I hope she won. That would be to awesome, then she could just shut up at school ;).   I took a magazine quiz today. It said I was to depressed for my age group... WTF. They said if they were my parents they would have me put on watch...*sighs* I'm, not going to kill myself. Look face it. I am not the suicidal "type" Well, I am but..I made a promise to Billy. So there. My mom is going nuts. She read my mag and was like, "Well, we should consider it" Whaaaaaaat? No. No. No. No. No! No attitude ajustment! Why me?! Why?!  I went out for some pizza with my friends.  >Jane >Krista >Julie >Lucie >Francois >Alex We were all supossed to go to the park after. But I wanted to go home. Lets start walking eh? Bah, Pizza was awful. Yuck. {Veggie for me :D} We all made GawdAwful drink mixtures. Like Ketshup and vinagire with diet 7up. I drank it. Ew. *vomits* Yuck!  I think I better start working on my NEW french project...*yay* >.< ~S-em
      
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One word; NO.  Last night one of my cousins got married Jackie. Well, for me, this was to be another boring wedding reception, were you know all you're going to do is sit and whine.   Well, it was until Carole asked me if I wanted a drink. Erm, like a REAL drink? She was like whatever™ you want dear. I said, well, how about some Vodka. Without even telling my mom. She went up and got me one. I felt pretty cool. Standing there, with a drink in my hands. Oh yeah! Until the bartender came and asked me if I had some ID on me. I knew I wasn't of age to drink so, I said it was my friends. I was just holding it while she was dancing. He smiled at me and then left. Right at that moment, I knew I couldn't have anymore to drink, or else. But, on a normal trip to the washrooms. I ran into Jennifer, Tina and Amy. All my cousins, all up for a great time. They seen my drink, and they were like "Do you smoke?" That I simply refused to do. Nope. No. That's not me. The drinking was. At the end of the night, I had had a round of Tequilla shooters, 4 Smirnoff's, and a beer. I had never drank before. And, now. I have. I will be going to the next weddings for that side of my family. That was way past awesome! Now, I have a HUGE headache, I can't concentrate, and I'm all shaky...Ew. It was worth it though! Oh Yeah! I think I only did it because I was depressed. I kept the Smirnoff's coming, the tequilla was just another thing. More like a dare. Ouch. I miss Jenn. If she was here, I probably wouldn't have went to the stupid wedding. I would have went to her house to hang out and have some fun joking around. Either that or talked to Billy all night long!   Icky. Billy is also going through some hards times now-a-days. I think he misses Joey. His Ex. Joey and Billy were perfect for each other! I loved double dating with Shane. I was sure Joey had a thing for Shane even if Shane was straight, and Joey was gay. Bah, it's all the same. Billy needs to rest. I think he has always been there for me. I spent the night over at his house almost all week. I didn't go to school. Neither did he. We skipped together. It was great. Until we went in to the corner store to get some slushes and we say him. Joey. There, with a girl in a total make-out session. Now, I was friends with Joey. And he never told me he was Bisexual. What!?   Billy ran out of the store. I stayed there and watched Joey and his "gal" make out for awhile he finally got up, and said to me "Em, what in God's name are you doing?!" I looked at him and told him to check his in-voice, then check his sexuality...before going and using MY best friend - ever again! He just looked at me, and you could see he was embaressed. Well, why!? He seen out the window. There was Billy sitting down on the sidewalk. Probably counting the grains of sand. *sighs* Aww...Billy! Joey grabbed my arm, I pulled away and left to go outside. Fuck the slushes! Billy and I walked all the way home silently. Thing was...we were headed for my place. I wasn't going to stop and say everything I had planned. So I went to my house. When I got there, my parents were gone as for Tom and Mookie. Well, we're alone. Lucky us. Right then I realized my answering machine in my room has over 20 messages. 28 to be exact. Some from Joey, some from Jules, others from Mookie. Oh well, lets "delete" them all so it looks like I care. Deep breath now. Ok. Done.   Billy threw himself on my un-made bed. And just started to cry. Oh, Billy crying. Not a good thing. I looked at him and started crying too. So there we were, crying on a Wensday afternoon, in my bed together. We stayed that way until the phone rang, and I knew it was going to be Joey. It was. He was just talking and ranting and raving about how much he was sorry. I said not a word and hung up. That was the last time I talked to him. And I hope Billy and him get back together after he gets everything right in his life.   ..::Billy! I know you're reading this...and I just want you to know...I love you! And I'll always be there::.. ~S-em
      
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Having a bad day. Or a bad week. Maybe even a bad month. I can't stand this anymore. I can't. I promised Billy I would stop the cutting once and for all. But, I can't cope with Jenn's death alone. I've been with her sister Julie for the last couple of days. Just sitting there and crying. She's 16, and had one sister and that sister is dead. I hate this. Why? Oh Why?! I wish I could know what she's feeling. I am feeling really really bad. Can I imagine her, all alone. For the rest of time. I Love You Jenn! We All Do! R.I.P  My computer breaks down in the middle of the week. I'm totally fucked then. I fixed it myself. I'm really good with computers. Well, I would like to think so. I used to suck at it. But computers were involved in my life at the age of 5! Ok, 11 years later, I'm a computer wiz. Yuck. I won't be fixing anyone's computer for awhile. I haven't left the house for over a week. I only left to go to the Funeral Home, The Funeral and when she was burried. This is too hard for me. I thought I would never say that. *sobs*  When I saw Jenn's boyfriend, the first thing he says to me was "I suppose this is the lowest of the low?" I just stood there, and nodded my head. Afraid that if I would cry, I wouldn't be able to control myself. Julie on the other hand was letting it all hang out. I think that they almost had to get her out of the Funeral Home once or twice. Jenn is already missed. More than I had imagined before. That morning I remember when my English teacher told me. I froze. And asked him if I could go home. He nodded, and said "Well, what do you want me to say Em?" I just burst out in tears. He just let me walk out like that. But I didn't go home. I walked around town until school was actually out. I walked for almost 5 hours. I didn't know where I was going until I passed by Jenn's house knocked at her door. Julie answered. And I just gave her the biggest hug. We stayed in the doorway at least 15minutes. We All Love You Julie!   I can't believe it. It was ALL OVER the fucking news! What!? They called Jenn a "Long-Time Drug Addict" What?! No No No! That's bullshit. Simply. I mean, how could they do that to her? Her family was so pissed off. {Julie, was the most.} At school, this girl said "She died! So what? She was good-for-nothinG! She'll rot in Hell" One of Jenn's cousins came up to the girl, slapped her, kicked her, and was screaming like nuts. I am proud of her! Way-to-Go! That girl deserves to die! (I sound like her! Icky!) Ok, no death wishes!  I wish I could write more...But I can't I am shaking like nuts. It's taking me hours to write this. And no one is reading. Oh, I should go continue my Novel. "Tales of the Disturbed" I have over twenty pages full. I think I might post some up here. But I'm not sure. It's bad. And all these ideas of death my ruin it all! ~S-em
      
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, let's describe THAT.  Today is the tommorow you worried about yesterday...*thinks* How stupid is THAT?!  I worry about everything and anything...I hate suprises, I hate the way the sun rises in the morning, I hate it when everyone seems happier than me, I hate it when people assume just because I wear black means I am goth, I hate the way people ask you how you are when they know you feel horrible most of the time, I hate YOU! I'm no people person, whatchya gonna do about it eh?!  Right now, I'm going through a rough time. I don't know what I expect of life anymore. I mean, what am I supposed to expect of it! If it's like they say "Life is what you make of it" Well then I wont be going to far. Because I hate life, I hate living, I hate everything about the aspect of breathing and existing. I wish I could cease to exist, yeep : that's it!  As you can read, I am a very bitchy person, who hates people. Bah, not everyone...but, you know who you are the people I DO hate. I am not at liberty to say their names, they would obviously deny that they've been really stupid.  Well, I can always write later...Because now I HAVE to get offline before my Mum goes nuts..! ~Em  
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have now decided that I am going to delete all my other Journal/Blog type things. I'll be keeping this one, my LiveJournal, my melo and my MySpace. Four shouldn't be too hard. But people will have to keep checking and checking. =) Oh well, woop-de-fucking-do for them I don't give a shit. It's not like they actually care. I could die tomorrow and no-one would notice. Except for maybe... Mike. Yeah. He would notice, it would be way to peaceful for him... He's at his place now. Not here. I think he only comes here every two weeks so I won't get too lonesome. Heh. It's alright, I don't care. The only thing I miss is Maxx. Tim's cat. *sob* Him and Lucifer [My cat] got along quite well. But now, I'm stuck with a dog... *GRR* Dog's are nice though. Yeah. Blue is pretty cool.  So, I'll try to update this every couple of days. See if it comes out with anything. =\ Probably not. I really can't spell. >. ,  urlLink DeadJournal , &  urlLink Blurty ] They have all the same layout. Really. It's weird. DeadJournal is a tad bit diffrent though. It's just 'darker' [Der, DEADJournal]  I have one of each. But LiveJournal is my favorite out of the four. I really enjoy MySpace &amp; Melo too. Though I am having some problems customizing [totally spelt wrong] my Melo. Weird. I seems so simple. Oh well. MySpace is my favorite of all. It's awesome. =) Anyway, I must be off. I wrote some new songs for Death, and yeah. Some are really cool. [~]Untalented[~]  Speak of later...right? SmilingShay 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Oh my! They changed it again. I should update more often. I guess I've just been to busy with my other ones. I have way to many. And to try to come up with a subject for every one of them would be too hard. I have a... >Blurty >LiveJournal >Melo >MySpace >FaceWhore >Blog *duh* >Greatest Journal Ok, so no wonder I don't find the time... I also have some journal's posted in various MSN Groups. I'm such a space invader. Oh. Almost forgot. I'm over Rick forever. He told me he was staying in Calgary for the school year, since his Grand-parents are willing to keep him. Oh well. Plenty of other fish in the sea I guess. Heh. *sad* I can't help but be. Anyway... I've been mostly updating   urlLink  my melo   , my   urlLink  MySpace    and   urlLink  LJ   ...So, check 'em out if you want regular updates. You may have noticed that my last name has changed on my profile. I've been adopted. Once and for all. I'm probably going to be living here for awhile. I'm out of Tim &amp; C's. =) Now, here with my Gram Gram. Oh, she so nice. But it's late and she can probably hear me... typing... and my limit is like midnight for online crap. So this is it. Until next time, ShyShay [~]    
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Finally. Rick called me yesterday...from calgary...and he's coming back from calgary on August 26th..yay.. He said that he and this girl named *Corrine* are hittin' it off pretty well..*cries* NO NO NO! If he read this he'd be pissed off...hehe...oops? I told him that I didn't mind! What did I do?! When he's here he's all over me;and when hes gone I'm here bitching and whining! Because I want HIM...*blushes* What's so special about Corrine?! [OMG Jenn if you are reading this...I sound exactly like Shane..ack!]Well...enough of this, just thought I would update because I havent in awhile [-]Lots Of Love[+] Until next time dahlings! SophistocatedShay xx 
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      9 THINGS YOU ARE LOOKING FORWARD TO - A shower - Sleeping - Rick's phone call - The Movies with Mookie and Van - Getting some money - talking to that certain someone - finding a new pack of gum - taking off these socks - Going skateboarding  8 THINGS YOU WEAR DAILY - black eyeliner - weird ring thingy - black lipstick - black nailpolish - underwear...(if that's what you mean) - Usually a concert tee shirt - chapstick - weird necklace thingy...  7 THINGS THAT ANNOY YOU -bad spelling/grammar -people who constanly say "lol" -the way nail polish chips off -you annoy me...thats for sure -preps -best "friends" the ones who were there, but betrayed you *coughNATcough* -parents   6 THINGS YOU TOUCH EVERYDAY - my computer keyboard - my clothes - bathroom door - my keys - digital camera - my hair  5 THINGS YOU DO EVERYDAY - brush my teeth - brush hair - chat - sleep - "eat"  4 PEOPLE YOU WOULD WANT TO SPEND MORE TIME WITH - Danielle - Rick - Van - Meagan  3 MOVIES YOU COULD WATCH OVER AND OVER - Eurotrip - Eloise - The Cat in the Hat  2 OF YOUR FAVORITE SONGS AT THE MOMENT - Sliver - Nirvana - Du Hast - Rammstein  1 PERSON YOU COULD JUST SPEND YOUR WHOLE LIFE WITH - Akihito =D  
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I called you tonight. You answered, and then I froze I can't do this anymore I love you. I can't tell you... Because you love her.  I just don't want to hurt you.  Never. 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It would be awesome. But nahh... Of course not.  Lloyd is back from Boston.  Tae's computer is still fucked.  Danielle is still on vacation from as far as I know.  I'm sad and lonely, and have no one to talk to. Except for the nice Finnish dude... Josh. He introduced himself as Ville Valo. Heh. Nice try.  I'm bored. Lame updated... Live with it. SexyShay? 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Weird title, I know... But I'm not even sure myself now-a-days. If someone asked me who I was. I'd say 'Shannon-Emily' But... who 'is' Shannon-Emily. It's such a stupid question! Oooh, who is the girl behind that wretched name? I have no clue. I just consider me... well, me. Just normal. But when people who have known me for a long time, they know I'm not 'normal' But then again... who is normal these days.  I Am...  Small town girl, I am. I don't get out much. I like blue cotton-candy with club soda [Who would have known?] I've always had long hair, I've never cut it short. I've done drugs, and came out of it alive. [Result: I'm fucked up in the fucking head, fuck man!] I had two brother's. An older one and a younger twin brother. I only have one now. Mike, the older brother he's 18. [Xavier August Jean-Louis Beaulne, may you rest in peace] I like to read, I can't read more than one book at a time, otherwise... I get all confused with the story lines and such. I've had pink hair -I swore I knew what I was doing- I like extreme make-up. And clear lip gloss. I hate glasses, and I have to wear them all the time. *Grr* I like emo [No, I'm not emo] Ok, forget that last comment! I don't enjoy labels. Though I am a mix of everything. That;s what I would like to think. I think fast, and I type even faster. I usually end up regretting what I say to certain people. I've made serious mistakes, but it's just basically Live Life And Learn? I am parentless. My mom died when I was young. My dad is some random fucktard. *I hate him* I've been in several different homes across Ontario [It can be a bad thing] But right now, I'm back to VKH. Where I belong! I'm addicted to the internet. Well, not really. Just a bit. I like to drink, not nessicarily 'till I get drunk. But vodka seriously rocks! [Rum & Coke is a must too] I smoke. Too much. I am a perfectionist. I am not afraid to admit I'm perfect! ;) I care for one person and one person only, and that is my dear brother Mike. DUDE, You dissed my pancakes.... in front of Vanny. *insulted stare* How dare you? I am a world known stalker. hehe, Catch me if you can. No one knows what it's like, to be the sad man? I know what it's like. I smile, I laugh and I take prozac. No really. I am suicidal at times. I can get through it without hurting myself most of the time. I am addicted to eyeliner. I like beach towels. The colours... are cool. I am Shannon-Emily. Lesser of two evils maybe? 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate you! I wish you could just die! DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE! Going around talking shit about my friends, thinking my brother is SO into you. Well guess what... HE ISN'T! He hates you more than anything in this world. Just stop. Please, stop trying so hard. It's severly annoying. I hate you.  Anyhow... now that that is over. I would like to point out that that is not directed to my brother's girlfriend, Vanny. No way. I love her. =)  My hair hardly smells anymore, just a light sent of C-R-A-P... No more L'Oréal for moi... And I should really go shopping. School is starting in a month and a half...or so. Anyway, I need new clothes! =) I love clothes. I really want a new guitar. Yeah, I really do. But, I'll wait till I have enough money for clothes, school stuff, piercings, SHOES, a tattoo and then MAYBE I'll get a guitar. Or I should just cut my list down. I don't know. =heh, well this was like a 5 minute update. So yeah. Check out my LiveJournal or something I might be updating those soon. Yeah, peace out... SaVVyShay[~]  
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No way. I didn't let myself do this. It's not like me, and I know better. *sigh* I miss her so much. Mike got back home today. Oh lord, I actually missed him. And yeah, finally got to see his new piercing, it looks, er... Kind of... Icky right now. Soon, I'll get my lip & eyebrown done. Yeah, that'll be awesome. =) Mike said it doesn't hurt at all, well lemme tell you... your tongue HURTS. It wasn't actually THAT bad, and it didn't get infected all that much. I took it out though. It was just annoying me to no end, having that in my mouth... 24/7 [I knew it was a stupid idea] Meh, there goes 80 bucks to waste. All I have left is my ears, and navel. =\ Anyhow. I have a sunburn. Ouch...  Family is falling apart [Atleast what's left of it]  And it sucks. I haven't known them all that long, and I hate them already. Fucktards...  
      
</post>


</Blog>