<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Discuss... 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Football, eh?  Jumpers for goal posts, extra time, baldy geniuses, civil unrest.  What a game though!  Can't wait for our next humiliation.  Wasn't Ledley King good though?   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thought I'd better post a topic (wouldn't it melt in transit?), just to show I am able to.   I bet the Frenchypogs are crapping themselves at the thought of facing that rock that is Carragher. I await Rob's rant about how he's underated and so forth. I will concede that when the alternative is Ledley King he is the lesser of two evils but it is indeed a dire state of affairs.   So I guess my question is what happened to Matthew Upson and what did Wes Brown do wrong? (apart from being ginger)  Mostly Henry will dick on Carragher. Mostly.  Sworth 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       At Jim's request, here is a short, boring story about what happened in London at the weekend for Mike and Rosie's birthday(s).....  Went to Lovell's after work on Friday. The train (Virgin, obviously) was 35 minutes late at Birmingham and proceeded to add a further half hour before even reaching Coventry. An astonishing feat of incompetence, even for them, as I'm sure you'll agree. Should have been at Basingstoke at 9, got there at just after 10. Brilliantly though, the barrel of a train manageress was so busy "dealing" with angry customers and shelling out the equivalent of Africa's combined GDP in taxi vouchers, that she forgot to make me pay. Cool. So that was £42.40 saved (£42.40!!! - wankers).  Went to Ryan's house, saw Richard and Helen too and sat about smoking/joking/licking up Lovell at NBA StreetJam.   Had an enjoyable morning sharing some right-wing views with Lovell's parents before heading to London for Gay-mes in Finsbury Park. Al quite reasonably pointed out that we ought not to play any "traditional English games" for fear of being arrested for stirring up racial hatred. After all, Captain Hook lives around there.  Highlight of the afternoon was when the annoying "noisy throwing toy" got stuck in the tree and Smeaton immediately lost the football up there too trying to get it down. At least an hour of throwing objects at the tree ensued.  There followed a game of (by now quite drunken) rounders in which there seemed to be no consistent rules but rather a steady flow of cheating from key protagonists - notably Hawkins and Lovell. I was no way out!  Afterwards, back to the Manor ladies' boudoir for barbecue and binge drinking. Lovell threw a huge whitey, but handled it as only he can - by making it very funny. The usual crowd in attendance, plus a few extras such as Rhys who came back from Barcelona.  Don't remember too much more about it and made a snap decision to go home immediately upon waking and somehow managed to get to Marylebone and up to Birmingham in one piece. I did however have a great time sleeping on the very crowded train, safe in the knowledge that I was chuffing out nerve gas with a 5-metre kill radius. Barbecue and booze had turned my insides rotten. Brilliant.  Phrase of the weekend:  "I'm going to cut off a length of bum-rope"  Fully expect that to make an appearance in Forrester's links (and also at selected parties).  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I go to portugal tomorrow, mwahahahahahahahah....no football tickets though grrrrrrrrrrrrr   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some of you are getting the hang of this now. Keep adding the comments and allow discussion threads to be created. I'm going to invite more people to the site once you've all had a go at posting and commenting.  If you're not stuck behind a big fat Firewall you should be able to put photos up, like Forrester has. But try and avoid making them MASSIVE.  Carry on. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Is anyone else in awe of Forrester's ability to grasp 'puter-based technology in an instant?  Look at him, with his photos and his profile. It's like some sort of Voodoo!  PS. He's 35! Fucking hell. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Easy  Watching The Return of the King last night, Joel and I got onto the subject of LOTR-related merchandising and product branding. The two main areas of activity were breakfast cereals and medical conditions (not technically merchandise, but so what).  Here is what we have so far, any additional suggestions??  Cereals;  BRAN-dalf Ara-CORN flakes Gondor GRAHAMS   Medical;  Osgiliath-LETE's FOOT Lego-LASSA FEVER Merry-Merry 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What is your favourite food? I really would like to know. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Excellent. J-Bo's web-mongery pays off. Nice to see where our £110 Virgin train fares to London are going.  I commend this site to all you oafs worldwide.  Please feel free to post some pics - especially nudie ones. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is hoped that this site will serve as a central meeting place and forum for all of us renowned for being turd at keeping in touch.  The idea being that everyone adds regular posts about what they're up to, i.e. birthdays, parties, get-togethers, festivals, holidays and general news.  As soon as I've figured out the free photo hosting you'll be able to post photos of your shenanigans. I can see you're excited by that.  I'm sure everyone's got stories to share and invites to dish out, so go for it. This blogging lark is a piece of cake once you get into it. I hope.  James 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What on earth was the music at Greenstock about then?&nbsp; The sun's out, let's listen to some heavy rock.&nbsp; No.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Who's going to Greenstock?  I thought we were all going, but the London crew ahve been a bit quite about it haven't they.  Anyone any wiser? 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I suggest we open a book between us, or some sort of sweep at the very least.  most sixes; most wickets; finalists; winners; pints consumed before sleep etc  any ideas?  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>