<Blog>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aloha,  It's Monday - I have the Monday blahs - I swear I come to work to take a break from my weekends.    I've decided that babies spit-up on people the way that dogs mark trees.  "Okay," they think to themselves, "Here is a brand new person who smiles at me."  Followed by them yaking the slimy white mucus all down your arm, shirt, onto your shoes (hopefully you are wearing some), all over your shoulder, etc.  " There !", they think, "This new person is marked as  mine .  Henceforth, they shall clean my dupa, feed me and otherwise scramble to find out why I'm crying."  Then, they look up at you sweetly and smile toothlessly, and you say, " Awww  - how cute!".    Yes, another baby spit up down my arm.  And then, she grinned at me.  (sigh) - What are you gonna do?   Let's talk about airplane flights.  I booked a flight today - and paid a  good 150.00$ more than I would have paid 10 days ago.  What is up with this bilking of the world citizens.  Shouldn't airfare either stay the same or even go down close to the flight.  I would think that if there are open seats closer to the flight date, they would want to reduce the price to book people on the planes.    With the current system, people are forced to plan their trips well in advance.  If airfare were cheaper, I think there would be more spontaneous traveling.  I spontaneously go to Memphis.  Why wouldn't I spontaneously go to NYC if airfare weren't so damn cost prohibitive?  So, Commercial flyers are a bunch of Punks!   Okay - that's my opinion on that -  Let's move on the new guy on the horizon - Kyle.  Kyle is a sweetie.  Smart, sweet, polite and by all accounts a cutie too.  We talked on the phone for about an hour.  And, we didn't run out of topics.  He did tickle me - he asked me if I knew what OPEC is.  To test my intelligence.  I said, "What? The Gas people?".  Which is still not the best answer.  The correct answer, which came to me about 20 minutes after we got off the phone is Oil & Petroleum Energy Commission.  But, hey - he was just checking to make sure I knew it had something to do with fuel. :)  Which was very cute.  In my opinion anyway.    It's not a bad little question to root out the dumb girls.  And any man worth his salt doesn't want to date a dumb girl.  Well, I take that back - lots of decent men want to date dumb girls - but only because they are insecure.  And I wouldn't want an insecure man anyway.  Confidence is a desirable quality. (wink).  Even average guys become hotties if they are smart and confident.  Aloha! cutesox 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hola,  I saw the new Texas quarter today - pretty slick!  It is my new favorite of the series.  It is very simple - Texas with a big star on it.  And it says "The Lone Star State".  Now, it would have been so much cooler had it said, "Don't Mess with Texas!".   Especially since they are trade-marking that phrase! :).  Talking of Texas, it is always important to note that the Dallas Cowboys SUCK!!!!    Yes - I have strong feelings in that arena.  I am a big football buff.  I love the NFL.  My favorite team is the Buffalo Bill's.  They give me a warm fuzzy feeling.  I'm elated when they win, and quite pouty when they lose.   Being a Bill's fan - I have my own little football axis of evil:  1)  Miami Dolphin's:  Because I'm a Bill's fan.  Duh.  Dolphins gear offends me.  I had to make sure some guy in the bar knew that last night too.    2)  Oakland Raiders:   They are ineffable evil.  They play dirty.  I can't respect a team whose players who make it their modus operandi to cheat and hurt players on the opposing team.  It's evil and I don't like them.  They are a bunch of PUNKS!!!!  3) As previously established, The Dallas Cowboys :  They too, are a bunch of silly punks.  The Cowboys are comprised of Wife beaters, druggies and thugs.  And - Seriously!  Was there an election?  Because I certainly didn't vote them, "America's Team" as they bill themselves.   Clever piece of marketing buck-o - but I'm not buying it.    Yes, I'm passionate about my football.  I love it. I am a fantasy coach.  And I follow it almost religiously.  My Fantasy team is named the, Soul Rippers.  My guy friends teased me that I would have some cute, fluffy name.  Like the Cute Socks or something - Or the pink fluffy bunnies - so I went the extreme opposite with the meanest name I could conjure.    My pick 'em league name is the "Fighting Cacti".  Which amused me for some reason.  But then, I find I get more fun out of life by being easily amused, than by being jaded.  Just for today - Be happy!! cutesox   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a native Yankee - But, having lived in the South for the majority of my life - I have a keen love of iced tea.  And all southerners like their tea Sweet.  Sweet tea is a very personal thing for a southern person.  And so, it is for me as well.  The Yankee part of me still likes my tea good and strong.  It should be a strong brown color.  Like, you know... Tea.  As a southerner, I like it sweet - but not too sweet.    Now, all good southerners know you brew your tea hot and strong (condensed), put in a full cup of sugar.  Mix it in until it dissolves and then mix it with cold water and ice.  Some then set the tea in the sun.  Some add lemon.  Some add verbena.  Some mint.  It's a personal preference.   But I like a half cup of sugar instead of a full.  Which, in most southern eyes is a travesty - but hey - I'm still a Yankee in my bones.  And sometimes I go a little weird - I leave out the sugar all together and add rose water.  It's delicious and will settle an upset tummy. :)  Now - some restaurants do an excellent job of brewing tea.  It's brown, and sweet - but not colored sugar water.  And I'll usually order half sweet, half un-sweet at restaurants where the servers are extra nice - or if it is slow.  However, here, in the South - the capital of Sweet tea - there are those idiotic restaurants who will bring you - yellow tea.  Yellow tea is not tea- it doesn't look like tea - it doesn't taste like tea - it's colored water.  You might as well be serving water.  It's a travesty.    Then, there were the extra "special" (Special BUS!) servers in the Backyard burger drive-thru on Saturday.  They have good strong tea.  I get my tea - and I take a good swig and I thought I was going to hurl - it tasted alllllllllllll wrong.  I looked - the concoction was yellow!  Grrr....  Then, I realized: It's half tea - half lemonade.  WTF?     But at least then, It was palatable.    As everybody knows, when you take a swig of something and you realize it's not what you expected- it's really nasty - like drinking a coke only to realize it's your friend's Dr. Pepper.     Where am I going with this?  Nowhere - I'm rambling - I told you this would happen. (wink)  You  were  warned.   Arivederci, cutesox
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello,  Today was kind of a bummer day - my good friends' dad died.  I didn't know him, but I'm really close to Cindy, and wanted to be there to show my support of her.  She was 100% "daddy's little girl".  Not having a dad - I can't relate.  But, I was so touched at his funeral.    First of all, the place was packed.  Standing room only.  Everyone who knew him came.  How wonderful it must be to know someone you loved, was loved by so many others.  He must have been an amazing man.  The out-pouring of love was phenomenal.    I was doing just fine - no tears - until Cindy went up to the podium to speak.  Woah, Nellie - that's when the water-works started.  Hearing how much she loved him and was feeling his loss, hit me really hard.  Cindy's little brother spoke too.  He was sweet, and funny. It was amazing that they could make us laugh.   They , the bereaved - making  us  laugh.   Their whole family was amazing.  They had a capacity for humor which is rare.  It moved me that even through their tears, they were able to laugh,  and  make us laugh with them.  Very special group of people, Cindy's family.    I must admit to being just a tiny bit jealous of the relationship Cindy has had with her father, and her extended family.  She knows who her 4th and 5th cousins are. :) Which I find amazing.  I know who a couple of second are. But I don't think I could name more than two.  Not growing up in a close, loving family environment like theirs - it's hard to relate.  But I know that it is something rare and special they have.  I really wish my own dad could have been a part of my life, growing up.  So, I could have some of those same strong feelings that Cindy has.    Something else very special about this family is their relationship with God.  Everyone of them, knew that the deceased was close with God.  They had his worn, highlighted bible to prove it.  .  But it wasn't just that - he showed it by actually walking that "path" the clergy is always talking about.  By the amount of love he showed his fellow man.  Not just the love he showed his family.    Everyone who knew him, loved and respected him.  Also, his family felt assurance, that while he isn't with them anymore - He is now with God.   I haven't encountered that before - Complete assurance that your loved one has moved to a better place.  They were sad.  Very sad - but happy at the same time.  Happy that he was with God.  I tell you what... I felt challenged by it.  Challenged to better develop my own relationship with God.  To walk with love.  To be more like Cindy's dad - whom I never met.  But I wish now, that I had.  Have a nice weekend - and do something nice for someone else!!! cutesox
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that is the question of the year - Why are boys stupid?  Perhaps I need to write a small guidebook for men who go out in public.    Disclaimer: I really do like men - provided they don't smoke, have a mullet - or kids by 3 different women.  But Boys have a huge capacity for losing all their intelligence when put in front of women.  It never fails to amaze my friends and I.     Rule #1 :  If I look at you and smile - you can come over.  I think you're cute and want to find out if you're charming.  Rule #2 :  If I look at you and don't smile - please don't come over.  I may be making fun of you.  Rule #3 :  If you offer to buy a girl a drink and she says, "no, thank you" - that is your cue to  go away .    Rule #4 :  If a girl smiles at you, leans in and asks, "So, what are you doing this weekend."  That translates to, "You are cute, so far haven't annoyed me too much - Ask me out".  Rule #5 :  Text messaging is  DUMB .  Pick up the damn phone.  Of course if you are lacking verbally, and will make a complete ass of yourself - don't call - go find a dumb girl.  Rule #6 :  If you are at a bar, and there are girls within ear- or even eye-shot, don't be a pig.  We can detect foul behavior at a distance, we don't need to hear it.  Rule #7 :  If you are on a date with a girl, and you are driving.  Don't order a drink unless she does.  Otherwise she'll label you as an inconsiderate moron.  Rule #8 :  While we are on the topic of inconsiderate morons: If there are girls standing at the bar, while you are sitting - ALWAYS offer up your seat to a standing lady.  This also correlates to opening doors, helping out of cars, not blowing your nose at the dinner table and not using your fingers to push your peas onto your fork before you put them into your mouth.  How old are you? - Three!?  Rule #9 :  Do Not - Do  NOT  wear white socks with black dress shoes.  Don't wear knee high socks (even pushed down) with shorts.  Don't wear socks with sandals in the summer (preferably never - but we can forgive you in the fall) - and do have more than white and/or black socks in your sock drawer.  Let's see some patterns, Gentleman.  Argyle socks are the classic choice.  Rule #10 :  Don't touch a girl unless she touches you first.  Nothing is creepier than a guy who assumes he can get inside your personal space without a direct invitation.  Okay - that's all :) I'll now step down off my soap-box.  I'm sure my friends would have more rules -  but these will do for now.  Ta-Ta, cutesox
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Salutations,  Attention LR Ladies: Okay - Salon Nula is hands down the best place to have your hair cut or colored in the metro area.     She is vunderba (cutesox word meaning: very wonderful)!!!    So, Saturday I once again went to my hair mecca of Salon Nula where the fabulous Nula put those gorgeous blonde highlights in and cut my hair.  Plus, she's really funny - so the two hours it takes to get everything done flies by. :)    Later I took my Little, Chelsea, to the Travs baseball game to volunteer for Big League.  It was fun, she was such a good girl and a big helper.   I finished off the day by picking up Lee Anne from the airport.  I am soo happy to have my partner in crime back :).  She even brought me a present!  - In Key West she bought me this FABULOUS purse.  If you are lucky - I will take a picture of it and post it.  It's a pink and black bustier purse with dangly beads.  Very hip.  Sunday - the adorable, wonderful, angelic, precious, beautiful, sweet, cutie ptitutie honorary niece was christened.  She looked so perfect in her little christening gown.  Her mama and daddy were glowing too.   .  She knew it was her day.  It's so interesting to be with babies and small children.  It's a miracle to look at the world through their eyes.  To see it so fresh, new and magical.    Now we go 180 degrees - Sopranos!!!  Last night was the season finale.  Last week Ade got whacked.  This week - after long speeches and proclamations that Tony S. was backing up Tony B.  - Tony Soprano drove out to the orchard and BLAM - Shot gun to the head.  Blood on the firewood.  Johnnie Sack wasn't happy.  But hey - he's been busted by the Feds - kind of serendipitous actually.  I still think that at the end of the show - Tony's gonna get whacked - or go into witness protection or something - and Paulie Walnuts will be the head of the family - to me that would be comedic.  It would send me into fits of giggles.    Round off with today - Okay - if you are going to be on TV - and there is any chance you will be within 500 feet of go-karts - wear pants.  Today, for my Big League TV spot on the Channel 7 morning show, I wore a flirty blue skirt.  And much to my surprise, the news guy was all about some go-karts.  Meanwhile, I'm in a skirt!  But, I'm not one to let a little detail like that stop me from having fun.  So, away I went holding down my skirt.  And even though I lost - I think, and the ladies in the studio agreed, I really did win the race after you add in technical adjustments for the skirt  .   But I take satisfaction in knowing that I'm a better putter than KB :)  Bwa-ha-ha-ha-ha!  Sayanora, cutesox
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay - So after work, yesterday, I go baby-sit MM and JL.  MM is 2 and JL is about six months.  I love little kids.  Especially kids like MM.  She's too cute.  But, when they throw up all down your side and onto your foot...the "ICK" factor makes you think twice about having your own.    Yes - spit up between your toes is definitely something that makes you stop and think about whether or not that extreme life style change is something you want to be a part of.  Of course, then they look up at you and smile.  Your heart becomes a puddle of "AWWW" gooiness, and you hug them close and say, "Oooh - I want one of these".    If you are truly intended to pro-create, the little darling *won't* puke on you a second time.  If, however, they choose that moment to splatter you again with breast milk - you may wish to avoid the experience. No, JL didn't treat me to anymore viscious spit up.  But it was sufficient enough an "ICK" moment to last me the entire week.  What else:  Oh, yeah - Cajun Snow is the BEST place in all of Little Rock to get snow cones.  The grape is my current favorite.  It's nestled in Hillcrest. Look for the oodles of people standing around a shack.  Hasta la Pasta, cutesox 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Spring Daffodils the sequel - :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Spring Daffodils&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello -  Everyone else in the world has a blog - and I thought to myself, "Self - why not you?".  Everyone has something to say.  Whether or not it's relevant doesn't really matter.  We all have a voice - even if no one is listening.    I'm a rambler - what I ramble about will generally depend on what goes on in my own life.  Or perhaps what bugs me about the world at large - and trust me - I'm a girl who has an opinion about everything - so you've been warned.   .  Hopefully this site will be fun and therapeutic.  And if you are at all entertained - bonus. :)  Just remember - sometimes I'm a "stream of consciousness writer"- so if I ramble (and I will) - that's just part of who I am. :)  And remember: Just for Today, Be Happy :)  cutesox
     
    
</post>


</Blog>