<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            It was the end of my shift and I still have'nt made up my mind.  There was a very strong typhoon going on outside at Signal No. 1 and the wind was blowing skirts up everywhere.  After a few minutes of pondering over a cup of lukewarm company paid chocolate , I decided..I'm gonna go.  I hate lining up for a movie.  I hate it when it gets noisy in the theater.  And I ABSOLUTELY hate noisy KIDS running around in the theater. But alas, my desire got the better of my sense of comfort.  I'm going to see  SPIDERMAN 2 . I had my reservations at first.  The first one was good, but not spectacular.  I saw it in Angeles City when I was still a tutor along with my brother and some friends on premier night.  My expectations were that this would be a clone of what Superman 2 was.  You know, when Superman got fed up of being Superhuman and not being able to be with the love of his life, therefore sacrificing his powers.  You know what THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I GOT! However, as I recall,  I lLOVED Superman 2. Although  SPIDERMAN 2  recycled an old formula, it was a tried and tested formula nonetheless. It works...for superheroes, at least. Sam Raimi's treatment of the new Spiderman movies concentrates more on the personality of Peter Parker.  It doesn't take a lot to figure Spiderman out. He swoops in whenever there's trouble, saves the girl, boy, puppy whatever the case may be.  Puts him down on a street or a park, says a lame joke and takes off.  Peter Parker is a more complicated character.  Conflicted by the his dead end job, his schooling and of course the love of his life Mary Jane and his "responsibility" as vigilante savior to the people of New York,  Peter Parker lives a dual life that's taking him closer to the edge.  He comes to a point where he doen't know who he is anymore, you know kind of like how we are sometimes. Alfred Molina is the perfect Dr. Octopus. It seems like Spidey has a penchant for schizos for enemies.  The way Henry Osborn as conflicted Gollum- wise was similar to how Dr. Octavius was controlled by his AI  mechanical arms.  Funny he never got any superpowers but was able to resist  large chunks of brick and concrete without bleeding. Hmmm, just an observation. The real gem here was the human storey of Peter Parker and his struggles to live a normal life.  Although, we know know what he chooses in the end. All in all  SPIDERMAN 2  is a great summer movie fit for a good night out. It was definitely better than the first.       
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I live in a very densely populated part to San Andres bukid where you see kids playing badminton in the streets and young girls flirting with the jobless young college graduates.  If you walk a little southward of Zobel Roxas street, you will see an old tindahan in the corner placed below an old residence made of wood. Look into the street crossing Zobel Roxas where the tindahan is, you'll see a small red room extending from the tindahan' side like a big red tumor.  I say red because the room is colored blood red. If you look at ti really hard it will look familiar to you if you saw Mark Meily's "Crying Ladies".  That's the small shack Sharon Cuneta's charagter lived in as a single ex-convict trying to make ends meet working for a chinese store owner.  The tindahan was Hilda Coronel's character's sari-sari Store.  The rickety second floor apartment was Edgar Mortiz's character's house where most of the "noise" going into Sharon's room comes from. Mark Meily's "Crying Ladies will be shown in This year's CineManila opening tommorrow, to be held at Glorietta 4. I recommend you seeing it because it proves how much we can improve if we just forget about all that cheesy hollywood stuff.  Not to say that there wasn't a tinge of hollywood in it.  The idea was very original. It was our own.  No cruise ships, no European cities as settings, just a simple story of a simple woman with a really strange job that is unique to the Philippine culture.    urlLink  Speaking of film locations, here are some more...   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been having problems with soap lately. I am in the process of making a study on what the most effective soap is.    Safeguard   is nice, fragrant and very recognizeable. It has a smell that I have gotten used to as I grew up. The beige colored Safeguard is the most commonly used soap, I think.   I have also tried using   Zest  . One thing about Zest is it gets very hard when it dries up, so whe you try to use it for the millionth time it feels like its brand new, only smaller. However it feels like its loaded with chemicals you know, something "industrial"  like what the that fish guy on "The Beach" wanted    Lifebuoy   is very fragrant. you can put lifebuoy in a tray half filled with water and youll have it turn to mush, but your bathroom will smell like the pirated version of eternity sold in Greenhills.  Whatever soap you use, just make sure you dont do what my friend in Cebu did. He was a little too close to the toilet....        
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            I feel sorry for Britney Spears. Sure she's the most popular girl in the world.  Millions of dollars.  Thousands of guys after her. However the way things are going, her image change from schoolgirl to slut, the 2 day Las vegas wedding/divorce,she must be inches away from losing her marbles. Then suddenly, this.... Just recently another story hit the papers concerning Britney Spears being involved in an accident.    Britney's mom accidentally ran over a paparazzi photographer after shopping for a pet at a local pet store. Britney apparently went into a panic attack after hearing what was described as a "sickening crunch" when the un"lucky" (corny pun intended) photog's leg got caught in the path of the left front wheel.  Britney was so upset by what happened that she had to be consoled by the ambulance driver (intended for the photographer!)  The photographer had to wait for treatment on the sidewalk after they were done with Britney.The driver held her hand as she bawled, mascara trail dripping down her cheeks.  She was clinging on to the new dog she had just bought at the pet shop.  The pet was to keep her spirits up while she was recuperating from knee surgery she had which injury was the reason for the cancellation of ther world tour.     Inches....just inches away.  ..or maybe it's just the stress she gets from studying Semiconductor Physics? Click the image to view this page.    urlLink         
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ever wondered what you would do in case your parachute failed to open during your routine weekly sky jump?  Lets say you rode Cebu Pacific on the way to your lola's birthday when..shucks! The pilot choked on an airline peanut and passed out leaving the crucial task of landing to YOU!!! Lets say you were able to successfully crash-land the plane on the waters between Masbate and the Sibuyan Islands, you swim (or float), awaiting the next thing that flies accross the sky to signal for help, then suddenly....SHARK ATTACK!!! All of this during a nasty rainstorm with thunder and lightning...in the open ocean.  My favorite Worst-Case Scenario is "Wrestling free from an Alligator".  Click on the image for more fun "Worst-Case Scenarios"!     urlLink       
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            It was 2:30 in the afternoon, the end of my shift.  I was ready to grab my bag and log out and take the bus to Pampanga after a long week of call center work whe I realized one thing.  Once I get home, no one will be there.  What can I do to  pass the time?  I remembered one of my office mates who is very fond of Korean and Taiwanese movies has this vcd of  "My Sassy Girl (Yeoupgi Jeogin Geunyeo) " .  When I was teaching Korean expats in Angeles City 2 years ago, my students couldn't stop talking about this movie.  They even showed me jpegs of the two main characters in Korean high school uniforms  flashing IDs on a bar owners face (see image below).  I always dismissed this as patriotism, being that Koreans have very rabid "love your own" attitude. So I grabbed it, "this should keep me occupied."        I am not a romantic film buff.  I prefer independent releases and epic war movies. But there was something in  "My Sassy Girl"  that kept my interest for more than two hours.  I'm not big on the whole "destiny" thing.  Sure as heck, don't believe in it. But "MSG" comes across as being melodramatic and funny without being cheesy.  It does'nt abuse the " kilig " factor which a lot of our movies use as life support. No "Aga-Kristine"-type romance here. I heard that the lead characters aren't that popular in Korea in the first place.        The guy,  Cha Tae-hyun , is a pop singer and this was his first feature. Ge kind of reminds me of Ranier from  StarStruck  for some reason.  One cool thing about Tae-hyun is his facial expressions while watching Sassy Girl puke her guts out on the old man in the wig. He comes out as a lovable sissy when they break into a theme park only to be kidnapped by a runaway soldier.  Jun Ji-hyun , only had a previous mediocre role in the movie   "Il Mare"   to her credit, but shines as Sassy Girl.  I didn't really get hre name in the movie.  She plays a really convinving drunk, a girl asking for trouble, a fragile wounded soul all in one breath. Plus, she's funny. The high heel shoes chasing scene is a classic. There were also some  parts in the movie that just made me go hmmm.. like in the first motel scene where Tae-hyun comes out of the batthrom butt-naked after answering the phone to be asked where  Sassy Girl is to be picked up in her drunken state, and the police come  seconds  later just as he is about to pick up a towel to hide "himself".  Another one whoud be during the "train game" scene with the lipstick line on the train floor. Although this may be one of the funniest scenes in the movie, the sudden appearance of a patrol of soldiers  in a public train  is rather implausible.     This film comes highly recommended for the idiots (myself included) who had ecountered their own "Sassy Girl" at one time or another.  It will remind you of the time you got beaten up by a girl but didn't mind. When she drew attention to the both of you and you just wanted to shrink in shame. And when how much you missed her when she was gone. For the rest of you normal folk, its a good two hours of  fun while learning Korean phrases like "Ya!  ju-le?"   ("Hey, wanna die?")          10 ways to win the Sassy Girl....    1. Don't ask her to be feminine. 2. Don't let her drink over three glasses. She'll beat someone. 3. At a cafe, drink coffee, not coke or juice, . 4. If she hits you, act like it hurts. If it hurts, act like it doesn't. 5. On your 100th day together give her a rose during her class. She'll like it lot. 6. Make sure you learn fencing and squash. 7. Also be prepared to go to prison sometimes. 8. If she says she'll kill you, don't take it lightly. You'll feel better. 9. If her feet hurt, exchange shoes with her. 10. She likes to write, encourage her.      
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            You've probably heard about the new Documentary Feature by filmmaker Ramona S. Diaz about former first lady Imelda Marcos aptly called "Imelda".  I can't wait to get a DVD and show it to my grandpa.  It would be hilarious to see him cuss like a sailor in front of the TV again.  The last time he did that was during People Power.     urlLink  click here  for the "Imelda" movie official website.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Have you ever seen a movie where you come across a character and said to yourself, "...maybe (insert actor or actress' name) would have played that part better". Or gone through a terrific movie with one flaw--one character that wasn't given justice, not because the actor was bad, but because the part just didn't fit him.  I bet you have encountered cases where a whole movie was ruined because one of the major characters was "Just Not Right". Well, let amaze you with my vast stock of useless knowledge and give you   my list of  "Top Ten Most Painfully MIscast Roles" in both Phillipine and International movies.  Enjoy.          10. Sean William Scott as Kar- Bulletproof Monk  Sure he trained for the role.  He had moves. He had skill.  But it's hard to see him without thinking of the perverted Stifler humping the back end of a pickup truck in American Pie.        9. Kris Aquino as the Activist Leader- Dekada 70  Although she only had a bit part in the movie as an Activist leader with a megaphone  rallying the students around her at Palma Hall, she had the gargantuan role of convincing the "real" audience  that a spoiled Atenista who has more regular facials and body scrubs than her monthly period can actually pass of as a student leader sympathetic to communist inclinations. Sad to say, she failed.        8. Lito Lapid as Lapu Lapu - Lapu Lapu  Im sure he had good intentions with this movie.  Truth be told, I admire the effort he took in learning Cebuano and reseaching for the role. The fact of the matter is, The idea of a Kapampangan playing the role of a visayan tribal leader just doesn't jive with me. Plus did you notice that he was clean-shaven? Lapu-Lapu's "tabak" was probably as sharp and as close as the Gillette Mach 3        7. Harrison Ford as Alexei Vostrikov -K19 The Widowmaker  Come on, who was convinced with his terrible Russian accent?        6. Edward Norton as Steve - The Italian Job  I love Edward Norton.  He's one of my favorite actors. I like him particularly in  American History X  and  Fight Club . He is good as the everyman, the uptight white collar slave, the neo nazi, the helpless victim.  He just isn't "hateable", which is why he was wrong for the part.  Steve was a snitch, a crook with no word of honor. He stole from the people who trusted him.  This guy was supposed to be satan. He still ends up being the nice guy that he is.  I actually felt sorry for him in the end.         5. Diane Kruger as Helen -Troy  Who was this girl anyway?  Helen's character acording to Homer's Iliad was supposed to be so alluring and beautiful that men would fall in love with her on the first glance and "launch a thousand ships".  The Producers could have done better by putting in some unknown model-type girl and not baywatch-type Diane.  There is a movie currently in circulation in the pirated CD section of your local palengke called  "Helen of Troy" . Sienna Guillory played Helen (see image below) and she was good for the part too.  If only they could find someone like her to have played Helen in  "Troy" .               4. Colin Farell as Bullseye -Daredevil  The role was originally offered to, but turned down by Vin Diesel.  Colin is very good as the sleazy, slick hustler or the pretty badboy, but not as a bald superhuman villain with a nervous tic. Bob Goldthwait would have done a beter job. Plus, Colin has an oddly shaped head not like Diesel's  well defined dome. To see him bald just adds my disrespect for the character.        3. Daryl Hannah as Cynthia Carter - A Walk to Remember  Dont you think its a little bit too early for Daryl Hannah to be accepting teenage-son-advice-giving mommy roles. Sure theres Susan Sarandon  and  Diane Keaton, but Daryl is nowhere in their age bracket.        2. Al Pacino as Big Boy Caprice- Dick Tracy  Sure he was a gangster. The Godfather. Michael Corleone. Aside from being one of the worlds greatest screen actors, he broke the mold of the gangster image.  To see him play another stereotypical gangster was just pitiful. Maybe he was in it for the costume.        1. Robert de Niro as Fearless Leader- Rocky and Bullwinkle  I have to be honest.  I didnt watch this movie all the way through.  It was just too painful.  Did Bobby do it out of love for the character.  Good heavens, I dont think he did it for the money. There was even a part in the movie where the director shamelessly had him utter the words that he made immortal as Travis Bickle ("Are you talkin' to me?") in Taxi Driver with a silly  nasal pinched voice. He  was so cool as the unstable Travis but he killed that for us.  I wonder if he was on crack while  making the deal for this movie? 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
              In the rock and roll world, when you hear the name Dream Theater, your'e talking hard guitar and keyboard licks complex chord progressions, odd time signatures but most important of all, netherworldy melodies and rhythms so difficult to reproduce that even the most accomplished musicians in the rock and roll world would be left scratching their heads saying, "how the f*&k did they do that?"  I had been looking for their album  "Six Degrees of Inner Turbulence " for the longest time.  I had already previously purchased their latest album   "Train of Thought"   from one of my  "Quiapo contacts"  (wink, wink, nudge, nudge).   "Six Degrees..."  was never released locally. It took me two years to finally get myself a pirated copy.  I was not dissapointed.  The album starts off with  "The Glass Prison" . This song picks up where the left off in   "Scenes from a Memory"  ...static, but what comes after that is everything but.  The highight of the first disc is the epic  "The Great Debate" .  A song with the the controversial experimentation on stem cell research as the theme. On some of the dreamtheater.net message boards, the fans provide very interesting commentary on the objectiveness of this song with regards to the morality of the topic.   The second disc contains just one song, the 43 minute theme of the album  "Six Degrees of Inner Turbulence" . This song, is in my opinion, Dream Theater's crowning achievement in terms of song lyrical content. It does not fall short of the technicalities of the first songs in their early albums, although they save up on showing off their chops on this one, which is always a good thing. Its good to know that they have finally concentrated on really making songs that one can ponder on instead of their extended music tutorials.  They had also previously made some real lyrical content improvements with "Scenes from a Memory", this one takes it to the antiseptic-smelling hospital halls, the screams from the isolation chambers and the silent cries for help in the suburban front yard.  The central theme of the song is a six part study on mental instability.  The first cut is the  "Overture"  or a summary of the music thgemes throughout the song.  It then kicks off with  "About to Crash"  which is about manic depression. A very toouching portrait of a man's love for his delusional wife.  "War Inside My Head"  is a heavier section with a  take on Post Traumatic Stress Syndrome, or war shock. One may relate to this as John Rambo's condition in   "First Blood".  I didn't quite get the exact theme on "The Test that Stumped Them All" other than some references to shock treatment and solitary confinement on a padded cell. It slows down with  "Goodnight Kiss"  about a child dealing with the loss of her mother. My favorite part is  "Solitary Shell"  which is about autism.  It's jazzy, almost alternative tone kind of sets this section apart from the rest of the song and kind of gives it a reverent homefront type feel. have a cousin who is autistic and could relate to the lyrics narrating the behavior.   "As a boy he was considered somewhat odd,  kept to himself most of the time... ...but in every other way, he was fine".   I bet he'd like this song too if he could get a chance to hear it.  I gave him my  Rush  "Test for Echo"   and I heard he he loves it. We are all a little insane, sometimes we have the guts to admit it, but often times it is much easier for us to just label someone elsa as insane to make ourselves feel better.  All in all, this is probably is the best album I have listened to in the past two years. Ironically, this album had already been previously released for two years. This album restored my faith in music as an escape to another world, which is always a good thing, considering the present situation.   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      500 friends.  Well it has been ages since I touched my friendster account.  I only finally got to manage it today. It all started out as a way for me to waste company money while not taking calls. January saw the end of a very gargantuan queue over the hoidays.  My friendster account was getting really boring.  Everybody I knew who ever bothered to create an account was already in my friends list.  Those who I invited, but didnt know personally, either accepted my invitations, you know, just to be polite, or rejected them because they thought I was psycho. My online life was going to the dogs.  Then I got this bright Idea.    Since most of the people I invite at friendster are girls (pretty ones at that),  I thought, "Why not create a profile just for girls, -- Kapampangan Girls!"    I originally used one of my junk email ads as the target email ad and signed up as "Deng Mangalagu". Kapampangan for  "the pretty ones" .  First, I invited the ones I knew.  Made testimonials for them. It was pretty standard it went:   _____ is a CERTIFIED KAPAMPANGAN BEAUTY!!! 'ala ng lalagu pa kareng KAPAMPANGAN!!!   Come February, girls were starting to ask for invitations to my new profile.  I got an average of 10 friend requests a day. I was lucky to get 3 in a day in my personal account. Surprisingly enough, a lot of these girls hail from the States and Europe.  The testimonials they give are equally amusing.  Here are som examples:   "Pampanga chicks have a touch of elegance, an aura of sophistication, are intellectual and are gosh dengit very beautiful indeed. I miss Pampanga! Y'all will always rock and I'm proud to be one indeed! We'll forever be malagu =P Mwa to all!"    -Christine      "ahahahaha!!!kapampangan r indeed damn pretty nd hella kewl...juz l0ok ol dosh kapampangz..such a switteheart nd possess fascinatin beauties...lolz proud 2 be one of them...talagang mangalagu tmu...tnx fer addin me hir...ala ng makasambut keng lagu tmu dba?..aite den...ima bawnce off fer now...god speed!!!KAPAMPANGAN BEAUTIES...KIP ROCKIN...>>>payce outz! :P "    -Glad'z Haven     "dAkAl pUnG sAlAmAt aT mIyAbE kU kEnI... tAlAgAnG aLa nG lA2gU pA kEkA tAmU nEh?! hEhEhE!!! aBa aKiT dA nMn iNg kAtUtWaNaN nEpO? lAwEn dA nAmU rEnG kEkAtAnG pIcS... lOl!!! kApAl... jOkE... bAsTa iNg aSaBi kUmU iT's sO nYc 2 bE hErE, KAPAMPANGAN ROCKS!!! mOrE pOwEr 2 aLl oF DengMangalagu!"    -Uber Luvr      "The true beauty of a woman is reflected in her soul; it is the caring that she lovingly gives, the passion that she shows; The beauty of a woman with passing years only grows ..." Kapampangan beauty reigns forever!     -Nikki     "im proud to be a kapampangan... eventhoguh im here in us.... i agree dat all kapampangan are beautiful....salamat king meg create keni....u rock....KAPAMPANGAN BEAUTY RULEZZZZZZZ......peace out!!!miss ko na pampanga.....huhuhu!? "    -GkRiEkYaZy,	     I laughed when I read this one:   "haha.. (cute nmn neto..)all ya kapampangan gurls out there.. be proud of who u r!!! fuck ol those ilocanos and bisayas.. cuz we're the pretty ones!!! hahaha.. PEACEOUT!!"     --Angela      "I'm in Sales & Marketing so i always meet different kinds of people, usually the male species when they learn that I'm from Pampanga they would always have this same line that goes..."Kapampangan ka? Ahh kaya pala maganda ka!" kasi daw magaganda ang mga kapampangan.THIS IS TRUE! Need i say more?"     -Shanna	    One very important thing I learned with this experiment is that Kapampangan Girls like to set themselves apart.  They like the fact that they are being considered the prettiest of all Filipinas.  It has, I think, something to do with the Kapampangan pre-disposition of being "mayabang".  Just as much as the Ilocano has the same of being "kuripot".   I even had a guy congratuate me for reaching 500 friends.  I would have posted his message but of course, silly me, I accidentally erased it.  I was in a rush to make the second account.  We have a firewall in the office banning Friendster to be accessed through the intranet.  Luckily, all you need to do is poke the refresh button a few times, the login page gets to resolve.  I still havent put in my verification code but i already had 2 friends waiting to be accepted.  Not to mention some copycats like "lalagu lagu girls" and "Kapampangan Hunniez".  Ms Zhang Ziyi is my image model.  She'd be proud            
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            It was still 7:51 and I was already at the main entrance of the Caliente bar. "Hintay, hintay ka muna pare, wala pa kasi yung mga ticket, sorry", aplolgozed this long blonde haired guy in black leotards and 5 inch soled workboots. One by one came these troops in black, with smokes in onehand and their pocket in the other. T-shirts with the logos of Slayer and Deicide(?) silkscreened at the front. And Tattoos, holy crap. Tattoos. Where was I?  This was supposed to be my reintroduction to the Phillipine metal scene. I had been away from this crowd for so long it started out as very foreign to me, but after five minutes it all started to kick in. The attitude, the angst, ths smoke, the volume and the ocasional hawking ans spitting. Not to mention the generic chant "Rawk on, bebe".  Of course I was sitting in as quiet little corner in the bar when the first band came in.  KRONOS  was their name. I was impressed by the drummer, who was a chick. Their vocalist , who was also a chick did some really ear-splitting banshee wails in some parts of their set that got the crowd.  Then there was the second band  LAVOS BECKON , which wasnt very impressive except for the guitarist who was probably too young to drink. He was carrying this 7 string RJ and was doing scales. I thought to myself, "these young guys get better and better" I was just sourgraping by looking unimpressed during the whole set.  The others were a blur, not very impressive musically. There were a few noteworthy moments though, like this death metal makeup band  ARCHAIC ARGOT , with a singer who drew a knife and was doing stabbing actions to his stomach. One time, he actually exposed the large scar in his tummy probably from some surgical procedure or a childhood accident. Fear was their tool. I just hope he went and actually stabbed himself on stage. He would have done us a big favor.  Then there was this comic/novelty death metal band called  CHAMBER 69 . Here's how their set went..   "This song is called WRRRAAAAAOOOOUUUUUGGGHH!"   (2/4 beat drums with bass and shredding distorted guitar for about 2 minutes)  "WRRRAAAAAUUUOOOOOOOOOGGGHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH"  STOP.  audiernce applauds.   "Thank you, this next song is called "Genital Herpes"   (2/4 beat drums with bass and shredding distorted guitar for about 2 minutes, again)  "WRRRAAAAAUUUOOOOOOOOOGGGHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH"  STOP.  audience applauds.   Thank you. They leave the stage.   Up to this moment I still cannot figure out what the freak that was all about.   The highlight of the night was  FUSEBOXX  and  ETERNAL NOW . I came there especially for  FUSEBOXX  and I have to say that aI was not dissapointed. Their "Outlet" saga was probably the best piece of pinoy prog metal I have listened to since Wolfgang (although formatting their songs like YES and Dream Theater Songs does not exactly make them Progressive).  I even bought their independent release  "Listen"  being sold at the club entrance.    click image to see their site:  urlLink         I can say  ETERNAL NOW  are a bunch of aliens who took the bodies of Filipino college students and to be able to play in their clubs and share their otherworldy music. Wow, can this band play. Their lead guitarist is obviously the leader and architect of the group. Dream Theater's influence is very heavy on these two groups. And I love Dream Theater!  The night was worth it.  To say the least.  I would do it again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Its time that we acknowledge the inner geek.  Check out this neat article about...  urlLink Superhero Duels!    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I love music.  I cant live without music.  I have been listening to music since I was five - when everyone else was either still sucking their thumbs or sniffing on their stinky blankets, I was listening attentively to my Father's Chuck Mangione albums and my Uncle's Steve vai Tapes. Every Song has a part that just defines it. My favorite song part is Pearl Jam's "Evenflow" In the near-end part of the song, the band just slows down and tones down with Jeff Ament just grooving on the bass.  In the Music video, you might recall this as the part where Eddie Vedder climbs up the stage's scaffolding to prepare to jump into the audience. At the end of the 8th chord block they erupt into a loud last block after which Eddie bursts with an "EEEvenfloooow!". This song defined my teenage years.       urlLink  Here are the 50 coolest song parts of all time.     urlLink  Click here  for Chuck Mangione's Site.     urlLink  Click here  for for Steve Vai's site.       
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So many "jolog" definitions on the Net and yet most are inaccurate.  I asked my students the origins of the word and they gave me all these palusot (weak reasons)--that it's the baduy, bakya crowd of the 90's, that like cockroaches, their number is legion, and they are here to stay. Seems that to most of them, it's even cool to be jolog, better than being coño. And though the pa-coño kids (junior social climbers) are frowned upon, the worst type of poseur, according to them is someone who's feeling urlLink  jolog.               
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay I had just started my first blogsite.  It has been a while since I checked friendster and I miss it.  This blog will be about nothing.  You hear me,  NOTHING!!!  I wish I could write about urlLink  Harry Potter  ,but I haven't seen it.  I wish I could write about how much urlLink   The Day After Tommorrow  sucks, but I have not seen it either.     
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             Wow, the new  Star Wars Movie  title is finally out.  Release Date is   May 19, 2005  .  Everyone else is in, along with  Peter Mayhew  who reprises his old role as   Chewbacca  . It doesn't seem, though, that we will be seeing a young   Han Solo  . Mace Windu (  Samuel L. Jackson  ) is set to die a hero's death in this movie.  The is also a rumored second duel between   Skywalker   and   Dooku  .  Well let's keep our fingers crossed.  May the   Force   be with you...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             Ever heard of that urban legend of the crafty "pasahero" who always brought P1000 in his pocket to pay the jeepney at 6am.  He always got free rides because the jeepney driver (considering that it was morning and it was his first run for the day) could not provide change for his P1000. This happened every day. The jerk would wait for this particular jeep and pay the same P1000 bill and the irked driver would always have to give it back. One day the driver got sick of the guy and decided to prepare.  He had accumulated quite a number of .25 centavo coins that day and managed to come up with P1000 worth of .25 cent coins. Morning came and the same scenario ran, Jerk pays up. This time the driver hands him an SM bag full of P.25 centavo coins.  The driver laughs allong as he drops the idiot to his stop, carrying a 5 lb bag of quarters. Oh the frustration if that bag were to just rip open. Well the reason I tell this story is because, It happened to me this morning.  Only I didn't intentionally leave just P500 in my pocket. I go to work at 5:30 am and I rode the trycycle to get out of the subdivision I live in. Needless to say he was pissed.  He brought me to the next gas station to get change.  As if we weren't down on our luck being in this mutually irritating situation, the gas station didn't have loose bills either...BUT...they do have a lot of 5 pseo coins.  Hence I was handed a bag of P5 coins, straight from the bank.  I had to bring this bag in my hefty bag and count the stupid stack at my work desk.  I got P450! I was duped! This Sucks!  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Ever wondered why there are sooo many pretty girls in Friendster?  I mean, A lot of my "not-so-pretty" friends get crowded Inboxes full of invites because of one picture they have on their profile that was caught in a good angle and in good light. Merong nagpapa-cute, Merong galit kunwari, merong nakalabas ang dila, merong naka panty, merong anime, merong artista merong baby picture kahit bawal daw.  Theres this really cool site that explains all this.  urlLink Click here  to see what I mean.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For a very short while, they took the firewall off of Friendster in the office, I took all the opportunities to log in and make changes.  I changed the profile info and took out that cheesy poem I had made for a special someone (It seemed inappropriate to share such a private piece of aesthetic "gem" for such a shallow cause).  I also changed the background on my MySpace profile. Now the firewall is back up again.  Invites come in trinkles now.  Not like before, however contributing to this would be the fact that I can't log in and invite more girls, it's the self invitations that keep it going.  Its surprising that I still have 27 pending friend requests in DengMangalagu 1 after having 501 members.  Anyway, check out what I got....      
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             Funny, Infuriating,and Creepy  .  These are the words that best describes the Ramona Diaz docu-drama " Imelda ". I had been waiting for the movie since I first came to hear about it.  I was very pessimistic that it would not be shown in local theaters, adding the fact that Imelda herself  filed a motion not to show the movie. The courts ruled a restraining order on the premier to 24 days. 24 days ain't that long. The movie was a feast for the eyes of Imelda bashers.  The shoes, the singing, Marcos' dead corpse covered with wax, everything you could ask for. It started out with good notes on Imeldas roots to her apparent nervous breakdown during Old Ferdie's senator days until the early years of the regime when she started making goodwill tours to Libya to talk to Q'addafi (or Kaddafi, I still dont know how to spell it) to attending state dinners in the White House.  A lot of the resource persons had a lot of good things to say about Imelda.  Things take a bizarre turn when she starts to explain her existential theories on the Cosmos and "Peace and Order" on a piece of drawing pad as referenced on her  her " book "  ,"  The Circles of Life  ". "We have many gods but one Creator" she says, as she draws an apple shaped figure in the pad. This movie turned out to be a very fascinating trip into the psyche of the "Iron Butterfly".  A journey into origin of her wacky logos for the "  Bagong Lipunan  " programs and her narcissistic claim to be the embodiment of th Filipino People, "Loving and Beautiful". Most of the things that gives Imelda away are the actual things she says.  It's amazing how level Diaz was in the treatment of the issues.  She had reason to be.  She was deep in the belly of the beast having to interview Imelda's closest friends and confidantes and was careful not to ask the wrong questions.  The opposing opinions were provided by American statesmen and filipino Matial law journasists.    Fr. James Reuter   gave sume very funny coimments on how Imelda would not shut up for 4 straight hours. The treatment was so even and balanced we really have a hard time deciding who Diaz is siding with. We all know, however, that this is the most effective way to catch a fish...with it's own mouth.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          At last  Angelo De La Cruz  is free.  The nation is in a state of euphoria as one of its hardworking sons who was struck by the great misfortune of being in the wrong place at the wrong time, had his luck turned around through good decision making and heartfelt prayers from home base. Being a fellow Kapmpangan , I feel glad and proud to be of the same bloodlines as Angelo, I'm sure Kapampangans love all the attention too.  We are again center stage in this great cinematic moment of global proportions. After all the prayers, the glorious homecoming. After all the pancit has been eaten and all the media turn their attention to the next salvage victim across the street...in comes the real problem. We all know for a fact that the US is not very pleased with President GMAs decision to pull the troops out.  A New York Post editorial labels the move as condoning terrorist behavior.  Two Bulgarian hostages were beheaded by the extremists previously but the Bulgarian government didn't budge. Many global observers would probably ask why we were such " sissies " like Spain and Thailand. I would like to state for the record that I support the decision to pull out.  Our president needs the confidence of the people.  The global community is probably aware of the fact that we are an immature nation (a nation who looks upon moviestars to save it from hunger).  Most people don't realize how hard the decision was for the President.  Letting Angelo die would be equal to letting us all die.  Of course this not the actual case. But the President is aware of the consequences of her actions if she left Angelo alone. What the masses  are not aware of (or don't care to know) is how much this is going to set back our relations with our greatest ally and supporter.  We will have to anticipate some economic turbulence because Uncle Sam is not going to hep us like before. Expect the masses to be mad at GMA again for letting the economy lag.  Can you see my point?  Any which way, SHE loses. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was planning on watching  I, Robot  today. I was always fascinated by the ideas of Issac Asimov.  Bicentennial Man  was a a great book and I got to read some of his other short stories as well.  Anyways, I was sitting on my workstation minding my own business when a group of guys from HR were having lunch (my station is near the pantry) . Turns out their topic for the day was the movies to be premiering that week. One of the guys started talking about  I, Robot  apparently he already saw it on pirated DVD... AND GAVE OUT THE ENDING . I was&nbsp;within earshot of their conversation, And I heard EVERY FREAKIN' THING! Way to go, Einstein! You just saved me P80!! BRAVO!!! YOU DA MAAAANN!!!   Just like Ben Parker said "  With great power, comes great responsibility  " All DVD owners should practice a little discretion with the plots and endings of the movies they see.  THIS SHOULD BE MADE LAW. I once had to sit through some genius in a theater tell his girlfriend the whole "fascinating" story of " Spiderman 2 " . I never really enjoyed " The Sixth Sense "&nbsp;at its full extent because, my friend decided she couldnt bear the pressure of NOT telling us that Bruce Willis was a ghost!!  We all enjoy movies. We will all enjoy movies better if we just keep our mouths shut and let everyone else enjoy the same experience we did!!    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          A holler out to my fellow ACE graduates in Cebu!&nbsp; Kumusta na ang mga business nyo?&nbsp; Here's a pic of the people I went to lunch with in Mandaue during the BYU study. Thanks Bro. Tony (the good looking guy in the green shirt).&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             Before I give out my review let me tell you how I got the DVD.  I was walking down The Angeles public market one day near Plaridel to shop for some DVDs.&nbsp; This has become a regular ritual for me since I bought my DVD player.&nbsp; I actually enjoy "hunting" for rarities and old favorites more than watching them at home and realizing that they suck. Anyways I was thumbing through some dvd cases..you know the usual  Troy , was there,  Starship Troopers 2 ,  My Wife was a Gangster 2  and then... I stopped.&nbsp; I couldn't believe it.&nbsp; They had&nbsp; Halestorm's  "The Home Teachers". What was a " Mormon-genre movie " doing in this part of this predominantly Islam section of the market? Did they accidentally pick up a copy of the original and make hundreds of pirated copies and put a copy&nbsp; in my hands in a serendipitous twist of fate?Needless to say, I bought it.   The Home Teachers  is the story of two members an Elders Quorum class that couldn't be more different from each other but nevertheless, were assigned together as hometeaching companions.&nbsp; Greg (  Michael Birkeland  ) is a father of three and can't live without football, so he watches it every Sunday after church.&nbsp; Nelson (  Jeff Birk  )is a scriptures-on-CD salesman who can't live for the next month without getting 100% hometeaching.&nbsp; The two clash heads , encounter gnomes, mooseheads and destroy toilets for the next six hours trying to get to the three families assigned to them and complete their home teaching assignments.  A lot of the laughs in this movie are obviously intended for Mormons, so it would probably leave a lot of non-members stumped.&nbsp; The influence of Farelly brothers comedy is very evident in this one.&nbsp; Although they really needed to tone down on the toilet humor so as not to offend their target audience.&nbsp; It starts out hilarious but the pace kinda gets a little slow in the middle, like the scene with the escaped convicts in the Winnebago and the conversation in the police car trip back to Salt Lake which was set to probably give more depth to the characters. The " Your Not Alone " song sequence was probably given a lot of thought for a long time, but just came flat out corny.  All in all it was better than  The Singles Ward .&nbsp; Its nice to know that Kurt Hale and his team are getting the hang of mixing madness and Mormonism...but it still needs more improvement.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            When I was 11 I thought that  McGyver  was the coolest guy.  He could get into nuclear power plants and prevent radiation leakage using a melted chocolate bar. Ha! Bet those "brilliant" Russian scientists never thought of that!  He could make a firesuit out of melted rubber hoses. I once tried to melt plastic to make a costume for my G.I. Joe, but I almost burned our dog doing it.He could kill a snake using a standard issue swiss army knife (I had one of my own, and I'm talking about the P2,000 ones from Switzerland, not the  bangketa  variety) and use a flare gun to propel himself away from jagged rocks while he parachuted over a cliff.  I could go on....  We have also seen a number of 80's TV shows being produced for the big screen.  I think nothing is more eagerly anticipated as a feature  MacGyver  movie.  No doubt it will be a huge blockbuster as that it already has a built in fan base and can still be modified to the current times to get more fans.  The real question is, who will be  MacGyver ?        Paul Walker.  Fast. Furious. Plus he's american.        Thomas Jane.  We still have to see if he'll do well as  The Punisher         Damian Lewis.  Has leadership charisma as shown in " Band of Brothers ", but will this Brit look good in a brown leather jacket?        Colin Farrell.   Forget about it, Unless you want a Mac that nails chicks more than he completes missions.        Orlando Bloom.  Too prissy? Yeah I thought so too."You have my bow..and my swiss knife."        Viggo Mortensen.   Here's a serious choice.  A real outdoorsman, perfect as Mac.  But people might see too much of Aragorn in him.        Brad Pitt.   Pretty boy who can be tough and rugged as well, but could be too big of a star.        Ed Norton.  Sorry, had to add him.        Tom Welling.  Too young.  Plus I think he's being reserved to be the REAL next Superman.        Jude Law.  He could be the perfect European McGyver.   Who do you think will make the perfect  MacGyver ? Hey, why not make your own list then post it as a comment.  I'd like that!         
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I have a migraine. I know some of you are probably saying  "Big deal, I've got hemmorhoids"  But hey, migraines, common as they are, may result in plane crashes, stock market faliure, and possible nuclear fallout.   Can a hemmorhoid do that? Huh? I've had this since last night and it's killing me it';s keeping me from making this blog. I used to watch TV and stare at the computer all day and never get a headache. It's hard enough sitting in front of a computer all day with a throbbing head..I have to take calls from whiny americans for the next six hours too. I wish I just had hemmorhoids  (...wait, be careful what you wish for , you just might get it.  I'll just wish for...uhh, Jennifer Love Hewitt.)        
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             Bikes. Girls. Bikes. Murder. More Bikes. I dont see how this could have developed further into a good movie.  Torque  is all about fast bikes and the zombies that ride them.  Th movie starts out with Ford  (kinda ironic for someone who rides a bike, a little irony in there for sure)   the fastest rider in "ever" coming back to the USA from Thailand presumably because he was from the government and gets mixted up with some bikers called the Hellions led by Ice Cube's character Trey. Ice Cube's brother Jr. gets killed by Henry James the leader of a rival muscle bike group but pins it on Ford. Ford has to prove his innocence by, guess what, out-racing everyone else for the evidence. Dont get me wrong.  These kinds of films don't really get a lot of accolades for their writing or story development.  But the people who did this movie could have done better and breathed life into the story instead of...say put more bikes. Sub plots like the family conflict in  Biker Boyz  and the morality check in  Fast and the Furious  gave a little meat in their respective stories at least.  One guilty pleasure would probably be the showdown between Monet Mazur and Jame Pressley. When you see two chicks beating the crap out of each other while on their bikes, you know your in for a treat.  If you're out to get the DVD, I just hope you like bikes, because it's all you will get...oh and girls.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I haven't been getting that many invites since they banned Friendster at the office. Its funny that they let me do my blogs at work while they buld a giant firewall on something that doesn't take that much bandwidth.   My DengMangalagu project is however still consistently getting at least 1 invite every 2 days.  I dont get to check as much as I used to.  I have to go to an internet cafe just to follow up on my testimonials and messages and stuff. (Yawn) life is peachy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             After a long time, (long before my  My Sassy Girl  phase for sure), I saw  10 Things I Hate About You  again last night.  Its amazing how those high school life fuzzies come back like an old fungus on you after wearing unlaundered socks (okay, too much info there). It also reminded me of my undying infatuation with my onscreen sweetheart (when I say onscreen, it doesn't necessarily mean that  we're on the screen together.)  Julia Stiles .  My friends always teased me for having a "major Jones" for Julia. "Square yung mukha niya", "She's not really that pretty", " She alway plays the mad, antisocial chick.", and of course," Taray niya! "  Well that's exactly why I LOOOOOVE her! I always saw Julia Stiles as the typical girl next door. Not too pretty (well, compared to the staple teen flick regulars Hillary Duff, Mandy Moore and Anne Hathaway), but enough to get you interested.  Julia  has the face that doesn't strike the first time,  pero gumaganda siya habang tumatagal . One of the things that made her a star was her infectious ability to "get jiggy".  It was I first saw that 10 things party sequence where she dances drunk on a table when I said, " Hey, ang cool ng chick na to, ah ".  That infatuation turned into obsession, when I saw "Save the Last Dance".  She immediately got inagurated into my "Top 10 Girls of All Time" (which I will feature in the future, so stay tuned.)        At a time when Hollywood keeps looking for the big "new thing" new with the perfect face and the perfect anatomy  (coughlindsaylohancough!),  It's comforting that they still trust the tried and tested "real girl".  I cant wait to see  "The Prince and Me" .  I just hope they don't give her screwy lines and bad directing.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            The legendary  Zatoichi  gets a remake in this Takeshi Kitano version of the classic tale of the blind wandering swordsman with a mission to right wrongs and give you a wicked nice backrub while he's at it. Kitano plays the quiet and often times bashful  but fierce  Zatoichi  in his full charismatic glory.  The opening whack-up scene took less than ten minutes but seemed like an intoduction to non-Zatoichi followers and seems to tell us kids, "This is why he's a legend".   Th story begins with  Zatoichi  wandering about with his deadly red cane/katana blade  in his right hand, stumbling into a village where the Kuchinawa clan rule with an iron fist.  He is taken in by a poor "tindera" type with a good for nothing nephew who is addicted to gambling.. you know, your typical Malabon set up. Zatoichi turns out to have a knack at "sensing"  how a dice rolls so he becomes a regular with the nephew at the local gambling den owned by the clan.. you know, the typical Muntinlupa setting. Things get interesting when two geishas cross paths with  Zatoichi  and tell their sad tale of murder, revenge and their pain with Kuchinawa head Ginzo as the author.  Then, its whoopass time!!!  A simple story with  simple twists keep this movie intersesting.  I just found the digital blood and samurai effects a little distracting.  It was said that this was a very violent movie, but dont expect any Kill Bill type blood spurting, but you get a lot of fast swordplay and fast deaths. Plus, the keyboard music souded like it came from a Casio 380. My favorite part was the Geisha dance. I didn't know how entertaining a geisha dance could be.  It kinda puts you in a trance.  Come to think that the dancer wasn't even a ... well I'll let you see the movie first.  All in all it was worth the watch, just don't let the distractions get to you. Plus, if you are not used to japanese movie endings you might just want to dismiss the last 10 minutes of the movie.       
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            I caught my cousin playing  Fatal Frame  one day on his   X-Box  .  He says its the best game ever (next to the EA Sports NBA series, according to him).  Of course I had to agree.  The graphics were excellent, Its as if actors were playing the game's characters.  They looked real.  The ball playing and the boxing games feel like your watching the NBA or watching at Caesar's Palace...only you're the one moving the guys.  I couldn't help but recall where my cousin and I started out when we were kids.  We were in front of a black and white TV all day during the summer...playing   Double Dragon  !!  Before   PS 2   and   X-box  , before   Dreamcast   and   Playstation  , HECK! even  before the   SEGA Saturn  , there was the small red and white console in every home called the   Family Computer  . Every kid had it.  No question.  We weren't rich, but we had it. It cost around P2,000 or so at that time, a lot for a 10 yeasr old back in 1989. But our Tito Ed bought us our own and we loved him for it.  We all have our favorite games, here are mine.         PACMAN . Although originally released for play on the original  Atari console.  You can't NOT hate this game.  Probably  everyone's introduction to computer games.  Hindi pa rin siya  nakakasawa.          YIE-AR KUNG FU .  This is the only screenshot I could steal  off the net.  I like it because it is basic.  a- punc h, b-   kick . up arrow- jump , down arrow- duck ...easy.  you dont need  to be specially fast to beat the enemy.  Something a gaming  doofus like me would enjoy playing.         DOUBLE DRAGON . I remember cussing in front of the TV after  getting beaten in this game.   Pagagalitan ako ni Mama   afterwards. When my uncle bought this game, i had my exams  the morning after.  I could not concentrate. I couldn't wait  to get home to play Double Dragon.  I remember playing all  day after school, not thinking of my Science exam the next  day.  My mama had to pry my hands away from the joystick with  a crowbar to keep me from playing this game. The graphics were way cooler in this game compared to the  other games during its time.  There were many stages, and I  love fighting   Abobo  !         ROCKMAN .  This game will forever remain the greatest 8-bit  game of all time, second only to   Mario Brothers  . I remember  being obsessed with this game. I told you that I suck at  video games, I have to confess, I NEVER finished it.  My  cousin Blue was the KING of   Rockman  .  It would only take days  of after-school play for him to beat   Cut man  ,   Elec Man   and    Clash Man   and eventually get to   Dr. Wily  .  He did the same w  ith   Rockman 2  .  I could spend a whole day just watching  someone play this game and finish it.         SUPER MARIO BROS. .What   "The Godfather"   is to movies.   "Super  Mario Brothers"   is to video games.  Nobody would have gone  through a normal childhood in the late 80's if he did not  play Supe  r Mario  .  If I'm not mistaken, the concept of  putting sub stages within stages was introduced in this game.  This was also the pioneer of the secret path to stage  selection.  If this does not bring back memories of your  childhood, nothing will.  The mere intro  "Tenen-ten, te-nen,  ten!"  is enough to bring tears to my eyes....Y_Y         THE GOONIES . Although the game was very far off from the  original movie story,  this has got to be the best developed  video game adaptation of a popular hollywood movie at that  time.  We all know that the bottom line for any video games'  success is its playability, regardless of it's movie or TV  franchise.  I have to say, even experts find this game tough.  Primarily because of its tremendous stages. My fingers got  tired just making that boy walk around!         GALAGA . Classic. Simple. It may be one of the most primitive of the games here, but who doesn't love it?  The principles are simple. Shoot them all before they get down to earth while dodging away from their " Bug lasers ".  I see people in the office playing this game and pac man over the internet. Usually its the older guys like the Manager.         DIG DUG . Who didn't have that  500 in 1  game cartridge when they first came out?  Now you can see these games strategically imbedded in cheap VCD players sold in Greenhills, but back then, you had a great deal whan you had " 500 in one ". This was usually a staple in those cartridges.  I never played this game. I thought it sucked.  But whenever anyone opens the topic of   Nintendo   or   Family Computer  , this somehow pops into my head first.          SUPER CONTRA . If you didn't like this game,  BAKLA KA !  Simple as that!  I had this fantasy that they would make amovie out of this game starring   Sylvester Stallone   as the guy in blue and   Arnold Schwarzenegger   as the guy in purple.  I guess everyone else had the same idea, huh? Comments Please!            POOYAN  . My brothers ans sister will not forgive me if i did not include this game.  Although this is more of my siblings' favorite, it brings back a lot of memories from when we still had a small black and white tv to play all our games in.  My brother Jon even made a " Pooyan dance ".  I'd show you how it goes but you'd ask me to stop doing it midway.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
            A little eye candy for all the dudes out there.   Aya Ueto , as you probably already know, plays  urlLink  Azumi  . The spunky samurai who can cut you with both her blade and her smile.  Born 15 September 1985, she is a regular magazine model and " Pop-idol ", (the japanese version of " kikay " actresses in my book.) Azumi 2 is scheduled for release in Summer 2005 and joining the cast is no other than the equally gorgeous  urlLink  Chiaki Kuriyama   of Kill Bill Vol. 1.    urlLink  Picture 1    urlLink  Picture 2    urlLink  Picture 3    urlLink  Picture 4    urlLink  Picture 5    urlLink  Picture 6    urlLink  Picture 7    
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
         If you haven't  heard of  Chona Mae  of Valle Verde by now, either you are actively staying away from it or you are not really into blogging.  The Chona in the City blog about a maid from Romblon living in Valle Verde is only a few weeks old but is gaining popularity like wildfire. Her profile was visited  4613 times  as of today, pretty good considering her account was created on July 26.  If any of you can see my hit counter (I can't see it right now, site must be down) I probably have a little under 200 hits for the whole month from a few close friends. Chona's story is the stuff of telenovelas and romace booklets.  Whether it is true or fiction does not really matter.  Its's amusing, funny and addictive.  You can't wait until her next blog. Her little anecdotes on her "  Mam Tess  " and "  Sir Jeff  ", and her run ins with  Reynante , her annoying suitor and The new helpers  Aling Choleng  and  Myrna  are enough to get you hooked. With her popularity,she needs no introduction. As Chona would say in her own words...  urlLink " I'm chona mae banaag but you can call me chona for sure".  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          I have owned this album for some weeks now and I am waiting to get tired of it.  Truth is I can't.   Steve Vai  's latest studio album is still  in the works. I got a hold of his live album DVD " Live at the Astoria " a month ago.  I can't get enough of this guy.  His music sounds like it comes from another visceral plain, a totally different universe. When I was still 13, my standard for good music was if it sounded like the theme songs of the cartoons I was watching.  Whenever I listened to  Steve Vai , It somehow reminded me of robots and spaceships, aliens and warships.  I used to do very well doing his songs with air guitar (with my left hand too, mind you), but when I finally learned how to play, Iwas frustrated that I couldn't do his "simple stuff".  The album is a more culturally diverse mix of melodies and rhythms.  " Blood and Tears " has a dominant hindu flavor all throughout.  " Ultra Zone " is african, " Asian Sky "  which is Vai turned J-pop, sounds like either an airline commercial or the theme song for Dragonball. Vai described the name " Ultra Zone " as being the musician's state of mind where everything he plays is perfect and cannot make a mistake.  Michael Jordan expressed the same idea when playing basketball.  Any which way, it is easily understood.    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here are some screenshots of the visually breathtaking " The House of Flying Daggers " by   Zhang Yimou   of " Hero " and " Raise the Red Lantern ".         If you thought the colors on " Hero " were awesome, check these screenshots out.  I restrained myself from posting a shameless amount of  Zhang Ziyi  pictures, so just check them out here.    urlLink  Picture 1    urlLink  Picture 2    urlLink  Picture 3    Can't wait to see it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Here's an example of a movie that exceeded all my expectations. Imagine two hours thinking you're watching a pretty linear movie and less than halfway through turns into the biggest headtrip you'd ever experience awake.  Eternal Sunshine Of The Spotless Mind  is another screwed up (and with it I mean brilliant) creation of  Charlie Kaufman  of   Being John Malkovich   and   Adaptation   fame. The first two were made with director  Spike Jonze  who himself is a borderline film genius/psycho.  This time  Michael Gondry  (  Human Nature  , also with Kaufman) takes the director's chair.  And with brilliance, I may add.  Jim Carrey  plays  Joel , an out on his luck introvert who has enough self confidence issues to make Woody Allen look like Fabio. He meets  Clementine , played by  Kate Winslet , an impulsive, free spirit who makes rash decisions as often as she changes the color of her hair.  Clemetine and Joel's relationship hits the rocks and decide to break up.  Clementine has all memories of Joel erased from her mind through a company called   Lacuna Inc.   Joel is devastated as he meets her again, but Clementine doesn't remember him.  He was advised by his best friends to take the treatment as well and be better off.  Joel, although only half decided, takes the plunge.  The Lacuna guys, headed by  Dr. Mierzwiak  (  Tom Wilkinson  ) and his assistants  Stan  (  Mark Ruffalo  )  Mary  (  Kirsten Dunst  ) and  Patrick  (  Elijah Wood  ) and make a map of his brain to find which memories to erase. During the treatment he is asleep and sees each memory zapped out.  He feels his love still undiminished and decides to call it off IN THE MIDDLE OF THE TREATMENT! He chases his memories around his head trying to save what's left of Clementine in his head, giving the Lacuna treatment a run for its money.     The film contains Kaufman's trademark trippy scenarios.  Extremely eccentric characters, entering a person's mind, taking a peek at their embarassing memories, inferiority complexes and outlandish, trashy settings.  The film kind of has a seventies feel all throughout, mostly because of the outated costumes and grainy 8'' film used for most of the scenes. Fans of the Blair Witch Project may feel familiar with some of the memory chasing scenes. A great headtrip with an interesting premise, what if we could erase the memory of a lost love, do we also lose what's in our heart?  I hear copycats typing already.     
     
    
</post>


</Blog>