<Blog>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear readers,  This entry is for a very select mailing-list because it is going to contain details that i don't feel are fit for general consumption. Feel privileged.   Some of you I'm taking a risk with - trusting your descretion and discernment - so be good.  My friend Ryan, a couple of people he knew, and yours truly, had what's known as a 'bourbon night' (its known as this by no-one except myself) and so, as is traditional, went to a strip club last night. Needless to say this was my first experience of such an establishment - and very likely was my last. I won't say  the place lacked class, but i will say there were no doors on the toilet cubicles and said facilities were designated to their respective genders with the graphic titles 'chix' and 'dix'. Enough said. But don't get me wrong though, the atmosphere wasn't actually at all intimidating and we're not talking (please pardon the phrase) 'crack-ho's' here.     Now it's not that anything happened to me personally that i would be ashamed of or even embarrassed about that I'm not mentioning this little adventure to everyone. It's just that I wouldn't want to worry people who might read into it some kind of desperation or self-destruction that really isn't there. Though I had reservations about the venture, Ryan is one of the only friends i have here, i do respect and trust him, and hey, I'm on friggin holiday! It was however, a night which sailed pretty close to the wind (or whatever) in a number of respects.   Well let's leave the details, I'll not sensationalise. I would like to say this though: while the initial novelty of naked and - how shoudl I put this? - 'talented' women does appeal to some instinct that is quite compelling, and produces something of an intense experience, I found it so short-lived that i could hardly believe it. First I was bored and then I was depressed. I brought  this up with Ryan at the time and he didn't have much to say about it really - though I could tell we were on the same page. We moved on to this other place that was much less in-your-face (particularly appropriate phrase actually) where there were still alot of naked, but it was more about just playing pool or talking with your friends. In this place Ryan spoke with such clarity on how the idea of strippers made him feel (particularly in the wake of a break-up of about three-weeks of age), that I could just about stop myself from hugging him (you definitely don't want to start hugging guys in this kind of bar by the way). It was a beautiful moment. After that, we (certainly I) began having a really great night. Went to a more regular bar (though it was still kind of gritty) and I was talking to some really nice American girls and all in, a good time was being had by all.       So the conclusions I'm drawing, the 'moral of the story' I suppose, is a bland and predictable one - not worth spelling out. So I won't. But i will say that the experience was very worthwhile for me, opened up areas of thought i hadn't considered before, and last night was one of the best nights I've had in Portland. James.  *If you would like to unsubscribe from this 'Special Edition' Travelogue, but continue to receive the regular journals, please reply with "I didn't even know it was possible to get a piercing there!" in the subject line. 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear readers,  day fiveish/sixish. I am now living with Kerry (pronounced 'kiri'), who is an improv comedienne. And yes, I do think that's pretty funny! LIfe is, as Gump of  course famously said, like a box of chocolates: Even if it get knocks out of your hand and its contesnts scattered all over the ground, you can usually salvage quite a lot of it, it doesn't taste too bad, and you might even find some discarded change or other treasures while you're down here. Kerry's nice. And I'm really glad that about this. It'll certainly be much more comfy than the hostel. I saw her act. She had quite a range from 'kid divorcing her mother' to 'leather shoe addict' to 'squirl making a living through sex appeal and a bushy tail'.   Could someone please send me a list of how animals' names are spelt? It's a real weak-point for me.  And here's another serendipity: I had, by chance, met the local bartender, Ryan, in Dublin a few months ago. He came on my tour of the gaol. To him I am most most grateful for the hangover i am now suffering from - which was procurred at a very very low personal cost (present headache, mild ausea and blearyeyedness excepted).   I went busking a little bit after i sent the email. I was just playing to relax and cheer myself up more than anytihng else. Didn't pick a very busy spot; Just outside the library where I go online. I made one dollar and about a third of a bag of American Spirit tobacco. Cool.  Last night in my drunken slumber i had the returning sensation that i  was sharing my bed with a rodent of some description. All became clear in the morning, as the smell from my blanket (which I had put on top of the hostel's ones because i had been cold the night before) came to meet my already sensitive stomach. I had shook myself free of my hairy nemesis - but its scent stalks me still. It seems the f-creature had been sleeping in it.   All in I'm very happy now. I've met some great people and I'm having fun Everything, as they say, is coming up Millhouse.      James.  *If you wish to unsubscribe to this travelogue, please reply with "Qu'est ce  que le Millhouse?" in the subject line.* 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers.  Day four. Now living in a youth hostel. While herself was swing-dancing last night, I made good my escape. Things had taken a turn for the  worst, not so much that anything had changed, but with Donal's departure (more on that later), there was silence and quality time enough to realise that I was deeply unhappy and had had all the discussions about elaborate and complicated feelings that I ever wanted or needed to have on this holiday. Besides, myself and the ferret were particularly disagreeable. He had nicked my shoes. All of them. Hidden them under the couch.   She had given it a bath, and in a confounding sequence of cause and effect - it actually smelled worse than it ever had before. As I was contemplating my situation while sitting on the couch, it transpired that it was not happy enough with the shoes i had carelessly left inside my rucksack, but wanted the ones on my feet as well, and he began tugging at the laces. I was living in a hostile environment. I was reminded of Wilde's comment to the wallpaper in the room over Shakespeare and Co. where he Died, "One of us has got to go..." and decided, as Wilde did, that it was myself. My race was run and kirby the ferret had won the lady's affections.   On the trip to the hostel, my bags were considerably heavier than my heart, I'm happy to report. I'm sharing with a guy who introduced himself as Udon from Japan. I grinned slightly as i resisted the temptation to say that I was Potato from Ireland and met his friend Baguette from France on my in. Udon sleeps like someone who is blowing up a beach ball but doesn't have to inhale. Always exhaling. It's quite comforting. Almost oceanic.   The weekend was fun. Donal from fourth-year philosophy, who some of you might know (but I didn't), came for a visit - and his companionship was much much appreciated. It really is nice to hear a familiar accent in a strange city. Went to a Saturday market where almost everything had to be made of something that was perfectly useful before it was made a craft: Jewelry made out of coins, forks, spoons, bike parts, fossils; chopsticks made out of... eh you know, trees. All kinds of wierd stuff.  By the way folks, if anyone is looking for a particular book, I live beside the biggest book shop on the West coast and I have a voucher for the place that needs using so let me know. I'll save it or post it or whatever. Really.  Just briefly, to let you know what the place is like: Portaland has an 11% unemployment rate so everybody hangs out. All of the time. People play chess, drink coffee and pierce and tatoo themselves all the livelong day. Everything is pretty laid back, no-one seems angry about anything. Haven't seen a single drunk person, and the homeless community (which is thriving) seem to be content and polite.   C'est tout.  James.  * If you wish  to unsubscribe from this travelogue, reply with "Quit yo chicken  lickin' - dog" in the subject line * 
     

        
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear readers,  It would be great to compose a really witty and incisive account of my first full day in the US on my shambolic holiday, but sadly jetlag is not just the excuse of a few grouchy flyers, it is a condition which actually exists (whooda  thunkit?) and from which i am now suffering. NOt so much that i sleep at the wrong time so much as i can only now  sleep for four hours at a time and my mind is now only geared to recognise if my body is tired or hungry and has dictated that i must be at least one of these at all times.  Now its not that i'm such a self-centred person that I imagine that you all want to hear what i ate for breakfast this morning, but it really is the little things that make you feel like you're on holiday. To say that the Danish was bigger than my face, is not only far from an exaggeration, but is in fact a great insult to this pastry, who if it could talk (and  hey why not? This is America!), would suggest that if only it had had teeth (like it had asked the wizard of oz for) it would have been it that ate me. I then picked up the local paper to see that a 15545 pound, five foot tall, rodent was the subject of a small front-page article. Naturally given the culture i now found myself in, i was expecting the article to read something like, "Mrs. Schneider (57, Idaho) made the discovery when she went into her garage (pronound garaujsh) to get some supplies from the Y2k stock-pile, which had remained the family's main source of nutrition when their apocalyptic predictions proved false..." But it actually turns out that the rodent in question is a native to prehistoric  Venezuela. So there you go, America hasn't always had the monopoly on 'big',that it currently enjoys.  From door to door was a twenty-two hour journey, and while i won't say that the welcome i received at the airport was worth it, the wealth of goodbyes I receieved before i left certainly was. So without naming names, thank you to all the lovely nice people who lent support, advice and farewells. For those of you I didn't tell (and let's face it, i didn't have a lot of time on my hands to do so), Gabrielle phoned to end our relationship, forty-eight hours before i left for Portland. This was, to put it mildly, unfortunate. NOnetheless, I'm staying with her at the moment and the situation is workable. We're not 'broken-up' exactly, but hairline fractures are visible from the initial collision. What can i tell you? She's complicated. I probably won't spend more than a week here now, I don't think. Heading to the East coast to catch up with DAve and Rob and see my favorite New-Yorkers.   For the moment I'll hang in here. I've actually had a pretty good time so far. Had a fun night out with Gabrielle's friends last night. I've little say, but that they were nice (and a just-nice amount of crazy) people and I had fun with them. Drank something called black bew which was nice. Kind of like Newcy Brown. It turns out they do have Amber Bock here - it's not just a Texas thing. Saw a billboard but haven't located it in a bar as yet.  Living with a ferrit has proven a little strange though. it's a very docile creature, and does have its moments of playfullness, but, and honestly this is true, it is much smellier than a dog, and while it is considered by some to be 'cute,' I don't think i will ever, as long as i live, see benignity or normalcy in drinking water from a glass that a ferrit has stuck its head in and licked from or allowing it to hang out on your bed when it feels like.   For those of you who haven't met Gabrielle, she's lovely really - but eccentricities abound and recently have become quite  prominent. I'm sensing that this is not a holiday I will quickly forget, but suspect that I'll soon suppose many of its scenes were in a film I once saw, because the sheer madness and novelty of it all has left me with a peculiar detachment as if it  were all fantasy. It's all just too strange to take seriously.  If you wish to unsubscribe from this newsletter, plese reply with 'Bog off Buckley' as the subject title.   All the best, James. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers  We aw now in Collyfawnia (as the new governer of this sunny state might say).   The drive up to San Francisco was really very beautiful and we stopped in two small towns that none of you will ever have heard of: Bishop and Wesley. The drive was quite disconcerting though because, while road-kill was a phenomenon that occurred in some abundance on our trip, we saw evidence of far more serious collisions on the Californian interstates than anywhere else. There weren't enough remains to see exactly what the animal was but the blood splatters were enormous. Those of who how might under-estimate the seriousness of such an event, please see attached jpg [aw crap there's no attachment: it was a deer in a windscreen - scary stuff].  San Francisco itself provides traffic hazards of a very different variety: hills like you wouldn't believe (I still can't get over them myself) and *very* expensive and/or treacherous parking. Myself and Rob ended up abandoning the car on the far west of the city near Golden Gate Park (for the initiated) and undertook an odyssey of some scale trying to get back across the city by public transport on a Sunday night. The crazies were out in abundance, and were unavoidable given the overcrowdng of the buses at this hour, but luckily we escaped with our money, lives, and innocence.   Last night we went out hustling pool with Jeremy (who I met through Ryan Portland). That was a lot of fun. Jeremy seems to be a very 'good' driver, but being unused to the hilly terrain, and indeed travelling through narrow streets at high-speed in general, I came very close to losing my dinner on quite a few occasions. This morning, myself and Rob hauled our ailing bodies out of bed at the ungodly hour of eleven to catch our boat to Alcatraz and very thankfully our stomachs withstood the boatride over (rob was perhaps the more likely would-be thrower-upper, if I might descend to one-upmanship for a moment). It was a worthwhle journey, and while its an interesting place, the history pretty insignificant: it's a prison on an island and that's about it. There weren't very many prisoners there and few of them were of any real historical importance. The one thing that is of some historical interest, the events surrounding the Native American Reservation that was there in the sixties, wasn't even mentioned on the tour. The best thing about Alcatraz is the view it gives of San Francisco - which is amazing. It was a really clear day and the city and the bridges looked great.  Tonight will probably be a quiet one, starting the treck to LA in the morning.  If anyone has any requests for books fro city lights, get the in immediately, I'll be checking my mail at about 6pm (tues) irish time.  Oh and the stuff about bums and queers in San Fran... believe the hype.   James.  *If you wish to unsubscribe from this travelogue please reply with, "Are you sure you're sraight? Yuu're such a cuty-pie I could just eat you right up," in the subject line.*     
     

        
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers,  My nipples are pert (but everything else has receeded). Somehow in the Californian heat of Barstow, there exists a motel pool with a temperature just shy of freezing. Enough Said.  The weather has been pretty sweet since Flagstaff. From there We went to Boulder City, Nevada, and then to Las Vegas for two sleepless nights. Boulder City was my first experience of the desert heat. I think it was weirdest there (or maybe I've just become accustomed). The air felt like you were breathing in the rejected air from a vacuum cleaner or like you were walking around in a reasonably inocuous but none-the-less ever-present fart-cloud.   Perhaps, for a city like Vegas, one should start with something like: "It was the best of times, it was the worst of times," but alas it's already been done. Vegas is a wonderland to the happy and a suicidal nightmare to the sad - and either way extraordinarily expensive. The 'free' booze of the Casinos and the universally available cheap food for which Vegas is for many most fondly remermbered had dried up by our arrival. Maybe we're out of season, maybe that's just not how it's done anymore. That said, I had the most amazing Buffet in the Bellagio - the only thing that could possibly spoil such an excuisite meal would be one's own gluttany - and I pushed it as close to the edge of  exploding all over the room as I could. I also had the pleasure of the company of five delighful young women at the buffet who were impressively as much martyrs to self-gorging as I was: a bunch of fellow fourth-year-trinitarians who were J1-ing this summer. It was great to meet them Vegas was (at times) a lot of fun.  I'd like to dwell a little on the ills of Vegas, but I really can't decide what the most confounding aspects of this extraordianry living circus are. I'll talk about it in greater detail in person I think, but to draw a quick analogy - imagine feeling like that caterpillar that has to keep secreting goo so that the swarm (or whatever) of ants won't consume it: that's Vegas if you just add lights and people constantly offering flyers for strippers and hookers - throw in a few zombies for good measure too. We left having had no more than four or five hours sleep for the nights we spent there - and are probably not quite recovered.  I feel like I should have more to say, perhaps if Vegas wasnt' so Vegas I would have. Now when I think about it, the novelty I can remember quite clearly is getting static shock from just about everything I touched.   Hmmm.  James.  *If you would like to unsubscribe from this travelogue, please reply with "Roy should have been mauled years ago... He was begging for it!" in the subject  line.*        
     

        
</post>

<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers,  Those of you who are still reading these emails and not deleting them immediately upon their arrival - I commend you. It is a feat of endurance that is easily more impressive than a three-thousand mile roadtrip with flatulent travelling companions. And to those of you who have long since given up - well you're not reading this are you? So nevermind.  In 'Maloney's' of Albequerque, they serve beer in litre-glasses. Like I don't feel like a mini-me enough of the time already? Still, though my puny arms could barely manage to get these herculian goblets to my lips, I persevered and succeeded... if success is measured by the severity of one's hangover. It wasn't just the beer actually. A woman who worked there also gave me a cocktail (called a punany - whatever that is ;-p), which though it was nice, was a flavour I could still taste approximately twenty-four hours later. The people we met there were fun and it was one of the most enjoyable nights out I've had so far.   From Albequerque we somehow managed to stumble out of bed in time for checkout and travel over 300 miles through the incredibly beautiful countryside of New Mexico and Arizona. The horizons were just amazing and sometimes were 360 degrees. I've never seen anything like it. The skies are so beautiful, and change dramatically as you pan around we could even see it raining in places miles and miles away. I really liked New Mexico. We didn't get to Santa Fe, but I find myself thinking to myself: "next time..." I definitely think I'll be back again.  We are now in Flagstaff, Arizona. Heading off to Boulder City tommorow on the way to Vegas. We went for a swim this morning in the outdoor (that's right!) pool - and it was really lovely. It's hard to believe that it's so warm and nice here when it couldn't be anything but cold and dark in Ireland. Or is there an unseasonal heatwave? I've actually been swimming quite a bit on he holiday - we've booked into places with pools every second or third night. It's been quite necessary as a counterbalance to the effects of greasey (over-)eating and spending so much time in the car.      Oh, and just in case my travels might possibly help some future tourist to America: here's a phenomenon you need to watch for. Most often, your toast will be buttered for you but the buttered side will be down. (I've put my heart in danger of immidiate seizure on more than one occasion as a result of this - luckily it has continued to beat despite the stress I've put it under). On a second butter-related issue, it's generally white and not yellow. On pancakes it will be in on top in a spherical scoop. Like icecream. It's not icecream. I know that now.   From Arizona University, wearing my winter shorts and sandals, Adieu.  James.  *If you would like to unsubscribe from this travelogue, please change your email address to something I could never possibly guess* 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers,  Ok. It's now Thursday and about a thousand miles later. We've made it out of Missouri with a brief excursion across a corner of Kansas, through Oklahoma, across Texas, and into Albequerque, New Mexico. Phew.   By Monday night we had made it to Tulsa Oklahoma. AS for what happened in Tulsa, I can't remember a single thing. Tuesday was at the edge of Oklahoma in a little place called Elk city. On the way there, we went into what alleged to be the largest McDonalds in the 'free world' - 'Free world,' because there's a bigger one in Beijing. It was about the size of every other McDonalds I have  ever been in. Despite the fact that the building itself was quite large, it's capacity was comparable to the one on O'Connell Street. So I was profoundly unimpressed by its size, but what was kinda good was that it is loccated not beside the interstate but over it, and a statue of the famous Cherokee Will ('I never met a man I didn't like')Rogers (lasooing) is in the car park - because this is where he was from. Exciting stuff.  In Elk City, we went to a Karaoke night, and honestly, by the fifth song, I was still surprised that yet another person was singing a Country song. It's easy to forget where you are when you go from the discomfort of a car to a Holiday Inn that looks much like the last one. The lyrics of all the songs were gloriusly grim - from "I was drunk the day mother got out of rison" to "Papa loved Mama, and Mama loved men... now Mama's in the Graveyard and Papa's in the Pen." I was going to do "Indepedent Women," but I realised it wouldn't go down to well with the truckers just in the nick of time.    On the way through Texas we went to Groom to see a 150 foot metal crucifix and stayed for the biggest lunch I have ever eaten in my entire life (it also has a 'famous' leaning water tower (i.e. it's broken) - and despite what the signs said, I wouldn't exactly describe this as an 'attraction'). As for the rest of  Texas that we saw, well, yeah, it's pretty big... and we almost hit a low-flying owl... and it rained... and well that's about it.   So now we're in New Mexico, I've had green chile soup - so yes, I have lived. It was pretty hot. Albequerque is pretty big and it seems like a very nice place so we're going to stay here tonight as well. The chances of Dave getting a haircut today are higher than they have ever been on this trip. I still refuse to shave.   We're not going to make the wedding in Vegas, but we're going there anyway to meet some more Irish people - which should be fun because being in excusivley male company in confined spaces for long periods, while I'll not say it hasn't been fun, is of limited appeal.  Feeling zonked and honky-tonked,  James.  *If you would like to unsubscribe from this travelogue, please reply with the musical refrain, "Because your wanted by the Po-lice and my wife thinks you're dead," in the subject line.* 
     

        
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear readers,  We are fast approaching a It's-Monday-it-must-be-Missouri type scenario. All the Gas-stations, motels and Wendy's diners (home of the traditional-style hamburger) are merging into one - giving my unconscious mind the impression that we are driving around in circles all day and not actually going anywhere.   WE have made some fun stops since my last chapter though. We made it to the aforementioned Catsup bottle just outside St. Louis (Missouri) but were disappointed to find that the bottle itself was only about 50 feet tall. Rob spoke for us all when he said, "Well it's kinda big... I suppose." We were expecting a 170 foot bottle but actually, it's raised on a very high platform  which accounts for the rest of its height (See attached picture).  WE also stayed in the University town of Rolla where we drank a lot of beer but didn't talk to anyone except our barmaid and the woman who asked Dave for an ashtray. We're really going to have to step up our womanising if we're going to pull off this epic twenty-something's road-trip rite of passage type thing with  any dignity.  Having woken up hungover getting harrasssed out of the motel (the dingiest yet - holes in the sink, rubber sheets on the beds) first thing in the morning, we went forty miles out of our way because Rob kept singing the words "Meramec Caves" to the tune of "If you'll be my bodyguard" - which somehow made going there seem like a good idea. Fourteen dollars a piece and more stalagmite jokes than you ever need to hear later, we'd seen the cave lit in every conceivable color to make them seem interesting, and had sat listening to Katie Smith sing "God bless America" while they projected an American flag onto some 75 million year-old natural formations.TAcky though it was, and cynical as I am, I have to admit I felt a warmth somewhere in the cockles at the last encore. It was either admiration or indigestion from the Denny's breakfast we'd had in the early hours of that morning on our way back to the pub. AS a true American might say, I guess we'll never know.             Apart from a fifties-style Steak n' Shake, Springfield Missouri blows. It does, however, offer an oppurtunity to sing what one can remember of the 'Springfield Springfield' song from the Simpsons though (an indulgence gladly but poorly fulfilled by myself and Dave).   We're now sixty miles outside Springfield in a place called Carthage on the old Route sixty-six. Clark Gable stayed in the motel we'll probably stay in tonight. We came here because 'Road-Trip America' said it was a town like the one in the 'Back to the Future' films, and Rob sang the theme-tune until we agreed to go. This is the system that seems to work best for us.   We've now clocked-up about 1500 miles.  James.  *If you would like to unsubscribe from this travelogue please reply with "Would  you like fries with that?" in the subject line.*  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Reders,  From Indiana, Pennsilvania, (in which we left screeching tyre marks in an attempt to flee Scott's motel before they discovered Dave broke the toilet) we've made our way, driving directly into the sun - d'oh, to the state of Indiana. What town in Indiana I hear you ask? WEll what else could it be but... yes that's right folks... Evansville.   Having been disappointed to find that a trip to a house shaped like a shoe in Halem, Pennsilvania was impractical, our first leg took us to nowhere other than truckstops and the unexpected luxury of a RAmada hotel in Ohio, which was (bizarrely) cheaper than anywhere we had stayed so far. We then went on down to Cincinnati (known variously as 'porkopolis' and 'queen city')in the hope of seeing something (having seen nothing in the previous 24 hours) and were overcome by the startling dullness, and yes i'd even stretch to say ugliness, of this famous city. So we went to Kentucky for breakfast. Once there we went to 'Gunsmith Guns' to (possibly) buy a rifle - and didn't. Funny, in the pawnshops even, you can pick all kinds of weaponry from precision bows to  revolvers to rifles. Nice place. I'd recommend trying the grits if you ever go - but only because I wasn't actually brave enough to do so myself.   Determined to see something, we made a circuitous journey through the old-time town of Madison (where we had milkshakes that make you swell - literally) and utilised a fortune telling scales which costs one cent. I am 130 pounds, and can sway many people but meet my match in the opposite sex. I think that means I'm a tranny - I dunno. We only really went through Madison, Indianna (ok confession time - I forgot what state that was in and had to irritate everyone by asking. But now it's certain - yes it was Indiana) to get to Louisville (pronounced Loo - avil), Kentucky which is the home of if not the biggest baseball bat in the world, the biggest i think I'm ever going to see. This place was also alleged to have a fountain that shoots water 375 feet in the  air every fifteen minutes,  but according to a homeless man it has been out of action since 1989. But that's ok because we'd done it. We saw something.   Later today, we'll be on the famous route sixty-six, and personally, my vote is a detour to Collinsville, Illinois the 'condiment capital of the world' where they have the biggest catsup bottle in the world. Don't ask - I don't know why - but perhaps it's because there's only so many interstate Wendy's a  person can take before they can only be satisfied by over-sized everyday items.   Thanks for the news flashes from the real world - keep them coming,  Onward and sideward,   James.  *If you would like to unsubscribe from this travelogue, please reply with, " YOu call that a knife? This is a knife!" in the subject line.     
     

        
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers,  The madness. To those of you I owe replies - my apologies. I have been restricted to trians planes and automobiles and have not had much opportunity to be on the information superhighway. I'll see what I can do now - if I don't get back to you be asurred i wanted to and will try over the next few days.   I'm currently squeezed into a half-sized chair in the children's area of the library in a little town called Indiana, Pennsilvania. I left Portland on MOnday morning in a drunken, but decidedly satisfied haze. Once again I owe great thanks to Ryan and Jeremy and Kerry and Renne for helping bid fairwell to  POrtland in style with a pretty wild night and Ryan most specifically for dragging himself out of bed after what can't have been more than five hours sleep to drive me to the airport. I'd tell you all a little bit about that night but well... nevermind. Topping the thank you list is kerry who put up with me all week, and really lifted my spirits, and kept me entertained and happy at what otherwise would have been a very very difficult time. Kerry, you can expect a pretty hat (or two) in the post over the next while, you've probably seen the hat you loaned me already on the head of a Portland vagrant, and I can only give you my apologies and a promise of recompense.  So, I made it to New YOrk via Denver Collorado (where people actuallly wear cowboy outfits who are not going to fancy dress parties). It was the most spectacular flight I have ever been on in my whole life - and thankfully I managed to keep down my breakfast. I had only time to get into a NY taxi, see the Chrysler building and stay the night with Sarah in Manhatten (thanx :-)). And hit the road with Dave and Rob. A 380-mile drive got us to Indiana Pennsilvania to visit the lovely (I assume - haven't met her yet) Michael (don't correct my spelling that is her name even though it is not usually associated with the fairer (I use the term loosely) gender) - an old flame of Dave's -  and over the next two weeks we're making our to vegas for a wedding! Oh, don't put those two facts together, they're not the happy couple (but hey anything could happen) - rob's uncle is tying the knot (having loosened a few of his previous ones it seems) and we're trying to make the wedding.   This has been a very factual nuts and bolts chapter it seems, just briefly I'll mention the ways in which Rob's 'value-for-money' ethic makes me happy. We got the cheapest rental deal available within a hundred mile radius of New YOrk city by taking a train journey to the little town of South Amboy, New Jersey -  where he somehow successfully stood his ground and refused to pay the extra levvy for being under twenty five, but did concede under some peer pressure to getting the collision insurance. We arrived (minus Dave who had 'other arrangements') at the HOliday Inn at one in the morning and Rob managed to get fifteen dollars knocked off the bill - and had an night-cap cigarette from the couple of hundred he bought from some native Americans because they don't have to pay the duty on them (being under their own law) and can sell them a lot cheaper. NOw anyone else who wakes up about seventeen minutes before the latest time for check-out (as we did) might panic, but under rob's exceptional organisational skills we managed to take full advantage of facilites and  squeeze in a morning swim and a shower before we checked-out.     Well, the children are starting to freak me out - I think they want me to playwith them. I don't know - a lot of them look sticky. Sorry for the rush.   Signing off,  James.  *If you wish to unsubscribe from this travelogue, please reply with "I love  you, but I'm not IN love with you," in the subject line*  
     

        
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dear Readers,  I began with jet-lag and I am ending with jet-lag. This has been the longest gap between chapters. Some two weeks I think. My apologies. It wasn't that i didn't have internet access it was that events were such that I was confounded and didn't know what to say. So much happened... and yet so little. The trip from San Fran to LA was pretty crazy. We made a diversion to Santa Cruz on the way which lasted far too long - purely on account of great charm of the person we were going to meet there: A rich model who studies psychology and fancied Robert (Yes, a female model!). Leaving Santa Cruz was the most dangerous leg of the journey we undertook (minus Dave - soon to be on his way by train to meet  me in Portland Oregon) because it was late at night, the fog had fallen, and we were on a twisting hair-pinned road that had real elk/deer-things running on it and no street lights. To cut the story short, we made it in the very nick of time for me to fly to Portland (thanks Rob) and Robert didn't score because someone's granny died.   In POrtland Oregon, two very unexpected things happened - firstly Gabrielle had an unprompted complete change of heart, regretted the break-up at the beginning of our trip and said she was still very much in love. So I gave it a second chance. The other unexpected thing was also of a romantic nature: Dave and Kerry (improv comedienne, told you before, stayed with her in POrtland the first time, we like her etc.) shared a mutual appreciation of the beauty and goodness of the other, and oh, oh it was so romantic and wonderful. I wholeheartedly approved because they're both just fabulous.   Myself and Dave both extended our stays in Portland for the sake of our love-lives and for me, it meant that my trip to NY was cut short to six very fun hours with Erin, (which was sad - but you have to do what you have to do) and spent whatever money I had left booking the new flight. I did however honour my promise to go to Cole in Louisianna, where I had the most striking American  experience of the trip. Summarily, the highlights of it were shooting fire-arms, horse-riding, sailing on the bayou, eating alligator, and meeting the smallest dog I've ever seen - and of course it was great to see Cole again.  Cole is the second person I claim to have matched-maked (with the lovely Sharon, FYI) in the last month. Unfortunately this coupling was also of residents of opposite sides of the atlantic ocean so sadly it also was cut short. What a peculiar speciality I have.  There is alot more I could say about all four places, but I'm eager to cut to the confessional. The end of my trip was so different to the road trip that it hardly seems to be part of it. So a word about each, the road trip: great; the emotional trip: tough.   And now for the outlook. Firstly, I have a deeper knowledge of, and a fluctuating mixture of respect, admiration, and affection for my travel-companions... sorry it's too late for me to think of a gag to sneak in there. I think my friendship with the pair is now well-secured. Secondly then, a reflection on the reason i went to America in the first place: the girl. What can I say? What's appropriate to say? I'm sad about what has happened and I  can't really brush over that. Here I am back in Ireland, with my original expedition seeming to have failed in a most tantalising way - a profession of love and commitment five weeks and a lot of heartache too late. It feels like time and money have run out. What's in the future? No really tell me - that wasn't a rhetorical question.    I graduate Monday - so that should be fun. Y'all know how much i like to dress  up.   Thanks for reading I hope to be in touch with you all soon.  James.  
     

        
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      On Monday I was in work by nine and I felt so damn good having slept so damn well that a bag of liquorice allsorts spilled out on the road struck me as a work of art and I took in the sight with all the delight of a child with a bag of sweets. The weather was mild, the streets were dry, and I was about as full as I can be of life on a Monday morning. Ah sleep. It really does a body good.   Predictably I've abused my new-found friend and have tapped into my sleep/happy-reserves over Monday and Tuesday nights coming in shy of the oft-recommended eight hours thanks to my delight in going out for a social drinky most week nights. I would have offended my aforementioned new friend more gravely were it not for the services of my old pal flexi-time who not only doesn't mind getting stood up, positively relishes it!  "Flexi-time, today I praise and thank you. Not only am I still in relavtive favour with sleep, I also managed to take a little break on the way to work this morning while I waited for the rain to subside. Frankly, you're only smashin. If only you weren't so friendly with work. That work is so damn boring and time-consuming! Well I know you guys go way back and I'm only using work for money so in many ways you have the moral upper hand, but....but....but....oh I can't criticise you. You're wonderful. The very wind beneath my...eh...shoes. Did you ever know that you're my hero? "  "What do you mean you thought you were my hero? No, Quasi-Mojo, you're not. You're a naughty stinky monkey. Don't look at me like that. You know what you did..."
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Myself and Quasi-Mojo took a trip to Cambridge, England this weekend to visit Diarmuid, play Croquet, and soak up a little of the life we'd like to have (and probably could have were we just a little more adventurous and willing to do the research to make it happen - which so far we're not).  Q-M rode for free as neither Ryanair, National Rail, nor Taxi Drivers charge extra for imaginary monkeys. Nonetheless, Quasi-Mojo declared loudly and repeatedly on our flight that he was not going to pay for his seat as he shared it with a six-year-old boy who kicked, grabbed, and otherwise molested him as if he were "some kind of unthunking gunk." He finds it difficult to express himself sensibly when he's bemuddled. I wouldn't have expected it, but he's actually a nervous flyer and does sit down for take-off and landing - not sure what he got up to during the flight as I was asleep but he usually finds some entertainment (the fewer questions asked the better) with the crew.  I was surprised to find myself enjoying croquet so much. It's quite a clever game and requires a fair bit of skill and finesse, but it happily proved to be both friendly to novices and cruel to more experienced players. Throw in pims, bad-losers, trash-talk, strawberries and cream, and more sandwiches than you can shake a croquet mallet at; and you've got yourself a very fun day indeed.  The formal dinner was attended with mixed degrees of formality from the expensive tuxedos (not that there are any cheap ones) with fancy cuff-links and shiny shoes to the post-fancy, perhaps even meta-fancy (or some other kind of ultra-modern-fancy that defies the usual coherence of lanuage for the sake of hyperbolae) which consits of something like ripped jeans with a tuxedo jacket. I also saw one guy in a skirt/kilt that I think was made from a shawl with a hat pin in it; very Jude Law (or equivalent) indeed! Personally the only innovations I made to the norm was wearing what was an entirely second-hand ill-fitting tux (bar the bow-tie which was new and fitted rather nicely thank you very much), the cuffs of which were linked with safety pins thanks to the 'you-always-forget-something factor' which unfortunately could hardly be mistaken for the deliberate fasion vrais-pas (?) mentioned earlier. From what I could see, the women were more traditionally clad - which I appreciated because I get confused rather easily. Hmmm. Well let's not turn this into a 'Hello' column. Moving along...   Very much like my last visit to Cambridge, it was the experience of the people I had the privilege to speak to and hang-out with that I valued most. I find Diarmuid's associates very interesting and receptive and surprisingly mute on their areas of research. Naturally,in the spirit of politeness and genuine curiosity, I did ask a lot of the time but it is generally something that isn't really considered socially important. This may have worked in my favour when one way or another it became suggested (possibly by me but that's beside the point) that I was an orphan, a juvenile delinquant or both as a result of my contact with bon jovi (I promise this stroy makes sense - it would just take too long to explain), but a stronger pssibility is that it was a sufficient deviation from the Cambridge norm to leave me looking quite sketchy and undesirable indeed. Funnily, my only regret is attempting to salvage some dignity and clarify the rumour. This attempt was poorly executed, and Quasi-Mojo mocked me at length for attempting it as it betrayed a certain soft-spot I was politely consealing as one usually does, and led to Quasi-Mojo continually doing kissy faces and conspicuously caressing a certain individual in an attempt to embarrass me. Thankfully I've become accustomed to his ways and talented at ignoring him when necessary.   Well let's not lose sight of the important things. Everyone in Cambridge is just delgihtful and I was taught a new word: defenestrate. The meaning of this word essentially is to summarise the cumbersome description, 'to throw out of a window'. Quasi-Mojo also learned something new: that he can stick paper with a (now patented) mixture of his own bodily secretions.  Didn't go punting in the end but a fine time was had by all. 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Q-M was idly reclining on the reception desk as I was writing the last blog. He stuck his head over the monitor to read what I was doing. I can't imagine how he can read upside down so well and at such close proximity. Where do you learn a skill like that?  Anyway he went back to recling on the counter beside the door and recited the following in soliloquy    I don’t know how many  Syllables there are so Why don’t you just shut...  At this point he demonstrably (if you know what I mean) extended his right hand and closed over the door.   Quite poetic I thought.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Is it seventeen  Syllables in a Haiku? I can’t remember now.  Sitting in a pleasant breeze  The work phone keeps ringing  It all comes to me.  Then there is silence and Stillness takes the breeze There's nothing left to say. 
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There can be a culture in a legal practice of everything being of great urgency and importance. This was certainly the mind-set I was endevouring to cultivate in the firm I was working in because I felt that a high level of professionalism was owed to our clients.   Ideally, staff in a legal firm should also be well paid because they work so damn hard. But this is rarely the case for the less experienced administrative staff members like myself who literally get paid peanuts. I might have been able to abide poor pay for the sake of experience were it not for two things: firstly Quasi-Mojo pottered around all day inconsiderately eating the very peanuts I was working so hard to earn (he likes to throw them high up in the air and catch them in his mouth - but when he misses - approx 40% of the time - he leaves them scattered about the place so that he can do a protracted ant-eater impression when he has a good number), and secondly I really didn't get on with my boss.  I suppose a lot of legal people treat others in terms of maximising their own financial return from them. Their self-respect is entirely based on driving hard bargains and screwing people. Interestingly, they actually feel like it's their duty and not merely their entitlement. It's amazing to watch. I'm still incredulous.   Anyway, in the workplace it manifests in excessive demands, tantrums, and pathological buck-passing. My guy was kinda funny peculiar. He had (and you'll be forgiven for thinking this is a joke or an exaggeration) no concept of the alphabet and had chosen (yes chosen!) an albhabetic filing system. This necessitated my going into his office to pull files from his shelves any/every time he needed one. In the beginning I didn't really question this - it seemed like a plausible story - but then he started giving out because he couldn't find the files I had pulled for him and LEFT ON HIS DESK! So he suggested that I email him to tell him when the file he is looking for is on his desk. Then he just couldn't find anything - I'd hear his blissfully obnoxious voice over the telecom: "I'm missing my cheque-book/keys/brain/whatever."   When stuff went really really missing it was hilarious. I kept a meticulously ordered office and so looking for stuff was just a matter of my glancing into my office. This infuriated him and he would always insist I lok in my office when the only logical possibility would be that it was in his. Quasi-Mojo was really funny one day this was going on and he helped by doing his thinking then having-an-idea face and then investigating everyone's nosrils and ear cavities.   He was also pretty great at doing a boss impression. For some reason he associated this guy with a rhinosorous (sp?) and would roll up a piece of headed paper (as it's more expensive and the boss hated to waste it) and make it into a rhino nose. He'd scrunch up his face and shrink his neck and get all angry and charge at things. But he also did a very good boss-on-telephone impression that I found very witty - especially when he did it while squatting on the boss's head. He's such a good friend (if i can call him that). It was a shame I was so busy and had to ignore him most of the time but it's great to look back on it now and it did make my days seem a little less intense. But if i'm honest, i didn't (and still don't at times) approve of Quasi-Mojo's irreverent attitude.  When I left that job for one that paid more and didn't require me to do much work (unfortunately), the guy wouldn't give me my P45 which would usually mean that I'd have to pay emergency tax. But as it happened, I didn't have to pay that much over the odds. I knew that he was doing it out of spite and malevolence but I didn't want him to sit around and not know for sure whether or not I knew why he was refusing to issue the document. I suppose I wanted some way to allow him to reflect (on some level) on the fact that he was being a big meany and to explore his justifications by confronting the issue. Convincing him to send the damn form was not the issue as I knew he would not issue it until the Revenue Commissioners contacted him and I had already reported the matter to them. I'd like to blame the monkey but it really didn't have anything to do with him.  After a number of phonecalls to his office (he refused to speak with me each time) we had the following email exchange - read into it what you will:    Dear XXX,  As you know, I have been on to your office a number of times enquiring about my P45 and am obliged to pay emergency tax on my earnings until after I receive it.  You can appreciate that this is a great inconvenience to me and I would ask you to attend to this matter; give me an indication as to when it will be done; or indicate why you did not want to attend to this hereto.  Yours sincerely,   With the greatest respet James, there are matters which have kept me out of the office and I must say I didn't appreciate any harrassment from yourself in relation to the matter.  I am under no obligation to explain anything to you in relation to the matter.  The matter will be attended to on my return to the office.   XXX, Let me just say briefly that it certainly was not my intention to make you feel harassed as a result of my contacting you but I did wish to stress the importance of the matter and am glad that you are attending to it now.  Regards,   James I'm not obliged to make an explanation to you as to why this matter wasn't dealt with.     I could explain my perspective on the psychology of this exchange at length, but I'd rather leave it to yourself(ves). Let it be what it is - however dubious my own role may seem at first glance.   I still haven't written anything about when Q-M showed up again. Sorry I'll get round to it eventually.  
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I work in an environment where I feel like (to butcher a biblical metaphor) my light has been man-handled (well, woman-handled moreso)under a bushel. I'm particularly powerless/unmotivated to do anything about this as I am a temporary employee and I'll be leaving in September. Any attempt to burst forth from said bushel or even set it alight from the inside would not be very productive. Quasi-Mojo usually cheers me up with his miming and his particularly distinctive version of yoga of which the main feature is the release of gas from his rectum. I believe the louder the release the greater the health benefits.  Anyway, I am also kept amused, even though I feel quite mean/weird in the process, by one of my colleagues' use and misuse of the English language. She has a penchant for adapting idioms and many of her adaptions are just delightful. Unfortunately I should have taken closer note, but here's a few that spring to mind that I heard over the last week or two:  "I'm sick to my back eyes with this..." "I'll be losing money hand over heels here"  To me when some clever retort was made to me:  "Cheeky is as cheeky does eh?" I asked what this meant but she declined to explain it. "She sends me this form and expects me to make heads or tails of it." "God. If they'd brains they'd be intelligent!" "She was kicking mad" "She's having a Mickey over there" Refering to a middle-man type situation: "That's just putting a piggy in the middle of the process."   I'll write some others if they come back to me. The other fun thing she does is instead of using the past tense with 'should' she uses the present. So it's "That's not what you shudda doin'," and "I should have gettin those ages ago," and  "You should've hearing what he's after saying to me," and that kind of thing. Magic.  I actually wouldn't have taken much notice of it if Quasi-Mojo hadn't taken to stopping what ever he was doing and clapped his hands while hopping from foot to foot every time he heard something unusual.   For legal reasons the above account should be filed under fiction.   I'll say more about Quasi-Mojo's reappearence in later posts.  For now,  Adieu   
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I love to generalise when I'm explaining myself. It seems to make everything I say sound almost inevitable. Case in point:   Everyone has blanks in their lives. I could display what I have for you because I do have shrapnel: dismembered memories with drips of emotion and insight oozing out and drying up, but why bother? They've served their purpose, and I don't need to keep them. They can clutter a place so easily. I'll just mention them in passing if I find they are close to hand and worth talking about.   Quasi-mojo came to school with me when I was five but he stopped coming quite early on because he found it difficult to keep my attention and he found the whole affair so utterly distasteful. He said it took all the pleasure out of scratching himself, and that scratching himself was one of very few pleasures that he had.   He scratched himself a lot actually. In fact scratching himself was one of only two things that I've ever seen him do with his right hand: with it he held a cigarette and scrathed his considerable and prominent genitalia. It's always surprised me that the phrase 'himself' or herself refers so readily in our language to the activities involving genitalia but it surprised me even more that Quasi-mojo followed the convention. His left hand mostly gesticulated or interacted with the orifaces of his face and posterior.    So without saying too much about what we got up to before he left (I'll come back to it now and again later) I didn't see Quasi-mojo again until I finished my schooling. I remained in education until the age of twenty two and then I took a trip. I kept an account of this trip for friends and family; twelve chapters in all. Of course I'm about to say, "...and then we met again," but if you have an interest in that account before we continue our story, the twelve blogs from September to November 2003 consist of the very same. I called it a travelogue (as in a 'catalogue of travel' as opposed to a 'travel log' per se - not that there's an awful lot of difference)    
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Many children of many cultures share their beds with special furry friends and they largely agree that such friends make the finest, loving and most understanding of bedfellows.  There comes a time however, when despite the love and understanding (displayed most often in terms of the availability of cuddles in the former case and being unpeturbed by bodily fluids in the latter case) these furry friends become redundant and, though it be harsh it also be true, are evicted.   I expect we are all somewhat au fait with the phenomenon. One way or the other, this is my story: I had a number of such friends as a child but unlike my peers, mine were either abducted, intimidated or otherwise convinced to leave. I don't know exactly what happened and I don't think I ever will (or want to), but one Spring morning when I was four I woke up without them and found by what I expected was no coincidence, a monkey casually squatting in profile on my bottom-right bedpost. He was smoking an odourless cigarette and turned his head to look at me as he inhaled.  If I'm honest, I hadn't yet noticed that my furry friends were gone, but I understood his meaning right away when he spoke: "We all need friends Horse, but no-one needs friends like those." In that wonderfully direct and beautiful way we all have at that age my response was to ask "Are you my friend Mojo?" He cocked his head back and laughed. Well, I say it was a laugh, it was at least comparable to a laugh except that it was a noise which also registered displeasure and repulsion. He looked at me intently but I didn't think there was any Malice in it. His response insofar as I can recall and from what I know now of how he goes on, was something like: "Now listen Horse, you are in many ways not a horse but you're close enough for me to call you Horse. I'll do you the courtesy of not calling you Boy or that other thing - like you wouldn't call me Monkey -  but I think you even know already that I ain't mojo enough to be Mojo. I mean at my very best - and I'm proud of it I add- I'm only ever going to be Quasi-mojo."    Well you were a child once. You don't need me to tell you the name stuck.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My love-affair with a refrigerator named Jess started even before 
     

        
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been trying to tinker around with the blog a bit to make it better but the best I've come up with so far is that now anyone who wants to talk smack about me (or anything) on this site can do so without fear of me tracking them down and shaking their hand in the street... eh... like a dog... a well-trained one.  At the moment I have more fingers than readers - but nonetheless, make yourselves known! Anonymously? Well no - sign it... or not... or whatever. What you do is click on the little thing that says "Comments" at the bottom-right of the blog and then libel yourself all the way to court! It's great!  At the moment I'm trying to teach Quasi-Mojo to use a keyboard - which he finds difficult - or rather he finds easy because he just uses his fists - but what i mean is I find it difficult to read which I suppose is a slightly different issue. His spelling isn't the best either, but feck it. He says he'll try and write something for you all soon if we get the time.  Dave Lynch is a superstar by the way (no favouritism intended I know he's not the only one out there - really though someone had to say it).
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ...and what have you done?   Sorry didn't mean to spook you there. Relax. It's not Christmas.   It might as well be though (ever noticed how that phrase makes no grammatical sense?)- the weather is cold, I'm looking at my bank statements and wondering why I don't have more money, and I'm also thinking about my  urlLink New Year's Resolutions .   Now that I have been accepted to the  urlLink Honorable Society of King's Inns , I'll be a busy little bunny with lots to do, whose often known to look at his watch and soliloquy about his lateness for his date. I probably won't have a date though - I'll just be late for work (assuming employment) or class.   Hmmm. My feelings about my prospective busy-ness (and business) are  urlLink somewhat mixed .   So my 'new year' is going to look very different from my 'old year.' And  urlLink like God , I will probably look on my creation and see that it is 'good'. And also  urlLink like God , I will see that it's not  urlLink entirely flawless  and actually a fairly  urlLink tricky business .   But I'm quite happy that my plans are beginning to come together and I'll soon be out of  urlLink this place .   BTW, just because I'm having a little  urlLink yuletide moment , it doesn't mean  urlLink (as some people thought)  that you can ask for  urlLink presents .      
     

        
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I very pleasently had the excuse of playing tour-guide to thank for among other things, the company of an engaging, effervescent, (and a long list of other compliments besides) woman from Hong-Kong and a visit to the IMMA - both of which are rare treasures to me (with the latter being almost entirely my own fault unfortunately).What this leads me to muse on here for public consumption are two things:  Firstly, I would like to recommend all and sundry - excepting those who are suffering emotionally (particularly depression) - to visit the exhibits of Sophie Calle and Margherita Manzelli in the Irish Museum of Modern Art. I've been impressed, intrigued and disgusted by art many times, but so far as I remember, I haven't had anything run amock in my head and confound me like the paintings by Manzelli. I wouldn't be telling you much by describing what they look like, so i will say rather that they have this strange familiarity about them like they are from a dream one forgot one had. And utterly shocking for reasons I can't quite understand. Even if I do count up the weird things about them that account for the powerful effect they have, it still does nothing to shed light on how such devices appealed to the mind of the artist. It's really exceptional. As for Calle, her stuff isn't at all as mysterious - one knows exactly why and how it illicits the reaction it does. Neither I nor my adopted tourist for the day could actually 'do' all of the exhibit - which is either a detracting aspect of her work or a sign that we are lightweights and need to do some arty bulking-up (yes- the latter is most likely). Well worth a visit though.  So secondly; so-called 'Irish' Culture. To be honest, I was embarrassed (and noticabley so) by what I saw in terms of Irish Song and Dance. I would compare it to someone judging 'Irish Food' by what they were given on their flight over or something like that. One difference though is that there is no hype when you get your unopenable bag of peanuts and your fizzy drink that's as much aluminium can as it is beverage. In contrast (and now I have to adit it was a weak metaphor to begin with), what I saw in the city centre yesterday was so proud of it's contrivance that I had flashbacks to Vegas - where I will say with my hand on my heart you will see something closer to Irish song and dance than I did in 'The Bridge' and the 'Arlington Hotel' on Saturday. Sadly - and very very sadly though - there is little in the way of alternative.  Hmmm. I'm ranting like a retiree. Enough. Think I've got the bones of what will be an overly wordy (yes it is possible) letter to the editor of the Irish Times in that paragraph.      
     

        
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Last night I had disturbing dreams. A friend I've known from the age of five was so deeply upset with me that he resorted to abuse and harrassment. This was not all. There was plenty more besides. But the morning rush and the extra-experiential nature of dreams conspire to fuzz-up the memory. Quite apart from the slight stomach upset of the weekends festivities - which I'm happy to report were considerable - related issues were also on my mind. The dynamics of friendship are not only complex. They are ever-changing.  It's interesting how one person or image can take the place of another or a number of others in a dream. The actions of the friend in this dream were not his. They were another's, but still I have been concerned over the last week that we had an unnecessary and needlessly exaggerated difference of opinion very late one night and I don't want him to resent it. Perhaps there was little call for that particular tangent but there won't be any harm done. After eighteen years of friendship I perhaps shouldn't be too concerned but naturally contientiousness cannot but be an ingredient in any such long-lasting association.  Quasi-Mojo doesn't believe in 'freindship' - only in 'friends'. Well, more accurately, he says he doesn't know what it means or involves. I think an exact quote would be: "Horse, it's about rules. The thing about it is that everyone makes up their own rules. You've got two things rampant in the consensus: you got bad rules, and you got people changing and breaking their own rules. Keep it simple. With me, what you see is what you get: my friendship is long and hairy and it flaps about. It fluctuates with my mood - I use it for love, but then again it might just pee on you - and everyone knows what they're likely to get from it. With me there is no friendship - there's the people whose bits you can see to be worth paying attention to and who don't mind looking at yours, and then there's everyone else." At this point, he stroked his friendship reassuringly and as he turned away gave me a funny look and said, "Why d'you think I call you horse?"   I've always been impressed when Q-M decides to venture a metaphor - but often rather than make a concept clearer, it just gets hazier, and most often that's actually the point. Somehow I derive some reassurance nonetheless - and if nothing else he makes me laugh.   In a more inexplicable dream, I went back to the Artane Boys Band to look around. The experience made me cry uncontrolably (if there is any other kind). And that one I really don't understand.
     

        
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A girl with pink and black hair often crosses from D’olier street to College Green/Pearse Street with a gracefully equine (or so it seems to me - not everyone admires how horses walk like I do) gait at approximately 8:55 am on a weekday. I know this empirically thanks to the coupled phenomena of traffic lights and a routine. I also know that a woman of unmissably large frame who invariably wears black, rides her big (also black) bicycle with a basket on the front, down Lord Edward Street closer to 9:00 at least most weekdays. I also happen to know that she is on her way to the fifth floor of Trinity College Usher Library and that she plans on 'sshhh-ing' anyone who plans on communicating verbally while she’s up there. Furthermore, if such communications are not ceased (by sshhh-ing) I also know that she will (and has before) contact a security person because they can be more persuasive with their keys that rattle and their clunky shoes.    One of the interesting things for me about my awareness of certain aspects of the routines of these (to name but two) individuals, is that were I to speak to them, I'm quite sure that neither would say they have ever laid eyes on me (insofar as they could remember anyway) - and in the latter case, I'd have to say I'm quite happy to keep it that way.   Have you ever walked up to someone and said, "I've been seeing you around so often, I thought I'd come and say hello," and have them respond as if you had just landed from outerspace and greeted them in Klingon? I know someone told me that this happened to them but I can't remember who it was - which leads us to suppose that they are not very instantly striking or engaging and it's not much wonder that this sad story is their's.  So think about that (how does being didactic suit me?). There are people watching and thinking about you and you don't know they exist. Maybe a man, maybe a woman, maybe even a monkey...
     

        
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I went to eat in an Italian restaurant tonight with Quasi-Mojo. I had some food and some wine and he didn't order anything. He sat, he smoked, and he took a not-uncommon jab at my lifestyle. I thought what he had to say was interesting, though I'm not really in a position to address it as I can neither entirely refute his logic nor embrace his point of view. I don't think he wanted an answer from me anyway. The conversation went like this:   "I'll buy you something if you like" I said, "I know you would," he replied. "I've been thinking about that for a while." "What? You're playing it cryptic tonight?" "Not at all. Let me ask you this: why would you buy me something?" "Because you are my friend, I like you and I have the money, and I wouldn't mind giving it to you if you wanted something. This isn't being cryptic?" "I'm good company?" "Yes." "I'm good company when I have something, and I'm bad company when I don't. Isn't  that  what you mean?" "Well, I'd be more comfortable if you had something maybe, but I don't see..." "I know that. But I had to  make   you  admit that." "I don't know where you're going with this Quasi-Mojo. Do you have a point?" "You know I do Horse. Sad thing is, you know what it is but you won't address it." "Well I don't know... fine... help me out here." "You make money and you spend money because you are afraid. You are afraid to 'plumb the depths' as they say, of your experience. You fear being without. My being without reminds you and it scares you. As you said yourself, it makes you uncomfortable." "I was just being..." "No. sorry. I shouldn't let you come in here. Let me go on. Living my life of non-productivity and the poverty that leads to allows me to really feel who I am and what my needs are. You are too afraid to make that experiment and you secretly envy my doing it. You intend to live a life where you produce enough wealth to allow yourself to fulfill needs that you don't even know you have. You will work and acquire to meet the needs you've convinced yourself you have, while concertedly refusing to find out what your needs are. And - and this is a big 'and' - in an extravagent show of ignorance and irony you 'sympathise' with and are 'generous' to, the friends that actually have more than you. More courage. More knowledge. Less money. You envy them. You don't empathise with them and you are not generous toward them. You are trying to sabotage their pursuit because if they are more like you, you won't think about what you are missing, and if you can 'help' them, then you have justified your own misguided path to yourself. Think about it. The fit hits the shan. Who freaks out? The guy who has nothing to lose? Or the guy with the house on the hill? And it's not just the money that'll make you weak. Working for the man? No choice when to work or not to? Who owns your time? Who owns your life?" "Listen, my defences are low tonight. But you're obviously missing something. "Who owns my time?" Who owns this salmon! The king of the swingers wanted to be like Mogli? Why wasn't it the other way around?" "Is that a serious question?" "Would I be happy being like you? Are you even happy being you?" "Are you happy to know me?" "Yes, but..." "Do you love me?" "Well..." "Are you going to finish that salmon?" "No. Go on. Take it."  "I'm glad we had this talk Horse. I feel better. I think we both feel better. I'm going to the can. Monkey business."    
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      When I’m not doing whatever it is I do, my hobby is to  urlLink ring the bells  of Christchurch Cathedral, Dublin. Quasi-Mojo usually hangs around outside if he comes along. The push factors of the belfry are that, on a practical level, the stone staircase to the belfry makes him uneasy (it’s “dark and itchy” apparently); and on a philosophical level, he thinks it’s unwise to institutionalise neuroses.  The pull factors of the area outside that, on a practical level, there are things to clime on; and on a philosophical level, there’s a pussy-cat in the grounds with whom he has a special relationship (these two reasons are actually one and the same, as they say, and I note the misuse of the terms ‘practical’ and ‘philosophical’).  After rehearsal last night I went over to the pub for a couple of Cydona’s and some socialising even though I was a little tired and something in me just wanted to go home and have a nice bath. I caught up with Quasi-Mojo as I was walking back to where I had parked. He was leaning from the top of the fence smoking what was no-doubt a post-coital cigarette, and before I even got close to him, he yelled to me.  “It’s a treacherous world Horse! It’s a treacherous, sordid, and confounding planet. The seediest I’ve ever visited.”  “It could be worse my friend,” I responded,  “tell me what’s happened. Did you break-up?” He jumped down to walk with me.   “Hmm. Patronising, insensitive and unbecoming.” “I’m sorry, you’re right Quasi-Mojo. Please accept my apology as I accept your admonishment, but something untoward has happened I presume. Pray tell comrade.” “Well I’ve had some time to consider how to break it to you, and this is what I’ve come up with. It’s a Limerick.   I don’t like the way Buckley smells, And a hunch-back could ring better bells. You get on my nerves,  But you didn’t deserve To get the back wheel of your bike with the new block that cost you forty five euro last week, nicked while you were across the road drinking two Cydonas and thinking you’d like to be in bed.”  “Aw crap. Seriously?” “Yeah seriously, you really didn’t deserve it. Crappy ringing tonight by the way. How are we going to get home now?”     I got the bus to the scene of the crime today and brought with me an old wheel. I shared the journey with about twenty-five Spanish teens who made the journey quite uncomfortable for the rest of us who were vying for space, standing in the aisles trying to avoid the idiot with the bicycle wheel. As they stampeded off the bus one of them stopped in front of me (delaying her colleagues), put out her hand and said, “Conrazulasions.” Having allowed my surprise and reluctance to engage with her to register, I extended my bike-filth fingers to shake her hand and she said, “You are the only man in Dublin!” I didn’t respond verbally but did get visibly embarrassed. Some lady apologised to me on her behalf, and as I went to find a seat a guy said to me, “You should get off with her mate.” I did respond to that, but it was so mumbled that it won’t have made any sense to anyone.  When I got the wheel on the bike I shared an accomplished nod with Quasi-Mojo - not knowing but secretly feeling that it wasn’t going to work very well  (which it hasn’t done). He jumped up on my back wrapping his arms around my neck and gleefully shouted, “Conrazulasions!”  
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Last night I attended ‘An evening with  urlLink Janet Street-Porter ,’ with Jenny in the very lush Newman House on St. Stephen’s Green. Quasi-Mojo declined to be my plus one at the event. I'm sure he would have enjoyed nicking handbags, humping legs, dipping himself in the ice buckets and that kind of thing, but he just didn't go for it. In fact he dismissed it summarily with a brush of his hand, a look of disgust and the words, "So base. So rude."   Outside  there was quite a cufuffle as people gathered to hop on board the very first public outings of the flashy new  urlLink LUAS  Tram. Like the event we attended, it was without charge and involved a lot of sitting around and wondering what everyone else was doing there. Both events would have had a similar exclusive feel that was tinctured only by the presence of certain conspicuous nobodies who are blatantly untalented at savoring a privileged position - and might i add, such shortcomings are not at all always a bad thing.  In many ways, the whole occasion was an opportunity to reflect on such issues of status and how it is won. Obviously we gain or lose status by the opinions of others, and in many ways it is not by merely achieving our own goals that we receive status, but - and this is particularly the case in the broad phenomenon known as 'the media' -  by achieving the goals that other people have but can't meet themselves. So opinions are powerful. Janet Street-Porter (as she stated herself) "made a career out of having an opinion on everything." But what's so great about JSP's opinion? I suppose the answer is not in it qualitively but quantitively i.e. the fact that so many people heard it.  As was evident from the lame questions at the end; the fact that few people talked to her at the ensuing champagne reception (no strawberries or cheese: lousy penny-pinchers); and the very obvious reality of her being 25 years older than the average age of the audience; JSP was not up there because she was liked or even becasue she was that interesting, but because she could act as some excuse for up-and-coming-whatevers to come and shmoose and look pretty and influence some useful people. Only trouble was it seems, that no-one of any 'use' was actually there. Still, people looked pretty and there was free champagne.  Janet did say some things that were interesting (if not contemptible to jealous people like me). When discussing which medium she favours (radio,tv,print) she said that it was difficult to say because just like men, they all come with chips. This initially confusing metaphor became a little clearer as she went on. She meant gambling chips. She described how these chips are gradually lost and then they have nothing and it's time to go looking for some other chip-holder. She's been married four times. What a refreshing attitude!  I've found that if you wave at LUAS drivers, they wave back. I hope I'm not the only person who's going to do this,  but I fear that if everyone waves there may be some anti-waving legislation passed by those lovely people we elected to government who look after our best interests.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      People use the phrase "monkey on my back" (admittedly not very much but nonetheless they do) to signify someone irritating. "Why is this?" You may well ask.   Well from personal experience, I can tell you a few things that are not merely a  little irritating to the uninitiated.   First there is the weight of the creature, which is worsened by it's propensity to bounce when it is on any moving craft. Then there is the fact that when a monkey is on your back it changes it's normal mode of conversation (if it has one) to a  mode that consists mostly of kicking and slapping. When it is not kicking or slapping because it has nothing to say for itself, it will continue to bounce nonetheless and will turn its attention to goodies that can be found on its steed's scalp and in its orifices. Despite what you might think, the nostrils are not immune from these investigations. That leads us to the surprising coarseness of a monkeys fingers and the not unsurprising smell which is pretty bad anyway and is made worse if it is smoking a cigarette. Not that this is the case with Q-M because interestingly, I can never smell anything from his cigarettes - but if you're a non-smoker, and you find a smoking monkey on your back, it's something you should be prepared for. But I digress, the combination of the weight and the coarse fingers left a rash on my forehead (which he was using as balance) after the trip down to the video shop on Sunday. Quasi-Mojo said yogurt would clear that right up and I agreed, but in his opinion I was "unbelievably and unforgivably clumsy" as I missed my forehead every time I attempted to self-medicate, and lost the whole carton down my mouth.   The thing is though, one gets used to having a monkey on one's back and being the messed-up, neurotic creatures that humans are, we get confoundedly attached to this sort of thing. Besides, walking down the street, hand-in-hand with a monkey just looks silly. But anyway, the rashes, the neck-strain, the slapping, the nit-picking and everything else are things I'd actually miss. I don't think I chose this though. I think it works like a disease. It's possible to get infected with a certain type of behaviour, and then there's little you can do to extricate from this disease of the heart. In many ways, it's my own fault. I didn't wear a crash-helmet. And I've seen this phenomenon in my romantic relationships too. Some people say, Oh I love her despite x,y,z (all bad things) but honestly sometimes I really think, bullfaeces, if she wasn't x-ing, y-ing and z-ing so much you would be entirely disinterested. Well, it seems (lately anyway) that I miss the erratic unreasonable girl and the attentive accommodating girl moves me little. Interesting. Confusing. Ridiculous.  I now declare the floor open as to the moral of the story.  
     

        
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      When spitting from one's bike at speed there are but two options in my opinion. The first is to spit to the side in which case pedestrians, traffic or one's own shoulder run the risk of bieng loogied. The second is to spit to the front. It is possible to spit directly onto the ground in this way but there is nothing quite so satisfying as spitting dirctly onto your tyre causing the spit to ricochet forward onto the ground with impressive speed and efficiency. It's like getting the ball on a pin-ball machine to fly up the super-duper-chute or some such equivalent - I'm sure you know the feeling - smashing something that's far away with a catapult is also simimlar - unless you've just hit the patio door or a treasured garden gnome. Be warned however, for if you miss the tyre your spit might just land on the inner rim of the wheel and this causes the spit to be propelled back toward you. It's never nice to have something gooey in your crotch is it? Is it? Hmmm. Anyway, in exceptional circumstances, where the product has a high viscosity (if my understanding o fthe word is correct) it may even hit you much higher up. I remember in my earlier teens I spat in my own eye on the way to band (as it known to everyone who went to 'band' - in the USA they'd call it 'band practice' because they like big words but interestingly, not unusual spellings).  For advice on puking from the windows of taxis, consult my colleauge Mr. David Healy, who is contactable through myself, or Fingal County Council. 
     

        
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm not sure what I want to talk about today.   Maybe I could say something to do with how i feel irritation to see someone using a superfluous amount of handtowels or napkins - which is a shame because I see it  urlLink so often.    I could talk about  urlLink young children  and how when they piont to things they angle their hands horizontally while  urlLink adults  angle them vertically. That's intersting - however breif.   Or on a personal note, there's the inexplicable tiredness of today and yesterday that saw me get out of bed in the former instance, slump from sitting on my stairs to lie down for a while on the landing, and in the latter to sit on the edge of the bath and rest my head on the sink clutching a toothbrush i hadn't yet brought myself to use. It even resulted in my getting a video (Lost in Translation - It was good while I lasted) after work last night because I didn't want to read but I had to switch it off and go to bed before it ended - even though I thought it was very much worth watching.  I could even make room for a few lines of how I just about manage to mask feelings that are descending daily toward contempt and loathing for someone I am in the presence of for about thirty hours a week, but I am ultimately unconcerned by this - its a normal aspect of the working environment.   I find the vignettes from the Children's Court that appear in the Irish Times very interesting and there haven't been any this week.  I bought a red  urlLink apple  for a change and it was too hard to eat.  None of these things seem fit for blogs really and even if they are jumbled up together they just read like ramblings of a drunk or a hangoveree or an insomniac or depressed individual. I'd like to think that I'm none of the above. We all have moments.  So there will no blog today - just an admission that inspiration is proving elusive and a window  (that needs cleaning) inside my temporarily sluggish little head.   
     

        
</post>


</Blog>