<Blog>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another weekend passed and now I have another week to look for a job. I had some teases by companies but nothing solid. I was offered to work at home and travel to Ukraine once a month but I haven't heard back from them since Friday so I'm hoping Monday they will contact me once again.   I had a interesting week with my friend Katie and a lot of my next door neighbors. Katie and I went for a ride with no destination and ended up in Whitney Point for a huge massive Ice Cream Banquet. It was sure good but huge! On the way there we saw a huge ass turtle crossing the road. I'm not lying, I put my size 13 shoe on the back of it didn't cover half of the frickin thing!  I guess I'm using this page more as a open diary and when I have my occasional rant and raves. Interesting huh? I'm thinking about putting some really cool features on here if blog supports them so stay tuned. I'm also going to have a online Radio Broadcast going soon for those people that like everything from jazz,country,swing,rock,folk and blue grass. Sounds fun eh? I bet! Well I'm running out of things to say so I'll end this here n'shit  Later N' Shit, Steve
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, it's been four weeks and a day and I'm still unable to find a job. I put in several applications but no call backs. I really don't know what I'm doing wrong or is the economy that bad? Someone said to me the other day our economy is the best in 10 years. I think she may have been on crack or something because I'm going to have to totally disagree with that.    I'm getting ready to go see my old friends band next week  urlLink Savercool  it's the last show since Shaun saw me come home and freaked out and got a job in Miami. Lucky bastard found a job off of monster.com for Alienware based out of Miami.  I jammed with him and his bassist Mike the other day and we got tore up but at the same time tearing up riffs left and right. Mike is a pretty good guitarist and I look forward to jamming with him again even though he's a very good bass player as well. They invited me to play next week at the show for a few songs and man do I feel honored and privileged. I started out with Shaun when I was about 12 years old and he was about 8 or so. I had a two string acoustic guitar my mom had in the closet and Shaun and a CB Percussion drum set. We played Enter Sandman for hours! We used to record ourselves with a old Fisher Price tape recorder. I think I remember shaun saying something about having them tapes. I might add some of them on this site if that is in fact true.  After doing that off and on for a couple years I moved out of state and still tried to play the guitar   and a black man told me I sound more like a bass player on the guitar and told me to switch for my best interest. Then he invited me to go to a church with him with a bunch of black folks. I got there and these people were jumping out of there seats and screaming and hollering. About half way through the service this black man comes up to me and says, "My father said you played the bass very good." I said man, I never played the bass in my whole entire life. He said, well you do now and handed me a 6 string Tobias neck through bass with gold everything. I got up there and started playing with these incredible musicians and it just came to me.  I haven't put it down since and that was about 14 months ago to this day. Anyways that's my rant for now. Catch you on the flip side..   Savercool's last show ever will be on Wed. June 9th at the Cyber Cafe West on Main St. in Binghamton, NY. We hope to see everyone we know there because they deserve the support after some hard work they have done considering everyone went to college in a different county. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally got a job at Sears as Inside Marketing Manager and it pays pretty decent and I'm pretty sure I'm going to enjoy this job. At least I know it's a secure job since I don't think Sears is having any trouble in the market at the moment. It's in Ithaca so that means I need to look for a small place thats cheap and look for someone to take over my other apt. that I have a lease on in Endicott. I don't know who would want to live with my roommates considering they are loud and irresponsible but who knows.  I like Ithaca a lot and it's like being far from home without being far from home. I like the fact that my original home town is only 30 minutes away "Whitney Point." I know it's really not a big deal but it is to me considering i hate the Binghamton area and Ithaca is a totally different environment and I'm in love with the place. Ithaca college rules, I went up there with Sarah the other day and the whole bottom floor is a bunch of practice rooms with pianos. I'm talking grands, baby-grands and such it's incredible. I finally got to hear Sarah sing the other day and she blew me away you know with the whole show bumps and such. I don't get that very often unless it's unbelievably good and it was by far the best thing I've heard live in a long time. She hit a high Ab and it blew me away. Well i better get moving instead of sitting here writing to no one but myself.. Later n' shit!    
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not sure if people are even reading anymore since I stopped writing on this blog. Nothing has changed much. I got a half house in Endicott NY that I enjoy but tend to have to many people there every night and don't get much sleep.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I found a job @ BAE Systems but the first two weeks I was there they decided they didn't need the department anymore. They told me sorry and they will try to get me back in there whenever another posistion opens up that I'm qualified for.&nbsp;I didn't even get to prove myself to them but I guess shit happens.   I've been visiting a lot lately with my friend Sarah out of Ithaca. She's going to school there and is studying music education and is also a opera singer and vocal coach she has a beautiful voice and personality and so far isn't  Psycho .&nbsp;  Some crazy shit went down this last weekend but I don't have time to write about it right now so hopefully I will find some time later.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>