<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For those who demanded it!!!  Here are the long awaited pictures of the house.  Pictures of the INSIDE of the house will be posted later when I have more time.   urlLink    The Front from the Driveway&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    The Back Yard&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Other Side Showing the Garage&nbsp; urlLink    Here's a shot of the house and garage...you can almost see my convertible tucked away inside the garage...   urlLink    The Other Side of the House&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Detail of the Front Farmers Porch&nbsp; urlLink    Here are details of the side of the house, including the Farmer's Porch.  I can't wait until we can find something to put on it to sit on!  There's a Chimenea sitting in the basement, just waiting to be used, but we have nothing to sit on.   urlLink    House as Seen from the Driveway Entrance&nbsp; urlLink    This is probably my most favorite shot - that the house is almost hidden from the road.  It provides so much privacy!  For those of you who suck at playing "Where's Waldo", the house is sitting in the upper left of the picture behind the foliage...  The North 40 is to the right.  The picture is taken just as the driveway starts at the road - the mailbox would be on the cameraman's right...   urlLink    View of the North 40 in the Distance as Seen from the Porch&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Close Up of the North 40&nbsp; urlLink    Here are pictures of the infamous North 40 where I spend all that time mowing. :)  So far, I've run into 2 snakes, a large ant hill, and a bunny burrow (yes, the bunnies are OK - I got to them in time - but not before my inner red-headed school girl shrieked when she saw something moving under the hay...). 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Barry and I took in the most fabulous winery this past Sunday - Priam Vineyards produces some of the best wines I've tasted so far - in Connecticut and in general.  Their whites are fruity and smooth, and one of their reds puts most Cabernets or Merlots to shame.  For $5, you get to taste seven of their wines, and keep the engraved wine glass as a souvenir!  Plus, if you want, you can take a glass of wine ($5 for a full glass) up through their vineyards to a gazebo to relax and take in the beauty of the area.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The blatantly discriminatory Federal Marriage Amendment is coming up for a vote in the Senate.  It is CRITICAL that you write your senators to tell them to vote AGAINST writing discrimination into the constitution for the first time EVER.  The  urlLink Human Rights Campaign  has provided a  urlLink VERY simple way  to write your senators online.  You don't even have to know WHO your senators are to participate - the web site will figure all that out for you.  It only takes a few minutes, and the results will be historic.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Mansfield Hollow Dam&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Mansfield Hollow Dam&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Mansfield Hollow Dam&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Mansfield Hollow Dam&nbsp; urlLink     Here are some pictures I took with my picture phone while Barry and I were taking a 4 mile walk along an earthen dyke surrounding Mansfield Hollow Lake.  The dyke is a very popular walking destination, and with views like this, you can see why.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey!  Great achievement - I found out how to create and use a links section. :)  Be afraid...I'm learning HTML...  Ack!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Barry at Sharpe Hill Vineyard, June 2004&nbsp; urlLink     Here's a picture of Barry when we set out on a gorgeous day to take in 4 of Connecticut's 13 wineries.  There was nary a cloud in the sky, the temperature was perfect for an outing in the convertible, and we started with Sharpe Hill Vineyards right near our house in Pomfret CT.  For $5, we got to sit in the outdoor courtyard, trying each of their fabulous wines (there were 6 in our tasting - one label had already sold out), and we got to keep our wine glass, embossed with the winery's logo.  In addition, you can help yourself to walking through the vineyards while sipping a glass of their wine - I highly recommend this because at the top of the hill there is a breathtaking view of eastern Connecticut.  We also visited Heritage Vineyards in Lisbon, Jonathan Edwards in North Stonington and Stonington Vineyards in...gasp...Stonington.  All in all, we really enjoyed Sharpe Hill the best (bought a case there!) and are seriously considering having our wedding there next year.  Their restaurant is only open on the weekends by reservation, and boast wonderful wood-grilled meats.  Can't wait to try that out!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So my initial reaction to the house when I first was shown it was that it was perfect in all aspects - land size, house size, location - except for one: the wacko neighbor.  Here I was, standing in this cute house with an open floor plan, cute farmer's porch on the front, and a gorgeous bay window in the dining area...that looks directly into a KEEP OUT sign painted in red letters on a white background.  In addition, he had 3 full length mirrors propped around his yard, all pointing to the new house.  "What's up with that?" I asked my realtor.  She shrugged, as baffled as I was.   urlLink    Neighbor's Keep Out Sign&nbsp; urlLink     Needless to say, my initial reaction was to avoid the house.  But 3 weeks later, when Barry and I were going from house to house in the area with my real estate agent, I stopped by - mistakenly thinking in my blur of properties that I had seen that it was a different lot than it was.  So when we pulled up, I apologized, saying that I must have switched lots in my mind and didn't want to bother him with the house that had the wacko neighbor.  Well, Barry would hear none of that.  The house was too cute and too perfect for us, and basically he emphasized that the neighbor wouldn't be a problem because he could "take care of him."  I didn't want to know what he meant by that because I might find out one day. :)  In the end, we bought the house, despite the sign which continues to face the property.  But as summer creeps upon us, it becomes less and less visible as the overgrowth between our properties takes over.  And the mirrors?  Well, the neighbor finally moved them and assembled them into a screen-like contraption and placed it within his garden that actually looks really pretty there.  I still haven't met them, but then again with the signs, I don't expect I will anytime soon...  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, I learned a valuable lesson the other day - don't leave your open sliding door unattended when you live in the country.  Otherwise, Ninja Squirrels will prance about, seeking nuggets of nutty goodness - and anything else that might be lying around.  I was upstairs engrossed in a video game (many of my friends reading this are probably saying "so what else is new?").  During a break, I came down to get something to drink and the screen to the sliding door was ajar.  Immediately, the worst scenes from every horror flick I'd ever watched streamed through my conciousness, making it VERY difficult to contain that inner redheaded school girl.  I closed the screen, then carefully stalked through the house, looking for ANYTHING that might have gotten in.  Ten minutes later, my blood pressure was returning to normal when I determined that nothing was in the house with me, when I saw the kitchen garbage can had its lid askew.  Then it dawned on me that something had smelled the rich aroma eminating from the repository (OK, OK - give me a break - trash day was 2 days away!), got the screen open, then plunged head first through the trashcan lid to retrieve a prize before scampering back through the screen when they heard me coming down the stairs.  I just want to know where the squirrels have their black ninja outfits made...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Jeff and Barry at Disney's Animal Kingdom Lodge&nbsp; urlLink     I figured I would take some time to introduce ourselves.  The picture is that of me and Barry, taken as we were about to end a fabulous 10 day vacation at Walt Disney World.  We were sitting waiting for the taxi to take us to the airport when we realized that after 10 days, we didn't have ONE picture of us together.  So, this one was hurriedly put together.  I'm the tall one. :)  There will be plenty of posts on us later, but I really wanted to try out getting a picture out here, and thought this would be a great one to start with.  In the future I hope to have pictures of the house to share.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      News article on local NPR this morning indicated that a young black bear was spotted roaming the streets of Willimantic yesterday.  While they *attempted* to sedate him, they apparently didn't give him enough because he simply ambled off and disappeared into the woods.  It seems that the bear population has grown recently in the area, and spottings are becoming very frequent.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a great idea for a beautiful day.  This weekend we went with friends to The Harvest restaurant in Putnam CT for Brunch.  Aside from being reasonably priced, the place served a fabulous meal with the best coffee I've had in a restaurant in ages.  After brunch, we went down the road to the main section of town to go antiquing.  Aside from the fun of poking around a large collection of tchtchkes, the town also has their variation on the Cow Parade (most recently seen in West Hartford) where calves are painted, decorated, and scattered throughout the town.  And don't forget to walk down to the bridge near the dam - what a beautiful site!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lions and Tigers and...Coyotes?  Yep.  I was nearly home the other night when a really, really scruffy dog ran in front of my car, heading away from my house.  Then I realized that it wasn't a dog, but instead a coyote.    Better not leave the cat out.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just noticed that the ad that appeared above my blog was for both a) self-propelled lawn mowers and b) lawn mower repair.  Something tells me that Google is examining a bit too much of my web site for it's targeted ad campaigns. I mean, OK, so I've run over a few roots, branches and rocks while mowing my "lawn"...Alright, I've run over a LOT of them.  Hmmm...  perhaps I better write down that link before it disappears...
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "There is no spoon."  This was my mantra when attempting to bestill my rapidly beating heart.  My inner red-headed school girl gleefully leapt out as I screamed in horror at the monstrous hairy spider that was sitting on the floor in front of me, waving it's front legs as if it were Morpheus taunting Neo into attacking him one more time in the training simulation.  It took only a moment to glance around, looking for the right weapon in which to vanquish this hideous foe.  Spying a worn sneaker set against a door to prevent it from slamming shut (the windows were open since it was a nice spring day), I leapt into the air, everything slowing down so that I was painfully aware of every detail, every moment.  Each of the spider's eight beady eyes trained on me as I passed overhead; it jumped to the side in anticipation of something, but not apparently this.  I landed, grabbed the shoe, and tossed it unerringly at my opponent.  When time returned to normal, I was left staring at a scene of carnage.  The sneaker was coming to rest against a wall, and the spider was twitching in death, mangled by an orthopedic projectile.  Where did I put that leather trench coat...?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why did I think I wanted to mow the yard?  First of all, "yard" is really stretching the meaning of the word when it comes to my property.  It's mostly straw with strands of green poking through it.  But there is one area of the North 40 that was getting pretty wild.  I probably should have had someone come in to slash it down for hay.  But there was something intoxicating about having a mower.  I actually spent two weeks thinking about what I wanted in a mower.  It wasn't until my first 5 minutes of walking behind my new shiny self-propelled red mechanical menace that I probably should have gotten something I could RIDE on.  DUH.  Whatever.  Now, exercise really isn't in my vocabulary.  So after 10 minutes, I'm sweating in a way that might unduly compare me to a Richard Simmons work out video and noticing that I'm gushing blood out of my arm.  Apparently a mosquito the size of a VW Bug didn't get the memo that gay men aren't supposed to donate blood.  So on I went, trying to keep my new 7 horsepower walker moving in the right direction when I run over the reminants of a black plastic sheet.  The noise was atrocious, but nothing compared to the results - a squirming green and tan snake letting me know how annoyed it was to my ripping up his perfectly nice home.  Suddenly, I'm dancing around in a blind panic screaming like a red-headed school girl.  Yeah - THAT's an image sure to invoke machismo with the neighbors.  Time to call up a lawn service...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm convinced that I'm channeling Eva Gabor, even though I know that she is alive and well in some corner of the world.  But the fact that I, a suburbanite (not quite urban - I never got that sophisticated) gay man, have purchased a home in the country.  VERY country.  But you'll learn more about that in future postings.  I decided to create Absolute Tchotchke as a way to diary my experiences in home buying and ownership.  After 43 years, I have finally given up my renting ways and purchased a home of my very own.  And has it EVER been an awakening.  Given how many times I've had friends call me naive, I just had to start journaling my "adventures."  Welcome to that corner of my mind where all the dust collects on trivial and inconsequential tidbits...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I finally got off my butt and decided to publish the pictures of the inside of the house. Hope it was finally worth the wait!!    urlLink      Kitchen in Ivy/Grape/Wine theme &nbsp; urlLink       urlLink     Kitchen Detail &nbsp; urlLink       urlLink     Bay Window with more Grape and Ivy &nbsp; urlLink      The kitchen and Bay Window areas have a grape/ivy/wine theme going, and I think Barry did a great job putting up the accents. We had a great time finding stuff to put into the kitchen - apparently the theme is very popular because we had no trouble finding accents at discount prices.    urlLink     Living Room &nbsp; urlLink       urlLink     Front Door to Back Slider &nbsp; urlLink      The living room has a dark sage/maroon/tan color scheme. Originally we had a theme idea of TUSCANY! (it's important to note the exclamation point - think of Will &amp; Grace and "JUST JACK!" when describing the theme). Since then, we're still pondering what we want in there, but so far there's only color, no theme. We have a great mirror with faux copper finish that will hang above the couch - the copper will pick up the copper in the coffee table frame, so that should be really nice when it gets up on the wall.    urlLink     Dining Room with Countertop Table &nbsp; urlLink      For the dining room, we picked out a gorgeous countertop table. Actually, while Barry loves this table, it's the only room where we have had disagreements. He wanted to turn this space into a TV room, leaving the living room for guest entertainment. But I really wanted a nice dining space for when we had family over for dinner. At the moment, our theme for this room will be Japanese/Oriental; he's gotten a really nice Geisha doll for the centerpiece, and has some wall hangings that we got at Disney that would look nice in here. Needless to say, our dinnerware will probably end up being black japanese-style plates.    urlLink     Garage - see Barry's new car on the right? &nbsp; urlLink      To finish off the first level, here's an inside shot of the garage, complete with both cars. Barry's brother, Steven, helped him purchase his new Toyota Corolla, which was a huge help. Having a car he can rely on for distance travel to and from work has sped up our discussions about Barry moving into the house. And if it wasn't for Steven, I would NEVER have gotten the garage door openers up! Thanks, Steven!!!    urlLink     Master Bedroom - a mix of themes. &nbsp; urlLink       urlLink     Master Bedrom from the other side.&nbsp;  urlLink      And finally, here are the pictures of the master bedroom. The furniture we got at a Rhode Island chain called Cardi's, and we just love it. It's sort of a art deco style in a cherry wood, but we pulled a polynesian theme from the painting hanging over the bed. So we have a polynesian/palm/bamboo/English Colonial thing happening that's quite pleasant. The palm tree theme carries over into the master bath as well.   That's it for house pictures! Hope you enjoyed them. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    UConn's Titan Arum - the Corpse Flower.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    My neighbor, Melissa, in front of the Corpse Flower.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Why am I smiling?  It smells like 3 day old roadkill in here!&nbsp; urlLink     Well, I got to see the Corpse Flower that is blooming ridulously close to my house.  UConn's Life Sciences Department has grown this unusual tropical flower from a seed the size of a Lima Bean.  It flowers VERY infrequently (it was planted 10 years ago), and when it does, it's amazing.  The flower grew from a small stalk to over 5 feet tall in less than a month.  When the base of the flower opens, it emits a NASTY stench that smells like something died several days previously on the side of the road.  In the middle of summer.  *gag*  But this was a once in a lifetime chance to see something unusual. :)  More information can be found on  urlLink UConn's web site .  If you don't see the link directly, you can search on "corpse flower" to find articles on it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think at some point you'll see many of the articles disappearing off of the web site.  Where did they go?  Well, blogging tools often "archive" older posts to a special area once a month.  If you look on the left side of the web page, you'll see (eventually) a set of links for "Archive".  If you click on June 2004, you'll get to all of the stories posted for June 2004 (duh).
     

    
</post>


</Blog>