<Blog>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so i got bored i thought i would post this gay little thing i wrote while i was half asleep last night. It is stupid and for laughs... so dont be a dumbass and take it seriously... 0.o  the past can not be changed. the future can not be seen. all there is is the present, the moment i hold in my hands. forward! with the sky above, and the blood in my veins.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I wanted to post a picture as well but it would seem as though the bloggerbot is down (the thing used for posting pics). I will upload one and add it to the post after it gets up and running.  Antec Lanboy Case This is a very nice looking case with a very stable power supply. It lacks sound insulation but that can easily be fixed with some mods ;)  GIGABYTE 7VT600 Motherboard  AMD ATHLON XP 2500+ 512K 333FSB Processor (overclocked to 2800+) For the price this is a really sweet cpu. Some day down the road I plan to upgrade to a higher end P4 or something like that, but I think I am going to wait til the next generation of cpus to come out. SAPPHIRE RADEON 9600XT 128MB Video Card  This card is amazing. there really is nothing more to say. KINGSTON VALUERAM 512MB PC2700 Some times i think i should have gotten some pc3200 instead, but the price was quite a bit different and I still dont know how much of a difference it would have made... LG GCE-8525B CDRW 52X24X52 its no dvd burner but it does what i need :P MAXTOR DIAMONDMAX PLUS 8 40GB Hard Drive Yes, I could use a little bit more space. I am getting another 80 gig hard drive really soon. PANASONIC 1.44MB BLACK 3.5IN FLOPPY DRIVE Vantec 80mm Stealth case fans (2) Vantec Aeroflow CPU cooler  The thing is a freaking vacume cleaner that can be heard all the way downstairs if there is no other noise in the house (a freaking 70db). But it should be expected with a total of 12,000 rpm of van power. ~grumbles~ stupid heating problem... Philips 109B5 LightFrame 3 19inch monitor This monitor is just sweet. Reasonably priced, stylish, really bright, high resolution, high refreash rate. I did have a problem with the first one i gouht though. After a week when i went to turn it on the picture was really fuzzy and could not be fixed. So i brought it back, got it replaced and have not had a problem sense. Acer 54e 15 secondary monitor  This thing sucks so bad. It is just one of those cheap, mass-manufactured monitors made back i nthe 1990's for budget computers but it really kicks ass when using photoshop, dreamweaver, soundforge or something like that to save alot of room. Sound Blaster Live! Dolby Digital 5.1 Sound card It was cheap, and by cheap I mean like $40. It is a great card that gives me everything I need. The biggest problem is the fact that the drivers are so horrible and outdated so I am using some of those third-party type drivers. It works I guess. Logitech z-560 500watt 4.1 surround sound  yes, it is only 4.1 but there are very few speakers that can match the quality and power of these guys. Sony MDR-CD280 DJ Headphones I have had these ones for quite some time, yet they are still really good. The lowtones (base) is really bad but these things have really taken a beating, have overall good quality and look not too bad. Plantronics .AUDIO 60 Stereo Headset Logitech Wingman Rumblepad controler  I normally love logitech so I do not know what the heck happened here. There is some sort of retarded problem with the left joystick that makes it so it doesent respond when you move it to the right and there is no fix for it other then unpluging it, and then plugging it in agian... recall it already!!!!! Microsoft Wheel Mouse Optical mouse Microsoft Multimedia keyboard HSP56 Micromodem 56k modem  its old, its not a voice modem, but i didnt pay anything for it so there. HP DeskJet 656c printer  Yes, i know this printer sucks but i am not into this 'lets buy a high end printer, so i can buy high end paper, so i can buy high end ink, so i can print high quality pictures, so i can pay for my incredably overpriced ink more often' fad... HP ScanJet 2300c scanner Lexmark X125 Printer/scanner/fax on network   Software worth noting:  Windows Xp Professional SP1 Microsoft Office 2003 Adobe Photoshop CE Adobe Acrobat 6.0 Pro Alcohol 120% Diskeeper 8 Fruit Loops Studio 4 Sony Sound Forge 7 Microsoft Encarta 2004 Macromedia Suite mx 2004 (dreamwaver, freehand, flash, fireworks) Mathamatica 5 CuteFTP XP Pro  I dont know if it is just me but my posts seem really weak... its just there is not much to talk about these days other then school and who wants to hear about school. Well i guess i could tell you about the apple juice i drank last night...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is one of the shots taken when I went on holidays out to b.c. with my special babe. We had such a sweet time house boating. When I finsih up the site and she starts posting here I am sure she would love to say some stuff about it :D. All in all, it kicked ass
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I would just like to say hello to everyone visiting alifedivided.com. Our site got shut down because apparently someone found out about an upload script I had been writing and used it to upload some not-too-legal things. So here we are at blogger. I am not sure if alifedivided.com will ever become a full-out website again as it is a lot of work and blogger has a lot of nice features to it. If only I was able to create other sections with just plain html... Anyways for now this is where it is at. If blogger ever opens up it's pay thing again I will deffinatly go for that as I hate that thing above the blog just as much as you do (thank god for admuncher :D). I ordered some sweet new stuff for my computer which I will deffinatly post pictures for when I get them, it is some really sweet stuff. Well, until then take care.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>