<Blog>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    cruising&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      	                       by             jon wilcox    STORIES started November, 1982 BLOG started June 3, 2004  Introduction Part I  I sat back comfortably in the Acela Regional and watched the brown dusky twilight of a November Massachusetts evening glide past the window. The bus from Boston to Manhattan is faster, surprisingly, but the train provides considerably more legroom, and an arrival time that would not be drastically extended by a Westchester traffic jam. If cell phone use was eliminated it would be a nearly perfect form of transportation. Three conductors conference in the aisle next to me, their attire and their demeanor seemingly unchanged for a century, I look up and imagine them breaking into the opening number from “The Music Man.” The large male conductor turns and leans into my row to let his female colleague past. His belly is too big to button his jacket and he leans it over the edge of the fortunately vacant seat next to me in a position that resembles what he must look like leaning into a urinal. He turns and continues speaking to her, swings his head around when she passes and removes his stomach from my personal space. He does not offend, however—practically nothing does these days. Shivers run up and down my spine. If they are from the Yohimbine my psychiatrist recently prescribed or the satisfaction of the twenty-year arc ending around me, I am unsure. This is clearly not the world I lived in in 1982. It is easier for me to remember some of the minutest details of my life then, than it is to remember the name of a restaurant I ate in last week. But they say Einstein didn’t remember his own phone number, so I don’t mind.  Twenty years ago this week I rode in a bus down University Avenue from St. Paul to Minneapolis. The fall of my freshman year had passed by in a haze undoubtedly caused by the thrill of leaving my parent’s house, the challenge of courses I couldn’t sleep through and ace, the combination of beer, vodka, and lemonade Hamline freshman called “strip and go nakeds,” and another organic pleasure known as “Maui-wowie.”  I had had sex with only two people previously. A female camp counselor named Sandy who stole my virginity on the 4th of July in 1981, and a boy in my High School that most affectionately, or not so, was known as Rob the “choir fag,” or Rob the “drama head.” At a graduation night party that became a tame Midwestern choir kid’s make-out orgy, the two of us found ourselves fondling each other as we kissed the two Sheilas. The two comedic girls of the same name were always suspected of being lesbians. Rob and I escaped to the privacy of an empty room down the hall where I discovered that I had somehow magically developed a talent for performing filatio. Rob completely freaked afterwards, to which I had two thoughts: “this seems out of character for a ‘choir fag,’” and “you didn’t even do anything asshole.”  “What does this mean? What does this mean?” Rob screeched. If I could put myself back into the situation with my current perspective, I might have responded:  “It means I gave you a blowjob.”  But the fact that the most-gay person in my school couldn’t really deal with the fact gave me pause. In fact, it gave me fear. What did this mean? Perhaps this was unnatural. Perhaps even the gayest of characters isn’t really gay. I was pleased by my newfound skill. I had imagined I was preparing for someone really special as I gave myself the best orgasms of my young life by probing around with a broomstick or tennis racket handle. Perhaps it is depraved as everyone says.  The 16A rolled across the intersection of Snelling and University and I boarded. I had forgotten to get a transfer but afraid of trying to explain that to the driver, I paid another 75 cents and headed to the back of the bus—where the cool people sit. A mountain of laundry for mom filled one bag; a mountain of homework from the past three weeks filled the other. As usual, I had attempted to cure a hangover with a big breakfast of pancakes, eggs, bacon, orange-juice and Coca-cola. It almost worked and I felt strangely energized and ready to face my family, a task that took surprising amounts of the stuff.  Then it happened. And I believe that is the appropriate phrase. For this was the beginning of the writing of this book and it happened to me. I “knew” I would write it, and I knew that this moment was the start of it. I didn’t know it would take twenty years to congeal in my brain before it actually got down on electronic paper. But I have never and will never forget the absurd moments that followed and what went on in my brain. For years I had no idea what exactly it was that burned some of these moments so into my memory, but at least now I have some clues.  Ahead of me on the nearly empty bus about six rows, a strange pair sat across from one another on the aisle. A black businessman in a suit and trench coat sat with his briefcase on his lap. Across from him, an even more un-politically correctly described “old lady” sat with a plastic scarf covering her hair, her cat-like metal eyeglasses neatly pushed under the scarf and an umbrella in her hand. It’s not many Minnesotans that carry umbrellas in the winter--what’s the use? But perhaps she was from elsewhere.  Suddenly, and without warning, the black businessman sneezed. But it was the kind of sneeze where the person plugs their nose and tries not to let the sneeze out. It sounded more like a high, shrill mouse squeak than a human sneeze. I don’t think it’s good to sneeze that way. I think the energy of the sneeze needs to be projected outward. When someone sneezes that way, I think the energy from the sneeze is projected directly back into the brain and probably causes some kind of brain damage over time. I don’t know this as a medical fact, but most people I tell agree with me. When I sneeze, I try to do the opposite, I don’t necessarily cover my mouth and I blast the sneeze out and make as much noise as I possibly can. I often add an “oooooweeee” afterwards to add to the drama. Now that’s a healthier sneeze.  I think the swallowed sneeze also indicates a lot about the sneezer. It implies a good deal of anal retention and fear. I knew that man was uptight, probably an accountant or lawyer, was spanked a lot during his toilet training and enjoyed balancing checkbooks and other things that he could make “perfect.” As a reaction to the businessman’s sneeze, the old lady turned suddenly and then paused, as if to say, “What the hell kind of sneeze was that? Don’t you know you can get brain damage from that kind of sneeze?” But she didn’t say that. Instead she uttered what I marked as a completely absurd thing to say in a quiet, stilted, timid voice: “Gazhuntheit.”  “Thank you,” he replied and wiped his nose with a handkerchief.  Now I was appalled. What the hell kind of conversation was that. Is that really what two people in the world should say to each other as they drive down University Avenue on the day before Thanksgiving? It was obvious to me that the woman had never spoken to a black person before. Thus the pause when she turned to see the sneezer. She feared and was attracted to the man at the same time. Growing up in a rural area she had never seen a black person until well into her 30s and she’d never, never spoken to one before. Then, when she did have this remarkable opportunity to connect with someone of a different race for the first time, what does she say? “Gazhuntheit???”   Completely absurd.  Then the real moment happened. I suddenly began thinking about what I was thinking about. How did I get on this rampage about gazhuntheit? How did I know so much about the businessman and the old lady? I knew what I was thinking about them was true. Absolutely. But how could I know that? How did I start making these circles around my brain, perceiving about my perception?  Then I got this wonderful, warm, loving feeling in my chest. I loved the black businessman. I loved the old woman. I love the world and I see that we can connect with one another just like this couple did on a 16A bus riding down University Avenue on a Wednesday in November 1982. Another discovery: Does everyone have thoughts like this when they are riding public transportation? I think they do! I am so happy and so enlightened and I want to share that with the whole world in a book. I must write this down in a book called “Thoughts While Riding Public Transportation,” and let people know this amazing fact: we can connect with each other and that is good.   Introduction Part II  I arrived in downtown Minneapolis in the early afternoon to transfer to a bus that would take me to my Grandmother’s home in Golden Valley. After my epiphany with the couple on the 16A, I was feeling at one with the world. It was a brisk November afternoon in Minnesota, which for most of the rest of the world means freezing cold. I bounced lightly in place and blew on my hands for warmth. Suddenly, which is a word I’ll use for most of these moments, a voice startled me from behind.  “Is that a backpack?”  I turned to see an elderly woman—although I wouldn’t say old—she was smartly dressed and had a warmth to her face that would cause me to say “elderly.” Besides, she definitely wasn’t wearing a plastic scarf over her head.  “Excuse me?” I said.  “Is that a backpack? My grandson wants one for Christmas and I didn’t know what they were.”  “Yes, this is a backpack…that’s what is alright.”  “Oh, I’m so glad I asked you. Thank you. Are you going home for Thanksgiving?”  “I’m going to my Grandmother’s. I’m meeting my family there.”  “Oh, that’s so nice for your Grandmother. Are you in school?”  “Yes, I’m a freshman at Hamline University.”  “Oh, is your Grandmother Nellie DeCoursey.”  “What!? Well, yes, um, how did you know?”  “I’m her neighbor, Elizabeth. I’m waiting for the bus too.”  As if my one-world feeling needed to be increased any more at this point, a small-world interaction brought me to an even higher feeling of euphoria. Of all the people to run into in crowded downtown Minneapolis, but my Grandmother’s neighbor and of all the topics of conversation to draw us together but a backpack. The magic continued.  Unlike many times to follow, my euphoria was not followed by a deep fear that the world, or I, was about to end. I remember once driving by Flying Cloud Airport and down an embankment overlooking the Minnesota River. At this time of year, it overlooked a breathtaking pageant of red, gold, and orange fall colors. It was truly beautiful and I remember feeling so good that I could run around and kiss each of the trees. But quickly, the euphoria began to worry me. Why did I feel so good? I felt so good that it seemed the only answer was that I was about to die. I began driving much more conscientiously. I began to prepare for oncoming cars swerving into my lane. I pictured the twisted wreckage, my body burned beyond recognition, my parents trying to identify me in a morgue somewhere. That was pretty much enough to kill the euphoria.  As I will attest to in Chapter 5, cars are public transportation. But it is communication through steel. Wearing suits of armor on the freeway, usually our conversations are none too polite. Who hasn’t given a good “fuck you,” to a driver around us, with a gesture, a swerve into his lane, or high beams in the rear view mirror? It’s easy. Who would ever do that to a person next to us on the subway no matter how obnoxious they were being? Take off the armor and we’re much more like the person next to us than we’d like to believe. Take off the armor and one human is pretty much like the next. 	   CHAPTER 1  BILLY JEAN IS NOT MY LOVER  I’ll try not to get sentimental as I look back, but St. Paul, Minnesota was a wonderful place to go to college. There are seven major colleges and of course the behemoth University of Minnesota not far away. I chose Hamline University because my father was a Methodist Minister and therefore I received a third off tuition, and because the school I really wanted to go to, Carleton College in Northfield, had had the nerve to waitlist me on the first round.  There are those decisions that change everything forever. I used to regret the decision to go to Hamline. I used to regret many things. But in the end, if some of the greatest joys in your life come from some of the most painful and disturbing times, how can you regret them?  In the fall of 1982 Michael Jackson was still black and presumably sane. His album “Thriller,” had sold 700 trillion copies in perhaps the last big sweep of LP sales before cassettes and CDs took over the market. It was still pretty cool to like Michael Jackson, even if you were a freshman WASP at an urban liberal arts college.  In January, all the liberal arts colleges celebrated the Interim, or J-Term period. A month long chance to “study” marine biology in Hawaii or painting in Italy if you were rich enough, or to only have one course to cross campus for during the nastiest month of the Minnesota winter.  I had not auditioned, but “coincidentally” got the chance to change classes and sing in an opera for my J-Term project. Students from five St. Paul colleges were coming together to perform, “The Unicorn, the Gorgon, and the Manticore,” by Gian Carlo Menotti. The Director was a brilliant and warm man, who I subsequently saw play “Sweeny Todd,” at the Chimera Theater. Years later, I also heard he had died prematurely of “Legionnaires Disease,” in closeted 1987 Minnesota, I suspect this was a code word for AIDS.  I forget many of the details of what came next, so I will keep my comments to what I believe are “just the facts.” During the rehearsal period, a soprano named Janice Tomkins and I began dating, began a sexual relationship, daydreamed about what our children’s names would be (Drew was the first choice for a boy). One night, I smoked pot and tried to break off the relationship because I felt so guilty for doing so and didn’t need another mother. She said she thought it was cool that I smoked pot and asked me to come and get her the next time I was going to do it.     CHAPTER 2  The Big Man On Campus  The metaphor did not get past me.  Few did in those days.  In my manic-psychotic dream that spring of 1996, the entire world was a metaphor.  The mountains around Pasadena resembled, no, were the mountains around Jerusalem.  Street signs shouted subliminal messages that only the chosen could see.  The signs had always been right there, but only now were the messages making themselves known to me.  Even daily routines like showering took on magnificent meaning.  I said aloud, “A baptism every day, John,” consciously inserting an “h” into my name so there could be no mistake as to my identity. But the metaphor that later struck me most strange was the open closet door.  Not the altar that I had prepared in Peter’s spare bedroom.  Not the thirty-four cents I used to buy back my soul from the beggar outside a 7-11 when my total had come to $6.66.  Not even the nap I took in the mountain hideaway where I was able to sleep soundly and watch myself sleeping at the same time.  The closet door wasn’t even an intended metaphor.  One of the two sliding doors needed to be opened to balance the energy of the two mirrors.  The powers of feng shui, psychic energy cosmic balancing, and the ability to see angels, devils, and subliminal messages from God were among the powers granted to me in those days.  I have never felt as blessed as I did then.  I know I am still blessed, but if only I could feel it more like I did at that time.  But those days were part of the insanity that I will call the second time I came out. The first and third times were far less dramatic, but more of what might be called, “real.”  My first real boyfriend and I came out to each other on Halloween night in the fall of 1983.  Returning to my dorm room from an off-campus costume party where he played a minstrel-like Michael Jackson and I did my best James Dean impression, it now seems pretty obvious that we were gay.  But in small-town, pre-AIDS, southern Minnesota, these two nineteen year-olds had not yet reached that level of sophistication.  I hadn’t dared to tell anyone about the incident on the night of my High School graduation.  (I mean, everyone knew Rob was gay.  How could he have been so upset about a damn blowjob?)  Becoming consciously aware of our homosexuality held little appeal with no campus gay and lesbian organization, no gay bars closer than Minneapolis, and no role models except for Boy George, Liberace, and ostracized cousins.  So, as Dan showered off the shoe-polish, I anxiously waited in my single room with loft.   He was beautiful.  I was surprised we had even become friends.  He looked everything like the college hero.  I was surprised when I found out he wasn’t a senior, but a sophomore like me.  He was friends with all the cool people in choir (is that an oxymoron?) and he was in a frat.  I had barely survived my freshman year at another college where I desperately searched for a girlfriend, then found one who, as fate always has it, was as lonely and in denial as I was.  Within three months she was pregnant and we got engaged then disengaged. Then I got drunk, stoned, and taken to County Hospital with a pulse of 180 and a blood pressure of 170 over 130, capillaries popping in my brain.  I left that University by ambulance and did not return.  My new isolated, idyllic, rural private Lutheran college promised a welcome escape.  So with all the confidence and false-bravado of a nineteen-year-old who’d just been trash compacted, I was surprised when the B.M.O.C. called me over to his table during lunch.  I was even more surprised when we actually became friends.  I mean, I lived in Wahlstrom—the nerd dorm.  I couldn’t believe that a respectable resident of North Hall and the only freshman to tour Europe with the Gustavus Choir last year would dare set foot in my pod of six-single-rooms around a common area and bath.  And yet he was!  And he was in the shower now.  And he's coming in here soon in a towel.  Shit!  The next few moments were among the most fearful and exciting of my life: Dan in a towel and white-faced once again; me in shorts and a T-shirt sitting on, and looking at, the floor.   “I need to tell you something.”  I say, horrified by my own words.  I glance at his eyes.  Am I really going on with this?  “What is it, what’s wrong?” The soft, strong tenor voice teases and taunts me.  Why would he think something is wrong?  Is it just because I can’t stop staring at the flecks in the gray carpet between my legs? The moment of truth.  I leap off a ninety-foot cliff into the inward rushing Pacific or headfirst onto the bare rocks below.  But I cleverly coded the language so that perhaps the meaning could be altered if it wasn’t well received.  “I think I like you too much.”  I finally say and actually muster the courage to look at the beautiful face.  And then, an amazing thing: soft brown eyes, the hint of a smile, a blush, and an answer that thrilled, frightened, and exhilarated:  “I don’t think so.”  That night may have been the happiest of our relationship.  So relieved to have found each other, we had no thought of what this night meant to anyone outside of that single room.  We never made it into the loft.  But on the floor below, with the window over us framing the thunderstorm outside, we touched, we kissed, we made love, we held each other and did nothing but breathe.   It was light by the time we slept and only two hours after shutting my eyes, still in Dan’s arms, my alarm clock’s piercing tone threw me into a frenzy of clothes, toothpaste and scrambling to meet fellow music students for our trip to the American Choral Conductors Association convention in Minneapolis.  Whether it was the two hours of sleep, the six Sloe Gin fizzes or something else in my stomach, all I remember about the drive up was staring out the window at the dead grass by the highway and trying not to throw up.  The sound of various students trying to brown-nose our professor did not help my condition, either.  I probably wouldn’t have joined their conversation even if I weren’t so afraid that if I moved I would vomit.  After hearing a dozen or more of the Upper Midwest’s most prestigious choral groups and driving back to campus, I found Dan by the library, by chance.  I was afraid again.  Had we really done that?  Did he still like me?  For God’s sake what did it mean?  Should we let it happen again?  And the most frightening thought of all: what if anyone finds out? 
     
    
</post>


<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HOLY TRINITY BATMAN!  by  Vannessa Soto  &  Jon Wilcox
    
</post>



</Blog>