<Blog>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, few days never never log in pc le.. haha  Today veri buzy also neh, helping frend from Batu Pahat to look for the working place on interview. Successful to ne.. She got the offer.. SGD2,200.. hop i m able to get tis kind of job wif lots $$..  Working niteshf wif Sabaria.. David Chin brought me a jar but at the end i found out was a glass ma.. wat a joke..  Meet friendster fren.. Mandy Yeo, and she was finishing her contract at Hang Ten, Will go for NP 28 Jun on tis school openning, course is "early childhood"..  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ai yo yo.. Sunday leh.. but but tiring 1 sia!  Worked til 8am and my colleugue, Sabaria, fetch me home direct to Toa Payoh coz she was on d way to visit her relative der at Blk 150..  Then after taking bath, stil managed to take a nap about 30 mins coz need to attend Wedding Lunch, Roger & Amy big day mah...  Meet Ding Shun, Raymond, Annie, Wan Xin at City Hall MRT before went to d party. But but guess wat, Hui Mei wil b late, 12pm, n she ask Li Ying to wait 4 her.. So, at d end v all go off 1st.. Guess how much i put in the red pocket..? SGD88, sia, liao lui liao la! But then boh bian lo, ppl wedding once a life mah.. hehe.. Total Suntec staffs tat i knoe was 4 table, Joaquim aunty(+MeiBoey,Casher-Yvhone,HelenChoo etc),Big Short(, StallMy table#23, sit together with LiYing,WanXin,HuiMei,LiJin,Raymond,DingShun,TiongSoon
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Again.. tired.. went to EXPO today, bought MP3, 256MB, We!Wa!, SGD199..  Working niteshf now.. Partner is Sabaria.. She is going to be tiring coz got Citybank faulth.. Stupid job la! The media ID for Backup Server was wrongly define! Wasted about 10 mins to figure out! Thanks GOD didn't waste lots of afford der!  Friendster new friend added = Mandy, Spoken a while but out of sudden disconnect without inform! Wat a rude person she is..! Nvrmind, mayb she hav something urgent or time 4 sleep la..  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wat a tired day after worked at Congress Kopitiam from 3-10:30pm. Working partners were James, Careen..  Singapore Idols Audit will be held tomorrow but can c the crowd already at Suntec..  Hear UFM1003,Yu2 Ling2, tat new got sales at Geylang, $1 for 10 durians, now heavy jammed!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1st of all, thanks for Cindy Yeo, who bring me to her blog.. Eventually bring me to hav my own blog.. Although tired now but still wanna to write somethings yo..  I m working nite shift on yesterday, my partner is Nora, she is pretty gals but too skinny le.. =) Must put on weight ya.. She is going to marry soon, 18 Dec 2004, if i remember correctly.  Yesterday got interview for new job at Insurance company, JohnHancock, as Finance Planner, intervier was Shawn S Tan, quite friendly guy but i rejected the offer coz the jobs scope like salesman de.. =(  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>