<Blog>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have so much to say, I can't wait to say all of it.  I am happy I saw one of my friends blogs today, he was introducing me to the idea and today was the best day to start.  School ended for me today.  I have mixed feelings about this, as always.  I now miss what I hate about my dayly rutine at school.  There are those moments durring the day that you can't stand yet you now start to miss them.  Speaking of moments, I have so many to talk about so I am going to make a list today of what needs to be said this summer, all of these things will show up at some point (not in this order):  EVENTS - Moving to GB, The first summer, losing Magic, The Grizzly Retreat, My first day of High School, My freshman year as a whole, 8th grade - the leaving, 8th grade, Before 8th grade, Sports-A-Rama (year 1), Leaving Fresman Year, The Softball Video, Animation Night Classes, The end of both 9th and 10 grade rush, The second summer, Day at the Bay (year 1), My year with Chris Rojas/Saying goodby to Seniors, The last day of 9th grade, Reading Chriton, Reading Harry Potter #5, The second summer, media camp (year 1), Cabo, Labor Day, Back to school (10th grade), The buying of my laptop, another first day (10th grade), My first semester (10th grade), The first day of second semester (10th grade), Invited to the table, Float Building, Sports-A-Rama (10th garde), Quad Dance (10th grade), May Play Day, Yearbook signing, A date, England (the 5th time is a charm), July 4th (one year that I forget the year of), Saturday Night fever, We will rock you, the seeing of High School plays, GSPN, DTC: Tech and acting Camp, Lethal Confinement  more may be added.  I wanted to list those because I didn't want to miss any.  I also want to list the topics I will discuss but maybe I should leave those as a supprise.  Infact, I thonk each event will have a theme, one of my topics and I will discuss it then.  As for todays discussion, I have written enough.  There is something I really want to talk about but I will leave it for tommorow (that should remind me).  PS - Harry potter 3 goes into theaters tommow, I have tickets for the first showing...that will be another topic for tommorow. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome,  I don't know who you are but you are about to meet me.  I decided to do this for one reason: myself.  Everyday durring my summer between Sophomore year and Junior year I will write about something, a thought or maybe an event in my life.  My goal is to have a story, one in which you can read any chapter of and understand one pice of me, not all but another day will lead you to another pice.  I have tried this in the past, not a daily basis but every once in a while talking through words.  This summer I will create a diary for myself.  If you decide to read this then take it for it's face value, the openions are only mine (unless I say they are someone elses).  I may get personal in here but I have decided, why am I holding secrets?  This is a pice of art, I will stop the day school starts and may create a new one but this blog site will stay as is.  I am cautius in creating this because I know it will be difficult to maintain but I have a feeling it might work because I have already made it a part of my day as you will read in a week or so.  So enjoy, I will post another post for today as this is only an introduction but there will be one a day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is the first day of summer and tomorrow the Seniors graduate.  If you don't know me my niche is media, I love video production and I have no idea why.  Anyway, we always film graduation in live-to-tape.  That works by making a live feed from 4 cameras in different places around graduation to a switching board and we record a program that is basically edited live using the switcher.  The point is two people can set this up in like 4 hours so I switched up at school today at 7:30 to start.  It was a lot of work, real work that I am not used to but for some reason today was different, I was pumped up and I went above and beyond actually enjoying the totally boring and utterly exhausting work that needed to be done.  We finished around 11:30 and I went to Harry Potter 3.  Like expected Harry potter was packed and mostly with kids I knew, I had 9 other friends in my group.  Needless to say it was great but different, after all a director makes or breaks a movie and this one made it, only different than Chris Columbus, the pervious two's director.  I then left calling my dad for a ride.  He told me that my asst. principal Mike McGuire called me because he needed my help on something.  Why don't people like Asst. Principals?  I spent from 4:00 to 10:30 struggling on a video having a great time though!  Asst. Principals have such a blast!   If only people would realize how great they are.  He now has my back for 2 years because of a couple hours I spent with him.  Life if what you make it, make it!  That is my theme for today, my theme is that I could have gone home and spent 6 and a half hours watching TV or helped someone truly in need because of a deadline by Monday.  I knew something he didn’t and I used my brain to help rather than not.  Did I lose anything?  No!  Did I gain anything?  I have 4 asst. principals and one principal who will go to bed tonight thinking... that Andrew, he's a great guy.  I was treated to dinner tonight, taco bell.  Yeah ok, the food wasn't fancy but I had a great time.  Again, it is all what you make it.  Personally I hate taco bell, I was even offered Carl's Jr., a place I would prefer but I felt that even taco bell was them going out of their way and I needed to go along with it.  During dinner Mr. McGuire got up and said he was going to go buy a meal.  He left the place and went to ask a homeless person outside what he would like.  The guy refused and walked away.  Isn't that interesting... he would rather eat that burger he just grabbed from the trash.  Why?  Did he not want to be a charity case?  People are strange.  Everyone has a story that makes them who they are.  What did you do on July 23, 1995?  Do you know?    Chances are you learned something that day, it changed you along with the next day and the one after.  Learning is what life is all about, we are here to understand what we see and interpret it.  Life is a sequence of random events before one becomes death.  The important thing is what you learned from it because that is who you are.  Without those events you would be nothing.  So go make some!  Go do something!  if you cannot think of anything to go then help someone, go to a random person and help them with what they are doing because then maybe they will remember that on July 23, 1995 some crazy person helped them and they will remember not only the lesson but the day.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was graduation.  I woke up and went to direct the video for graduation.  One student brought up a great point; he will never again go to High School.  He accepted this though; he understands that he needs to move on.  I however cannot.  I actually have a hate for summer.  The likes out weigh it but I dislike it because one day is gone.  It was an eventful day along with today but still at the end of it there will be many uneventful days.  What a waste!  Yet, those days are why I like summer, doing nothing.  I HATE THAT!  The whole summer I am upset that it will end.  I cannot enjoy a lot of things because I know they will end.  I think that is why I don't like change.  A big change can cause chaos in my life.  Traditions are important to me and because of that I have very few with other people.  I have traditions like watching Gillian’s Island during lunch in the summer, this summer I can’t do that because it has moved to a new time and it is causing chaos!  I don't know what I will do during lunch on Monday.  Today’s home is saying goodbye, we all need to do it many times in our life.  The idea I guess is really to make it as hard as possible.  Enjoy your time.  I have a second chance, that graduate doesn’t, I can still enjoy two more years that he can't.  Take your chance and start enjoying what you do on a day-to-day basis because it will end at some point and you don't want to regret not living it up! 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Disclaimer:  I wrote this at a bad time of the day, I look back over it and realize that some of these things maybe should have been kept to myself.  I then thought of my introduction and realized I have no secrets on this site so these are just my random thoughts.   Why are you wearing clothes?  Why did you get out of bed this morning and go through a routine including getting dressed?  I was going through some baby pictures of my cousins laughing at the nude ones as usual.  Then I realize that when they took these pictures they could differentiate between nude and not yet they chose nude.  Why?  I know... they hadn't yet learned shame.  They were not yet embarrassed to be nude.  That is dumb though, why do we hide ourselves?  I am sorry to sound so much like a guy here but the only reason we wear clothes is because we are taught to be embarrassed of nudity.  Now being nude is like loosing virginity.  What if someone became totally attracted to elbows, the "got off" on the opposite sex's elbows.  Don't they see pornographic material every day?  The only reason why they are "private parts" is because we make them private.  We only show ourselves to someone who we love.  Call me a prostitute but I don't care who sees me nude.  Why are we all so homophobic?  A friend of mine told me he was bisexual last summer and suddenly I can't look him in the eye.  As much as you like to deny it you do not view a gay guy the same way as a strait guy.  Are we afraid that they might like us?  That makes no sense!  Take someone really; really ugly from the opposite sex, are you afraid of them getting a crush on you?  Chances are you aren't because it doesn't matter; you don't need to date them.  That is the same type of thing, someone you aren't attracted to liking you.  No matter what you say you are BI.  I do not care what you say, that day of swimming in PE; you hoped you saw some dropped pants.  The reason I say this is because we all want to see what we can't.  We hate mysteries.  Now when you did see the dropped pants it didn't look all that great but the mystery kept you wanting it until that point.  Ok, different situation maybe but something of that sort did happen to you at some point and there is no reason to be ashamed about it.  I say all this with confidence of it being true because I have talked to many others with the same view.  Now, I think most of the views I expressed are a male point of view and for females the joy of seeing a nude guy is not as much of a joy.  Yeah it is that hidden thing but I don't believe they need to keep seeing it like a guy, it is more of a been there, done that thing.  I found this funny when I discovered what the majority of females enjoy about sex.  Guys like it for the orgasm (duh) but girls tend to like it for the relationship and the connection.  Case in point masturbation.  Girls can't always orgasm form masturbation, this is why.  Now those that can are just plain horny and most guys classify as sluts when they themselves are no different.  Girls, I got news for you... every guy you know masturbates.  Guys I got so offended by this, if you feel that way right now then stop.  Go one whole week with none.  Finished that?  Go two.  If you are on your third then email me and I will retract that statement and entitle you a god.  It is difficult for guys to miss, we just suck and are bad people because of that.  Now the reason why I found this whole discovery funny was because I have a friend who was almost proud that she had never "pleasured" herself.  She quote, "Can not imagine finding enjoyment in doing it to (herself)" yet guys can.  Girls just have different motives.  Now I think I have said enough about sex and such but I still need to finish my point.  If we all just stopped wearing clothes then they will be forgotten about in 2-3 generations.  The only reason we wear them is we are told to.  I am not saying we should get naked, I am just asking you to consider this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, today's story is the 9th grade Sports-A-Rama.  Infact I have a couple stories that all happened because of it.  To be hones I didn't yet have any friends.  I had made some but in the what, 10 months I had lived here the only friends I had made turned out to not really be friends.  I don't really know why I signed up to be in Sports-A-Rama, I guess it was because I had no clue what it was.  As it turns out it is 7 games that are just totally non-athletic.  You have the mattress relay with 4 guys getting a girl across the gym on an air mattress and then there are things like the chicken toss where you need to shoot a rubber chicken across the gym.  It is basically a rally outside of school.  It is tough to get in because about 40 people want to get in and only 25 make it, you just need to sign up before they do.  Well I made it!  I showed up to the first meeting starting to understand it then realized there were only like 5 other guys on the team.  If there is one question that bugs me it is "Who are you?" because I have no idea how to respond.  Do they want to know my name?  So then I need to sound like an idiot saying "My name is..." and it doesn't help when they don't hear me and ask me to repeat myself.  To be honest I still love the shirt I wore that night.  It was one I get in a small town on the Grand caiman Islands called Hell.  It reads "Official Computer Nerd From Hell", something that now has become a joke.  I don't know how the conversation started but they were joking around and asked me what I thought about a guy with one arm.  Not a real guy, just what I thought about seeing someone with one arm.  And that is when the conversation started.  Someone else chimed in, "What would he have, just a nub?", "Hey then he could be called nubby!"  This name somehow became mine as a joke.  To this day I am still referred to as Nubby.  It wasn't intill the middle of Sophomore year that I was reminded where that came from.  The name had changed over time and I was referred to as C-Nub.  I have no idea where the C came from.  One lunch I asked the two creators of the name, Paul Nutherveld and Josh Dawson what it meant and apparently this was the discrepancy.  The Nubby came from Paul but josh added the C from my shirt, "Official Computer Nerd From Hell".  I don't know if the whole Nubby and C story are true but it was that day when I asked where it came from that they told me all this.  At Sports-A-Rama I thought I fit in.  I thought I had become a friend of theirs and that I was now in there click but for the remainder of the year they weren't my friends, they would say hi to me but it wasn't till much later that I found out they were making fun of me.  Halfway through my 10th grade year I decided this had gone on long enough and I sat with them at lunch.  I was welcomed to the table but not really as a forever welcome, kinda a day pass, maybe a week.  Well I stayed there for a the rest of the year and will return next year.  For those of you who have read Lord of the Flies, I am piggy in this group, I constantly am picked on.  I have been asked why I put up with it but to be honest I don't mind.  I think it goes back to 5th grade when I was suffering depression that I grew up and learned that kids were idiots and those who were different got picked on for no reason and that was wrong.  Since then I have distanced myself from those that are different but never said a bad word about them.  It wasn't until a week after I started thinking over my philosophy with my new friends that we stared learning about Gandhi in history.  I then realized I was acting like him.  I was figuring the only way to fight these idiots was to let them get no reaction out of me.  And it ha worked, I fell no pain at all now when I hear something mean, no pain when I am punched, they are my friends.  Why?  Because they are great people and the one or two of them being idiots are not going to ruin a relationship I have with the others.  Now some may call me crazy but I know it will stop eventually.  It may take most of Junior year but by my Senior year I will have the best friends I could have asked for.  I think I will leave the theme for you to figure out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am back up on my summer schedule.  It was suggested to me last summer by my grandmother because I had become nocturnal.  I could not go to bed early and would be waking up around 1 p.m..  She suggested just getting out of the house.  So I developed a daily routine.  Here it goes for last summer:  9-10: Getting up and watching Regis & Kelly while doing so 10-10.30: Getting down to Starbucks on my Roller blades 10.30-11.30: @ Starbucks 11.30-12: Getting home and swimming 12-1: KCRA News at Noon 1-2: Lunch w/ Gillian's Island 2 on: Free-time to swim, read, work on my computer, or just watch TV  This summer the only thing I changed is I have nothing to watch during lunch, I am still trying to figure out a program, I might need to move lunch to noon.  You know, there are a lot of good programs on at noon but I can't find any at one.  And this is my summer, I complain that I can't watch a TV show because it isn't on anymore.  You know, I would call myself lazy but I am not.  This is not a lazy summer.  I go to the gym 3 times a week, I rollerblade to Starbucks once a day.  That isn't lazy.  It is relaxing, and that is the point, the point is to have an easy summer but not a lazy one.  I am tempted to leave it at that for today but I feel like writing more.  Today during my free time I am going to be working on my next movie.  I still need to work out details in a script before I can write it.  Our original Idea for the script was to do a Swimfan remake, just alter a couple things but as I look it over I realize the plot was not as good as I thought, the movie just made it sound good.  If anyone has any plots feel free to comment to this post with them or just email me with them at andrewcefalo@surewest.net and I might use them.  And today has no theme, I can't think of one to match my rant for the day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What to write about today?  Well nothing new is up so I guess I will hit something from the list!   Leaving Pleasanton: I don't know how to describe my life up until 8th grade.  I was mostly searching, searching for something I was good at, people to be with and who I was.  I am told a lot I am mature for my age but any of my peers will tell you that is totally false.  I was raised as an adult, an equal member in the house and with that there came a lot of things that are different than most people.  One is joining into a conversation.  I have my own views and often disagree with my parents over things like religion and even arguments they get in with friends and family.  I think this way of growing up forced me to become more mature but just in my thought process, not my actions.  When I was in elementary school I was for the most part a loner, I preferred thinking and being by myself.  Again I thing this was because I thought about things differently than others.  The point is by 8th grade I finally caught on to this whole 'being in school' thing.  I say that 8th grade I finally became popular.  Media had a lot to do with this.  I stopped searching in 6th grade, I had found it, I LOVED VIDEO PRODUCTION!  Then by 8th grade I was the best at my school (and I still sucked even at that) but for my school, I was recognized.  I got friends simply because of that and life was great.  Then the bomb drops!  The "Andrew, were moving" speech comes and I am totally lost.  I got through it but leaving my best friends was very tough.  Ben Hubbard and I swore that we would not separate, every month we would visit each other.  I think it was our parents who stepped in front of that, it didn't really happen.  We tried to communicate and we still do but not a lot.  I can't talk to him on IM because he does not talk, he just goofs around (just like when I was living there).  So we try again every once and a while.  Don't get me wrong, I am not saying goodbye here, the guy is still my best friend, we just don't talk a lot.  Saying goodbye was tough as always but I think at least with Ben and his family it wasn't as difficult as others because I knew we would say hello again.  As for everyone else I will never say hello to again, I miss you and if I didn't say it... have a great life.  Todays theme is keeping in touch.  If you ever need to say goodbye to someone here is my advice:  make sure you can always say hi whenever you want.  You don't need to though.  When you move you change, you become someone different.  They may not be used to the new you and that might take some adjustment but at least you can always pick up the phone and call or send an email.  That is an important part of maintaining a relationship.  My mom had a best friend she had to say goodbye to and did so for like 13 years before they decided to talk again.  She is so cool and has become a friend of mine now.  I am very happy they stayed in touch and am glad my very good friends and I are. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wrote this a while ago.  When I started up this site I decided to save this post for a day that I forgot to write.  It may seem a little out of place because as I sait this was really, a while ago.  As I look around my school I see many students.  I was told all through my life everyone is an original; everyone has his or her own personality.  Yet when I look at this school I see something different.  In fact I am going to show this y categorizing everyone into two groups.  When I categorize them you will see that I am right in stating that this is true.  You either get along with people or you don’t.  Now everyone fits into one of those groups.  Sure you have people who are more social than others and everyone enjoys being by themselves sometimes but there are people who for example my parents do not like being around other people.  Those types of people do not make many friends because they simply don’t want any.  Those who do like being around others at my school I further categorize into tow more groups.  I find that there are a lot of copy machines and then there are the broken copy machines.  The broken copy machine is the one we call an original.  Everyone is not original, a part of their personality is and they try very hard to fix that flaw.  There is a dream personality out there somewhere. For every person striving to be like “models” there is a person doing the same with personalities.  I have thought about what this perfect personality is and it is a mix from many things.  That is why I say it is a broken copy machine; it is a copy machine that mixed your document with a couple other peoples.  For those who just can’t wait for me to say what this personality is I can’t.  It is just like a model, you don’t find a model that looks just like all the others, you find a model that looks similar.  This personality will typically follow these guidelines though.  One, they know what to say.  This is the biggest, timing of words and picking the right ones when that time is right.  Why we care so much about this beats me but it is important nonetheless.  This is my biggest flaw and I never have been able to master this.  The second is your outlook on life.  This one isn’t as big but it is important, is the glass half full or half empty?  Now both can be worked with and as long as you work on all the other aspects it will be fine but I must say the correct answer is neither.  Every situation needs to be evaluated for it’s ups and downs and you react on the one it has more of, if it truly is 50% either way than you must have an alien or something because I don’t think that happens to often.  The third aspect goes hand in hand with the first, a comical personality.  There are so many different varieties of this and you can take whatever approach to it that you want.  You don’t need to crack a joke for everything you say, you just need to understand sarcasm and how to use it while also knowing when to throw in a joke that isn’t a “you had to be there” one.  In fact, to be safe, never tell a “you had to be there.”  Those that just mimic this totally, none of it is their own take on it are the copy machines.  You need to have some fun with your personality (this is sounding corny but go with me).  I see people who try to hard to copy someone.  They are striving to be that person and it is very obvious.  If you find yourself being that person then add some of your own flavor to what you are doing.  The most important thing is to listen, listen and watch what everyone is doing, you may just learn something; you may just see what I am talking about.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am surprisingly busy right now.  I did check the calendar and according to it I am on summer right now.  How could I be busy in a time where I have no deadlines?  Wait I do!  I always put myself under pressure with deadlines.  I think that is because I can only relax knowing that the relaxing needs to end soon and I need to get back to work.  That "5 more minutes" feeling makes the time I am wasting seem like much less of a waste.  I have a deadline with the Lethal Confinement DVD's that I set!  The end of next week, why?  Why did I set it then?  AM I CRAZY!?  Seriously, I have 10 weeks to relax yet I force myself to rush to get something done in the first two.  Then there comes the times like new when I am rushing to get the job done by the weekend.  First of all, I am on summer.  Weekends are the same as weekdays only I have both parents home not working vs. on home working.  Second of all, I HAVE ANOTHER WEEK!  The end of 9th grade was crazy, I was doing like 5 major projects and rushing because the day school got out was all of their deadlines.  The first day of summer I had no priorities, no deadlines.  I was totally bored!  This year I think I had the same number of deadlines by the end of school but they were all even more important!  So now I am totally swamped with 2 weeks left before school gets out.  What do I do?  I relax.  That was my theory, why rush?  If they don't get done, they don't get done!  As it turns out I completed all but one, the Lethal Confinement DVD.  Please leave a comment on this topic, am I the only one who goes through this rush?  I hate doing DVD's.  They are such a pain.  Firs of all you need to make your materials.  Once you have used up all the space on your hard drive editing the stupid video you sit for six hours and wait for it to encode.  Now you have no space at all so you dust off the external hard drive from your last project and plug it in.  Now you need to make menus.  Open Photoshop and realize you have no idea how to work the layout.  You figure that out and hopefully don't need video in the menu because then you need to go edit it.  You start the Photo shop portion of the menu and realize you have no extra content and decide you need some.  After pulling some out of your ass you ask yourself, why would someone watch this?  You put it on there anyway.  Then you open the DVD program and author all the menus.  This will take a day if you are lucky.  You test it, build it and test it again.  Finally you settle for what you have made and decide to burn it only to get an error and you have no idea what it says!  Video File Read Error was this projects error.  I spent 7-8 days talking to people on the apple message boards looking for an answer, trying all different things.  Finally I figure out that the main video file is corrupt.  I NEED TO RE-EXPORT IT!  I DELETED A BUNF OF IT YESTERDAY!  So then you need to re-capture and re-export.  yay!  DVD's suck!  Be thankful that people will sit there every day working $10 an hour to deal with this for you to click "Play Movie" and never look at any other menu but the main one.  Well today’s theme is relaxing.  Go relax and get rid of those deadlines.  If you constantly push yourself, not taking the brakes you are screwed! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I arrived at my best friends house today.  I will be here today, tomorrow, and Monday enjoying the time with them and remembering my old town.  Today we started by going to my old school.  I miss those long walks there and back everyday, that 30 minutes that some would hate had some of our most memorable times.  Those were our catching up minutes on the last 24 hours.  Today that 30 minutes was a catching up time for the last year.  It is amazing how much you miss.  Take for example "My School" the school that I arrived at on it's first day at 6:00 am.  It was my school, I loved my time there and it is on my top couple things I miss most list of this town.  The next stop was the card shop.  The thing I do miss most.  Frank, so many memories!  One of the best guys I know (top 10 in no order).  He was really like a father while I lived here.  He gave me an $80 birthday present last year!  I guy is so wonderful!  We had a chat before I decided he was to busy and we decided to come back later.  We made more rounds, stopping off there again to say hi and have another short chat.  Then we went back to Ben's house and organized a poker game for the evening.  I lost $0.60 tonight but we continue tomorrow and I will win, I would put money on it!  Ben kicked our butts and is up like $7.50!  So... I have been around town, re visited everything (including my own old house) but something is missing.  As I go through Stephens Yearbook and look at my class now I see no changes... The hot ones got hotter and the ones I met in 1st grade look the same way I have always known them to look.  That is what is missing.  I guess I can consider myself lucky because if I moved back into town everyone would welcome me back, I would have all my friends back (I think).  Yet I now have a whole new set of friends.  I kida don't miss them here.  I know that after re-thinking it I realize it is not how I really feel but I am sorta mad that they have moved on.  No I am not, I can't be, I would have!  Do they miss me?  No, I don't think they would really care if I came back.  So I am better off where I am?  No I have enemies there too, infact I don't have a ton of friends.  So where do I want to be?  I don't know.  I also don't have a choice (I guess that is good because I would come back just for the Hubbards and the card shop).  I have already said today's theme in another day.  Enjoy every day and every moment so today's theme is totally random.  No, today's theme is If you have four cards in a strait, you still don't have a strait.  You will lose.  Meaning if you do something go all out, not just minimal.  It has nothing to do with today (other than the poker game) but I can't use the same theme twice. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I realized this blog is becoming redundant so I will refrain from goodbye posts as much as possible.  I think I will also be short today as I am not in the mood.  Don't get me wrong, I love it here.  I think I might be a tad homesick though.  I have been gone before for many, many says not 2 yet right now I feel like talking to my parents.  I think I will call them tonight instead of the other way.  I don't want to leave here but for some reason (I am mad at both of them)I want to talk to my parents.  I went to sweet tomatoes today, it was good to be back, I like it there.  We didn't do much today, it was mostly goofing off and now Ben is hooked on GTA: Vice City so he is off playing that even right now.  I won tonight in poker!  I left with $21, that's ironic huh?  I entered with $10 so I have made $11!  We might go see Harry Potter tomorrow (it will be my 3rd time) with my winnings, I don't know, I need the money.  I'm done.  No theme, go rest.  I think I just might go spa-ing right now as it is getting cold in this room. So I will go rest and you should too!  Talk to you parents too.  Oh theme!  Don't bluff... It doesn't pay! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I don't know if this came across right, I don't know if it says what I want it to say or mean what I want it to.  If at any point you get offended please stop reading.  My only point in the post is my offer at the end I guess.   This will be another nudity entry but in a different way.  I wonder a lot if I just think of nudity a lot because I am a guy or not.  I have started to avoid names on these posts when I talk about something like this or just something offensive but Carly, I will make an exception for you.  I have a feeling this post will not help me and will infact hurt me at some point but I will say it anyway.  I would not call her the "hottest" girl at school but she did win homecomming and she is on that top 5 list, Carly Skinner.  She knows I like her, she also knows everyone else does too.  I do find it funny that she had never been kissed until her senior year.  So carly is on a plane right now, as I write this.  She is going to Europe as a senior trip with a couple teachers and a bunch of senior friends.  She said sometime last year that on this trip she was going onto a nude beach with another girl to sun bathe topless.  Ok, I have been on one of those beaches and I hate to tell you guys but even the ones you don't want to go nude do.  I do envy everyone there that day though.  Man, I don't know what I would pay to be there that day.  I would have offered Carly a large chunk of change for a nude photo this past year but I was afraid of the slap that I would get and how every girl at that school would soon hate me.  Infact I would give a couple other names of people I would make the same offer to but I think that would cross the line on this post if I have not already crossed it.  So here's my offer: If I know you, that is the requirement, I need to know you.  I can send you a(some) photo(s).  One for one I would love to trade.  email them to andrewcefalo@surewest.net and I will reply with mine.  Heck, just email me and I will send mine first.  Yeah, there is porn out there but there is something different about seeing someone you know.  I almost made this offer to another girl this year.  I flirted with her all year.  Every single thing I sait to her was flirting and most of the time she was flirting back.  I never quite understood why though, why was one of the top 5 girls at our school be flirting with me?  That is why I never made the offer, I was not sure the response.  What would she have said if I went up to her and said, "Hey, do you want to go see each other naked?"  I mean, whats the big deal?  What harm could it do?  I don't care if she saw me nude, why should she care if I saw her. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well I am back home today.  I can't wait to go back to Pleasanton this summer (hopefully) but I think that visit was a good length.  Ben now has me hooked on Runescape, I had been looking for a game like this one for a while and when I saw him playing it I realized it was the online game I wanted but it did not look all that fun.  It is, got try it.  The beginning is boring because you need to train but once you start it is amazing how kind others are.  Someone gave me 160 gold for something he was only offering 30 for just because I was new.  I returened the favor by giving 30 of it to another new player (even though he was kind of a jerk about the tips I gave him.  Go try it, www.runescape.com and you hopefully won't be disapointed.  I decided to stay up an extra hour playing the game than I usually do and I am now pretty tired.  On the topic of tired I have a story.  This year there is one kid who I had 2 classes with, one first sememester and another second.  I never really had a conversation with him durring 3D animation but we said hi to each other on ocation.  It wasn't until the next class english that I get to know him a little better.  The guy gets no sleep.  He literally does not sleep.  It is usual for him to be up at 3 on a school night.  No sleep sucks, I pulled 3-4 all nighters this year for the first time (I still had a couple hours of sleep but never more than 2 on one of those all nighters).  They don't feel all that good, the next day you are feel sick in the stomach and really tired.  I don't know how he could do it!  He would sleep through half of english but even at that it isn't good sleep.  The teacher just ingored it but the girl next to him (who will also go un-named) would yell while he was asleep "WAKE UP!" and everyone would laugh then.  I still havent figured out wether it was at him or the situation but either way I felt bad for him.  Please people, sleep is priority.  If you are that busy that you cant sleep then you not only need to lose some prioritys but also do the following.  Anytime you spend durring the day being creative, maybe creating a story or just making a plan on a layout for a project can be avoided.  Before going to sleep tell yourself you will dream about them and just concentrate on them.  Keep a notepad by your bed and when you wake up write everything down that you dreampt about.  It works for me all the time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had to re-format my laptop yesterday.  Long story why but it seems fine now.  A while back a friend leant me OSX 10.3, Panther.  An updated operating software than what I was using (10.2, Jaguar).  I was happy because it was new.  I did not quite get the advantages, I did not see the 500 and some odd new features they mentioned.  After a while I guess I started to like it more, I was using it the way it was supposed to be used and that made it function better but I still don't know if it was better than the old software, just different.  So I kept the disks for a long time, it was like months, I mean months, it was like 7 or 8 and during that time I did like 4 re-formats because I constantly get corrupt files that eventually destroy more and more files and shut down my computer.  I am basically creating my own virus' with this computer and keep shutting my self down.  Luckily I have never lost a file during the process except for last nights.  I will get to that.  So because I returned the disks I did not have them anymore to re-install the OS.  I did have Jaguar still (It came with my computer) and I had made images of all 3 disks before I returned them so that I still had them but I have not yet made them bootable disks.  When I re-formated I went back to Jag because of all this and I have to say, it is just fine.  I may make those disks bootable and upgrade again but I don't have any reason to right now.  I would have been sad I am missing expose a couple months back but I don't use it anymore, no need, it is just a cool trick.  So I am making do with what I have, a skill I need practice with.  The file I lost though was yesterdays entry and if you are reading these as I write them that will effect you but I will re-write it after this one so those of you going through the archives can read it seamlessly.  I don't really like macs and commonly discourage others from buying them for reasons I won't go into but there is nothing like me weekly re-format on this thing!  It is like getting a new computer!  Ok, weekly is an exaggeration but it is a good joke for those of us who need to use Mac's rather than get to use them.  I have a couple apple jokes up on my site.  There is the picture of OSX 10.3 with a quote "The OS of the week".  Then we have the worlds first 17" notebook which I quoted as "The worlds first 17" paperweight".  And lastly everyone knows the apple slogan "Think Different" but lately Steve Jobs has been using a new one, "It just works" so I made a poster for him with (sometimes) under the slogan.  There are some great apple jokes out there though (once again for those of us who need you use apples, not get to). 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have really gotten into "Full House" again.  I mean really into it.  There was a point this past year where they were showing 8 episodes a day.  2 I was sleeping through and 1 I was in school durring.  I would watch the other 5.  Sometimes even gut up early to see the two I usually slept through (they were on the hour before I got up).  I wouldn't call it obsessed I just really liked the show because it was well, a good show.  I don't really do that anymore.  It is still on 8 times a day and I watch it when I am watching TV, I don't go out of my way to watch it.  To be honest there really are only 2 or 4 new episodes each day, thy just repeat the episodes the next day in the other slots.  For a while I also hated 7th heaven.  I never really had a reson except, well, Growing Pains.  I have tried to love that show, Growing Pains, I just can't get into it.  I always assumed 7th Heaven to be the same sort of thing, not even realizing the show is still going!  One day I decide to watch it and think it is dumb (seeing as how I am atiest and that episodes was a little stong on the religion) but it grew on me when I gave it a second chance.  Now I am going ot of my way to see every episode airing, like I did with full house.  Before Full House there was Boy Meets World (still the best of the three) but I do think I will go crazy when next week rolls around and there are 4 hours starit with just these three shows every afternoon.  So I have to much TV in my life, really, I admit it.  TV is supposed to be a bored activity but I do plan my day around it... take for example my summer rutine, all planed around TV.  I am not proud of this flaw in my life and I hope I can fix it soon because next school year I have no room at all for TV.  If you are like me then work with me, for the rest of summer stop making TV shows a priority.  DO no block your day into 30 minute segments with regular tasks.  Another problem is when the clock striked 6, it isn't 6, it is Full House.  When the clock strikes 7, it isn't 7, it is 7th Heaven.  Don't do that.  That is bad. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I dont know why she does it to be honest.  My mother loves to push people away and has pased on the trait to my father.  My parents get in this huge fight with my uncle and won't talk to him for like 3 years.  We find out he has cancer and drive down to see him right away.  You go to see someone you would not speak to?  Ok, ok, he is dying and is family, I can't argue with them for going to see him but man that wall dropped fast.  Different story.  My grandmother (mom's side) died when I was young.  From what I understand she was a great person but also died of cancer so it was at an age that for the time seemed young.  I don't think they have accepted my grandfathers decision to re-marry something like 6-months after her death.  I don't blame him, he spent years with someone then there was no one.  That would be tough and you would want someone with you, you are used to someone there.  His wife did need to be replaced, not emotionaly but phisicly... why should he suffer for no reason?  So my mom hates her... what is it, stepmother?  and blames a lot on her.  So the woman asks a lot of questions?  She is interested with moth people?  My mom calls it prying, even if it is, SO WHAT?  She holds this in for like 12 years, keeping her mouth shut anytime she is around her stepmother but vents the whole time she isn't.  I don't really like the woman but I don't hate her.  She is kind of ditzy but that is fine, I know lots of girls that are a ditz.  But a couple months after Gary was dignosed with cancer she lashes out at her stepmother.  It was something to the effect of "I hate you Jenny" ok, different words but it had that effect.  For like an hour and a half the argued, I sat an watched my mother dig herself deeper into a hole with her father.  First of all they are both wrong in their logic on the situation but my grandfather is not stupid and realized my mother hates his wife at this point.  How would you respond to that?  I am totally on his side.  I think my mother is being an idiot, she saw it take cancer for her and her brother to talk again but she builds another wall right after that one was taken down.  What an idiot!  I love her though, don't get me wrong, L really get along well with her it is just I have a different outlook on life I guess.  I figure why waste it?  I do have a theme today, STOP FIGHTING!  My mom constantly complains, all the time.  She won't talk to her father even when they are in the same room.  Fathers day is this weekend!  She was with him for an hour and didn't even say a word!  Life is to short to waste and I would expect my mom and my father who both lost someone important, and are going to lose another important person would understand that! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, it has been a while.  I have a lot of catching up.  For anyone who has not been reading as I go I have missed a couple days of writing due to this trip I am on.  To be honest I don't know which day I am writing for.  It does not matter though, I have a lot of down time today so I will just keep ranting.  I guess I will explain this trip.  I made it last year, out to Missouri for a week of daily deadlines and stressful classes.  It is made up for though with extremely enjoyable evenings of having fun with 34 other students with the same interests as I have.  I go to a week long class, well, summer camp but it is as one camper stated last year "Not your average summer camp".  We go from the coldest place I have ever been (the classroom) out to some of the hottest wether I have ever worked in (that is an exaggeration) to shoot some great footage, then back to the class to edit it.  Even the stressful times are a blast.  I can't wait to land and get started (I am on the plane right now, today is sunday even though this is for saturday).  There are still going to be a couple hours before the orientation but I need time to unpack.  So why do I enjoy it?  I mean lets be honest, we are at a High School, we are staying in dorms, and they are lectures.  But fore some reason it is exciting.  I get that rush that others get who can't afford an education but finally get to go to a school.  It is just a blast. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This post was written later than the day it claims to be.  Camp was to busy to write daily during.   Wow.  Interesting.  Two words I would say that summed up today.  All the campers walk into Hillcrest's Broadcast Journalism class today for the first time like I had done one year ago.  This time though I am pulled aside with Laura (another camper) as we are the two only returning campers.  We miss the opening statements (Tim saying he is not emotionally or physical responsible for any of us and that we all suck) for a private chat.  We are asked what we want to do...  FLASHBACK: Last year there were two returning campers, Jonathan and Leah.  Last year was only this camps second year so they were the first to return.  The instructors did not know what to do with them so they had them do "Real World: Camp STN", a summary of camp. [END FLASHBACK]  ...As last year did not work out well.  The returning campers did not fell a part of the group.  We both actually wanted to be a part of camp as if we were going there for the first time.  There was a difference still created though, we had the option to miss a session we already knew.  We both got the first one so we broke off into different classes 1 on 1 with an instructor.  Laura was taught Final Cut Pro I believe and I was taught how to interview.  I did not pick this because I wanted to do it, it was just because there is not one person at my school who can so now I can teach them.  If there is one thing I plan to take back from camp it is notes.  I plan to get every piece of knowledge thrown at me down on paper and know it so well that I can turn around and teach it.  We followed the regular day after that first lesson, going back over the same classes we had a year ago.  In the afternoon we had an assignment that is extremely difficult to do.  Everyone hates it, EVERYONE!  I still have the scars it left from last year.  Apparently we returning campers have it easy though so the teachers make it tougher for us!  They tell us this all day, "You guys will be doing the video only assignment too, just you guys will have it a little tougher."  Ok, the assignment is impossible to do perfect, how can it get together?  The idea behind it is you have 1 minute to tell a story using no audio.  ONLY VIDEO!  Also, Tim (AKA - Simon from American Idol) rips these apart.  It does not matter how good it is, he finds problems with it.  If it is perfect he will start saying the parts that are good, are now bad, the rules change.  Our catch... The ting that make ours harder... Arachibutyrophobia.  Yep, we have one minute to tell the story of Arachibutyrophobia.  So immediately we go to Webster... not listed.  How can this word not exist?  We then type it into google... the fear of peanut butter sticking to the roof of one's mouth.  Damn.  Needless to say we completed the task.  In-fact we get the least criticism out of all the campers (Tim was going easy on us).  For the last task of the day we are assigned a V.O.B. (I think) assignment.  The idea is every computer has captured on it already a little footage of a park being built and a couple interviews of the workers.  In addition to that we are given a page of info about this park and asked to put an interview on the timeline followed by some b-roll where we will place a voice over.  A simple task.  Once again the returning campers are to good for that, we get to do a full package!  Yay!  I stay up late editing the thing so it is ready for the next day.  Tonight we also watch the 10:00 news live form in the studio, that is always fun.  Thank you KY3!  I loved my second annual trip to the show.  Theme...need sleep?  No seriously, I intend to get little sleep to continue learning.  This week will be hell on me.  We eat fast food and get little sleep.  It is a blast and the most tiresome time of my summer.  I cant wait to dive in even deeper! 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How much worse can it get?  Seriously!  No wait, I am not upset really, I love this place.  I am finally here at camp STN in my 4 hours of down time before we start camp.  I am so excited... I hurry to my room, get in, exactly as I remember it.  Still Excited!  I meet up w/ a camper and go over the camp events for him because he is curious and I have done it before.  I tell him I am going to go unpack and will stop by in a little while to say hi.  I open my bag and start to sift through my clothes noticing some are wet.  It was a coke... a can of coke!  Who packs food in their suitcase?  Common people, like there isn't food where you are going?  I tell my mother this but she cant resist so she packs cokes!  One got stabbed, I don't know quite how but I have a feeling it was one of the plugs in my suitcase.  And so half my clothes are covered in coke.  I am writing this from the basement of our dorms in the laundry room.  Waiting for my first load of laundry ever to finish!  Of course I was cheap so I only bought one load of laundry detergent as it costs $0.50 each and I need to do one colors and one whites.  Of course the washing machine is a dollar a load.  So the colors are fine but the whites still show the coke a little, so what?  I don't really mind, it is clean.  Then I can put both colors and whites together in the dryer and it is only $0.25 a load, THEY DO THIS ON PURPOSE!  Anyway, 15 minutes till I am done and I am glad it is all over, I am done with them, it wasn't that tough and it only cost me $2.75 (wow, that was an expensive coke!)  I still have a couple hours to spare so I am fine.  The theme, don't bring drinks in your luggage!  I will explain the camp rundown as the week goes on.  Also giving updates on what it is like. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Internet Explorer just crashed on me.  I had typed up all of this entry and went to spell check and it crashed.  I have never ever had a piece of paper crash on me, I like paper.  I don’t like viruses, I am sure that is the cause.  That and Internet Explorer 6, never once did 5 crash.  6?  Oh, 6 crashes a couple times a day.  So now I am writing in Microsoft Word.  Here I go, Again…   This post was written later than the day it claims to be.  Camp was to busy to write daily during.   I am going to start with a glossary because I don’t find writing definitions all over the place helps:  EP’s: Executive Producers – The people in charge of everything that goes into a show, basically the directors. Lamberts: Home of the tossed roll.  Somebody comes around about ever 10 minutes and tosses rolls to customers who are asking for one.  You order your meal and when you are done you can ask for another helping at no extra charge. Nats Package: A package where there is no reporter, it is simply interviews telling the story. Voice over: (also referred to as a VO) Information given by a reporter where you do not se them, you can only hear them.  I stay up until like 12:45 editing this stupid package working on this stupid project.  I go to bed and test the volume of my radio alarm clock.  My roommate confirms that it is at a good level and we both go to bed.  A door in the hall slamming at 7:57 the next morning wakes us up.  My alarm did not go off and I take responsibility for that.  I am supposed to be the first one up at 6:30 to take my shower and then wake up the next guy who will wake up the next one and the last one.  When my alarm clock does not go off though, that good deed I do should not be abused by me receiving criticism.  My alarm clock did not go off, my roommate can vouch for me, and it did not go off.  The fact that we are supposed to be downstairs 3 minutes after we wake up though caused most of the camp to hate me (well dislike for about 5 minutes).  The day continued with remarks like, “You guys need to be back by 8:45, if you need to set your alarm clock do so.”  Totally uncalled for.  Laura and I worked with the rest of the camp for the morning doing the regular activities with them.  In the afternoon the camp had to do a package I still remember struggeling over last year.  A package has been edited on the “Miss Merry Christmas” pageant.  All the assignment requires is writing the VO for the package.  They get a quick press conference on the topic and are sent on their ways.  Their, not our ways, Laura and I talked the teachers out of us doing this assignment because it is an incredible learning experience but we already learned it and we do not want to suffer through it again.  Instead we get briefed on a huge secret at camp, the details of the big show.  We are told we will be the EP’s to the big shows.  And that it is plural, we have so many kids this year there will be two shows.  We will pick the package teams and the two groups.  We also chose our anchors and have a say in the stories the teams do.  On top of all of that they are also assigning us a Nats Package (see glossary at top of post).  Since there are an odd number of campers Laura gets a partner on that package (I have no comment about that other than the fact that it was extremely unfair).  If all of this is not enough tomorrow morning we will create a backdrop for the LIVE shows.  So that is all a lot of work but I am excited to get started on it.  This is why I came to camp, to work and I will work as much as I can.  Oh and uh, one more thing… eh-hem, uh, these shows need openings/Intros and Joe Carter, the camp intern offered to do one.  I can’t let both shows have the same intro so… I kinda volunteered myself to do one.  Yeah, I think that is the most work I have ever taken on in a 48-hour period of time.  The rest of the day: Campers had no idea they were being broken up into partners and groups for the next couple hours, in-fact they still had no idea what Laura and I were doing.  We had decided everything for the shows, Laura is team Yellow and I am team Red.  It is not a competition but I do have the better team.  We started anchor tryouts and I only had two or three people from my team sign up for them.  Laura has so real talent and then again some… no talent.  I luckily have the best anchor in all of camp; yep I was pretty lucky until Tim disqualified her because she was too good.  Damn.  I think we will re-organize teams tomorrow.  I also started taping my intro and it might turn out cool.  The campers finish their assignment and they are told their partners for the small and big shoot (same person).  That was it though, when didn’t give them any details.  Now they know Laura and I am in charge and have huge secrets we need to keep, I am not good with secrets.  Tim decided to move Lamberts from Thursday to today at last minute.  Yay lamberts.  If you don’t know what lamberts it then read the glossary at the top of the post.  A lot of food and reasonable prices.  So it is a camp contest.  Who can eat the most rolls and their full meal?  The first year the record was set at 7 rolls.  The second year (last year) it was beaten by two people and now stands at 12.  This year I decided to beat it.  I ate 8 rolls plus my full meal.  I WAS THE ONLY ONE TRYING!  I could not believe that.  So I now hold third place at camp STN in the roll contest.  And it is time for bed.  I must leave you with a theme.  Theme: Don’t eat 8 rolls plus a full huge-mungus burger. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This post was written later than the day it claims to be.  Camp was to busy to write daily during.   What a huge-mungus day (to quote yesterdays entry, I promise to stop using that word).  Ok, so Jill (Tim’s wife) was supposed to meet Laura and I at SMS this morning at 9 am.  Well first of all, let me give you a schedule of the day.  7:45 a.m. Continental breakfast in the dorm lobby 8-10:00 a.m. Field Shooting at SMS 10 a.m. Return to hillcrest 10:30-11:30 a.m. Great storytelling (Jerry Jacob from KY3) 11:30 a.m. – 1:45 p.m. Edit SMS assignments (working lunch) 1:45-2:45 p.m. Watch SMS stories 2:45 p.m. Plan the “Big Shoot” and load out 3:15 p.m. Off to “Big Shoot” 10:30 p.m. Back to dorm  So Laura and I don’t have anything to do with the SMS show, it is a learning exercise for the campers so they don’t screw up at the night shoot.  So Jill will pick us up at 9am to go down to hillcrest and start on sets.  I decide to be a nice guy and wake up everyone in my dorm room at 7:00 because of yesterday.  I figured this way I can make up for it.  They didn’t even seem to care, it was as if they expected it.  So I go back to sleep and set my alarm for 8:00 so I can be ready for Jill.  Well it goes off at 8 and I did turn it off.  I didn’t get out of bed though until I hear Steve Galian knocking at my door at 9:15.  He is telling me that they have some droughts and juice waiting for me.  Jill is also in the lobby ready to take Laura and I down to Hillcrest.  I didn’t get a shower yesterday, I need one today.  10 min. later I am down in the lobby and Dave is telling me they left 5 min. ago.  Damn.  It is not that it is real important for me to be there but I hate looking bad two days in a row.  They will take me down w/ the other campers at 10.  Ok, that is fine, I was just “packing up” getting everything “ready” to go to hillcrest, I think they bought my BS.  I get down there and they have done nothing, I forget the reasoning but I am cool with it.  Jerry will be there any minute and I want to tape his presentation because it will be good.  I get the camera ready and while doing to Jerry come over to say hi to me.  He is such a cool guy.  I had talked to him on Monday and told him that he has to be the funniest anchor I have ever seen.  I have so many stories of a year ago, how funny he was.  So he says hi because I am such a fan.  He starts up and I miss the first couple minutes because of the camera but it looks fine on the tape.  While they edit their SMS packages Laura and I finish our anchor tryouts and I get most of the recording done on my intro.  The critique the packages and they suck.  I am a little worried but these people had little time and I don’t blame them.  We leave for the big shoot and I am getting nervous because I have no idea how to do this package I need to do and I am just winging it.  Long story short I follow one group most of the afternoon and help them out.  I throw together some interviews (thinking I was actually doing a good job) and finish the taping of my intro.  Now that I have told you all that there was a little incident that happened in the middle of all of that.  One team was a little stupid.  We told everyone all week to make sure they had plunty of battery power at the shoots.  They brought a battery; they just left the camera on.  They left the camera on… left it on.  Common people!  Then they sit there.  On the side of the road, just sit there.  The group I am helping and I walk past them and ask what they are doing.  They fill us in and ask me if I have an extra battery.  I reply saying I do but that I need it… “For what?”  Well, lets see… I need it so that I can… wait, uh, oh yeah, USE IT!  They tell me I have no real important things to do and say that I should give it to them.  They ask the group I am helping for an extra battery.  That group lies, they have an extra but decided not to disclose that.  So now I have a group yelling at me about how bad of an Executive Producer I am because I won’t help them.  I just walk off.  The group I am with has an argument.  One of them agrees with me the other is against me.  What we got out of the argument was that it is not an EP’s job to stock workers with batteries, in-fact I shouldn’t even be on the field.  Also that if this was a real life scenario and they came back with nothing it is not me that looks bad because I would fire them.  I pass by them again later by myself and they ask for my phone.  One of them has a phone but they left it in the dorms.  I am roaming and so calls were $0.69 a minute but because not handing over the phone would just make me look worse I gave it to them.  They call the teachers, THERE IS NOTHING THEY CAN DO!  THEY DON”T HAVE ANY BATTERYS!  So I will quote the idiot using my phone, “So he has an extra battery, should we make him give it to us?”  No, at this point I felt like walking up, punching the guy and walking off with my phone.  Instead I stood there.  “He says he wants to talk to you” I hear.  Ok, I will take my phone to talk to him.  Dave is on the other line and asks what is going on, I tell him the story and Dave tells me I can figure it out, that is my job, maybe they can find someone w/ a battery.  Meanwhile the other two are yelling at me telling me to tell Dave I have an extra one, are these people really that dumb?  COME ON!  I tell them they are on their own and walk off.  Later the group I was with cough’s up the battery and the idiots are still furious with me.  For crying out loud!  I just ignore them.  I now have a new nickname, battery hog.  It did get funny that evening though.  We were waiting for team Yellow to meet us and a couple members of my group stood on the Branson strip side by side to the stopped dead traffic and attempted to get people to honk their horns.  It got very funny.  I have It all on tape. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This post was written later than the day it claims to be.  Camp was to busy to write daily during.   I have gone in great detain on past posts about camp because there was a lot to tell but today was basic so I will try to keep it short.  There is chaos everywhere.  People are rushing to get projects edited quickly (that is all we are doing today, editing the big shoot.  I realized today I had nothing as far as footage in Branson.  I struggled all day working with Jill trying to make something out of nothing.  Meanwhile Laura and her partner are working just as slow but having a great time.  They are sitting with Joe editing his intro and it looks soooooo cool!  I finish my package at I don’t know, 3:00-ish and ask for approval from Tim…  [SIDENOTE] I don’t know if I have talked about Tim yet but Tim has made grown adults cry.  Tim is the Simon from American Idol only with a different field of expertise.  He is so friggen cruel you would not believe it.  To top it off he is extremely manipulative when he wants to be.  He is extremely cool though. [END SIDENOTE]  He give little to no criticism.  He tells me to fix one thing and put it onto tape.  I am happy but confused.  He made my partner cry last year.  He spent 30 minutes telling us we sucked big time.  Now a project that sucks even more gets nor ripping apart?  Ok.  I want to work on my intro.  Long story short, I edited from the time I finished that until 3:30 in the morning (stopping to go out for dinner with everyone else) and was proud when I finished.  I still think mine was not as good as Joe’s but I got a hell of a lot more complements.  Theme:  The reason my package was so hard to edit was because I had no B-Roll.  B-Roll is footage of something, something that can cover a Voice Over or Interview.  I needed more shot of just stuff, things happening.  I am ashamed too because I usually have plenty, not today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, its over          I am sitting in my dorm… all alone.  There are three other students still here (they fly out at 5 and 6 am) but I am all by myself.  I have the radio on and was just re-writing my notes.  I don’t fly out until 6 tomorrow night so I will have some time still with teachers and I am just making sure I have everything I need.  Last year this night was fun, mostly because we all went out as a group to dinner and had plans tomorrow.  I think there were more students staying overnight last year.  This year though, the other three got burgers on the way home and it was a little to early for me so I decided to go out later.  I have already gone at this point though; I walked down to Hardies (Carl’s Jr. on this side of the US) at about 8 and got a burger.  It was a short walk, 2 maybe 3 blocks but it did seem lonely knowing I would go back to once again, an empty dorm.  I don’t really feel like writing to be honest.  I think I will stop. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was actually a great day.  I was the only camper left when I woke up.  I got up at about 7:30 to pack and checked out at 9:00 am.  It was strange waking up with nobody else there.  I hacked out with Steve Galion (a camp instructor watching over us in the dorms.  Dave picked us up and we went to hillcrest.  The first thing we needed to do was pack up all of the computers that were on loan.  That was like 8 iMacs.  Tim and Mike showed up late (I don’t blame them though, they knew we had work to do).  All of them had a meeting about some sort of booklet that is being made for STN teachers.  Meanwhile I had the afternoon to myself.  I spent it capturing different videos that will be teaching aids next year for me and other classmates.  I had a good time doing that actually and the plan was for Dave, Martha, and I to go see terminal before I fly out.  I have a couple Hard Drive problems though so we returned to the school after lunch and I worked those out.  I don’t want to leave though.  If I had my choice we would have gone to SMS dorms after fixing the Hard Drives and acted like the past week didn’t happen.  We would have gotten a new group of kids and I would be at camp STN for the third year in a row.  With that said it is not the students I miss, it is everything else.  It is the learning, the stress, the teachers, and the time when we are not working.  I love that week of making choices for myself.  It is watched over independence.  Like I am on a longer leash, not that I am on a tight one but it is nice to decide for myself I need some milk and be responsible for getting it.  I like the responsibility, I have none here because I don’t like things like laundry over a long time but once and a while a week of all the responsibilities would be fine!  I am now flying back and actually, I am not looking forward to my parents.  Maybe just one more week would be great! 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It seems like every year I buy a new Macintosh computer.  I bought my iMac the year I moved up here.  I sold it last year for my laptop and this year I am buying a G5 (keeping my laptop).  So about this G5…  I need money.  Tomorrow I will go out to find a job as I turn 16 in 7 days.  Tomorrow apple announces a bunch of stuff and plans will become more precise then but right now my goal is by the end of summer to have a 20” monitor and G5.  That is my plan.  Update tomorrow on what apple has done to change it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have to many computer problems.  My PC is so full of viruses it won’t open most folders.  I need to open things manually using Internet Explorer.  I used a program called Stinger to try and remove them.  It was a free program I got off the net.  It was prescribed by my internet provider.  It found 42 viruses/Trojans/backdoors.  Those included bagel, mydoom, and many other popular ones.  I have a big virus party on this computer.  It is funny, I had seen that Disney Channel movie “Zenon: Girl of the 21st century” and thought I would know the second I had a virus.  I thought my screen would go red and an animated worm would pop up and eat away the screen.  No really, I believed that!  So I run stinger and it does me no good, it tells me 42 viruses I am housing and that is it.  The frustrating thing is I have virus protection software.  It never informed me!  So I download (yes illegal copy, this is why I have 42 viruses) I newer version and it shows one virus… ONE!  Meanwhile my Mac is still having problems.  This afternoon my Mac decided not to re-start after re-installing Final Cut Pro 4 and Soundtrack.  Soundtrack kept crashing on me so I re-installed it and it forced me to re-install FCP4 with it.  So now it is stuck on the startup screen.  I put in the boot disk to try to fix the errors on it and it told me I had like 6 errors (mostly higharchy problems) that it couldn’t fix.  ARGHHHHHHHHHHH!  I am so frustrated!  I guess it was bound to catch up with me between all of the file sharing I do but it is sooo tough to keep track of.  I feel like I am a ref in a boxing tournament gone wrong.  I am trying everything humanly (and mechanically) possible to fix these computers, running back and fourth working on them!  I am going to go.  Theme: get virus protection.  Get your own personal IT guy.  In-fact get a lot of money so you can hire people to fix this for you.  Get money.  Spend money.  Help the economy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so apple announces probably the coolest monitor on the planet, a new 30” monitor.  The thing is so huge that it needs a card to run it that is like $700.  The card has two outputs.  That is two.  Incase you don’t already know, with two outputs you can have two monitors.  This 30” monitor takes two.  The thing is huge!  It does run for $3200.  $3200.  Go ahead and count to 3200.  now.  do it.  If only you had a dollar for every number huh?  This monitor is so pricey that it costs more than the computer!  Well here is my computer that I will get:  Dual 1.8 GHz PowerPC G4 512MB DDR400 SDRAM (PC3200) 2x256 160GB Serial ATA – 7200rpm NVIDIA GeForce FX 5200 Ultra w/64MB DDR SDRAM 8x Superdrive (DVD-R/CD-RW)  Apple Cinema Display (20” flat panel)  Costing a whopping $3099 total.  This is all low end actually.  In fact within a month or so of buying it you won’t even be able to get it anymore.  I am just hoping though that they update soon though because maybe I can meet the cut off for the new computer and for the same price I can get a better one.  For anyone who knows this stuff you may notive the DVD-R.  This is apples best burner.  Yes, their top end 8 speed burner.  Yet it is DVD-R, apparently apple has not yet caught up with the rest of the world on the DVD+R being the new standard.  They prefer to keep up with the DVD-R!  That sucks.  So what are my chances of getting this?  I thought good.  I thought, oh a job, I CAN GET IT!  Yeah right.  Count to 3099.  no don’t.  It is large, I will leave it at that (notice it is cheaper than the 30” monitor and the $3099 price includes a 20” monitor).  Now this price is an educational price so I may be wrong about it being cheaper but WOW!  That monitor must be the “shiznit”.  So I have a job interview on Thursday.  It would be a couple hours on Saturday’s at dry cleaners.  I will tell you how it goes.  I got turned down at many places.  Goosebery’s wanted my application but won’t hire until the school year.  Safeway is going on strike on the 17th but I don’t think they want a 16 year old.  They can hire me but I may not meet their impossible standards.  I don’t know what I will do.  I am not buying a single thing until I get this computer so I hope I get some cash quick.  My birthday is Sunday and I have a $1000 hurdle by then.  I figure if I can’t get that money by then it won’t be for a while because after that money is scarce.  I have a job on Saturday that will pay $100, I am recording a wedding for a couple hours.  I have a $100 to $150 already and hopefully I can fill the rest of the 1000 Sunday.  It won’t be a big deal if I don’t, I just really want to.  It would make me feel good for a while that I got together $1000 in a week and maybe it will motivate me to get the rest soon.  We will see. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       To be honest it is not the day I am writing for right now.  I missed today and I am actually going to write about this because it will come up later.  So I am going to write something today that was until now my biggest secret.  In-fact it wasn’t even a secret.  All of my so called friends knew about it and my parents have already found out.  It is not a secret at all, it is just something I don’t usually come out in the open about.  So here I go…  It all started at quad dance my freshman year.  I did not know who to sit with during the dinner so I sat with Brad Benkle and he was about to graduate and I would not hav much more time with him.  He, his girlfriend and his friend start to pry trying to find out who I “liked”.  To be honest I kind of liked many people and not one person in particular so I told the truth and said nobody.  It is a truthful answer.  They pried some more and finally gave up but then decided to ask me what I like in a girl and they were going to hook me up.  I know exactly what I like, I know exactly who I like.  She is in Pleasanton and I keep looking for a copy of her.  Luckily I have found many that are similar.  In-fact it isn’t until you move that you realize most people are extremely generic and are one of many.  I did not tell them this though, I told them nothing because I figured if I wanted a girlfriend I would find her on my own.  They gave up and I left.  I left thinking, “I do want a girlfriend, but who?”  So I walked around considering many people.  Infact I turned down just about all of my obvious choices and decided I really liked Allie Holt.  That was where it all started.  I knew very little about her.  She was our team leader in sports-a-rama and I got to know her a little during that time but never really had a crush on her.  In-fact I didn’t until that night.  I hung out with her group as I had met all of them during sports-a-rama that year.  Sometime during the dance I decide I would ask Paul Netherveld whether she was taken.  As I walk up to him he is with someone I have never met and asks me, “Andrew, who do you like?”  I was shocked at the coincidence and just told him “well actually I was planning on asking out Allie.”  “Allie Holt?” “Yeah.” “Dude, go for it!”  …and I decided to ask her at the end of the dance.  Now, I was planning on me asking being the first time she found out I was going to ask her but no, Paul told her during the next slow dance.  So now she knew and I was still going to ask her.  If I didn’t I would be mad at myself when I got home.  Cut a long story short, during the last slow dance the seniors formed the Senior Circle and my new friends formed our own circle.  I asked her if we could talk at the end of the dance and so we did…  “I think Paul might have already told you…” “Told me what?” “Do you want to do something next Friday?” “I don’t know, I might be doing something with my friend.” “Ok.”  …and I walked away, I stayed at the dance but walked to Paul.  Allie went to talk to her sister I noticed but to my surprise came back.  She said she had to clean up because she was in Student Government but asked if I would help…  “Andrew, I can’t date until I am 16.  I am only 15”  …so that is the story.  I thought about those words over and over again, time and time again.  I was glad I asked but haunted by the response.  She had played with me, I did not get a “when I turn 16” or a “I don’t think so”, I had no idea wether she would have if she could have. There is so much more to this story.  Float building was at her house the next year and I signed up because they needed parent volunteers and my dad like to work with wood.  The week of homecoming I learned a lot.  I met her family and got to know them real well.  I was in charge of the editing for Real World: Granite Bay and it was all taped at their house.  That week though, Allie started hanging out with Mike Caswell.  It was all the way until Winter Ball that they were “friends” yet seemed a lot like boyfriend and girlfriend.  Winter Ball broke them up because Allie was not yet 16 but her parents allowed her to go with Mike, she said they wouldn’t let her go.  In January she turned 16 and I didn’t even make a move.  I had decided to move on.  I don’t think I have but I am trying to. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Why are you reading this?  I mean honestly people?  Is my life that interesting?  I am thrilled tat someone cares enough to sift through entry after entry and actually care but at the same time I am confused.  I ask myself this while writing every entry.  I mainly write them for myself, it is a way for me to get out my thoughts and a way to remember them clearer but it is online.  I put it online so others could care, I just don’t know why they would care.  I figure when I become rich and famous people will care and will find it then because I will have crazy fans who read all 12 million entries that come up with my name on google.  If you are one of those people and I am rich and famous then you landed on a gold mine as this is basically a diary.  If I did not become rich and famous and I am in-fact working as a small producer in some small production company where not a sole cares whether I show up the next day for work then was there purpose to this entry?  Yes, it gives me hope.  This blog is not only a memory for me but also a memory for everyone else to remember me as I turned 16 one summer.  I will regret things I said and yet I will also be proud of things I discovered so early in life.  Then if the first of the two situations comes true I will be happy that people learn who I was, and that they don’t judge me for what I said on the red carpet.  This is me.  I am thrilled that whoever you are is taking the time to read it.  If you are reading this as I write it I am confused yet still thrilled.  If I am famous then ask me for an autograph the next time you see me, along with everybody else.  Only… lets make a way that I can separate you from them… shout WATERMELLON!  I will hurry to you and give an autograph along with a thank you for reading my crap. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had my interview today.  It was ok.  I don’t know, I wasn’t really prepared for it.  I was not ready for a question like “What are your greatest qualities” and “what are your worst”.  It isn’t that I don’t want to tell the truth, I just blanked.  I could not even give some BS for either.  Even with the time I have had since the interview I can’t come up with a response.  They are tough questions.  I gave answers immediately for things like “What would people say about you” and “What can you bring us”.  While the answers are not great that I gave I am happy with them because they were hones and on time.  The other two questions… I just blanked!  My parents are urging me to write a thank you for her time.  I think it is tacky.  I would do it if I had her email but a real letter?  Common, that is not me (hah, spell check wants me to switch that to I).  That is not a teenager.  I don’t think they understand that, it will make me look too much like I am being fed things to do by my parents yet bad in person.  I want to come across, as what you see is what you get.  No… Surprise!  I am actually really qualified!  Fooled you!  Am I boring you?  I have decided this needs to stop being a diary.  I read other blogs because of their opinions, not their life.  I will do that.  I promise as the writer of this blog I will cut down the diary crap. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was at a wedding today.  I was being paid to record it by a counselor at my school.  I had no idea who the bride or the groom was until today in-fact I did not know most people there… except for my school’s faculty, they were there.  She invited most of them too.  I always say I won’t do weddings because they are a pain to edit yet my website clearly says, “…be it a conference or a wedding video, Final Cut Productions will…” Of course that is not how I was hired.  My counselor had me recommended to them by someone (I am sure it was Mr. Newborn, my teacher.  So I am Sig agreed to do it and I was under the promise I would not need to edit it, and I won’t need to.  It was my kind of a job!  I am not going to go into great detail about the event, as it was not my wedding; I will never see the bride or the groom again.  The bride was attractive, Sig said she was chunky but I look past that.  Of course she was 23 and now married so why do I care?  I also had that mentality about the bride’s maids as they were all about the same age as the bride and all had boyfriends except one, she was married.  I really only like one of them too.  Why am I saying this?  I guess the thought just came into my head often seeing as how it was a wedding.  Point was, I got $100.  The End, I left with a check and a night to remember until the next wedding I got to.  I can’t wait until my wedding.  I just can’t wait to sit at that table in front of everyone I care about next to someone I am going to spend the rest of my life with.  Weddings are great (for the bride and groom, everyone else just suffers).  I guess I am always like that.  I want to meet someone I can be with forever, not just one night or even one month.  My best friend came up for my birthday tomorrow and we went to bed, as it was 12:30 by the time he actually got here. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is my birthday.  I saw Spider-Man 2 with Ben even though I didn’t want to.  Spider-Man 1 beat Star Wars in opening weekend records and I still hold a grudge but it looked good so we saw it.  It was good.  I decided to ask for nothing this year for my birthday.  There wasn’t anything big that I wanted so I decided to see what I would get.  My parents know me and they know what I want.  The only thing I don’t like are little things.  I like getting one big thing.  My parents have a knack for picking practical gifts because they cannot think out of the box.  Ben got me A disco light (I have wanted one since 5th grade), car air fresheners (uh, it is Ben), a plastic coconut (for mimicking Monty Python scenes), and his mother made me a shoe bag.  None of that was practical, I LOVED IT!  He was so creative and bought 4 presents under $30!  They were so great!  So my parents buy  CD labels……………...……they don’t want me to need to spend the money 100 Blank DVD’s ………… that is like $150, I usually buy them when I need them Mini DV tapes …………….. I need them but they are for work.  I also find them all over the media room for free DVD case inserts …………. I know the measurements, paper is fine, I can cut them out Printer Ink cartridges …..…. So I don’t need to go down to Kinko’s  All that stuff went un-appreciated because I buy all that when I need it, it is not a gift.  It is like them buying me a backpack, pens, pencils, markers, and binder paper.  It is a tool I dispose of regularly.  They didn’t get my point so my dad treated me like an unappreciative brat during the opening.  It is so tough to open presents in front of him!  Oh yeah, the good gift…  512 megs of ram for my Mac.  I knew it was coming, he quizzed me on the phone a couple days ago, I expected it.  I also told him on the phone that I didn’t need it, it was my HD that needed replacing.  So I got a great gift!  He is taking me down to the apple store to fix my computer PLUS I get the ram!  I was very happy with this; I hope they learn from that!  I was extremely appreciative when they got me a gift I would actually enjoy.  I know I sound like a brat here but if they were going to spend that much money on me there are many things I would have liked more.  $150 on 100 DVD’s seems like a waste on a present to me.  We went to see the fireworks tonight.  I felt really good to turn down something that afternoon.  We went to buy fireworks.  I remember last year’s after the fireworks, firework to be boring because they were like big whop, I just saw real ones.  I was glad to stand at that fireworks stand that afternoon and say I didn’t really want any fireworks.  We bought a pack for $10 because my mom wanted the sparkelers and my dad got a big firework for $6.  I said we didn’t need it but he insisted.  I did ask for a pack of smoke bombs though, they look great on tape as a grenade.  My parents even asked “do you want two?” and I turned them down.  That felt really good. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Gary Sullivan (Died: July 4, 2004 2:30pm)  My uncle died yesterday.  I have lots of memories with him and for the ones I don’t have I have video tapes to remember him by.  He was diagnosed with cancer around Christmas 2003 and had 1 month to live sometime in January.  That would be sometime in Febuary he was supposed to die.  He beat all odds, just like the rest of his life.  He took risks, he loved the adventure of life and he was always facing danger in the eye.  As a kid I loved him, as an adult I did not respect him.  I am a teenager.  How did I not respect him as an adult?  I put myself above him, saying he was making the wrong move by not purchasing life insurance.  I am not sure I was in the right position to make that choice but I would never jeopardize my family by doing that.  As I said he was a risk taker, that was what he did, he took a risk.  Unfortunately he lost yet won in so many ways I could never see as an adult, I only saw as a kid.  He bought stuff.  Kept buying, and buying.  Not necessarily saving just buying.  Every moment of his life he enjoyed, that was his goal (I think).  If it sounds as if I am talking bad of him by the risk taker analogy than you too do not approve.  Many did not; there goes that adult opinion.  I am not calling him a kid; I am saying he enjoyed his life.  He enjoyed it in a way none of us could imagine as we don’t live like that.  The right way, what a terrible phrase.  Gary lived the right way for him.  I don’t think he or any of his family regret his way of life, we all enjoyed it.  I feel like I am digging myself out of a hole.  I APPROVE!  I loved his way of living!  I don’t agree though, does that make sense?  He created my two best cousins.  Kayla (9 years old) and Ashley (7 years old).  He married my favorite Aunt.  Krysha.  He had such a loving family.  Wow, the memories.  I cannot begin to explain them.  I was not told about his death until the next day as it was my birthday on the 4th.  Krisha woke up early in the morning to Gary having discomfort.  She stayed beside him and called the caregiver who told her Gary had hours to live.  Kayla woke up at the usual time and stayed beside him until 2:30 that afternoon.  Ashley ignored him and stayed in her room.  I am mad at her.  Why?  She is after all only 7.  That is 7 years of memories, the reason I am mad at her.  I am mad for her; I am frustrated she did not have more time with him.  I am even madder at her though for not spending every minute possible with him.  Maybe she is one step ahead of me.  Maybe she does not want to remember him like he was when he died.   The mind of a 7 year old.  I wish I could write better because there is so much I want to say about the situation I cannot explain.  Krisha was saying goodbye to him until 6 when her mother pulled her away and told her they needed to have someone take him away.  It took 45 minutes.  Next problem: The fireworks.  The girls need to go see the fireworks but they will become a bad memory now.  They were told they were going to see the fireworks.  There dad never missed them, every year he went to see them.  This year he could not get out of bed to go see them and because of that he died so he could watch them from heaven.  They bought it.  The mind of a 7 year old.  It is amazing how they all are getting through this.  I have so much respect for all of them.  I hope they can all keep their memories of him clear in focus.  I will always have certain ones.  Most of my childhood included him, everything up to three years ago.  I am going to mention a couple of memories, not the best but things I will remember him by…  Cotton Eyed Joe: I loved this song.  I always wanted a copy of it and he was the only person I knew who had one.  I would always listen to it when I was at his house.  Pool: He was the only one I knew who had a pool table.  I had a great time on it Gary.  Vipers: I did not learn of this one until he had cancer as he was not involved with them until then.  He wanted to own one so bad he sold all of his cars (he had a couple old mustangs he was working on) to afford one.  He never got it, he had the money but the car he wanted to buy was owned by a flake.  The guy let Gary keep it in his garage until Gary could afford it but Gary never heard back from him.  It is still sitting there, a car worth over 40 thou, un claimed.  It can’t be driven because you need a special license.  I will never forget the smile a viper gave him.  It is the face I will always rember.  Gary, I love you.  You are my Uncle and I obviously won’t forget you.  You brought two wonderful daughters into this world and raised them to this point very well.  Krisha will do wonderfully continuing on after you and my family will help her in every way we can.  I can’t forget you, you made such an impact on my life, from holidays to Friday nights listening to disco on the radio.  I have never called you by your nickname (Gazbox) because I never knew it’s meaning but over time I have created my own meaning for it.  I feel that I can now call you by it because I know what it means to me.  It means everything I know you as; it means romping (I tried to look up a word to describe you and that was the best I could get).  You are and were an incredible person.  In the words of your daughter, Ashley, “you must have enjoyed those fireworks.” 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, well Ben went home today early in the morning (like 9:00).  Ok, so it isn’t early but he had us up past 1:00 every night while he was here!  So yesterday I went to sun splash for the first time!  It was a birthday thing I guess because my parents actually suggested it.  Sun splash (incase you didn’t know) is a water park near my house.  It look tiny from the road and cost a fortune compared to Water World in Sacramento but my parents hate driving out there.  It wasn’t as small as it looked * and we had a good time.  ~The * in the middle of the previous sentence is a break of 7.4 hours that I stepped away from my computer during.  So point is all day we knew my dad was making these ribs on the smoker and home made baked beans and personally I could not get my mind off those beans.  I am not a big bean guy but we were starving and those beans looked soooooooooo good, I cannot explain how good they looked!  It was a big pot in the oven and it was filled to the brim and it had all bits in it.  I know that does not sound good “bits” but it looked so home made.  You know baked beans…beans and sauce, but this was beans sauce and other ingredients.  On top of these beans looking good we were starving.  We had not eaten anything that day and the hunger I think hit us around 3:07 in the afternoon (no reason in particular, just a guess at the time).  So we have until 6:00 that we need to be there and no money, no phone (not that it would do us any good), no food.  We still had fun, just hungry fun.  We go home, we eat and fall asleep to the TV.  Asleep – I have not had many dreams recently.  One here and there off and on in different nights.  So what was different that night?  I had a combined dream that would not end that seemed to last all night.  I remember most of it, it was really strange.  Something there about bombs because I was one of the leader guys in the military and we were taking out different forts by these bombs, mostly hand held bombs that made huge explosions.  We were calling the nuclear bombs but I know what a nuke looks like and it is nothing like a grenade.  Then I go back to base camp and the people in charge there are the counselors from camp STN.  Then we are in Italy, same people and camp is being run.  My parents are in town too and I am trying to figure out my night because I want to spend dinner with the campers but my parents wanted to spend some time with me.  Then we go to some sort of train/warehouse that I have never seen before (it can’t actually exist) and I am with all of my friends from Pleasanton and Granite bay together.  Some event is going on that I don’t quite remember clearly.  Two big things happened though and I can only explain one of them.  There are back-stories on both and I have only told one of the stories.  So back on June 30th I wrote a post that had nothing to do with the day, it was about Quad Dance freshman year and I said it would come up later and here it is (go read it if you haven’t).  Allie comes up to me and kisses me on the cheek.  No big deal, it is a dream (there is a point to all this though that I will get to).  I ask her, “what was that for?”  I don’t remember her response but it caused me to kiss her back (on the cheek) and she said, “want to try again?”  So I go back in for the kiss but this time on the lips.  Now, why did I dream this?  Of course the rest of the dream makes no sense at all to me so why should this part be different?  Is it because I really do still like her?  It was after all just a couple of kisses in a dream that was totally crazy, and we were on a train/warehouse.   But this did strike me as odd that it happened.  In-fact in that part of the dream I was with my Pleasanton friends, Allie just walked up to me from the back of the crowd.  What was happening at the time too was important because it had to do with that other back story that I haven’t told, involving a girl I used to like in Pleasanton.  At one point though her and I became friends so it may not be what you and I are thinking but still, the whole thing makes me wonder.  So why did I dream all this?  Well there are a couple of reasons I think: 1 – The level of sun yesterday 2 – The level of chemicals (including chlorine) from yesterday 3 – We fell asleep with the lights on and the TV on (of course we did turn all that off at 2:30 in the morning when I woke up but still! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have wanted to write this post for a while.&nbsp; In-fact I am going to love writing it so much and it brings up so many other points I think I might just go off on a big thinking tangent over the next couple days with my thoughts and what I think about.  &nbsp;  This conversation was started on Thursday night in the van and did not last more than 30 minutes while on the way to the buffet but while that van was moving a lot of opinions were expressed and a lot of secrets about people were revealed.&nbsp; Dave asking students what they could and could not do on their shows at school started the conversation.&nbsp; “Can you guys report about porn and teens?”&nbsp; He gets varied responses.&nbsp; “Can you guys report on gay students?”&nbsp; And there is where it all starts.&nbsp; I say that I do not understand the controversy behind gay people.&nbsp; You are not showing anything, just talking about it.&nbsp; In-fact, what are you reporting, there is no story!&nbsp; “What do you think about gay people?”&nbsp; That isn’t a story, it is segregation.&nbsp; That is like asking, what do you think about minorities?&nbsp; It is separating people.&nbsp; The story itself is the controversy.&nbsp; So I bring all this up and we get a split van.&nbsp; Introducing Kyle, Kyle liked this topic because he was totally against even thinking about gay people.&nbsp; I’m sure if he had a gun and was in a situation that involved gay people…it would no longer involve gay people, this was his thinking.&nbsp; He just flat out hates them.&nbsp; I on the other had, while not being one of them, do not dislike them.&nbsp; That is what makes this conversation so difficult.&nbsp; If you stand up for a group, suddenly you are a part of that group.&nbsp; I fought like crazy.  &nbsp;  Kyle’s points…  “It’s not normal” – Define normal (for the sake of him not being here lets actually define it).&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Conforming with, adhering to, or constituting a norm, standard, pattern, level, or type. Typical.&nbsp; Functioning or occurring in a natural way; lacking observable abnormalities or deficiencies.  &nbsp;  Ok, so his point holds true to a certain extent.&nbsp; The natural way.&nbsp; But my point of normal is that word typical.&nbsp; Typical can change depending on the population.&nbsp; It is natural that a penis enters a vagina but there are other places for it to enter.&nbsp; Kids cannot be made without the natural way so I will give him that.&nbsp; It is not the natural way but it can become normal; that is dependent on the population at the time.  &nbsp;  “It is gross, I don’t want to see that” – See what?&nbsp; Kissing?&nbsp; Intercourse?&nbsp; You are in public!&nbsp; They might not want to see you kiss.  &nbsp;  So I realized that I was getting nowhere with him.&nbsp; He disliked them just as anyone would dislike a minority.&nbsp; The funny thing is we actually continued and he said, and I quote, “I don’t have a problem with lesbians!”&nbsp; He actually said this.&nbsp; I don’t think he realizes that lesbians are gay.&nbsp; The word means the same thing!  &nbsp;  My point…  If a couple is gay then I don’t care, I don’t want to see it but I don’t care.&nbsp; Some people like anal even with a guy and a girl, I am grossed out by the idea.&nbsp; Luckily I don’t need to see it, in-fact someone I know may love it and it would not affect our relationship as friends.&nbsp; Personally I don’t like to see someone making out in public (gay or strait).&nbsp; I don’t dislike seeing it because it grosses me out, instead because I think it is like sex, in terms of something that should be done in private.&nbsp; So I don’t mind a guy holding another guy hand or a girl holding another girls hand.&nbsp; I don’t like to see it go farther in public but I’m not appalled by it if they do and won’t think any different of them.  &nbsp;  If you are like Kyle then grow up.  &nbsp;  So the conversation continues with Kyle.&nbsp; I ask him, “People are all different religions so we have no normal on a specific religion but many consider being religious normal, do you have a problem with atheists?”&nbsp; Kyle responds, “Yeah, I do!”&nbsp; Now I was appalled, this guy was an idiot.&nbsp; “Ok Kyle, up until this conversation you had no problem with me, you thought I was fine.&nbsp; Now, I tell you, I deny the existence of God.”&nbsp; “You are an atheist?”&nbsp; And now I am trash.&nbsp; I go from a fine person to trash.&nbsp; I am not going to go into the details of the atheist argument, I will in another post as it was just as long.  &nbsp;  I still do not understand the controversy in gays and the controversy in religion.&nbsp; If you believe in a specific religion than learning about others should not sway you.&nbsp; After all, you believe everything you were taught about that religion, you know it as true.&nbsp; Why would you be offended by another opinion?    
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Infinity series will continue tomorrow, I have another post to get out of the way before that.  I finally got my computer down to the apple store!  I have never been in one and for how small it is I have to say it is one cool store!  I can't believe how many cool things they incorporated into it's design.  The Genius Bar is amazing -- a little egotistical -- but amazing.  All the stuff!  I would not buy it there because software i get for free and computers I get with a student discount I cannot get at the store (not for high schoolers, I lie online).  Really a cool place.  The genius went through a question list asking question I was surprised the average person could answer.  We finished and he took the computer.  I checked out the store a little more.  I can't get them to fix the dents but they will fix any internal problems.  The dents would require a new casing costing $600-not covered by insurance.  I will go into a little more detail later about stuff. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This entry kinda continues from yesterdays.&nbsp; In case you missed it we are on the topic of religion and I am an atheist.&nbsp; The topic relates to an argument I had at camp in the van but I am going to try to leave the argument out of the topic here.  &nbsp;  Atheism is not a religion.&nbsp; There are no rules to what actually happened in the creation of humans at all.&nbsp; The only thing an atheist believes in is that there is no god.&nbsp; No higher being with power over us (or whatever god does).&nbsp; Simply “you deny the existence of God” and I do.  &nbsp;  I don’t deny god to make a point.&nbsp; That is why I hate the question “Why are you an atheist?” because it is to tempting to respond with, “Why do you believe in god?”&nbsp; People really need to ask themselves that question.&nbsp; They should go to church (assuming a religion here) and learn all that they can about what the bible says.&nbsp; Then they should go home and decide whether or not it was real.&nbsp; One family I know has 5 kids.&nbsp; All are Mormon.&nbsp; Why are they Mormon?&nbsp; Their parents decided to be Mormon.&nbsp; My point is that you are likely to believe what your parents believe; you learn what you are taught.&nbsp; My parents told me I was religious, they told me I was baptized but they never brought me to church.&nbsp; I am not saying that is why I believe what I believe.&nbsp; I believe it because I was told what I was and never pushed into the details.&nbsp; So if I was never fed the details over and over on a weekly basis then something like Noah’s Arc is a load of crap!&nbsp; Common, naming insects?&nbsp; Naming animals?&nbsp; A talking snake?&nbsp; Do people really believe this Adam and Eve garbage?&nbsp; So that is what went through my mind.&nbsp; I have since learned from the Bibles lessons, I have asked different families with different religions to explain them to me.&nbsp; I understand many faiths and I am so happy that they are all learning their lessons from religions.&nbsp; Those who actually believe the facts in the book though really need to re-think the logic in them.  &nbsp;  I never argue with someone with the intent to change his or her mind.&nbsp; I argue to broaden their horizon and have them understand that there are people out there that disagree with them.&nbsp; A funny thing is how defensive people get during these arguments.&nbsp; While on the van Kyle was calling me crazy and a freak yet he could not answer the question “What is God?”&nbsp; Ok, you don’t know but how can you believe in one if you don’t know what it is.&nbsp; If I told him my desk was god he would disagree with me but he cannot define what it is.&nbsp; It is like he knows what it isn’t.  &nbsp;  Atheist is an oxymoron because you need to have an idea what something is before you can deny its existence.&nbsp; I do not believe in things I cannot see or cannot feel.&nbsp;&nbsp; I can see nor feel god therefore I don’t know how to recognize it.&nbsp;&nbsp; That is the reason I deny it.  &nbsp;  I hate the fact that it is socially acceptable to talk about your religion to people but not that you are atheist.&nbsp; If you say you are atheist people suddenly get all-defensive yet if I was in a room of Jews and was a Muslim nobody would care.&nbsp; Yet stating you are atheist is like pulling out a weapon.&nbsp; It is a “I HATE YOU ALL” statement.&nbsp; My parents tell me to quiet down when I get into my point of view.&nbsp; If I was religious I could just start talking about how great god is and all he has done for us yet being an atheist I can’t even admit to in public.&nbsp; It is like it is a sin, lol, get it!&nbsp; No, really, it is like there is something wrong with me.&nbsp; People need be more open-minded.  &nbsp;The next couple posts (the Infinite Series) will go into this a little more.   
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We as a human race are just dumb.  I cannot believe we think are as important as we do.  When I look up at night I see stars, lots of them.  The funny thing is how far away they are.  I am seeing many suns out there, some could be the center of another universe...many are.  So if there are other universes out there why do we no believe that humans have been created twice.  We do have many believers in god and that it created us, how do we know there aren't more of us?  The thing that get me about it all is how infinite it really is.There is no end, ever.  If you got in a ship with enough supplies to go the rest of your life and headed at a speed twice as fast as we can send you you won't make it to the end.  If we sent you at 20 times what we can send you you still wouldn't make it.  If we sent you at 100 times the speed of light you would go on forever.  What I said was fact, there is no arguing with it.  The reason I can safely say that I am 100% correct is because what is there when it ends?  When space does end, what comes after it.  More space.  It is a fact that humans can't comprehend because everything we live has a begging and an end,  nothing we make, create, think up, or do can go on forever, all will end.  We cannot comprehend infinity.  We know what it is in terms of a definition and can imagine no end but even when we imagine no end we see the end because where you are standing right now is the same as somewhere in space.  Both are the middle of the universe,  Both are the middle of nowhere.  You cannot be mapped to a location on a map of the universe because there are no coordinates.  The universe has no end.  If this is so and there is no end then there are infinite planets with humans.  Don't agree?  That isn't fact, yet at the same time it is!   I cannot prove it but it has to be true.  I can't even explain it because even I don't understand.  There is no end that means that ever pattern of where planets are in a universe and how big they are compared to the sun and how big that sun is has to happen.  There is no end and it would be extremely strange if one combination only happened once, ours.  In-fact it would be strange if it only happened 10 times.  The weirdest one would be if it didn't happen infinite times. The universe has no end therefore patterns and combinations go on forever as to how solar systems are created which creates fish that can fly and birds that swim infinite times.  It also creates every other crazy thing we could think up and everything we can't think up, infinite times.  Call me crazy but I do not believe this, I know this!  As I look up into the sky, I wish I could see every planet out there, I wish I could experience all the ways of life humans and other creatures have created out there.  Then I realize, I haven't even experienced all the ways of life we have created right here.  Humans can only live in ignorance, that is what we are.  All that we can do is lean as much as possible about all the other places out there before we are wiped out and lose our chance. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have discussed the fact that space is infinate but I never mentioned the time.  Time is infinate, we all know that.  How many have actually considered that though?  Have you ever really thought about that?  I mean understanding that there is no end to the universe is tough to fully grap but time WOW!  time never began and never will end.  There was a start to humans and there will be an end but there was never a beginning or will never be an end to time.  It is so hard to grasp!  Was the universe ever something different?  Did it evolve?  Of course it did, that is what we call the big bang.  I do not totally get the big bang, I know what I think it is actually happened at some point but I don't know what it actually is.  I imagine it as space as a whole started to gravitate to one point, one sun that was to big and it pulled many solar systems into it, it became so compressed that it finally exploded, reforming the universe again.  Let me correct myself, I assume that happened, I don't know if it did and I don't know if it was the quote un-quote "big bang".  So if this did happen then it was meaning less, this big bang that supposedly created our universe only re-formed it, it couldn't of created it.  Where did it get created then?  God?  No because time is infinite, another one of my points in why god cannot exist.  If time had no beginning then god would have had to of been created at some point during it.  It is said that god created the universe but that brings up that question of what was here before he created it, what created god?  Or was god created by evolution (that is ironic) in a previous place that is different than what we know the universe as?  Are the a species of gods out there?  on planet god and they control different universes.  I joke about the idea of god evolving to show why I cannot believe in it.  Time is infinite and to believe that god created time or even just the universe is absurd.  I am sorry I brought god into this, I did not set out to rip once again on religions. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some people think they can only find true love once in their life and if they find it twice then they are lucky.  I don't get why people believe that of all the people on this planet they think the found the one and only.  When you fall in love you sometimes can't live without that person but even in that situation maybe you can't live without that person but you can find someone else you can't live without.  Finding love is not tough, finding love the second time is tough only because we make it tough.  It is tough because we have someone to compare it to.  There was a girl where I used to live who I had not fallen in love with but felt I could spend the rest of my life with.  I don't think I could have said more than thirty words to her yet I knew her in so many other ways.  If you don't believe me "Cold Mountain" is a perfect example.  I can get over for that reason though, I had not yet fallen in love with her but now I compare her to others and use her as a guide line.  I don't think now that even us loving each other would have changed much.  I don't think it would be to tough. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got back my computer today, it went in the shop on Thursday.  I am excited to have it back (it is so hard to live without Final Cut Pro for a couple days, I have been without it for a total of 12 days since I bought my first copy and I remember each and every painful one of them).  So I brought it in because it was corrupting files like crazy!  They said the Hard Drive might need to be replaced but it was ok because I am still under my one year warranty for apple.  The diagnosis and repair we would have had to pay was $310 not including any replacements and the labor charge of those replacements.  We didn't need to pay any of it.  A hard dive being replaced would have cost probably about $400 but the diagnosis showed no need.  The 8 hour diagnosis showed no problems at all in-fact, a perfect machine.  I am happy it is perfect but I was looking forward to a new hard drive.  So we are walking away with my just returned computer and I realize the cover to the battery (a welded on part) has fallen off.  Something that cannot just snap back on, it is like having the shell of a laptop removed and using it.  We bring it up to the desk and they say the battery needs to be replaced.  They go through all the files of status checks while it was in repair and there is no word as to it breaking in repair but there also is no word as to it entering the store like that.  They have no choice other than to give me a new battery.  It takes a while to go though that process but the $170 battery was well worth the wait.  I looked at the bill when it was handed to me and it shows what it would have costed if I was actually paying for it.  Apparently there was a service charge of $80.  The only service was removing the battery and installing a new one, something people with two batteries need to do on a daily basis, a process that takes 30 seconds...a process, I noticed, that was done wrong when they did it right there in the store.  I didn't question it because I didn't need to pay it but if I were paying it I would have been disappointed that they didn't ask me to do it.  Now it is back and I installed the 512 megs of ram I got for my birthday and havent noticed any changes (I'm sure there will be some just not yet.  There better be for $200!) 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What is on my mind today.  If I were to give you a weekly update every week, this would be this weeks:  I am trying to get more people to my website.  I don't really know why and that is my first problem.  I pay like ten bucks a month for a server that nobody sees.  I don't blame them because while I have a cutting edge design, I have no content.  For a while I was trying to think up a hook, something that I could do in 15-30 minutes that would get people to return weekly.  Then I thought...why?  Why do I care if I have a lot of hits, I am paying to entertain people?  There are plenty of other websites out there for that!  So I focused, what was my website put up to do?  Attract money.  I need to advertise it and make it an advertisement for creating videos.  I amped it up to be more "buy from me-ish" and made a fancy flier.  Ok, not to fancy, basic.  Yet at the same time eye catching, I spent hours on it.  It looked pretty good!  I brought it down to two local shopping centers and posted it everywhere!  It was in front of every store!  Next day...they were all gone!  They were removed!  Damn!  So there goes that Idea, they pay somebody to remove them.  Now I need a way to get a lot of people from this area to my site.  I could advertise on the web but that would go to everyone and I don't want to pay to advertise to them if I don't need them.  I am still at a loss on that idea but I saw this site by accident the other day, www.oldenglish.org and thought it was a good idea.  I didn't want to do it before but if I made a separate domain for it I could use the same server for both and I would get people coming to a site and I would still have my advertisement site.  The site (old english) is a group of college kids studying film who create skits to show online.  I just might do that.  Then I could make it link to my site and I could attract people that way.  Another idea is to let friends and stuff post their videos on my server and then they would have family and stuff seeing my site (of course why would they go through me if their relative can edit and shoot).  I got my computer back (see July 13th)  I am in the process of copying software right now.  I had all these files everywhere of programs I downloaded and finally I going to back them all up together. I had to get Toast first so I went to Limewire to get a program illegally to make copies of other programs illegally .  Toast is no created to do that but it works nicely.  I needed toast specifically for Final Cut 4 and Mac OS X 10.3 because those I had DMG's for and they were going to take up a whole disk (FCP one take up 4 DVD disks).  I have made the FCP disks and my computer cannot tell the difference between them ad the real ones.  My next problem is the Mac OS X disks because while the only use regular CD's they are a lot harder to make (they need to be boo-table).  That is tricky when all I have are a couple DMG's, it might be easier with the real disks.  I don't know if I can actually do it.  We will see.  Everything else is looking ok, I need the Application Support files for Adobe Photoshop 7 but I have the install for CS (8) so I might be ok. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I haven't posted in a while because I have been working on a series I would like to infinity. It is a couple posts about my faith and why I don't have it. I am sorry about not putting them up on a daily basis but I wanted to make sure I didn't repeat topics and it was all organized. They will all go up today.   My sleep schedule is really messes up. I am trying to fix it but it is tough to do. I can't just go to bet earlier. I want to fall asleep around 11 because I wake up at 9 every morning but most mornings I don't feel like getting up and because it s summer I just sleep, sometimes until 3. I don't go to bed until 2-4 most nights/mornings and need to stop that. It is not healthy and I don't feel good the next day. I am puzzled because I am at a loss every day, I set out to accomplish certain tasks each day and cannot seem to keep up with completing them. I am puzzled because it is summer and I have no need to sleep on schedule so thy should get done! I don't get them done so slacked my sleep schedule to see if that WAS the problem. It didn't help so I am trying to get back on track. I am worried also because I feel that at the summer I will ask myself, what did I accomplish with all this time and answer... nothing.   My new goals: get some sort of website up that attracts visitors, make a lot of money (like $2000), possibly get a job if money is not working out (but where?), enjoy more, learn broadcast journalism by studying, get my pink slip, write my next script.   I can do all that. The pink slip will be tough because I need to do a lot of studying but I am going to take it on!  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I am in a car with my mom on our way down to San Ramon for the weekend as it is Gary's Memorial this weekend (see July 5th).  I asked my mom, "I need to write a blog, what should I write about?"  She suggested the traffic going the other direction.  Why people sit in it.  To be honest I don't really care about that and she will never read this so I will talk about traffic in the future.  I wonder how much longer we will be using cars for.  Something like the Jetsons where we all have a spaceship probably won't happen because we can't just go anywhere, that would complicate things.  We also cannot make roads with those because that would not solve anything.  So to be honest I think the next big change in transportation will be public.  I think that soon (like 20 years) we will start to see a new type of transportation that is like a low flying jet, can seat about 20 people and goes to different stops about an hour away (driving time) from each other like a bus in the air. I saw something that was cool that gave me this idea on the discovery channel.  A jet is in the works for international travel that takes you into space.  It looks a little like the top of a spaceship and seats, like I said 20 people.  It would be an alternative to airplanes because it gets you there faster.  It might end up being cheaper too because you don't need fuel once you are in orbit (not sure about the less usage of fuel).  Any-who, that was cool and I think we may integrate it into a cheap public transportation as an alternative to buses.  This post sucked but I had nothing to talk about.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had a hard time naming this post... other choices are "Questioning faith", "Gary's memorial", and "People show character".  I lay in my bed thinking of the day.  So much happened, so much to write about.  It was the first time I actually let out a tear about Gary's death.  I had come close when writing his tribute though.  Today was his memorial and to be honest it was nothing fancy yet totally amazing.  I guess I will start there, at the memorial service.  The place is unlike most churches because it has huge windows at the alter looking out over the mountains.  We get a view we cannot even see from outside of the building.  The service begins and I am ok.  I cannot help but to stare at Kayla and Ashley, my cousins who had just lost their father.  I were getting through it but they were alone with their mother in the front row, it was a family.  "Father Fred" gave a sermon and I was trying to get out of it what I could, I have gone over my beliefs.  I am not going to criticize anything he said other than the one thing I am about to mention.  I was trying to get as much out of it as possible because it was important I set aside my differences in a situation like this.  One thing though, he said, "...and Jesus died to open the gates to heaven."  I nearly broke out laughing because of what went through my head at that time.  Can you imagine how long the line must have been?  Was everyone just waiting for him to die?  What happened to everyone that had died before him?  I brought this up with my parents and my mom was laughing and I was surprised, I even got a chuckle from my dad who is upset at my choice not to believe.  The speaker speak, giving great speeches and they played a song.  This song was so close to my heart it was unbelievable.  When I was young I first heard this song ant Gary's house, it reminded me of so much you would not believe it.  Gary told me to turn it off because he did not want listen to it at that time, it reminded him of his mother, I always will remember that.  They played it, I was the only one who knew it had a special meaning to Gary but Krisia knew he liked it so she had it played, I cried at how important it was.  Later I told her what it meant to him.  We went to the reception and I really want to cut things short so I will get to the important part.  I might have told the story about the vipers but in case I didn't:  Gary always wanted a viper, it was his life dream to own one.  One day the viper club knocks on his door with twelve vipers!  That would be twelve of them.  The go for rides on the freeway at like 150 taking friends and neighbors.  This group stayed so close it was unbelievable, showing up at different times to say hi, they were wonderful!  The viper group showed up to the memorial.  They brought 4 vipers and actally stayed for the whole reception, you guys are amazing!  I connected with one of them, a guy from adobe...he wrote After Effects software for mac.  He loved talking with me and wants to keep in touch, maybe join me in the apple developer's program!  Another one of the viper guys that was amazing was Frank.  Frank was not a big member until he met Gary, he saw an ad looking for a viper and while he dose not usually look at these it was identical to the one he owned.  He contacted Gary and offered the car.  He let Gary keep the car in his garage for a while and I started hearing stories that made me like this guy less.  They had the money and he was not responding to their calls.  Now that Gary has gone something happened and he is back.  He got the viper and gave rides in his limo to Krisa while working the preparations of the memorial.  He even drove them during the memorial and all this for free.  Frank says Gary did an amazing thing in getting him more involved with the viper club and he wants to re-pay Gary.  If all of this is not enough this guy is sending Krisia and the girls to Disneyland on him.  He is rich but amazing for being so generous.  So I am going to be more involved now, doing videos for them and such, that club has done so much for everyone, it is truly amazing!  I get back to Krisia's house and Kayla and I have a chat.  She asks me out of the blue... "Are you adopted?"  I answer no, I know for a fact I was not.  I thought it was strange she asked this as it had nothing to do with what we were talking about.  I sit in my bed thinking over the day and I just wish I could believe.  I wish I could walk out of this room and tomorrow tell everyone I am now a believer in god!  I ask myself, why don't I?  Why don't I stop being so stuck in my ways?  Then I realize, I can't.  I have put to much thought into it and cannot become a believer, I just know better and realize it as a lie.  I look back at the song that made me cry at that memorial.  I still have not named it, if you have it please put it on now, the name is "Seasons in the Sun".  This song is Gary.  I just put it on and as I write this am listening to it.  --As I think of it he his here.   -To much wine and to much song, wonder how he got along. -Goodbye, it is hard to die...when all the birds are singing in the sky, now that the spring is in the air, think of me and I will be there. -we had joy, we fun but the wine and the song like the seasons have all gone.  Gary, we had joy we had fun... goodbye my trusted friend... goodbye my friend it's hard to die. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got back today after a long weekend away.  Sig called me looking for advice about buying a powerbook and my opinions.  I looked online for updates and did some research.  My opinion was just that this fall Apple will announce a new iMac and possibly a new powermac.  With that said they may not update the laptops.  I find at late night a part of macrumors.com I had never seen, the buyer's guide.  Great place, it has the chances of a new model to come out.  I will defiantly look at this a lot.  This evening I saw a 7th Heaven and a baby book on it.  I wondered where my baby book was and went searching, I found a lot, finally getting the book.  It was interesting, I learned a lot.  It is amazing how much love a family has at that time.  My mom writes, It was hard during this first month.  4th month she writes, Daddy was home a lot more now.  I read all different stories from all different times getting as much info as possible.  I was surprised that my dad was the only one in the delivery room other than the workers, I thought someone had been there.  My mom went into labor at 12:45, I was born at 1:53, I guess there wasn't a lot of time.  Defiantly worth going through your own if you haven't.  BTW - I was 3 days late, I was expected on the 1st. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This weekend I felt so full, I had so much I wanted to talk about, so much I wanted to discuss.  I look over what I have written and realize I had said all of it.  I read something this afternoon though that might make a good topic.  I am upset because I love my iPod and it does everything I bought it to do.  Why should I be upset about that?  Apple introduced a new feature to iTunes called Party Shuffle that I want on my iPod.  It is not necessary but is just so cool.  It picks random songs and constantly updates the list to provide a nice selection, a selection you might not get otherwise.  Apple introduced it's new iPod today and lucky for me it had this Shuffle, lucky for me it has everything I want (now) and more.  It is all just an update too!  It all is a software issue and with one quick update I can have the new software.  I anxiously awaited this day when I could update it.  I get the update and realize that you need the new iPod to receive the update.  This update installs your iPod's most recent update.  I don't even like the new pod, I think the old version is actually nicer.  Not a big deal, I just keep mine but I am upset I can't get the update.  So I go online to find out why there was no update and apparently the update is a hardware thing.  They cannot update the third generation iPod's because the hardware is different for the fourth generation.  A guy on the message board says the only way around this issue would be product development and they won't do that because they have no gain.  It is all capitalism, something we can all get rich off of yet something we all lose hundreds and hundreds of dollars to.  I hate it, I can't stand capitalism.  I do understand that it keeps America running but it is not fair to the consumer! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I suck!  Seriously, I keep thinking... I will do so much better next year in keeping on top of school.  Who am I kidding?  I will suck just as bad as I did this past year.  I just am not a good student, the reason... well, I suck.  I am totally lazy!  I have so much work pilling on top of me, the only way to avoid it is to buckle down and really work things out.  I don't do that, I just let it pile.  I have so much to edit that I don't even want to think about it!  I am constantly forgetting to upload blogs (I write them, I just don't update the website).  As soon as I think about what I want to get done I think of  something else I want done.  There are no deadlines so I let new things pop up.  I just suck.  I need so many improvements it is unbelievable!  I am updating my PC right now... I finally got so fed up with it I decided to re-format, thinking it wold be simple!  It is so tough, I am trying to get to DOS but since Windows 2000 we lost DOS and it is impossible to get back!  I can re-install the software but it installs a second copy of it!  I cannot get around all this!  I am so screwed... I better get back to work.  I don't think I will be hitting Starbucks tomorrow, to much to do.  Then again, I just might because I am still working on my sleep schedule. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have a lot to get done and I am goting to get all of it done by the first of august except if I post a different deadline here.  Here are the things that I need to do...  Keep my blog updated Do DMV work Post new video files on my website Get the new website going Find a job - try to get it done by Aug. 1st but it is ok if I don't Write a script for Code: Name Alec Get a case for my laptop to use next year Make sure there are no conflicts that will continue into the school year Create the Lehal Confinement Disk 2 DVD -  End of summer Edit Gary's Memorial - August 28th but only if it is good.  Have a finished version by then that you can make better  It does not seem like a lot but some of those are big tasks.  I kinda feel like I am on a beach and I keep getting hit by all these little waves.  Some are up to my waist, some are only at my feet (each being these little tasks) yet at some point I know a huge one will come that unless I beat all the little ones it will drown me.  I really need to do well in school this next year.  The odds are like 1:52 that I will get strait B's and like 1:84 that I will get strait A's (those were random odds) so I need to beat those.  I need to come home with atleast 4 B's (out of 4) and some of those should be A's... infact I have media, I should have 3 B's and 1 A no questions asked.  We will see. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think I have it now, I know how to get everything done.  I look at my list and I pick one or two small things to do plus continue on with a big project.  Yesterday I finished my DMV stuff and got a lot farther on finding a bag for my computer.  I am still lost in what to get.  There are so many choices to chose from and I know none of them are right because I still have doubt.  Right now I am looking for a bag that is durable.  Something that can fall 3-4 feet and not dent the computer.  That alone is tough.  It is my top priority, the bag needs to do that.  Then I need to adjust what I need depending on what I find.  If it has extra space it needs to have lots so I can use it as a backpack.  If it has none or little it needs to fit in a backpack but still be able to be used as a separate bag (ie - shoulder-strap).  I cannot find something this specific to my needs.  My dad told me something last night that made me think.  "You need something that allows you to use it for school and a computer... you won't find it because not many people need that so if they made it nobody would buy it."  So I am going to settle at some point, there will need to be a compromise.  I will not compromise on durability... that is it, I will not budge!  My dad and I are fighting.  I am fighting because he has no time.  He is trying to do two jobs and is mad because my mom and I are demanding on him and he does not have time for them.  He wakes up at like 7 and gets to work, he stops only for meals and a couple minutes when my mom gets home.  He does not stop working until 10-11 when my mom is asleep, of course that doesn't matter because he goes to bed too at that point.  I have no time to bounce ideas off him.  Many teenagers would be happy, he does not want me around, he wants me to go off and do my thing, get out of the house.  I need his opinion on things though, I use it as a basis.  I know if he hates my idea not to listen to what he thinks it should change to but it needs to change in that direction.  If he likes it it needs to change but I am on my own and if he just makes a couple comments then it is fine (maybe do one of them).  I use that basis and it gives me something I like.  I don't have that anymore.  There is a special bond between father and son.  Entertainment loves to play off of it because everyone knows it exists and is ignored.  It is ignored in the sense it is never spoke of, it just exists.  I think mother and daughter get a similar bond but I wouldn't know because that too is not spoke of.  When one of these bonds are broke the relationship crumbles and while my parents would love for me to get out of the way as much as I want them to they seem to not grasp how upset they will be when I am gone.  I take so much time out of there schedule and it will take the next two years for them to realize how much they want that.  If you are still reading then you have got to the good part.  I wanted to focus on this but I had a lot of other crap to cover.  I was watching 7th Heaven and it was an episode totally about Matt (the oldest son, he is like 22 or 23 at his time).  Matt decided to pick up a brides magazine and read it.  He wants to get married and he decided he will no longer date anyone he can't marry.  While he is about to start med school he wants to marry now.  He pretty much decides the fist date is not to soon to ask for a hand in marriage.  He finds the right girl but she is Jewish, her parents don't want them to marry because they want their only child to have a Jewish family.  The kids ignore this and he proposes to her on their fist date, she accepts.  It is stories such as this one that I realize just how much I want that connection.  I really want to not get married but have a girlfriend I can spend all my time with.  Then there comes two problems, I don't have the money nor the time.  That is frustrating.  I can't make a connection, I can't have a friend because I can't afford it.  It should be a priority so starting today I will put it on the list...  Find a girlfriend that I can spend time with at little expense - Four weeks into the school year  I want to write a book.  I think I just might too!  I already know what about, "The not so Holy Bible"  I think It will be a good thing for me to write and while I don't think people will care enough to buy it I think it will be good for me to have so it can answer questions about what makes an atheist tick. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am currently laying on me bedroom floor at 12:54 am on Friday July 23.  My plan was to go to bed at 11 but much to my surprise that didn't work.  I am kidding, I knew it couldn't be done because I couldn't fall asleep until almost 2 yesterday even though I got in bed at midnight.  So why am I on the floor?  I decided to spice things up... live a little!  Sleep on the floor.  Or just lie here.  Then I saw my laptop laying nearby and decided to write.  I have so many things to think about, I just lay here thinking.  I drift from one topic to another forgetting completely what I had just thought about, just focused on the new thing that goes into a tangent to another topic.  One thing is bugging me.  [START LATER] I had two paragraphs here talking about one of the things I had been thinking about.  I have removed it before I posted it because it was me saying I would do something I didn't.  I chickened out and decided not to.  I have saved it and might post it later if I get the nerve to do what it says.  I do not sensor this blog, I have some stuff on here I would never tell people, the part I took out simply was not important and was not interesting.  If someone really has a problem with the semi-sensor I will post it but it is not importiant.  Now back to the blog. [END LATER]  So I want to write about something else now because it is only 1:09 and I don't feel like doing nothing right now.  I feel I get really repetitive on this blog, the reason for that is not a lot is happening, I get these ideas and I just keep thinking about them, then I can't stop.  Soon I have a whole plan!  I don't know what else to say.  A Thought: I need money, not just a little, I need like $2,500 and soon.  I am willing to work hard for it but I just can't find it.  I need something that uses my skills that can earn cash but I can't get jobs nor can I get hired at a company.  I can keep rambling but I won't.  I am looking forward to an upcoming vacation because of this blog.  I am going on a cruise and what better place than to write a blog.  I cannot update daily of course but man I will get some good posts, I might write extras because there are so many things to talk about on the cruise!  So many places to write at, lobbies... rooms... decks... times of the day! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't really feel like writhing today so I will be just leaving a comment.  I have been working a lot on making a site like this one: www.oldeenlish.org because it is a good idea and a lot of fun (I think).  The first stem is getting your content but I will not really start that until next week, I decided in the meantime to move to step 2, the site.  You all are invited to the beta version of this site to test it out.  It has no content yet but will soon.  http://www.finalcutproduction.com/videodesserts  Let me know what you think of the GUI (Graphical User Interface). 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I get 128mb of RAM replaced with 512mb for my computer.  This puts me at 512+128 (internal).  My computer should go at least twice the speed, correct?  I don’t notice any changes in simple tasks.  No problem, I don’t need simple tasks to go faster.  I need it to edit faster!  Today I edited on it for the first time, I am actually writing right now on my PC while my mac is figuring out how to render.  I am rendering a simple speed change that should take 1-3 minutes on my old ram, this one has been going for at least 5 and it is only at 24%!   [MOMENTS LATER] I just went down to tell my dad what was happening as he was the one who put down $200 to get the stupid RAM.  He did not understand why I was telling him…something is wrong with him today, I will get to that later.  He told me “well, take the RAM out, simple solution!”  Ok, no… NOT A SIMPLE SOLUTION!  More RAM = Faster computer, less RAM = Slower computer… that is not a simple solution!  That is a quick fix!  I don’t know what to do, I know that won’t fix it… something is wrong, I think I need a re-boot.  Life is not going well.  I feel a little crammed I think.  Life is not going well because while I am enjoying it I am not enjoying it in a way I want to.  For some reason I do not feel like getting up in the morning, for some reason I do not feel like doing the things I enjoy.  I need to get away, not just for a week though because I will return to this life when I get back, I need to get away from this life.  There comes the idea of a girlfriend.  I go away next week for a cruise but I don’t think it will help.  Another problem is the fact that I am extremely tired; I am not sleeping enough because I cannot sleep until 2 am and need to wake up at 9 am.  I am so tempted to sleep in most mornings but if I do it will make life even worse because I will spend to much of my life asleep and not getting stuff done.  I was on the right track a couple days ago… I was setting to do lists and doing them but the problem was the to do lists involved putting down a long task to finish tomorrow.  That is the type of person I am, I cannot put a task down if I am into it.  I will either really succeed in life or fail in life because of this.    [BACK TO THE COMPUTER] My mac just went to sleep!  It was rendering (well trying to) and it went to sleep!  The computer will not go to sleep if it is working, it is written not to… but it did.  I un-sleep it and it says… “Writing Video… 0%” …uh, not good!  Then the render screen goes away and pops back up.  It goes through every percentage at about 2% per second counting down hours then minutes from 6hours on each percent change.  I have no idea what happened but it is rendered now.  [BACK TO MY DAD] So I said I would talk about this and before I get back to editing I am going to finish this post about my dad.  He is acting really strange!  Last night him and my mom got drunk (no big news) and were acting their usual drunk selves.  It is easy to notice because they dance a lot more (well… they move in a fashion similar to the beat of the music).  My mom asks a lot of questions about odd things in any story I tell and my dad makes rude comments while just acting like an idiot.  Sometimes it can be funny, most of the time it isn’t.  I ask my mom why she didn’t get any movies at blockbuster (last week she said there were a lot of movies out she wanted to see) and she said she thought we would go out to Cold Stone.  This is a good trip and a bad trip; it is like a good thing with a catch to it.  We walk the dog when we go and yes... we walk.  You can imagine how they are acting at home compared to how they act on the street.  They are not good at being drunk.  Well they get a little more romantic when they are drunk so that keeps them contained but it makes me worried.  Earlier this night my dad had been comments in a fashion I can only describe as attempting to be erotic.  He makes a comment about him and my mom are going swimming “with our clothes off!”  ok, no, my parents don’t do that.  This is my dad being an idiot.  This is my dad trying to get a rise out of me.  Well so what, he was drunk and looking forward to bed that night.  We are on our way to Cold Stone and my parents are holding hands, something about that bugs me… the fact that they are with me and doing it, if they were alone I wouldn’t care.  This morning he continued to act drunk by making some strange comments in the car.  He was just being obnoxious in the car.  We went house watching!  WE HAD TO TAKE A SENIC ROUTE!  I was so mad!  We drove past Eddie Murphy’s Summerhouse and Jim Carry’s Summerhouse for no reason.  Then he starts saying to my mom, oh… that house is for sale, and we could get that one!  Like we would actually move.  They may move when I go away but they need to stay where they are because of both of their jobs right now.  Then he starts doing Eddie Murphy impressions and oh, the kicker.  Net!  Look at that one, net… LOOK AT THAT!  Keep in mind he is driving and while he is driving his “look at that one” comments are requiring him to look and him to point.  IT just gets on my nerves! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday I went to a nice Auburn for breakfast with my parents.  We have never done that before but it was a nice change of pace.  I noticed the coffee situation.  This place was not a diner as much as they would like to think they were.  IT was nice but not that nice.  What I consider nice about a diner is the fact that it is so homey.  There are the regulars that are there every day to watch a little TV while enjoying a cup of coffee they enjoy and maybe a nice home cooked meal.  The one waitress knows enough about them to pass as their mom or even wife and is always cheerful.  There maybe a cook in the back with some strong name like bill or hank and he wears an white apron.  This is my kind of place!  I love it in a diner because I feel so welcome.  I noticed at this place in particular that the item on the menu called "coffee" was this same fashion, it was made in a real coffee pot like any person would have and was served right out of the pot it is made in.  I then realized how much this bugged me.  I did not like the idea that my parents were drinking this coffee that was not their flavor.  It was like a false advertisement, here is coffee but you don't know what it will taste like, you have an idea but don't know.  What I didn't like about that can apply in other drinks but doesn't.  Drinks that are so person should not be served impersonal is what I mean.  The fact that they served my parents that coffee was degrading it's value.  It took it's special flavor out of it because my parents weren't drinking it for the fact they could only get it there they were drinking it because of it's label.  I drink milk a lot.  I go on a trip to a different state and i can tell the difference in the milk.  I go to a different town and sometimes even then I can taste the change.  I know my drink that well.  I get this far in the story and I realize I am making no sense and I think why did I ever start talking about this?  If you get my point then thank you for understanding!  If you didn't then ignore all that and I will continue with a real point.  On Friday I was given a $10 gift card to Starbucks that I am using today.  I wanted to try something new with it so I got a mocha.  I wanted to make a new drink and I realized they pretty much covered the bases with that one.  I figure start from scratch.  I got a mocha, I almost went for a latte but from what they told me it was the same thing except a mocha has chocolate.  So what do I add?  It tastes decent actually.  I don't know.  I think the Strawberry creme with added vanilla bean powder sample I had was nice but the Strawberries and creme is like $3 for a small an $4 for a large.  It is a little much so I passed, a mocha was cheaper and tastes fine.  Maybe I will get the strawberries and creme one day I want something fruity.  I think Starbucks could make money off a passport type thing.  Get like an account that you pay one fee for like 20 drinks and you save by using it.  This store is expensive.  I just want like a cookbook because during the school year I can't get down here and I can't afford it during the summer.  I am beginning to realize where it gets its name star-BUCKS.  I leave you with a short little pice I wrote yesterday afternoon and was not long enough for it's own topic.  Wow!  I just started using this program called Spy Sweeper today.  It I totally amazing!  It picks up on the smallest things my computer does that might be harmful.  Its purpose is to remove any spy wear or ad ware but the thing is like an internal firewall.  It tells me if my homepage is changed (like when it is closed if it changes or even if it is open!)  It tells me when a favorite has been added to my website favorite list.  It tells me when something has been added to my startup list.  It protects everything that a “hacker” could ruin.  I put hacker in quotes because we call them hackers but they are just programs that set up your computer a way you don’t want it set up (i.e. – changing homepage, adding unwanted favorites).  This program is amazing! 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today we go over interviewing 101…  As a Broadcast Journalist I found the following website very entertaining.  I stumbled across it by accident and have learned a lot from it.  I wrote the following email to all my fellow STN campers to tell them about the website so I will just put in that email…  As most of us know many news sources have a liberal point of view.  Many of us also know that Fox News does not.  My dad loves Fox News because it gives him news he is interested in; I on the other hand find it crazy.  I cannot understand how he can listen to those idiots.  While I have a conservative viewpoint I also do not like the way they treat their guests.  Fox News has a way of always getting the last word.  Someone decided to do something about it an is now showing people why what they are doing is wrong.  Anyone interested in TV interviewing should watch this video, if not the video then at least the two clips I am linking to.  The video can be purchased on this website...  www.outfoxed.org  The trailer can be seen here...  http://http.dvlabs.com/carolina/Outfxd2/Trailer_A(Med).mov  and a very good clip can be seen here (A MUST WATCH!)...  http://www.lessig.org/blog/archives/OReillyGlick.mov  Now, I link to that second clip because I found it extremely interesting.  I think everyone who is on this list serve should see it because it shows just how far O’Reilly will go.  Please watch it.  -Andrew www.wdykm.com  So why am I telling my blog readers about this?  Because while all of you are not Broadcast Journalists you do watch the news.  I am not trying to start an anti fox rally here, I am just agreeing with the rally that has already started.  The clip with Glick and O’Reilly needs to be watched by everyone.  It is defiantly a must see and I encourage all of you to watch it and pass it on.  I am appalled by Bill’s behavior and he needs to be cancelled because his “I’ll give you the last word” comments followed by him taking the last word is one of the many examples of bad journalism bringing down that so called news channel. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today’s post will be in two parts, I wrote on in the morning and wrote the other in the afternoon as two separate posts but put them together later.  [PART 1] On Monday I did Tuesdays blog a day ahead of time because it made a great blog entry and I had found it that day.  During the next day I felt like I was forgetting to do something because I had not written the entry.  It dawned on me at that time that the blog is helping me so much!  I set these long-term goals in summer thinking they will help me when the school year gets going.  The blog is a long-term goal but it cannot be accomplished without the short-term goal of writing every entry.  I need to do more things like this because of that.  When I figure them I out I will do them.  [PART 2] My name is Andrew Cefalo and I have a problem.  I am addicted.  I can’t stop.  I literally know I should just walk away but think to myself I am seriously, honest to god, addicted.  I can’t stop watching 7th heaven.  I found it imusing when I started but now cannot stop watching it.  I am not joking at all, I really cannot stop and thing I need treatment.  It is all I think about… well almost all I think about.  I can be doing something totally different and start thinking about it.  I don’t even really like the idea of the show.  It has great characters though and they pot them in great situations.  The fact that the show never ends helps to the fact that it is addicting.  I have made a commitment that once school starts I will no longer have my cable line plugged in.  It will be put away and only be taken out when I have a large amount of time on my hands.  I have an idea though to make that time cut down even more.  I am planning to get DVD boxed sets.  They are sutch a good idea because TV shows to me are like short movies.  You get your whole plot out in 30 minutes or an hour and have no need to introduce characters.  Buying a DVD set of a show is like buying 20+ movies at $50.  So what I want to get are… Boy meets world, Family guy, 7th Heaven, Futurama, and CSI (the regular one).  I am only seriously in the market for those first four though.  Two of them are not even out yet but are due in the next moth or two.  Since you probably are not in the market for these here are some specs…  Boy Meets World Season(s): 1 – 22 episodes/6 disks (8/24/04) Price: $50  Futurama Volume(s): 1 – 13 episodes/3 disks 2 – 19 episodes/4 disks 3 – 22 episodes/4 disks 4 – 18 episodes/4 disks (8/24/04) Price: $40 (vol. 1) $50 (vol. 2-4)  Family Guy Season(s): 1 – 28 episodes/4 disks 2 – 23 episodes/3 disks Price: $50  7th Heaven Season(s): 1 – 22 episodes/6 disks (9/14/04) Price: $60 (actually isn’t bad considering each episode is 1 hour long)  CSI Season(s): 1-4 (there are to many episodes and disks and I really don’t care enough to list them) Price: $80 (season 1), $90 (season 2), $80 (season 3), $85 (season 4)  The problem with CSI is it is very costly and to be honest not my favorite show, I just like it.  The other 4 shows I watch daily along with Who’s Line Is it Anyway which is not on DVD.  It just occurred to my while writing this that I can actually get one of these.  I was kind of in a pickle because I cannot afford to go out and buy a couple seasons of a couple shows.  Just then I realize I have a $40 gift card to Best Buy and no plans for shopping there.  I am still saving for my computer but I thing an exception is in order… $10 might be ok to take out.  After all, I do have $20 in my pay pal account I can transfer.  I then think… what would be the best use of my money?  What show do I like best… lets recap!  My name is Andrew Cefalo and I have a problem.  But that is not due until September!  And it is $60!  I don’t know what to do.  Boy Meets World would come in second but I am not fond of the first season.  Next would be Family Guy but can I buy Family Guy or Futurama without getting one of the others first?  I will think it over.  I am sorry about today’s lame post, I am at a cross roads of trying to make my life easier to live well and need some time to talk it over with myself.  I have the money to buy all those sets (when they come out) but that would pretty much kill my computer fund and I refuse to do that for a cause that is not worth that money.  After all, all these shows still run daily. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday I sat in my kitchen talking to my dad about the cruise.  This will by my third cruise and his second.  This time he knows what to expect he tells me.  He then tells me he knows one of three things will happen... (1) I will have a good time (2) I will have a bad time (3) Both and I will get in trouble.  Then I knew it was coming... the sex speech.  "...and to be honest I now know better, you are 16 and I don't care what you do because in a week we will never see those people again."  I was shocked to say the least.  First of I I don't think I would even try to get that far in a week let alone be able to.  I am shocked though that I have my fathers blessing (in a sense).  I am so excited now for the cruise... more than before.  It is such a great vacation.  There is nothing like the freedom you can get on a vacation like this, the freedom to go anywhere and do anything.  It is the opposite of what all the nee-sayers say about it!  I love the large amount of people on the ship, there is tons of space.  I LOVE IT!  Anyway, enough bragging.  Isn't it funny how we can spend a month preparing for a week?  This whole week I have been thinking what do I need to get done?  I know that when I get back school is just two weeks away and it is orientation week(s) so I will be busy.  [TIME PASSES] I am still sitting in Starbucks but about 5 minutes just passed as I looked around.  I notice that on the double doors there are brass plates where people puss the doors open.  One shows wear and the other shows none.  It is funny because the more I watch the more I notice the other is never used.  While writing this paragraph the doors were opened 6 times all 6 it was opened with that door.  I will keep count as I continue to clarify we will say (*L*) for the one that has wear and (*R*) for the one that doesn't.  Starting at the end of this paragraph if in the middle of a sentence I break out one of those you know what it means.  I love surveys (*R*) as it is just interesting to (*L*) look at the results (*LR*).  I love website stats and (*R*) to look at what people do.  I have always been inspired by something Stephen Hubbard did once.  He sat at an intersection and marked every car that came through it down (*L*) on a paper (*L*) to take statistics of the intersection.  I don't know if it was for school but it was something that has always stuck with me.  My parents love to people watch, not for stats... just likes to watch them.  I like that idea but only for stats.  Se how they react to certain things.  There is nothing like the (*R*) human (*R*) mind interpreting different obstacles, how it can differ so much.  If (*R*) I put a dollar on the ground and watched how people reacted before (*L*) going back and asking for it (*L*) back (*L*) I would get three (*R*) responses.  Some would leave it, some would pick it up to keep and some would pick it up to return.  Anyway, I am done but I will continue this survey, if you have been watching my point is standing up but not all that well, I wonder how that door could be so much more worn but not used as much....  *L*L*L*R*L*R*L*L*L*L*R*L*R*L*L*L*R*L*R*(SEE TOTAL)*R*L*L  {NOTES WHILE CONDUCTING SURVEY} HAH!  I just looked out of the window and noticed a guy sitting reading the paper but not.  He was looking just above it watching people.  That is so funny to me.  I think a reason this is not holding as true as I would expect it to is I am including the people entering, it might not be as worn from the outside and sub-continuously we see worn and assume it is the better way because more people use it.  Well it seems to be holing a little more true over time.  It must just be a human instinct... this is why I find stats interesting, ok... that door is used more... why?  The guy with the paper left.  Our total stands at (*R=13 L=18*) and that is as of the (SEE TOTAL) above.  I will go until one of them reaches 20.  And there it is... totals, *(R=14 L=20)*  59% of the time people use the worn door and 41% of the time they use the non worn one.  It is amazing how I know so much by just sitting here for 45 minutes.  If you were curious, while doing this math three people have entered the store, all three through (*L*).  Those included would bring it to 62% so it just depends on you pool I guess, I could go to 40 and possible gotten very different results.  I am going to stop here but while doing the second math only one person has used the doors and that was through the (*L*) door. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        This post is a little un-organized.  I wrote it over a long period of time and have not read through it to organize it.   My plan was to sit out in the park tonight and write this post.  I am outsidein the middle of a park writing thisbut it is not working how I planned it, I am not feeling the enviroment.  Before I write to the point of why I am out here I have an idea.  This next school year I will not be writing daily.  It wll be about 1-5 times a week.  I am looking at this blog wondering what it is missing finding content an issue, I will only write when content comes to me.  Another thing is I look at real blogs, blogs that are created by the writer and are hosted on a pay server and wonder why they are better.  It is obvious... PICTURES.  It dawned on me this afternoon while looking at pictures of Gary's memorial.  I went into 9th grade literally wanting to document my life, have a video camera with me at all times.  I grew up and realized it wouldn't happen.  I think I went to expream though, I need a camera with me at all times for stills.  I will take pictures more regularly now and will post them on my server in my new blog.  Pictures are so importiant and I got lost in that when I went to video, I lost my love for photos.  Another thing that set me off was poses, I need non posed photos, things you will regularly see.  This will be my new blog, photblogging.  I am going to take a break now to stare at the stars, I will be back.  The moon is so amazing, we just take it for granted.  We can only see it because it is reflecting the sun.  We are looking at a huge rock illuminated by our sun!  I is just amazing.  And how we see shapes on it, huge blotches, huge crators or water or something.  I don't know nr do I care, the point is that it is all faboulous and spectacular and everyone needs to see it, really see it.  I have not spent much time out here but I need to.  I need to spend more time out here without my computer.There is so much knwledge to be gained from the sky.  You can really think.  Nothing else matters, just this small amount of grass, the sky and me.  There is something to this going out thing though.  We are so caught up in our own meaningless lives that we follow a rutine everyday and never stray from it.    It is 11 at night but I fell like goinf knowwhere, just going around town.  Yet I don't.  I have that urge of just showing up somewhere.  There is smoething to going to a place you are usually at but at a time you are not.  That spontanious urge is something to live for.  I havent had a theme for a while but tonight I will have one... more of an idea.one night in the next week go out of your rutine, go somewhere that you don't decide to go to until you are there.  Just leve your house in any direction and when you get there stop for maybe thirty minutes just to be there.  This post has not been what I wanted it to be so I am going to stop but keep that in mind.  NOTICE: Starting Sunday you won't see any posts for 7 days.  I will be on a cruise. 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I really have no time.  I am getting ready for my trip!  My cruise!  I will write a better post durring the trip but until the 8th there will be no posts, they will all be put up on the 9th. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Somehow I deleted all the stuff I captured at camp on the last Saturday.  That bums me because while I will get all of it back (except one thing) when I get the camp DVD, I am mad I didn’t back it up to tape!  I went online today to look for souvenirs, I was curious as to how much I can buy them for online and to my surprise Hard Rock does not sell menu’s online!  Another thing… carnival does not sell merchandise!  I was shocked!  I go to eBay and it is all-seasonal (lol, spell check takes out that dash then says it needs it but when you add it, it wants it out again) so you just need to catch it at the right time.  I wanted to buy a London and a San Francisco Hard Rock Menu (the old one, see ‘Aug 2nd - St. Thomas’ for details) but I cannot find the right style from either place.  I found one London one but not only was it a replica for some anniversary it was not the true menu it was the grand opening menu.  I am just figuring out a souvenir company would be a great website.  A place you can go to buy things like menus if the stores wont sell it to you or you forget to get it.  Of course some people would just buy stuff without ever going there but that is their problem.  I am still talking to people online from the cruise (no big deal, I will for a while) and I hope we really do keep talking.  I am still working on the cruise posts, that is why they week is not up.  Each day I just made some notes as I really felt like I had better things to be doing then my blog… I was wrong.  I am completing all the thoughts still.  I will post when I am ready. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>