<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I arrive on the Campus of Ashland University at 1pm to register so i can find my room and building. i was assigned to Clark Hall, my city was Davidson, and my counties name is Holcshuh. I waited for my roommate for the longest time and she never came for a long long time, but at like almost 2:30ish i met her. My roommates name is Sarah Balney, she is a great/amazing person. i had soo much fun talking to her and hanging out with her the whole time we were there on the first day. we then had a meeting in our city hall to meet n greet all the girls who were selected to go to girls state. it was a great privalage to have such an amazing city and to have great friends. we walked into the room as strangers and we will walk out as best friends, the week we spent together will be remembered forever, since it was a great privilage to be selected for such a great thing. We then explored the campus with our city, *Z* showes us where things were and where to find everything. after that we ate dinner with our cities, and we then had a bond to each other, i then started to hang out with nicole, krysta and bridget. at 8 pm we all went as a city to the upper convo room to have our opening ceremony, it was kind of boring but i guess u'll have that sometimes. after we had our opening ceremony we started to form our businesses and have some fun. it was a great day n it had soo many memories, i'm glad that i got a chance to go to this. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      all school year i was looking forward to summer break, i thought oh i'm gonna have the time of my life, party all the time, hang out with friends. that hasnt seemed to come true yet, well to be honest, i dont even know who my friends are these days, none of them come around, call, or even acknowledge that i'm even alive. i wish i would just leave for the whole summer, but my luck my parents will say no. whats new, cant ever have any fun.     lately i have been really emotional, probably because i am leaving for 6 days, and i'm going to be with people i dont know. its a scary thought, yeah i dont seem like i'm a shy person, but inside i really am, i'm soo scared, i'm worried that i wont make friends, and that everyone will hate me, like they do here. what really upsets me is that i wont even get to talk to the 4 people that actually care about me for 6 days. no one wants to hang out with me, its like i'm invisible or maybe no one really likes me. i dont expect to have friends, and i dont expected to be liked. i guess all i can do is pray that this summer starts to look up for me, if not then i guess i will be gone before it gets too bad.   -maybe someday someone will really care about me, hopefully before its too late-
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      most days when i wake up i have this calm but silent feeling inside of me. i always have faith that everyday God will show me the way. some reason lately i have began to let myself sink into the temptation of wanting to be with someone who i know will hurt me in some way or another. i know that is strange, but it hurts more if i dont try to see if he has changed at all. i think at times no way he didnt change, but then at times i think wow he must really care. at times i wonder and ask myself if i really love him or do i feel this way because i have been with him for so long, and i know that he loves me for me. i wish that i could pull my strength that i have deep down inside of me and protect myself from getting hurt once again. when he is around my eyes become hazed and i lose sight in everything that was so clear before. In my head i think he has changed or that he will have the will to change for me, but i'm starting to think that i'm part of his game. i feel at times that i'm just another player in his game and when he is done he'll just throw me in the closet and forget about me forever. i hope that is never the case, because he really did steal my heart from the start, i just hope he saves it all before its too late. i guess i'll just have to wait and see!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know this is being published way after Prom, but I just created this so I want to share with you my experience. Prom was a night I will never forget, my date was a total gentleman who showed me all of his attention, I really appreciated that. I'm glad I went with my good friend, well at the time he was a good friend to me, but I guess sometimes people just drift apart even though you don't want it to happen it does. If there was anything I could say to him it would be that I was glad to be his friend even if it had to come to end (it was over stupid shit). My dress was absolutely beautiful, well I'll describe it to you, it was very poofy and white, it had purple and silver beads down the front.      Now I'll tell you about prom day. I got up at 8 to start getting ready, I showered. After I was done my mom did my hair around 10ish since my brother had a baseball game at 1. My mom and I made a last minute trip to walmart to pick up some last minute items from prom, then we headed over to the ball fields to watch my brother's team kick some ass (they are coached by my dad). My friend Stephanie was dropping off her brother and saw me with my hair done, she commented and said she liked it. After my brothers game was over we headed home to put some last minute touches to my hair. I got a call from my date saying he was coming over at 4 to get pictures. Well I then put my dress on and did my make up and all the other girlie things you have to do to be ready for a big day like this. Bryan (my date) showed up in his moms car which we took to prom and his mom was following him in Bryans truck. We took tons of pictures, then hung out for a bit at my house. We left my house and went to Bryan's to pick up something he forgot. After that we headed off to the Grand March, that wasn't too bad!!. After the Grand March we went to the country club and stood in line for pictures, and we did that then had dinner. Prom was over all the best night of my life, the most memorable moment was singing Hey Mickey to Mr. Blatnik!.       ...Cant wait till prom next year!!!...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       its been a while since i wrote something in here but i'm trying my hardest to keep this thing up to date. i am the happiest girl in this whole world because i could not ask for a better boyfriend. i am soo glad that i have him in my life every day to hold my hand and walk with me. we are approaching the date that we first started dating, finally a year, it feels like i have known him forever. one year down and forever to go. its the little things that he does that makes me smile n think that i love him more then anything in this whole world. my sweetheart took me to jamboree in the hills, this was my first year and i had&nbsp;a blast. i was sad about him not being able to be by myside on saturday and sunday, but he showed up after he got off work around 6 each day. i was soo glad to see him =). jamboree in the hills started july 15th (thursday) at 3pm and we got out there to campground a around 4ish with Ryans friend Jimmy. i was soo excited to see Montgomery Gentry close out the first day at jamboree. me, tabby (ryans cousin), carrie (ronnies ex-gf) went from where we were sitting to the beginning of the photo isle, wow those ppl were pretty pissed off, oh well, lol. the lead singer of Montgomery Gentry posed with t-roy n they were like singing to me and tabby, i have never been soo excited in my life. on friday Lonestar closed out Jamboree and they put on one hell of a show, but i was soo excited for saturday to arrive and let me tell u Jo Dee Messina was freaking awesome, even tho she was being stuck up and i didnt get to meet her backstage =(. saturdays weather was pretty horrible it rained all morning till about the middle of the afternoon, and i got sick from standing out in it=(. ZZ Top closed out saturday night and for me not knowing anything about them i would say they put on one hell of a show, and then sunday finally rolled around. i had a freaking blast, and i missed my baby a lot, i was drinking with ryans family, i love his sister to death!, she is freaking awesome. i got bunches of water dumbed on me, then the beer got poored on me. ryans cousin tyler was pretty drunk on friday n was acting weird smacking my ass n shit, i didnt really like that =(. then i danced with him and mel on sunday, he was looking out for me! i'm soo glad i got to go i did have a blast even tho i made ryan feel bad and lied to him about having fun to make him feel bad =( .. i'm too mean. 8 days till i celebrate one year with the one i love more then anything on this entire earth. i'm soo glad that him and i worked everything out and gave it another chance because it is worth it and soo much more. he is my life, my love, basically he is my everything. and some day i'm goin to be his wife =) =). i cant wait ... wellll i'm gonna go to bed since its way way late!!    &nbsp;  &nbsp;    &nbsp;  *I Love You Ryan Scott Everett  
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>