<Blog>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm starting this even after I read that article in the New York Times about the addictiveness of blogging. I'm not even sure how I feel about it (having a blog, I mean), but here we go anyway...  ...and speaking of which, why do people blog anyway? Some say boredom, but I know that isn't what intrigues me about blogs, or at least, what lured me into this blog. There is something just out of reach of my mind, something about making connections between things, and sharing those connections...hmmm, I'm not sure. Why do you blog?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Listening to:  Amelie Soundtrack   As the plane broke through the cloud haze I could see Italy far below me, lit in a warm yellow evening light and sprinkled with stone colored bits of humanity that must have been buildings. Mountains rose up from the earth like ripples or folds of fabric, oddly smooth compared to the mountains of the west coast of the United States. It looked like a place out of some sort of fairytale, or from one of those ancient maps with sea serpents stalking the edges of the ocean. It seemed an impossible place from the air, somewhere I could only visit in dreams.  We landed and left the plane, walking carefully down stairs to the airfield boarded a tram and were whisked away to the airport. Most of the people surrounding us were chattering away in languages I didn’t know, mostly Italian, but I think I heard some German in there and something else that sounded Eastern European. We all gathered inside the building and lined up for customs. The sign overhead read “Passporti Controllo” or passport control. Easy to figure out…so far. The men checking the passports looked incredibly bored and we all passed through without a hitch, gathered our bags and piled into the car to head home.  So who’s ‘we’? Myself, my husband J, my father D, and my stepmother Z. This is the first long trip that J and I have taken together in the nine years that we have been together. This is also the first time that I have been in a mostly non-English speaking country. We will be here in Naples, Italy (or, more properly, Napoli, Italia), staying with my dad and Z for 2 months through the summer - the longest I have spent with my dad in a long time. I hope that we all will still like each other by the end of our stay! Anyway…  Napoli is nothing like I imagined it…not that I assumed very much to begin with. The air is very dirty, which Z tells me is partially from trade winds carrying dust across the Mediterranean from the Sahara desert. It is very hot and quite humid – one does not make it through a day without being damp at some point. The driving is positively crazy! The lanes are very small and people drive (around corners, even) at astonishing speeds, seemingly careless of open car doors and pedestrians. My dad says that we will see many cars with lots of dents and dangling side view mirrors. Dad and Z’s car has acquired a few scratches and dents since it has been here.  But I love the place anyway. It is a strange new place and I feel that I am long overdue for such an adventure. There are so many differences from my American culture, some of them subtle, some of them extreme. Buildings are built with a different sense of aesthetic. Just down the street is an old Roman amphitheater, right in the middle of a very busy section of streets and shops. And there are shops everywhere, in places you would never find them in the US. Basically if there is a hole in the wall, there is probably a shop there. They keep odd hours too – pharmacies in an area will be open different evenings, but not all. There is the practice of Riposo – a rest or break in the middle of the day. Restaurants and shops are open opposing hours – if one is open, the other most likely is not. And the Italians! They are charming and hilarious, warm and expressive, talking with they’re hands and emphatic inflections. They really like to repeat themselves, saying “ciao” (bye), “si” (yes), or “va bene” (it’s all right) at least twice but more often five or eight times.  Some other Italian words that I have begun to learn are: riposo = midday break ovo = egg riz = rice grazi = thank you scuzi = excuse me salumeria = meat and cheese shop mercado = market demani = tomorrow dopo demani = after tomorrow dopo dopo demani = some distant time in the future  The first two days we were here Z took us shopping for food and we went out for pizza and gelato (sort of like ice cream, only better) in the evening down on the beach. My dad had to go to Sardinia for work, though, and Z went with him, so J and I have the apartment to ourselves for a week or two. Today, the day after Z & D left, has been a day of just lying around, watching Italian TV (Inspector Derrick!), and reading the various Italian language books lying around. It’s so good to be on vacation! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>