<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like chicken. Tastes good and makes a change from carbs. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder went to something called SUPERCOMM and left with me with Aunt Sabrina. She's a very fun girl - had me out and about, running in my ball every night. Kind of miss being over there actually. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I like my ball  The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      that party thing was very disruptive. Despite being placed in The Feeder's bedroom, I had multiple intrusions all evening. A drunken British girl slurred over me "hesss reaallll, not stuffed" -- very disturbing. I'm hoping The Feeder is suitably hungover today and won't be as loud tonight. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cage was cleaned tonight and I got to run around on The Feeders arm. A friend of The Feeder was over and I was fed pizza (yum!!), then they made mini cupcakes (drunk). All I hear is 'Party'. I'm hoping that means I get some cupcake and can wear a nice hat. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wholefoods fresh egg pasta is yum. Almost as good as the rice from Naan and Curry. I'm craving pizza too.. maybe The Feeder will treat me soon, I hear Pizza Orgasmica does a great spinach and feta combo. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Peekaboo  The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder cleaned my cage today - lucky because the sawdust had blocked my tube to the play area. I'd been stuck in my sleeping zone for two days. Not that I minded much as all I want to do is sleep anyway. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder's friend foiled my attempt at escape tonight. After consuming two vodka tonics, The Feeder was unware that the latch on my home wasn't entirely locked. Sadly she figured out the escape bid when I rattled the roof a little too loud. I'm hoping the friend comes back with more vodka so I can try again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder came home from work at 7.30pm and tried to wake me up. I simply opened one eye and curled further up in the nice tube in my cage. Doesn't she know I don't wake up until 11pm, when she's asleep?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My new home&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Didn't like the mazda miata ride very much. Way too bumpy. I just curled up in my tube until we got to North Beach which seems nice. Not sure about the dead animals everywhere.. will sleep tonight and ponder the animals tomorrow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder has left me. Again. Auntie Sabrina is very nice though. She talks to me more than The Feeder does, and she doesn't call me rat. Also seems to stumble in drunk less (or maybe that is because The Feeder isn't here to drink martinis with her). Oh well, makes a change from seeing Tucky the cat drooling over me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Fighting The Feeder for some more carbs  The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to Auntie Sabrina's for 10 days. I'm hoping she drinks less than The Feeder and buys some carbs for me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder and her friend came home at 7.30pm. I was half awake, but then they talked to me. And for some reason, I felt happy. So happy, that I fell asleep again. I like martini fumes. Bring on Belvedere martinis, straight-up, two olives. Good night.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me being caught after another escape attempt  The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I like apple and peach crumble.   The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Exploring my new penthouse cage attachment. All I need now is a leopard skin couch and a good stereo system.   The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Escaped again yesterday. I like freedom. Just a shame The Feeder almost squashed me when she came home drunk. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Feeder is betraying me. I kept hearing her saying "here Tucky, Tucky" and couldn't understand what she was talking about. Now I know. She is feeding a cat. The ultimate hamster enemy. I am not impressed. I'm sharpening my teeth for the next time The Feeder comes into my cage. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The English bloke dropped me. I discovered dust bunnies and leftover chinese crackers behind the sofa. The Feeder managed to catch me by offering up a biscuit. I like biscuits. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Actually, I like the English bloke now  The Feeder 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is a man in the flat who hates hamsters. I can tell. He isn't at all friendly and tried to kick my ball when I was in it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like having my tummy tickled. Auntie Sabrina tickled me this week and I curled up in delight. I only wish she'd learn how to pick me up, then I might get tickled more. Oh well. I wonder when The Feeder is coming back. Although, I quite like living in the Marina. Lots of cute blondes over here. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>