<Blog>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sigh.I do not know what is happening now.Last time George ignore me,now Cheng Heng.What's wrong with this guy.Like everything i do,is so wrong. Well no comments.Forget Cheng Heng.Forget about those you wont lose me, i'll lose you phrase that he said to you,Hira.Now it's not him that he's losing..but i am losing him.I totally lose contact with him...i feel so horrible..he used to be my good friend but all of the sudden he's ignoring me like he don't even have seen me before.Don't always break your promises Cheng Heng...yes..last time ine day i never sms you, you'll sms me and say how r u...you feel like i've lose touch with u.. afraid you might lose me,a good friend.I DONT THINK SO...when i needed u most,you'll be there 4 me..now...you'll totally ignore it...   Miss you for now.  Sigh.dont get to see my new crush.Am i desperate?Nah.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been about few months since i have not seen Naruto. I wonder how is he doing in the village.Is he up to any mischief again?  -Miss you forever. Talk to me again like you did in my dream. I shall love you forever.Till i get the chance to get to Japan,i hope to see you there! I will look for you! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wont tell all of you more about the story because i have forgotten about my essay. I have pass up. Well,it is about a girl who lives in a village that only allow people who is very happy always be one of a resident there.She was rather a sad girl after being suffering so much in love.No one loves her.She went up to the Sun every day when she is sad and mumble to it...She always regard the sun as her boyfiend..Poor thing.Evertime she likes a guy,that guy will go away for sure just like the sun that always move in the sky. One day,there was a heavy rain near her village.She was so nervous and panic all about it... Everyone in the village were so mad at her as she was crying!! She ran out of her village ASAP and she eventually knock on a guy.The guy was so concern about her that he brought her to his house to give her sweater and warm water and thereforth. As they were sitting down together they introduced themselves.Only then the guy knew about her feelings for the sun. How meaningful the sun is. Suddenly..he popped out a question to her and say " can i be your sun starting from now on?I'LL make sure i will give you sunshine brightly just like the sun you always look to! i Will be keeping you warm always!"who would not be shocked. Only then she realised that miracles do happen to her. And she believes now that...it was the day when the sun stood still for her and will not move away.    When i get my essay back,i shall scan it for u all!!! Give me your comments about this story!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Too bad that ivan likes someone else.It really mean the same thing as he belong to someone else...I am quite mad actually but sometimes i have got to face up to reality. I am lost out here.I wish my life could be as happy as my other friends...I wish it would and could happen. Ivan again,now became top of my priority...Cant let him go easily.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI I LOVE IVAN CHNG OON WEI  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well,i really do not know whether that cow has a girlfriend or not. It realie sucks. I havent been crying for quite a long time and these bitches came up to me and telling me off afraid i might steal their guy.Purlleeeeezzzzz!!!! He doesnt like me okay. All yours girls! I really feel so down about how people can really rebel on every guys i like. Who do you expect me to be with now!!! I really love Cow. But i am afraid it may not be forever as how it did to George..(duh!) Well, i am having a great tme wit my sweetheart though.   I think i am a flirt!! But it is only love triangle for me!! Stupid Hira!!  Argh!!! Am i dumb or what?? Cow here there but i always look dumb to him.  I dunno what else that i can do..
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      do i really like Ivan. I feel that this is just a fake game played with me.  IvAN!!!
       
    
    
</post>


<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello Boys and Girls! Welcome to Hi-*Miao*! Hmph! Today i felt rather bored as i did not attend school. Well,all because of this infection that i have fever and swollen throat.Much worse than a usual sore throat. This time i felt really cold!! Bad fever indeed.But i have to go to school no matter what tml. Life is so NOT great. But we have to appreciate the life we have now. Treasure it.. Here that boys and girls?
     
    
</post>


</Blog>