<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man this field trip sucked!! We didn't do anything, walking around not learning anything didn't make it any better.  Atleast if we were learning something I might have said it didn't suck.  On the bright side it got us out of class for a day.  It could have been improved if we got to ride the ferris wheel and eat. Next year I think it would be better if instead of a field trip they just gave us the money that they wasted on the field trip.   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are they real or just some story made up to scare little kids?  We may never know if these stories are real or not, but as far as I'm concerne, it doesn't matter.  To me it doesn't matter if they're fact or fiction.  If they're real then thats fine and if they're not then who cares?  We should just let people belive what they want to belive.  I'm not saying that I don't believe any of these stories I always give it a chance, but I could care less if they're real or not.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two years ago acouple of my friends and me decided we were going to go inside the abandoned Jefferson Davis hostpitol.  I had never been ther before, but had heard from my friends that it was a scary place.   We decided to go at around 12:00 midnight just to make it more scary we went in ther with some lighters and two baseball bats, just incase anything were to happen while we were inside.  We knew that there were security guards so we hurried to get inside.  We we got inside we could here other people talking and it wasn't really that scary, it was more of a rush, a felling of not belonging there.  Soon after we started walking there were many writings on the wall from people that had gone inside over the years.  We then went up some stairs to another floor my friend started telling us stories about people that had died there many years ago when the hostpitol was still open.  After he told us that then I started feeling a very eerie feeling and I felt as if there were people watching us.  That's when I felt I was in haunted place.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cousin Greg, is the relative which I am mostl close to.  We have known each other since I was two years old.  We do everything together, from playing video games to making music.  I enjoy going out ith him on weekends.  He graduated this year form Jeff Davis High School.  He will be attending U of H Downtown next semester.  We went to the same elementary school, the same middle school, and the same high school. But I'm not sure if I will be attending U of H Downtown.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The only tradition I can think of is the most obvious and that is when a girl turns fifteen years old she celebrates her birthday by having an extrvagent party known as a quincenera.  It is a very big celebration which starts at a church where the girl and her family have a service to show that the young girl has made her transition into womanhood.  She then has a reception where she is presented with gifts and takes part in a dance.  All of this usually takes months to plan there are many dance rehearsals as well as classes that the girl must take at church before she can be accepted by the church as a woman.  I my self have taken part in many fifteens as an escort.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this weekend I'm gonna chill wit Expo probably at her house or something like that.  Hopefully I'll get to spend sometime with my girlfriend Diana before she leaves to Kingsville for her summer institute.  I'm gonna most likely take her to go see the new Harry Potter Movie.  I really hope I get to spend time with her cuz she gonna be gone for two weeks and I don't know if she's gonna be able to call me or not.  School is getting tiresome for me, I have to go to school all day long.  I go to summer school in the morning and to the summer institute in the afternoon.  I'm doing more school durring the summer than I did durring the regular school year.  I'm gonna get no chill time whatsoever this summer, as soon as I finsh summer school and the summer program I'm gonna have to start working to pay my friends mom $1200.00 that I owe her.  So I just hope that this summer goes by as quick as possible.  This summer is really gonna suck for me.  I really hate to say it but I'm actually looking forward to this next school year.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>