<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HAPPY BIRTHDAY JORDI!...your like a sis to me and i will love you always and forever!  Last night i went to jordans for her birthday with all of her friends and it was a lot of fun.  i dont get to see her as much as i wish i could but the time will come when we drive and it will make life a hell of a lot easier.   today was a good day.   i had a violin and flute lesson this morning...oh yea i forgot to tell you, i got a new violin, its soo cool!  anyways and then my mom and i went to cape may to lunch and to the beach and to take a walk... then we went to the nursing home to visit my moms cousin jess.  after dinner i went to the boardwalk with dani and laurel, because what else is there to do around here...and believe it or not it was a lot of fun... it was the first weekend that it was packed in ocean city. we were walking back and forth up and down and boarwalk and we were starting to get board, when all of a sudden i saw these two boys walk in the opposite direction that look really really cute.  i grabbed laurel and dani and pulled them into the other direction so that we could follow those kids.  we ended up like practically stalking them and then we got infront of them some how, and then they were like stalking us.  if we walked slow then they would slow down and if we stopped so did then.  well once we got to the rides at Play Land, we were talking about going on the ferris wheel but we werent deffinitely sure that we wanted to so we stopped.  they overheard us say that and they stopped as well and then went into the park, which made us want to go on the rides too so we decided to follow.  we ended up getting in the line for tickets before them and then they went.  after we got our tickets we started walking and i said that i should of said soemthing to them cause i will never see them again...laurel decided to run up to them and she told them that i wanted to go on a ride with them, and then we started talking.  their names were mike and matt and they were from somewhere near the poconos in PA.  we all ended up going on the ferris wheel together and we spend the rest of the night together.  i talked to mike for a long time, and he turned out to be a really nice guy.  we walked all the way down the board walk after the ride and then we all swapped numbers so that we could hang out later this week.  they are staying until next saturday, which is perfect because dani and i are leaving for florida on sunday after they leave.  hopefully they will call tomorrow so that we can chill tomorrow nite....tonite was the first time that we actually had an amazing time at the boards tonight... tomorrows fathers day and i think im gonna have some trouble with that...fathers day is one of those days i have trouble with...i watch everyone spend the day with their fathers and im just there.  its hard.  this year i have steve, hes not really my dad but hes gonna be my step dad in january once he marries my mom. i got him a present for fathers day, but it still not the same and i still dont like the day at all.  at least tomorrow i am going to the LPGA which will sort of keep my mind off it.   well im gonna go to bed cause i have an early morning... love you sammi ps-i hope they call! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Heyyy!... Well, i havent' written in a while only because I have been majorly busy.  Im sure anticipating what the good news is...so I just might as well tell ya...I made cheerleading (thank gosh)! I was so nervous its unbelievable.   Anyways, finals started today, what a pain in the ass, but at least school is practically over.  I leave for florida on the 27th and I can not wait.  Dani's coming, and we are gonna have a blast!   Oh yea, and as of u kno who...hes still with his gf.  It's a waste of my time, I'm moving on cause I dont need the BS.   I gotta run cause i gotta get ready for my soon to be cousins 8th grade graduation....Im sry I cant write more but i will try to later... love you sam
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...well, cheerleading tryouts started today.  I'm really nervous still.  I don't understand.  It was fun though.  We learned the dance, its actually pretty cool, its really fast though but i will get it.  Laurel told me some crazy news today.  She told me about the weekend and what happened to one of our friends after prom.  I thought it was a little stupid of that person but what are ya gonna do, people are dumb sometimes.  Anyways, today at school there was like no one there cause everyone skipped... that was pretty funny.    I actually feel a little bit better then i did, I mean I'm not perfect yet but i am getting there.     School is almost done and I can not wait, but I have a lot to do in the next week its like circuit overload major!  I just have to play it by ear and see what happens, and hopefully this summer will be as awesome and i hope...i gotta run...love ya 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I feel like crap...I don't understand medicine anymore...you would think it would work but it doesn't, I just keep getting sicker...LOL..I can barely hear out of my right ear this sucks!!!! Well, that was a warm hello wasn't it.  Last night Dev, Liz and I went to the midtown concert.  It was pretty awesome, people were crazy.  Anyways, today I'm just staying trying to get better cause cheerleading tryouts are all this week.  Oh speaking of tryouts, I am sooo nervous its crazy.  I don't think i was every this nervous in my entire life.  Oh well, I just gotta do my best and see what happens.   For the past week I couldn't stop thinking about this one person.  I don't think he realizes how much he means to me, and to make it all worse he has a girlfriend.  When I am with him I get this strange feeling, something I never felt before.  I remember the first time I saw him.  I knew that our families were close but I never really saw him..Well to make a long story short...I think when I first saw him it was like love at first sight.  We are kinda friends, we talk once in a while...And hes grauating this year soo that means hes leaving in the fall.  Beause of all this, when someone likes me I'm like kidna mean to them i its like I take all my anger out on them and that's horrible.  I guess it's beacuse I know that deep down inside I think im suppose to be with that person. The whole situation is discombobulated! I have learned that life is a gift.  And the majority of the time it isnt that great but when times are happy and positive we have to remember them.    I gotta run...  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>