<Blog>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *Yawwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwn*  Yes, I am still online.  Blearghhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!  No one to talk to, unless u count my best friend who's off to a party and another friend who's turning down a crush. *Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz*
--Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ah........Here I am again. Sitting here once more, surfing through the net and then I found.....this.  Lol, yeh, another blog. This is my second one, and I'm hoping that this will turn out better compared to my previous one. =) 
 So...there isn't much to tell for now. I'm just like any other ordinary teenager. I am *ahem* currenlty unattached, lolz. Don't have a strong wish to find an "attachment" lol...but who knows? ;) =P Hehe..   
Everything's fine so far..I hope it would continue to be. Since I'm having my holidays now, I've been doing pretty much nothing but sitting at home pondering over the boredom of my life.  $Om3OnE h3Lp M333333!!!! 
Lolz, OK, guess that's enough. I don't have much to say right now, but if there's anything else going on in this girl's life, I'll keep you updated. Ciao! *muakssssssss*
-- Fluffles --
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ahh...I was supposed to go watch 'Harry Potter 3' this morning with two other mates. But then...uhm...some stuff got in the way, so I had to cancel.  I didn't wanna cancel it, but I had no choice. They were disappointed alright...and now I feel as if it's all my fault cos they ended up sitting at home anyway. =/ I told them to go without me, but then they didn't want to. *rolls eyes* Like it's so deadly for them to go out without me. Oh well...I'm probably going out with Lynn tomorrow. Well..I'm not sure yet, but if you're reading this, I'm sorry for cancelling, Connie and Rachel. =p We'll make it some other day, eh? Oh yeh...AND I STILL WANNA WATCH 'TROY'! PS: And it is so NOT cos I just wanna see Brad Pitt and Orlando Bloom! *hides behind couch and peeks out* I swear! --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Arghhhhhhhhh! I just typed out a particularly LOOOOOONG entry just now, but due to "technical problems" it disppeared in just the blink of an eye!!! : 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I. AM. SO. BORED. There's no one to talk to on msn or on IRC right now. =/ Don't feel like hanging on the phone tonight cos I feel like goin to the loo every once in a while and it's making me feel dizzy and my whole body feels as if it's made of lead! =P  I hate these moments....now where's my knight in shining armour to rescue me? 
 Lol, I wish it was that easy. =P Unfortunately, we're living in reality..so, yeh, it sucks.  Or am I the only one feelin this way?--Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lol don't worry. I am not heading towards a deadly nervous breakdown. Am just dealing with uhm...some girlie stuff. Pardon me. Ah....Lynn's coming over for a sleepover tomorrow. Hm....now to plan where to go..... I really wanna watch 'Troy'.... =) But then again no one wants to go with me! Bwahhhhhhhhhh wuakkkkzzz! Pathetic. --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know....sometimes people can surprise you. In many ways. I was once too quiet and shy. I couldn't mix around with people and I get very upset and cry when I see other people coming into my home. I guess it was some kinda of insecurity. It's always been there, planted in me. I didn't know what made me like that, and I still can't understand it all to this very day.   My parents were worried during my first day in kindergarten. They were afraid that I would not stop crying and wanting to go home. I was already 4 then, maybe nearly 5. True, I still had that fear in me when I stepped into my class. There were suddenly so many new faces. It was such a different environment. Miraculously, I survived.   I don't know how but I just changed. I started making friends. True, there were days when I simply refused to go to school, but my mum would always be there to pull me out of bed and force a complete breakfast down my throat then my dad would send me to school. But the problem was that I had stomachaches almost every day. The pain would be so intense sometimes that I just wish I could go home. But I knew I couldn't. Sometimes my stomachaches drive my dad to the edge because he needed to get to work on time and there I was, crying in pain, as precious seconds tick by.   But I have my whole family and all my friends to thank now. I've been through school for a total of 9 years so far. This is my tenth. I went to a girls' primary school for six years and then I moved to a co-ed secondary school when I entered Form 1.  That, I have to admit, was one of the biggest challenges I have ever had to face in my entire life. Almost everyone in the school speaks chinese, and here I am, unable to understand even ONE chinese word! I figured I would just be an outcast during my first few days. Needless to say, my whole first week sucked. It was the most terrible week I have ever gone through. I went home on the verge of tears plus a bad flu on the first day. And the heavy downpour did not help.  I had constant sharp headaches during my first week in high school. There is no way I can ever tell you that my first day in high school was incredible 'cos it just wasn't and I am not about to lie to anyone.  My mum saw that I was unhappy in my new school. She knew that I could not fit in into the environment. But I don't think she knew, even now, that I hated EVERY SECOND I spent in that class then. I kept to myself, for I didn't think that I could befriend anyone there.  Lucky for me, I found my friends. I can't remember how exactly we got to know each other, but I do remember that I offered one of my friends a little chocolate bar and her first word to me was "Thanks.". You couldn't imagine my happiness then. True, we were not exactly friends then, but the bond grew stronger by each day.    I settled comfortably into my class somewhere in the second week. I was starting to have more friends and I could approach someone more easily. I somehow managed to get up and walk through the fog of my sadness. I overcame my fears and faced my challenges. And now I have conquered them.  I missed my friends like crazy when I first moved, but now I realised that somehow it is also a blessing in disguise. I still do keep in contact with my old friends, and believe it or not, we are actually closer now. My best friend now was once someone I barely knew, until I was in Primary 4(fourth grade). I'm now in Form 2 (8th grade) and we're still very close together.   Throughout all these years, I have faced a lot of challenges, I lost some things, I gained more. I admit that I have "lost" a few friends. I never see them any more, but just the memory of us being together once is enough for me.  I have learnt that a true friend would and should stick by you no matter what happens, but you also can't be too dependant on someone else 'cos sometimes you just have to face it yourself. Just try to think positively, even though it's very hard sometimes, but you will have the courage to survive through it.  God made everything happen for a reason, and there is always something good behind it, so no matter what, always try to think on the bright side of things. Appreciate everything and everyone you have now for they might not be here soon. Maybe just a minute later, an hour, a day, a week, a month...who knows?   Learn to forgive and forget and you would lead a happy and colourful life.  --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Love.......what is it?  Many people say that it is a wonderful thing...but how am I supposed to believe that?   When will love appear in my life?  Many people ask these questions, yet how many people can answer this?  Are there rights and wrongs in love?  When shall I know the answer?  What if I fall in love but maybe...just maybe...I couldn't see it?  Or what if I don't WANT to accept it?  Then would I be in denial?  --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ........stupid stomachaches?! Arghhhh, just came home from a dinner outside and now there's a war raging in my stomach! =/ Maybe it was just the sweet and sour chicken rice I ate. Lynn ate it too and now she has a stomachache too. =/ Please don't tell me it was the food we ate. =P Cos that is, like, my favourite dish at that place and now it's upsetting my stomach. Lolz, maybe I should stay off that dish for a while. =( Oh well.. what more can be done? I'll probably end up going to the toilet neways, which, um..I'm actually hoping I will NOT need any time soon. =/ --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was watching Oprah this morning when I saw the American Idol winner last year, Ruben and Clay and Justin. And I'm starting to think that Clay Aiken is cute!  OH. MY. GOD.  Now is that a good or a bad thing? =/  HEEEEEEEEEEELP!!!! --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lynn's coming in a bit. Finally! I was just about to die of boredom. :| --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't exactly know what inspired me to write this, but I wrote it about a week ago. 

*******************************************************************

 FrIeNdS 

Most of the time, people don’t really care about their friends. We always take them for granted, thinking that they would always be there for us when we need them to. But have you ever thought about how your life would be without your friends? Without even one of them beside you? 
Imagine that you’re stranded on a deserted island (regardless of how you were stranded), there is no way out of it for you can’t swim and there isn’t a way to transport you back to the main land. So you are stuck on the island, trying to figure out how to survive. If I were to ask you, if you had the chance to have five things/person you would want to be with you on the island, what/who would you choose? (Assuming that there are no human beings on the island.)
Would you choose to bring your bed? Maybe your clothes? Food? A television? Some people might even tell you, they will definitely want their CD players, CDs and things like that. But would it even cross your mind even ONCE to bring your friend?  
We usually think that friends are not that important. We always think that they will always be there no matter what happens. They will always be there to stand for us. But what if, just if, one of your friends, maybe leaves the country and never returned home. What if one of your friends got involved in an accident, got into a long coma, and then passed away? What if you just return home from work/school one day and you found out that one of your friends is terribly sick and is already slipping in and out of consciousness? These are things that no one would ever want to happen to any of their family or friends. But these are the only things that could open our eyes sometimes. 
Imagine you received a message from your friend one day, asking you to have dinner with him/her, but you decided that you should stay home to finish off your pile of work, but the next thing you know, there is another message from his/her family saying that he/she had a heart attack. Things like this may happen, no matter how much we don’t want it to.
It is painful to lose a friend, whether or not you are close to each other. You might not even have talked to the person for more than ten times, but the instinct to feel the pain and sometimes, guilt, is there when something happens to one of your friends. 
Friends come in unexpected ways sometimes. You might find a friend while waiting for the bus or queuing up to post an envelope or some other ways. Every friend you have us special. Never think of them as a curse or anything bad, but think of them as a blessing; a gift that God chose to give you.
Think back to the situation on the island. Do you think that you’d rather die alone on the island after living there for years or bring a friend there with you where you can live happily together? Do not question the ways of living there, but just compare and ponder about how it’d be like with or without a friend there with you, keeping you company for years.
Would you be able to survive without anyone else there? Even if you could, do you think you would die a happy person?
If you have never shown your appreciation to your friend, tell them now. It doesn’t have to be said in a mushy way, but take some time to listen and comfort them when they are down, lend them a helping hand when they need it, or you can just sit down and have a nice short chat with them. No matter what way of bonding friendship you use, never take your friends for granted for they might be here today, gone tomorrow. 
So if you have not done it, thank your friend for all they have done for you or just for being there and if you have done any wrongdoings, do say sorry sincerely. True friends should and would forgive and forget. 

Written by -->> Crystal aka --Fluffles--



     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You keep running (running for you) I'm still falling (falling for you)
You dont notice, there's something new my hearts discovered
You keep running (keep running) I'll keep crawling (crawling until)
Until you notice
You see friends but I see lovers  --Taken from 'You See Friends, I See Lovers' by Westlife.--
Hm....now doesn't this quote sound familiar? Bet u have that been there done that expression on ur face right now. It's true though, isn't it?   *puts on a dramatic voice* And..OH! Doesn't it hurt so much?!   Lolz, dunno what got into me today. Maybe it's just the cold weather affecting my brain? :p  Hm.....now I'm wondering what to do next......been thinking all day..about how bored I am. Again. And I just received tons of forward mails which I have been receiving over and over again from THE YEAR BEFORE THE LAST!!!! Argh! Hmpf....better go find something to do now. Am just in yet another one of my weird moods. Blame it on PMS.  >:( --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did I mention that I have a piano lesson tomorrow at 8.30 am?! And a theory class at 9.30 am on Friday morning! *groans* --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       SCHOOL=ARGHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!  OK, I'm coming down with another one of those school blues day. Yes, I know I am having my holidays now, but it's ending in four days!!!!!! THAT IS SO UNFAIR! I've barely done anything! :P OK, so sue me, I didn't even touch my homework!! :P And now I'm stuck with a whole TON of it! I have a wood carving project, an art thingy, a history paper to complete and a plastic photoframe to piece together. AND I'm gonna be out tomorrow.  Talk about procrastinating, eh?  :P Oh well...I'm trying to finish off my history thing tonight and the art thingy. I'll work on the piecing together tomorrow. And the wood carving? I seriously don't know. :( Helpppppppppppppppppppppppp!!!!! --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hm.....So..here are the stuff that I've been eyeing and thinking of buying:

 To-GeT lIsT 
1. MiCrOPhOnE ('Cos I hate it when Rach annoys me using her mic and I just couldn't shout back at her using my own voice instead of written words! :p)

2. AnOtHeR pAiR oF eArRiNgS (been eyeing this since like..a decade ago! And I want a cutesy kind this time. :p Oh my..did I just say that?! Lolz!)

3. ThE cAlLiNg CD!

4. AvRiL lAvIgNe CD

5. NeW tUbE oF lIp GlOsS

6. A nIcE dIaRy

7. AtoMiC kItTeN CD

That's all I can think of right now. :P Will add in nething else I want lolz. -_- 

***********************

--Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhhhhh!!!! -_- So....we finally decided to watch Harry Potter 3 tomorrow. :p Oh well..it'll be fun, I suppose. Or rather, I hope.  Hm........am keeping my eyes open for some good purchases tomorrow....that is, if I can convince mum to lend me enough money. :p My last shopping trip washed all of my remaining cash out. -_-  Oh well...I just want something new for myself to just pamper myself a bit this holiday. :p And hopefuly I WILL get something good tomorrow. =)  --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Came home about a couple of hours ago. The movie was good. :) But now I'm all out of cash. :P I just got a pair of earrings just now cos my cash was running low then. Got that great Father's Day card for Dad...and that's about it. :P I need more cash....I was soooo eyeing the necklaces, rings and earrings at the counter! :( Oh well...now if Chinese New Year would just arrive earlier...........:P --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came back from piano class. Well, it was OK. :) Bought the new sight reading book. The bad news is, my practical exam is on the 5th of July (note: Shane's birthday!:D) Oh well...having another theory class tomorrow. Ah, lucky me, I passed up my book to the teacher last week, so there's no extra work to finish off today. :)  But I DO hope that my answers are correct lol.  Anyways, I've done my sticker thingy last night. Strained my fingers lol. Trust me, it's no piece of cake! :P  Ah..will be off to pick Rach and Connie soon. I better go practice my exam pieces now. Byezzzzz!! :) --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Arghh...it's time to go back to school.... AGAIN!  *groans* Oh well...so I won't be online till next Friday night. Wish me all the best for my exam papers! Byeez! Muaks muaksss! --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...tomorrow would mark the beginning of the third week of my new term in school. So far, everything's fine. My exam results were surprisingly well..good enough this time. =) Was a huge relief..  Aiming for uhm..better grades next exams tho. :P I have that interview thingy comin up in somewhere around September. *sigh*   Oh well..neways, I think it's time for some changes in certain areas of my life. Haha, which areas? That we'll know soon!  --Fluffles--
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ah...been a while since I checked in here. :P Well, been busy with schwork, and I'm not allowed to go online on weekdays. *Grrr* Neways, it's been a gud week. :) Well........a lot has been happening up till now.  Having a BM drama on Tuesday (the teacher asked me 2 b d narrator..n I haven't even read the script!), a stupid act from 'Phantom of the Opera' Eesh..I gotta say 'But..but I love u, Christine!' in my part. Talk about corny. Then I have to do some stupid patriotic song stuff for Moral.  EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEK!!! Some1 help meeeee!!! ARGH! Oh well, those r 4 our exam marks. Grrrrrrr...  Things r fine with everyone....ahem..spesh tat someone. Hahahaa...nah I'm not gonna reveal nethin too soon. Let's just say, only time can tell.   I feel as if I'm coming down with a slight fever and a sore throat. Which totally isn't good since I GOTTA SING!!!!!! *sigh* Oh well..I'll keep u updated on all d stuff! --CrYsTaL-- *I figured I should drop d Fluffles..gettin tired of it! :P*
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ........goin bk 2 sch 2moro. -_- Frankly, I'm not really lookin fwd 2 it. Y? I have a ton of work due 2moro!! 1 Eng essay, 1 BM essay, 1 drama script 2 memorise, 1 choral speakin script to REmemorise, a math exercise paper thingy, there's PJ 2moro(I'm usually fine wiv tat most of the times..but jus dun feel like 'PJing'..:P) Then to top it all off, I hav 2 write more books 4 my nilam proj. Have only written 3. :P And we hav 2 bring our BM txtbk 2 moro...which I stopped bringing months ago cos we never never used it.(I tink we did...jus once..yeh) So......been pretty much a lazy week. 2 many stuff goin on n 2 many ppl, 2 little time. Well...actually I cud hav finished my stuff a long time ago, but let's jus stop at "I'm plain lazy". --Crystal--
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from Connie's performance. It was great. =) I'm kinda tired now though. Well, nite nite bloggie. --Crystal--
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah I just got the post as the new secretary in my English Language Society in my school. =) Isn't such huge news, but just thought I would share it. =) Hehehe..I'm one out of the two afternoon session "shrimps" in the committee. The other one is Joanne, my classmate, who is now, also my vice secretary. So....=) That's pretty much the good news so far. I had quite an OK time in school for GERKO this morning. 
 Having Girls' Brigade enrolment on the 24th of this month. Ouch, and we haven't even started practicing our drill!!! Oh well. -_- I guess we'll be fine. As long as we all stay fit and no one passes out during practices and on enrolment day. I hate it when that happens!! Esp in school. :P But then again, lucky me, I'm never gonna be one of those RC ppl who have to stand and help anyone who faints or feel sick during assemblies. :P  Connie was steaming mad yesterday when I saw her in school cos she said the teacher (RC teacher) forced her to come for the RC exam. But she had to go for ballet practice for tonight's performance from 8 or 10 (somewhere there) to 1 pm, then she was asked to come to school from 2 to 3 for her RC exam, then she had to go back home and eat and take her bath then go to the city hall (uh...or so I think) to get ready for her performance before 5. I have to say that's a really tight schedule. But she decided to not go for the RC exam, and she said she is finally quitting RC. She's been talking about quitting lately, but she never got around to really doing it. But I guess it's final now. :P Neways, Chia Hsin or should I say, RACHEL...and I are going to Connie's performance tonight. :) Rach's picking me up at 6.30 pm. It's 6 now. Guess I better go get ready. :) See ya bloggie!  --Crystal--
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, like the title of today's entry read, my Thursday sucked. A lot. First I got up at a quarter to 8, then I rushed to piano class n arrived at cun-cun 8.30. Phew, teacher wasn't there yet. So I did my scales warming up n all those stuff, then lesson went on quite..er, not so well. My fingers jus wouldn't listen to what my brain was interpreting, so I ended up slipping here n there in my exam pieces. N that is so NOT gud esp. when my exam is only like...2 weeks away?! -_- Neways, I thot my bad luck wud end after piano class. But nooo...teacher made me stay extra 5 mins to copy down the notes. Fine..so I went downstairs to tell Mum cos she reached there at 9.15 tis morning. (Ouch, she must hav caught my horrible singing!!!!!!!!! ARHHHHHHH!!!!) Neways, I stubbed my toe so hard while walking up d stairs. God, it was so embarrassing. Luckily only my teacher was there, but my toe hurt quite a lot, til noon! =P Grrrrr! 
 So I went to sch, n I had to duty set up the PA system. But no one even did nethin b4 12.30!! Which was when the whistle was blown for the students to line up! So the whole process was a rush, but we pulled it off. Guess those grueling lessons Jason taught me paid off. =p It should neways, considerin wat he put me thru! Lolz. Then the whole schling time was like hell. Almost fell asleep in class. And Connie's 'friend' kept on stalking us like mad. I swear he's got nth better to do, poor guy. Then recess. I went to blok 3 to duty. There were ppl there..so I jus walked around then sat in the hall with Connie. OK, so recess was well...as usual. Boring. Then, class photo takin. Ai si!!!! Haiyoh, really no mood to take photo then la man! =p But wat to do. -_- Got that over n done with. N then almost fell asleep in Geo class again. Haiyahhhh!! How to keep awake?! So cold n i cud barely hear the teacher's voice! =P But surprisingly the boys were kinda quiet today. Maybe it was the rain. Haha... 
Well, turned out that I jus got a participation level in my Science New South Wales University exam. N well my cert wasn't given out during assembly. They only gave out the distinction and credits. That is like so......eeh! I told Mum they were SO SI AI BIN! N that IS so true. Soli lor..but it's true. I thot it was kinda unfair of them to do that, cos I know there r a few other ppl hu got participation too. Well, at least we tried. Don't we even get credit for that? THAT SUCKS! It pissed me off alright. OK, I think I've done enough ranting for tonite. 
 Well, at least there's no sch tomoro, cos the teachers r havin sum sorta lecture thingy...watever. Mum's goin. Bleh, so....I can't go out! I was planning to. But, yeh, watever. No mood to write liao la. Later maybe I will. K? Cya. Gnite, sweet dreams, bloggie. --Crystal@Piggie--
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm pissed right now. Very.   
 My day started off fine, and I thought maybe today would be a much better day than yesterday. Well, to be honest, it went fine. Till......a few minutes ago.  
 What happened? I honestly don't know. I just got frustrated at Cheng for something he said and maybe something he didn't say. 
 I know it's dumb and all....but I don't know. I just said I've got nothing to say and he said the same then I just logged off. I logged back in after a couple of minutes, and true enough, he went off just like he said. That was the last straw for me. 
 Are all guys just dense or stupid or what?! God, they're so hard to trust!!!  
 -- Crystal @ Piggie --  

     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Nyeh....so bored la!!!!!!!!!!!!! Eeh....Mum's comin home at 4.30 or so I guess. So....guess I shud get some reading n revising done. Ew. -- Crystal @ Piggie -- 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Eh....I see that the blog settings hav changed....or is it jus me? Hahaha...let's see how this works now. =P --Crystal @ Piggie --  
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's Debbie's birthday today. Just sent her an ecard wishing her happy birthday. =) Neways, today has been a normal day....nothing much went on. =P I dunno what to write now, lolz. I'll write in soon. Oh, yeah, Cheng and I cleared the air and things are fine between us now. =) Hehe..-- Crystal @ Piggie -- 

     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Someone's burning....one of our neighbours. Haiyah, made me go downstairs just to close all d windows. So mahuan.. :P Neways, tat's all I gotta complain for now, lolz. Mum and Dad r out..somewhere and my good ol sis......is also somewhere. But I dunno where. I'm talkin crap.  -- Crystal @ Piggie --   

     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm thinkin of changing the colours of the page a bit. It's gettin kinda old to my eyes now. Oh well....guess I'll see what I can do next week! Nite sweet dreams!

&nbsp;
xx Crystal xx

     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Connie just told me that she's now officially with&nbsp;Ting *--ahem--*. I still can't really register that....not yet anyway. It's starting to sink in.... It came as a suprise to&nbsp;me cos even though I did expect this to happen one day, I certainly did not expect it to happen now. =P Oh well...let's just hope this will be a good change. =)  
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  xx Crystal xx  

     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        And againnnnn.......................will be back in school tomorrow. This sucks. =P   
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  -- Crystal --  

     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         My     piano exam is on 30/7, which is next Friday. I am so freaked out!! =/ I went for an extra class just now and well...I guess my pieces are fine now. =) But that still doesn't make me less freaked out. Haha....oh, well, I guess all exams make you nervous eh? =P Or at least make ME nervous.      &nbsp;
   -- Crystal --   
 
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH....... now we "veterans" can finally heave a hugeeee sigh of relief.    
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  The new school prefects were already interviewed and selected yesterday. So now we have a whole new prefectorial board. Now it's hello to the newbies and goodbye to us oldies. Haha....well, in a way, I am quite relieved, but on the other hand, I am also going to hold even a bigger responsibility. I gotta teach the new prefects how to set up the PA system (although I suspect that most of the jobs would be handed over to Eric *muahahaha*).  
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  About 20-25 old prefects were chosen to be kept on service. And I am one of them. *Surprise, surprise, I am soo modest...not. Hahaha* Anyway, we were picked cos they need a few prefects to teach the shrimps how to get their work done. Haha...OK, so maybe I shouldn't call them "shrimps". Anyway, they will be starting to go on duties by next Monday and I am soooo looking forward to seeing them on their first ever duty. *I am so gonna look out for those nervous/freaked out and unsure faces..Muahahahahaha!!*   
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  I remember, I asked my group leader (AJK), "Is this Block 7?" Hahaha...that is like so..DUH! It was so obvious that I was at Block 7 but I don't know what came over me and I just blurted that out in front of him. It's so stupid and embarrassing when I think back now. =P Hahaha... I hope he's forgotten about that now. I don't want anyone to remember it. =P  
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  And I remember when there was a lecture for the prefects and I just started to elarn how to set up the PA system. Jason appeared and asked me to help him set up the PA system in the AVA room for the lecture and I was just blundering and stumbling all over myself like a fool. Haha...it was so damn humiliating!! He made me carry the amplifier and when I accidentally pulled it too hard, he asked me, "Why are you so rough?" Hahaha...that is one line I won't ever forget. I was like, "OH MY GODDDDDDD!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!"  
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  But I'm thankful for all that now. =) I hope my service was good. Lolz. And I guess I'll be retiring in maybe a couple of months. And once again, AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!  
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  -- Crystal --  

     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I dunno why but I just feel so bummed out right now. =( I was fine all through the day... had my theory class at 9.30 am, then I went over to the exam room at 10.30 am. I went in at 11.05 am or so and had my practical exam. My scales, arrpeggios, broken chords, chromatic scales, pieces and sight reading were good. (She complimented me on the sight reading..yeah!)   
    &nbsp;
  But aural wasn't too good *ouch* as usual, it's the singing stuff...my "listening to the piece played" stuff was fine *forgot what they're called*. =) I only got stuck at the "What is the italian term for 'playful'?" Uh-oh. Lol, well, I guess my koko's virtual good luck kiss worked. Haha.... maybe I should get him to grant a few lil wishes. Haha..but well, as u know me, they won't be so "little". Haha..well, school was fine. Got home, still felt good. But I dunno... guess I'm just tired or something...   
    &nbsp;
    &nbsp;
  -- Crystal --  

     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I am so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so BORED!    
  
  
 -- Crystal -- 

     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ah... I'm kinda sleepy now. Hehe... actually I'm supposed to be typing up my Girls' Brigade achievement questions, but well... let's just say I took a break. Haha.. neways, my day was fine. It was just a normal day. =)  

 I dunno if I've mentioned this before *am too lazy to check or think back-lol*. My class and another class is going to the stadium this Friday noon for the ASEAN Games closing ceremony. A lot of people seem to be asking me about the parade thingy though... and I have no idea. =P Haha... *yawwwwwn*  

 Guess I'm really sleepy lol. =P See ya, bloggie. Nite. 

 -- Crystal -- 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ahhhhh... I got a kitten yesterday evening from Auntie Annie, Mum's friend. I've been wanting one since....... years ago. Hahaha... I dunno how but Mum agreed to let me get one. I was so over the moon. Lolz.  
  
   I...uh... am still not so sure if it's a male or a female. =P It's a white siamese kitten with blue eyes. It looks so adorable! =) Lol that is how hyper I am. I wanted to bring it in my room but Mum said we shud just leave it in it's basket in the kitchen .   

  -- Crystal --  

     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Mum's phone went nuts the other day.... We brought it to the shop last nite and Mum said they would get me my own phone as my bday pressie. Yay! I picked a Nokia 3100. I'm gonna use Mum's SIM card and she'll get a new one. =) Hehehe... I'm still experimenting with it though. Am not too sure of a few stuff.  

 -- Crystal -- 

     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Arghhhhhhhhhhh!!   We're havin our exams now. =P Aduhs..  Had BM Paper II jus now. Was praying for the synopsis ques to appear..and yeh, my wish was granted. But OMGGGG!!! The 1st ques was a killer. 5 choices, wif practically no possible gud essay. Well, some ppl mite hav written greeaaaaaaaat essays tho... haha... Neways, I changed my ques in the middle while writing the 1st ques I picked, which was the letter thingy... but I had a feeling that I wrote the addresses in the wrong order, so I changed it to another topic on road accidents.. eugh. Haha.. ya it's a 'karangan fakta' n I hate that kind. But well.. I had not too many choices...so.. yeh, I'll keep my fingers crossed. =)   
    
  -- Crystal --  

     
    
</post>


</Blog>