<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well this is going to be my last one for sure...it's sorta starting to kick in now. i'm starting to really realise that i will infact be away from emily for a long time...it's gonna be tough if i could barely even handle it for 5 days. well i was informed one time a long time ago that length of time can be perceived differently on how much you are enjoying the time. the more fun you have, the faster time goes...so i guess i'd better have fun unless i want time to go by really slowly and then feel like shit...meh i guess there are some lyrics that can sum up what i feel: I know i'll see you again, whether far or soon. but i need you to know. that i care, and i miss you I miss you, Incubus Everytime i tried to tell you the words just came out wrong, so i'll have to say i love you in a song. I'll have to say i love you in a song, Jim Croce Two weeks without my lover. i'm floating in the boat alone. floating down a river called emotion Aqueous Transmission, Incubus"  So yeah that was about it...well i'm gonna miss my friends ,my blog but most of all emily. i truly believe that what we have can never be undone...just like a double knot in my shoes...ha ha ha emily will get it. (8) Goodbye fairwell...uhh dun dun dun dun crapiforgotthewoooooooooorrrdddssssA! Sam 

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well blog. you've been good to me. you've listened to my constant bickering and whining about...this and that. you know the old stuff. but i'm sure if you had the ability to mute me you would, but guess what? YOU DON'T!! ahh ha ha ha MY FACIST PARTY RULES THIS BLOG WITH AN IRON FIST! MUAH HA HA HA!!! anyways getting off a huge acid trip...last night i hung out with ninja and evan...we stayed up until about 6:30...saw the sun come up...made me reflect on things...you know...just what's going on with me now. but in the end it wasn't that smart of an idea i mean...i had to get picked up at 8:30 for a trumpet practice...meh. as usual I get very little sleep but for some reason i do shitloads better than i do when i get good sleep...hmm can we say negative influence? yeah it went well...except that i won't get a lesson until september...meh.   So yeah...this is probably going to be my last post until july 24th...it seems like so far away, but i'm hoping it will go faster. it's sorta weird though saying goodbye to people you won't see for a month...but it's sorta like, you have to do it so you might as well do it how you want to.  Well i'm gonna sign off now. i'm eating a hotdog with spices and such everywhere...and i'm gonna watch Love Actually...hmm i've noticed i like watching love films now...i guess that's cool..i mean for emily's sake. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well ladies and you men who are gentle...(otherwise known as gentlemen)i have done it...but i can't say that it was me who started...infact i don't believe i did...but i've now talked about it with emily...and frig does it ever feel good. the whole night started out with emily actually getting to my house first. tamsen and the rest of them, me and emily have decided, were an hour late intentionally. so we hung out with tamsen lisa and hannah for a while then they had to go because " we have to be back at hannah's house soon". *sigh* could you be anymore obvious? yeah then they left...then we left when they were still on the street...he he he getting right down to business...then we walk over to a park and we were swinging..on...can you guess? that's right the swings. and then we were talking to eachother for a while and then we started hinting about what we should've talked about...then she said "so do you wanna talk about it" i said "YES". ha ha ha i liked it though. i mean we talked for like 30 minutes about us and how everyone acted with us a lot...and other things and such...i don't think i should go into full detail for privacy purposes. then we walked home. and on the way to my house on Alma her mom drove by and onto the wrong street...i felt bad because i thought we wouldn't actually be able to say goodbye to eachother...then emily did the greatest thing...she said "ohh can you meet us at his house in like 3 minutes?" effing gold emily! effing gold! so we walked around the long way...and her mom was waiting at the curb and before she started to poke me and so i took her hand and we held hands for when we walked then when we saw her mother we went behind the bush and we hugged for a while...and damn i was in heaven. i mean i just wanted to stay there the entire time then we went around the corner...said goodbye and that was it...and as of like 11:45 me and emily have been talking and trading pictures...and it's soo awesome. i also got her adress so that when i'm gone i can send her snail mail...but i don't think she knew at the time...that i'm doing it every day! yar har har har. now this is sam's post scriptum but i've been informed that i should only send one a week. and i shall abide but you can't always play by the rules...yeah the hug was awesome though...i can still smell her...*sigh* i'm in love! Sam 

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well i've slept on it...and i am now less pissed off at myself for what i didn't do. and more happy for what were able to do! i mean we even hinted about what we were talking about. and everyone else with us was really obvious that they were trying to set something up "ok we're gonna play sardines, but we're playing in pairs. now sam and emily have to hide and we'll go look for them. but you have to be in the forest!" *sigh* nice try guys. ( i might have already said this) and when we were on the blanket i just wanted to lie down next to her and hold her hand... but no. then when i was leaving i felt like i had to do something but i couldn;'t do it at the door (lest my dad see us) so i said "thanks for a great time" and i hugged her...but ohh i wanted to hold on forever.  and enough with that...i can't believe it but it was practically my birthday party...they had decorations and everything...and who can forget the wild wild presents!. let's see there's tattoo's. aphrodesia smelling incense, a nurse barbie doll...that doubles as the chick with the eyepatch from kill bill...men's toite underwear...lady's frilly underwear. a cheesy romance book "you, my little fox, will be my mistress". 3 t-shirts, pickle party, eager beaver get's the job done, and the american eagle one that emily got me. and all the great cards!. especially tamsen's "well sam it's been fifteen years and we're still together. Love, Yer Cratch  Sam 

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well i will never forgive myself for this...i think i sound a little bit freakish right now. *sigh* i find it really strange because i had imagined to myself about how it would happen. i sorta figured that it would've happened when we were playing manhunt...and it was dark out and blah. but no...sam's and idiot and it never even took place. when we were lying down on a blanket outside on the grass i wanted to lie down next to her..and maybe hold her hand but it was sorta strange when everyone else was there so it nevere happened...i even had the perfect conditions. we were alone, sitting on her couch in her basement...and yet nothing...can i sleep...."NO!!"  ahh well i'll have to go and sleep in the male tight breifs thingy i got from the gang...or maybe the women's underwear hmmm...i wanna go into a coma right now and sleep for a while...BLAH! Regretfully yours Sam 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i am such a fucking MORON! This entire night i was planning on doing it!...but no...what does sam do? he pussies out! there were a couple times though when we just looked at eachother and we knew exactly what eachother was thinking. the worst part though was when we were ALONE! i still couldn't do it...although there were some sorta samples of what could've been said...but still. when i had to leave i had my bag o prezzies in my hand, and i was about to walk up the stair...and i froze...i was so close to saying it. I even started to laugh about it a couple of times. but still..FAAACK! leading up to tonight was just so strange because i was so sure that i could do it. but when it came to us being alone which is how i waited for it to be, i still couldn't do it. wtf mate? so now i'm sad...i'm going to go and sob. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well tonight is the night (i hope). and then...all will be good, exams over and hopefully i will come back to my house tonight with a little something extra: "Someone's" heart. as the title says...i am nervous+excited which = NERVCITED! ohh yeah i forgot...today also happens to be my birthday. so i guess this is my birthday present to myself. i don't think i can ask for much more than that. ha ha ha today is actually the first year where ANYBODY at school has remembered my birthday. everyone last year just kept on going...but then again if i really wanted them to know i would've kept my msn name as a countdown for it...but really a birthday isn't that special. all it is is marking the anniversary you pushed out of your mother's vagina kicking and screaming, covered in placenta and amniotic fluids...not a normal thing that you might celebrate. anyways i'm gonna go and eat din din...he he he din din..yeah and then...i'm going to the party...oh yeah...then we're gonna...uhh do stuff...yeah! Sam 

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   last night i figured that i might stay in...you know being that i had been up since 6:00 that morning, travelled for 9 hours in a car that i couldn't sleep in. but nonetheless at 12:00 my dad took me to evan and ninja's place (ask me about how he got THAT nickname) and stayed up until 4:00...woke up at 9:00. i'm a bit of a tard in that way. meh, still fun.. today i WILL study...i will study...I WILL STUDY!!! ok maybe not but just a bit...i mean i have to why not? i have the time...i can do it! and then i still have to have a trumpet lesson tonight because i missed mine on saturday morning, and i have a recital on thursday so i guess i might want another recital.  grr last night evan's sister wakes up and she friggin walk out in her underwear. i just ignored her though...i sorta feel like a tard just having said that. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The title says it all. Went down to worcester massachucetts (ooo i spelled it right) for the weekend to see my cousins for their barmitzvah's. i have now been to 4 barmitzvah's in my life time and in yiddish i can even say (unwillingly though just by repitition) blessed is the lord our god, creator of the universe...*sigh* i can't believe i just said that but yeah! ha ha i can speak a bit of hebrew! it was good to see them...although now i do really realise how much i love being canadian. 1: Canadians don't have as much fat people at every single friggin fast food restaurant. 2: Canadians actually have senses of humour and will be nice to you on the street, even for however inane the reason is that you're talking to them. and 3: It doesn't take a terrorist attack killing 2500 people to make them patriotic. but yeah...it was alright...except that when we started to drive away from guelph i could feel the "essence" of emily leaving me... and when i was sick of hearing god this and god that i would think up good ways to start off talking to her on tuesday and i have now picked it...but i'm still wondering if i have to be drunk to get the nerve to do it...no i wouldn't get drunk before doing something as important as that. The worst part about this though is that i couldn't sleep in all the hours driving and trying to sleep in a hotel room. and so now i'm friggin tired, i've had a total of 8 hours of sleep in the past 2 night...i'm tired and tomorrow i think i might study for the science exam...only maybe...but ooh ooh ooh tuesday is the day...(did i already talk about this?) i'm GOING to do this...i have to. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well two exams are down, 1 to go. the exam for geography was an absolute joke. i didn't study at all for it and i was done like 50 minutes early...wtf mate? the french exam wasn't as hard as i thought it might be, but then again i've been studying all week for it. so i'm hoping i do well... the next up is the science exam  funny thing is that the science exam is on my birthday. wow what a birthday present...meh i'm giving myself one later that night. tuesday night there's a bunch of us getting together for a "post exam party" which is the perfect oppurtunity for me to do what i have to do before leaving for an entire friggin month...can you imagine?  i was reading her blog today and it made me feel sad...i mean i never even think of falling for other girls right now. but she seems to be worried about it. i guess it's normal. infact she was the one who even told me a while back that "sam, you could get any girl in the school" and i was really stressed out because of it...i mean what do you say to something like that. i always thought of myself as repulsive to other girls but now...i mean this is changing my entire outlook on how i do things. and sorta going back to the whole issue here...she can be the worried one i guess thinking that there are better girls out there than her...but in essence there aren't. she's the one i want to be with and she is the one i hope to be with. no strings attached and absolutely no fucking cheating...gahh i can't even see myself doing that! anyways sam has to go to the U.S tomorrow. i'm afraid that it might be like another quebec trip where i'll be depressed travelling there...meh i'll make up for it on tuesday.  See ya lata BYE! Sam 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   No more pencil's no more books. no more teachers dirty looks...SCHOOL'S OUT FOR THE SUMMER.....SCHOOLS OUT FOR FOREVER!!!  ahhh great words put beautifully into context by my...uhh home dogg Alice Cooper...too bad he scares me So incase you're retarded and can't understand simple english...school is out and i'm happy. but i still have exams...two of which are tomorrow...well like i say...meh...i never really feel stressed out...or i might but i won't let you know about it. today was awesome though. everyone had cameras and so there was flashing everywhere (no not like in bourbon st in New Orleans)and so it was a lot of their intent to get me and emily in a photo together...and we had some really nice ones...then like 5 girls would be like "AWWWW" it was a bit embarassing. but then there was one with emily twisting my nipples and me in agony...they we're quite funny. ha ha, then tamsen and i skipped off the afternoon and hung out with maddy at my house...then next period we picked up some people and walked to ross...i think i need to start rethinking when we plan to go there...i mean i'm always tired afterwards, but this time i have to stay up and study. so i need to get a studying and work up the energy to study...i dunno but i feel a half all nighter comin on. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ice cream sandwiches rule! bla bla bla today was normal....done drama now....during play today i hit my knee on a table....it hurt...blah blah blah schwiggity schwa. Tamsen is getting really uppity about doing her little song for matt...it's quite cute."she" and i didn't talk all that much today...i don't remember if i saw her in the morning...at lunch i don't know why we didn't talk. and after school she was busy singing or something at the top of her lungs...it was funny. the only problem is that whenever she leaves to catch the bus it seems too early and it makes me swallow my heart when she leaves...meh busses are bitches. hanyways...i guess my blogs are getting shorter and shorter...tis strange. i can't believe i'm watching the federal election debate...these guys are talking out of their asses and they're like children when they interrupt eachother. gahh i'm reading her blog right now...and there's something about someone being a little bit too flirty with me...i'm trying to figure out which person that is. but i think i have an idea. i feel really bad that she feels that way about whoever it is...but i guess it's just my friendly nature. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Wow...sam does french interview project in 40 minutes, with notable help from jade. what does he get you ask...he'll tell you 75% yeehaw.  Today was pretty awesome getting to hang out with Tamsen, Lise and Benita who were intentionally late for geo. so we hung out in the cafe laughed and drew pictures of penises! ha ha ha but we won't say of whom. i am now informed that we are having an end of exam party at emily's house on the 22nd..hmm i said. the 22nd is also my birthday! what a coincidence...but i have a sneaking suspicion that they already knew that. i don't care...i'm actually flattered that i have friends who know when my birthday last year. no one last year remembered my birthday...ah fuck it.  anyways i've left this blog on for so long and haven't worked on it so i guess i'm done....seeyalatabye! Sam 

						
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well 4 days until exams start marks the start of my studying...i guess that even now it's sorta late to be starting, meh. Dan left this afternoon. it was quite nice to see him even if it were for just a bit  on saturday i was planning on maybe hanging out with some people and seeing a movie. so i figured "alright hanging out!" then i heard tamsen say "ohh we could get "her" to come" and i was even happier even though i would've had to leave my brother. but then it turns out that she had to babysit and whatev....but yeah that was my weekend in a nutshell... Sam 

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well my brother is back tonight...he's growing a moustache which is a bit greasy but he's still Dan. and his girlfriend is quite the hot number...he he he i saw his tat...it's pretty cool.so that's basically it...and whateva..  And now i believe because she has already said it that i might as well do it...even though it's pretty damn obvious by these entry's that yes me and emily i believe...are in love...and i'm not sure that i've felt this way about anyone...but she's brought out a side within me that i myself have never even seen. and hopefully we can sit down to actually talk about this more thoroughly but yes...now all of your little talking and giggling at us is over...but feel free to do it some more if you'd like to. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well the title...doesn't actually mean that there's a spy or whatever. But it seems that everyone actually no not everyone..but some people know about me and my..uhh mate may i say?  and i'm not mad or anything about it but i was just wondering...are we that transparent that they can tell? hmm maybe i need to work on my subtility. but i'm thinking now...i should be less secretive about it if everyone knows. i mean what's the harm that'll be done of it if everyone already knows. i mean even writing this blog makes it a bit obvious, but hey...fuck it. *sigh* but i know what i have to do. i need to talk to her...and i shall very soon...infact i mean the next time we can be together alone.but it had better be before i'm gone for an entire month...that's something that i now wish i hadn't really done now. because then i could've spent more time around. but i guess i had no idea about the recent events...so i guess you chew what you've got, then maybe you can go up for seconds. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   mmm Ice Cream Sandwiches are my new crack! extremely addictive but in short supply. i'll go get another.  another uneventful day Emily is sick during morning...comes in afternoon...i wish i had that sort of freedom. Stay in at lunch to work on drama skit...peter is a no show...time wasted which could've been spent productively with someone else. CELP metting tonight...mother getting pissy saying that if i don't have an 80 average i don't go...that makes me pissed off! Dan is home for the weekend tomorrow...awesome..can't wait to see him...shiver thinking about him and his girlfriend in the same bed next to my room...(shudder) short post...maybe bigger one tonight. Sam    

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's HAT! once again. wow today was stinky but interesting. since yesterday i've had to stay in the stupid resource room for 4th period geography because of stupid mr eccles. and the kids inside this place are absolutely retarded! i infact have never seen someone who has taken a basic grade 9 science course who doesn't even know the order of the planets or which ones are terrestrial or gas giants? wtf mate!?! so what does sam do. i'll tell you. he listen's to louie armstrong and various classical pieces, does his science homework and works on theory, that's what he does. extremely uneventful other than that.  except for after school today. here i am hanging around with the usual group after school. and long behold my beloved is there as well...and i get a comic clipping out of it. she said "it reminded me of you" or something like that i've sort of forgot. but the comic had a girl and a guy at a restaurant and the man said "Oh Tina...i knew that from the moment i saw you i wanted to spend the rest of my weekends with you." i thought it was amazing. although i do feel bad about here having to sort of make the first move. throughout the day i saw her and she seemed very reclusive and i thought that maybe i had done something to annoy here. but now looking back at it i'm thinking that it might have been nervousness about it...because i saw her and another girl talking before she gave it to me and by the way they were talking i knew something was making her nervous...wow the last sentence i wrote i actually put in her name just by instinct. damn. i'm glad i caught that one...hmm i guess i have the same nervousness that she does...ahh deary me. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well...i guess i must've totally forgot about an important even which would take an important someone away for a long time today. i'm like sitting infront of my computer talking to tamsen and waiting for her to come online...wow i'm such a creep. i hope she wins something tonight...she's good at what she does. hmm this was short. i guess i just make a "blog" entry everytime i miss her...there will proabably be another entry tonight...and maybe in the middle of the night too...and tomorrow morning, and at lunch and after school... Sam 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Shit, is it ever HAT outside. 32 without the humidity and like 40 with it.  sorry for missing a day. my compy's internet has been screwing up soo much. so i can't even get on msn or update my beloved..."blog". yeah, monday sucked. i barely saw "someone" at all just in the morning. it sorta felt like something was missing. and today was almost the same. once in the morning and once at lunch, almost no dialgoue. then after school today someone told me that she was looking for me so i figured that we might talk or something. so i go to the basment floor, and nothing! it sucks quite large testicles. but i guess that that shows we're so much alike. i don't know how any of this is going to work...but don't get me wrong it's not that i don't like her or anything, i LOVE her infact it's just being comfortable enough to say it to her face that's the hard part (sigh) we'll come around to it. i thought we might be able to hang out on the weekend, but then i rememebered that my brother has 48 hours of freedom and is coming to see me!!! i can't wait! 6 months without seeing him sucks so much. mmm we'll uhh stay up real late and play video games...just like old times. ha ha ha i heard he's getting my sisters old room which is right next to mine. i asked him how he was going to manage this when he and marie his girlfriend were going to pull this off, he said that he's going to pull the bed out from the wall so it doesn't squeak. what a guy. i feel sorta weird though. i'm the only one of my siblings who isn't going out with someone...i figured we're all in love (except for maybe dan, he might be in lust) but i'm just the one of us who is the least confident about these things...i mean looking at my brother. he's gone out with tons of girls. and my sister has had quite a few boyfriends but me...i had like one girlfriend and it wasn't anything special, infact looking back on it it was retarded. but why do i have to suck so much? well i guess one of us must "Carpe Diem" or seize the day. but who will and how? Sam 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well i can probably say that i have suffered one of the first injuries caused by love. Today around 12:00pm i was walking into my basement thinking about my special someone, when all of a sudden i spaced out, tripped down the stairs, tumbled to the bottom landed on my arm, but did nothing. I sat there motionless, my mind still hooked on her. my arm is a bit bruised but it'll be fine. so just a warning to you love birds out there...do not walk down stairs, use a motor vehicle or operate heavy machinery under the influence of love. *sigh* but now as i have just recently been informed...i cannot get together with this person over the next weekend. my brother is visiting from belleville. and don't get me wrong i really want to see him. but damn why do i have to be in love on the weekend that he comes down? so that's one less weekend that i get to see the woman of my dreams before i leave for an entire friggin month. this whole thing now has made me not want to go now. maybe i'll escape in the middle of the night and hithchike all the way to guelph then show up on her door. i wish i could...but i've devised an easier plan that doesn't involve me giving head to truck drivers for a ride (eww). i've figured that i could get a letter for each day that i'm away and write to her every day. and for the days that i'm in the wilderness i keep writing them and send them out all at once. that is my new goal for this summer. that and to be able to say what i want to her. Sam 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   why does it feel like a just bathed with poison ivy? i need one of those plastic hands on a stick...it would be like the finglonger. then i could do everything from a distance of 5 metres...(sigh) one can dream though. My night last night wasn't as boring as it could have been. I finally got the chance to rent scarface, because every weekend i got to the blockbuster to find that movie...i knew exactly where it was. but every time i go there it's out...HA HA not today my confidant's. yeah, good ol Tony Montana, that guy is messed up...every time he see's his sister with a guy the same music comes on and it goes to a closeup of his eyes. it's like wee ooo wee ooo. then to lengthen the amount of time i would stay up until, i rented not one but TWO video games...just to keep me up for precious extra hours.   well, she's left for the athletic banquet. ha ha if only i hadn't told off what's her name genelle in like the last two days of the volleyball teams existence i would've been there...meh cause and effect "i drink too much wine, i must take a piss" that's from the second matrix...damn i have to stop remembering stupid little things like that. but yeah she will be missed over the internet. hmm...next weekend maybe...ooo imagine if we got together again. it could be quite the event. and imagine atleast one of us doesn't get too scare to say something...and you know...jeez you'd have to wonder. what would we do next or like would it change the way we talk to eachother? i sure as hell hope not. i think we're perfect right now...hanyways...i have to go to my sister's apartment, maybe alex will be there too...awesome!  Sam 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   damn this harry potter craze. that kid cannot act. gahh and his friggin smile! it looks like someone is pulling on strings attached to the corners of his mouth but his teeth stay in the same place. damn that kid...and supposedly the one chick who plays hermione has no experience. she was like in 3 school plays and that's it...hmm it might explain a hell of a lot. and i feel really sorry for actors like alan rickman, sir ian mackellan who have to play in such shit of a movie where the only reason that they're making more of them is because children are manipulated so easily and get obsessed on a book and buy everything about it (ie. mary kate and ashely olsen). ha ha watching CNN right now makes me laugh. George Bush is making a speech and you can hear in the backround a person reading him the speach! ha ha ha stupid illiterate bastard. ahh...talking with someone right now...and i guess subliminal messages are the thing. why am i such a cryptic bastard right now...i should just come out right now and say it...yes yes yes...no i just lost it Sam   

						
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   wow, did you know that even diet iced tea fills the tummy...and now about last night. i feel a little bit easier than i was still pe'od but i guess that sleep is fine. i had a trumpet lesson this morning...it was pretty good. practiced 2 pieces i'm playing for a recital later this month. damn i hate the copyrights on music. but yeah i'm in waterloo as of now and i will be until sunday evening. nothing to do but something so i should find out how to do that. tonight should be just as boring as well. i wish i was with someone else so i could feel like i go back intime and do something that i really should have. but as my motto says "ah fuck it". but it's not like i don't care. infact i care more than you might imagine. it's just that that is in the past and i've gotta figure out how to do it next time. maybe i should have like a script on what i should say, it might work. ooo "the longest day" on at 8pm on channel 45...awesome...john wayne rules. wow, i'm boring and bored hey i've got an idea i'll go back to sleep and ponder about last night. dammit i can't believe i didn't do anything. and i was so ancy waiting for that night as well. ha ha ha just thinking about last night. my brother's friend drives to my house in his friends car. Joe and i are talking infront of the other two there. supposedly joe's moved in with kovac and they're having a party that night. everyone's invited...joe's a good guy but i was nervous about him being there when someone else was there too. anyways this is like what my 3 post..awesome this stuff is sorta cool Sam 

						
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i know...i tried to get off...but i couldn't do it...i mean i spent 2 hours alone with someone that i care about so much and the funny thing or maybe even the horrible thing is that we both can't talk about anything we want to when we're alone but we can have a messenger do it for us...what the fuck is so wrong with me? like am i physically incapable of doing this...i want to spend the rest of my life with this person and eventually marry them but what the shit. why am i stuck at what's supposed to be the easy part.  maybe someday i won't be such a pussy and i might be able to stand face to face with them and tell them how i truly feel. and maybe she'll feel the same way and all will be well. and all of the people who i might have talked to about this subject has asked me "what are you afraid of? you won't get rejected" and i've thought about it...i'm not afraid of rejection infact i don't know what i'm afraid of...it's something but AHHH FUCK I WANT TO JUMP OFF MY ROOF AND FALL ASLEEP IN MID AIR!!! or i need to sleep...but i don't know if i can sleep after this turn of events...and i know i said that i would be in bed at my first post but ahh i dunno...maybe i'll make another post...nah i'm tired and sad...no joke i'm in tears about this....STOP LAUGHING!  

						
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...tonight people came over...i guess because this is my first post i'll keep things totally anonymous...3 people at my house 1 guy, 2 girl. 1 girl best friend, other girl Unbelievable infact, marriage unbelievable and most people who know me know that i'm not exactly a person who talks histerically like this or in such a deep sort of way but just the events of the past 2 hours (even though i didn't realize it at the time) were absolutely amazing...and now writing this i feel like such a tool...i mean i never really recognised any signs or some of that stuff. but thinking about this and reading a certain journal i never figured what was going on or what i should've done i now wish like hell that i could go back in time and just change what i did or do something that i didn't...(sigh) i don't usually get like this. infact this is like my first time ever feeling this way about something. shit i'm rambling i'm sorry but this is infact an extremely boring journal...infact i don't keep a journal because i'm too inconsistent...if i ever do fill out a post it's because i really need to say something and i guess it's a little easier to do over the world wide web. and sorta going back to first talk topic i feel like i'm hurting someone by not doing what i could've or what i felt was right. anyways i'm rambling. i have a trumpet practice in the morning. it's 1:00 and the father is finally home...he said he'd be back at 9:30 but i think he was just trying to scare me. yar har he couldn't fool me any whoo most people won't even get to this page for a month anyways. crapfully yours  Sam 

						
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well hello all of you! It's been a long month i imagine. but i am now back at home. i guess my camp went down pretty well. we were up in temagami for 2 weeks and because sam goes friggin hardcore on trips like that i wore the same clothes for the entire time...yeah those clothes smell like "rotted spiced sausage" no joking...so bad...so smell. I think the only problem that i might have had the entire time would be with some of the guys. one of them alex...was a huge dick...he skipped a grade a while back so he's going into grade 12. and from this he got to be one of the most cockiest assholes i have ever seen. we'll be sitting around reading national geographics from the 80's (which i got addicted to)and he'll be like "hey sam, let's fight!" and he is some tiny little shit who thinks that his muscle was brought on by working out..but it wasn't..it's just him being small....grr i wanted to beat him senseless but i restrained myself...i feel myself to be a passifist. fighting doesn't really help you much anyways. then there was a kid from the U.S...miami actually. and he's always full of shit...i mean everything he said had to be bigger or better than what ever you just said. every body knew he was full of crap. but just him thinking that we were stupid enough to believe him, just makes me p.o'd.  Now i can imagine that you saying "Hey sam, that's not bad" you don't know crap! they pissed me off soo much. and i just about died through the month...but the thought of coming home kept me hanging in there.  and yes it's true this entire month i missed emily madly...and i read her blog as soon as i came back and it seemed like she was getting along pretty well...except for some other stuff. which was really depressing for me to hear that was going on while i was away. i juts hope that it works out for her...ooo ooo she and chelsea get back home tomorrow...and if i had it my way i would be there waiting for her at her house when she got there but i'm pretty sure that that is not possible. meh i can't wait to talk to her again though. i'm really anxious to see her and spend the rest of the summer together...yay yay yay fun! anyways yeah i'm back...month's gone by...see you guys soon. Sam  

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well howdy howdy. i guess i'm feeling bad about not putting in a new blog entry for like ...uhh a couple...no a lot of days. so here we go! starting from where i last left off.  i guess...uhh monday night i think it was. emily's soccer game got cancelled so she had nothing to do. so i employed the help of my chaffeur/parent to drive me to her house. and erblina was there waiting with emily in the drive way. and on the drive there i was shaking and i was really nervous because i hadn't seen emily in over a month so i was obviously extremely excited. and when i came into the driveway i was yelling out insanely in my mind but i couldn't really show it as i had wished to because erblina was there and so was my step dad. so i kept it to myself...if you ask me though i was really dissappointed to not have properly given her my "welcome back".  so we had a good time. we went to the house that her brother was house sitting at and we went on the trampoline...played "HOR". went back to emily's place watched the parent trap and tried to learn their neat handshake.  Then...on thursday, i went to the beach with emily erblina and kyle. and we got there at like 9:30 sat on the beach tanning and swimming, throwing a football around. then at about 1:30 i think tim got joined us and he seemed to be in a bit of a pissy mood considering he railed emily on the back with a sandal...and later hit her in the head which i didn't think was very appropriate. then when i tried to get up when we were on some rocks somewhere else i stumbled and hit my heel on a rock and it split the skin open and left a horrible cut which is still bothering me today. so yeah that was a pretty awesome day.  then on friday i went over to evan's house and we did the usual...watched movies..played video games. stayed up until 6:00 am. Then the next morning at 8:00 am my mom picked me up and we drove to southampton to one of her friends cottages. and there we...drank many alcoholic libations. but it was fine...i didn't get roaring drunk. then at sunset i went to the beach and watched the sun go down...and later that night when we went out for dinner...my mom sort of noticed that i was really sad...mainly because i was lonely and she could tell that so she's asking me about emily...and i just laughed because now everyone knows except for my dad. it's not that i don't want anyone to know it's just that i don't wanna go around telling everyone. so yeah...one successful weekend.  and now i'm here...to today. emily's online waiting for me to start talking again...and i'm downloading a music program called sibelius...illegally! wahhoo go pirating! and i'm gonna get some speakers from future shop...so that should be quite interesting...and nothing planned for tonight...hey! i'm free! Sam (8)now that we're together i've never been so lonely in my life(8)  

						
</post>


</Blog>