<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      err quite happy todae though. bought the book that i wanted: 张小娴： 相逢。  全都是精髓之一。是散文。 bz reading my book. lol. sooo wun update much. yeahz.  sch was sian.  Social Studies Mathematics (if u dun count Joshua poking at u full time behind u) Geography ( free period ) Chinese ( teacher din come but still got hmwk )   haix. goin to go back sch le. dotz. i feel so damn sick of it le. how am i gonna survive the darn o levels lor. imagine this: mock prelim. [okay. still okay] prelim [haiyo. so sian. study again]  o level [godz. I DUN WAN STUDY LE] haiyo. siao. 家 wrote some chinese stuff actually. but wun post it here. 家丑不可外传！ 哈哈。bb.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finally have the time to blog le. but it'll be a short one lah. literally have no time nowadays. so much hmwk to do and revision to do. argh. totally in no mood now. one thing i muz say though. jiesin im sorry. happy? u started it anyway. nvm.  in bad mood lah. wun blog. bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyy ppl. wun be updating anytime soon after this. have some prob wif my com.. have to wait for very long to fix lor.. lolz. soo too bad. haiyo. i go game le larh. byex.  stupid msn ppl. stupid com. stupid c drive.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyy. need help.. i rewashed everything off my com the other day rite.. then after that i reinstalled MSN version 6.2. then when i logged in, the screen wif all my contacts came out but after dat it became stuck. as in cannot move. the mouse can still move but it's in the bz mode le as in the hourglass mode. how? i need to use MSN. its my life.. haixxxx. *cries.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyy ppl.nv blog on monday lor. haha com kena washed. everything.. weepz. anyway. monday was boring larh. hmm. shall blog abt sundae.. haha. had yuhua concert to go to. hmm met nich at 2.00 at serangoon mrt. as usual. i was late wahaha. sooo met him then to my usual hangout : Plaza Singapura!! yeah.. haha.. after that met zakiah den went to st andrew cathedral to pick saga seeds. lolz. this time a lot a lot lor. with the help wif zak and nich.. haha. nich is expert in picking lor. he can find the saga seeds very fast leh. haha shant tell u all for u larh. but i guess band members shuld noe. nono. there's nth between us. haha family ties ba.. plus ive been always very bad to her ma.. lolz. the other ppl ah.. haiyo.  haha then after that went to take lots and loads and loads of photos. haha. siao le. stupid "model" photo gort passed around yesterdae. lolx. nort i wan de hor.  den after that went to eat.. then went to suntec city.. lolz. heyy there gort machine can wash photos lehz.. haha feel so high tech lor. haha.but the dumb machine ate 50 cents lor. haix. din realise the sign saying "no change given".. dotz.  almost late for the concert lor. we were like stuck at suntec at 7. 15? haha.. den we ran all the way there. tiring sia. like juz ate liddat.. but very fun larh. we were basically breaking like all of the traffic rules lor.. haha. anyway. yuhua is good lor. damn gd. esp the alumni band. haha. maybe we can go and revive the alumni band lor.. lolz. we gort josh, yijun and jingyuan leh.. haha and many others.. marcus , benson.. lol.. maybe can fight?!? wahaha. no larh..   haiyo.. i expected their godzilla eats las vegas to be gd le larh.. but din expect it to be soooo gd lor. haix. their showmanship still like superb lor. haha. i luv miss chan sia.. wooHOO!~ their sooo called encore was like.. can be considered as one full song le lor.. haha saw diana again. dun noe still rmb me or nort lor.. but i saw my best frenr again.. argh wilson sorrie i din call u to go but u came anyway larh.. lolx.. yeahz. gd rite.  those who din go shuld consider killing themselves leh.. lol, joanne and edo went too. or rather edo wif his girl-frenr. lolzokay okay enuff. then after that went to eat and take more photos. wasnt realli happy towards the end. and vaness shuld noe what i mean.. ill be giving them a piece of my mind larh.. haha. dun wanna blog abt yesterdae larh. boring. sundae was fun and very..  okay abt todae. nort gonna go out. supposed to go to outing todae but the sec3s postponed it. haix... nvm nvm.. jiayoux. im numb already. juz hope that it will go well. gd luck ppl.  okay okay.. am quite happy now larh.. lolx. yeah yeah yeah yeahz. haha. i no love le larh. give all away le..lolz bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      anyway. read this. gort this from my sec1 junior:  (i tink its sick though, she sec1 onli leh) A husband, tired of his wife asking how she looks, buys her a full  length mirror. This does little to help. As now she just stands in front  of it, looking at herself, asking him how she looks.   One day, fresh out of the shower, she is yet again in front of the  mirror. Now complaining that her breasts are too small!  Uncharacteristically, the husband said. "If you want your breasts to  grow, then every day take a piece of toilet paper and rub it between  your breast for a few seconds."   Willing to try anything, the wife fetches a piece of toilet paper,  stands in front of the mirror, rubbing it between her breasts.   "How long will this take?" she asks.   "They'll grow larger over a period of years," he replies.   The wife stops," Why do you think rubbing this piece of toilet paper  between my breast everyday will make my breasts grow over the years?"  she asks.   The husband shrugs." WHY NOT, IT WORKED FOR YOUR ASS, DIDN'T IT!"    ------------------------------------------------------------------- okay nvm on wif todae. woah. todae is one day which im back  urlLink home  early (dat means before 5 reach  urlLink home , assuming i spend abt 8 hours outside everyday) in the morning went to amk mrt there and reached there abt say 6.50? damn tiring, seemed as though my head weighed a ton. lucky my dad fetch. lucky me. lolz had to brief michelle and yong chun larh for their bm and dm understudy.. but i was supposed to meet them at say 7.20? haha. ended up that i din bring my headphones out then did some paperwork for band till then. met terry and chuan jian and nice them came to talk to me lor. haha. they were supposed to meet their frenrs at seven but when they reached at say 7.10? nobody lor. haha. and they were supposed to hve breakfast. lolz. wait i thot michelle lost the outing minutes lor. turned out as she typed it out and lost the original copy. hai wo rewrite everything according to my  urlLink memory . dotz. after briefing them, went up to the plaform. as usual, i was the earliest. saw pauline on the way though. lolz. next came vincent then after a while, matthew appeared out of thinair(idinseehim) b4 peizhi,lihuan joined us. lolz. and the latest was the organiser lor:xiwen. haha. saw some realli funny sights. and disgusting ones. saw ck. lolz. nvm.. haha.i was like omg ck.. then eeks. haha. nvm. then went to somerset to hve my seminar.. orh it was boring. seriously. i culdnt keep myself awake. oh yah. did i mention that anthony wanted to kill me. coz i told him to meet in sch or sth to brief his QMs, but i din say im goin. so i din go and he... haix. he waited for me i guess. wahhaa. he came in pe attire larh and attracted quite a lot of laughter too larh. nvm larh. ya gort ya dear daryl to sit wif u ma.. lolz. percussion.zzz.  nvm. the lecture was boring lor xcept for the break. haha. i enjoyed the  urlLink food  lor. weilong, me and vincent were like eating second and third helpings. haha. but we din finish all the fd on the table larh. we're nort pigs. tokin abt pigs: rmbed someone who suaned me that i can nv be a pig. i thot she was being nice or wat before she said that i dun even deserve to be a pig. juz becoz i sleep a lot.. she oso whatx. but nvm. it was onli suaning... lol  after that decided to go off wif my class. dun say i always nv go wif u all larh.. haha. lucky jiesin nort there. I solemnly proclaim: me and jiesin will hate each other for ever. lolz. her  urlLink dog  gort a castration yesterdae for like wat, prevention against prostrate  urlLink cancer . haha. errr. sooo we went to long john  urlLink silver  and saw yr, juliana they all there. victor immediately backed off. followed by joshua who tried to act blur and walk away. for god's sake, pls dun act lor. nvm. nort up to me to say anything lest anyone say me againz. okay larh. but ate there anyway.  after that walked then took the lift up to the arcade there. lost to matthew in one game. duno what to call that larh. but matt, jy and qy fought for racing oso larh. after that went up to bowling. rmb ppl i dun bowl sooo slacked there wif some ppl larh. matt treated us to cookies. famous amos! woohoo. nice sia. he gave me the big big ones. =) after that, receieved some soo called gd  urlLink news  larh.. okay nort very gd but im happy anyway... then after they finished me and matthew went off earlier and headed  urlLink home . the others went to pool. oh yah. i boasted to some of them abt the  urlLink movies  larh.. lolz recent de 50 1st dates: watched scooby doo: watched troy: watched van helsing: watched harry potter: watched shrek 2: watched e day after tml: watched spiderman: gonna watch garfield: gonna watch mean gals: gonna watch  lol yeah. think xiwen gort quite irritated by me. lol oh yah on the way back wif matt, we took to marina bay then took back to amk lor. haha. crapped lots wif him or rather bitched abt some ppl larh. at least he agrees wif me. but i think im evil in some way or another. im nort even involved but im like sooo interested..okay nvm. u all dun understand. errrr. supposed to meet ketsu todae and yesterdae but hes like ultra bz. haha. anyway ketsu is yuan ru's dream lover. from cat high lor. been suaning her. u noe the nice testimonial she gave me in frenster. it is becoz she wanted his picture. dotz. nvm. meeting him becoz he wants a score larh.. hes a clarinetist too though play db most of the  urlLink time  ba. one more thing shuld i go for choir concert? haha shuhui's paying $2 out of $12 for me leh. lol both of us leaders gort connection sia.shuld i or shuld i nort.   okay. everybodys like basically eradicated from singapore all go sarawak le lor. haha. less noisy though. not a lot of  urlLink sms . culd feel the effect instantly. used to receive 50 over smses a day but now haha.. nort even 25. yeah~haiyo. sundae still gort yuhua concert., maybe meeting nickky earlier again. vanessa u goin rite? u havent pay  urlLink money  yet.. band fund help u pay leh.. err. anyway sorrie ppl onli had 36 tix coz e  urlLink money  wasnt paid up in  urlLink time . see what happens when u all dun pay up.. grrr. i hope i can go. for all who duno, there's a band outing next tuesday and im officially a facilitator.lol  hmmm. i think crapped a lot todae le leh. i wun ever take 70 bus again. waited one whole entire hour for the stupid bus yesterdae at suntec. took 133  urlLink home  instead. grrr. angry. but nvm.. haix tonite have to study le. mum's been complaining. haiyo.. grandmama calling me eat le.. i go le hor. think gort salmon fish. haha.nice~ byex tc ppl.    love was when i loved u. one true  urlLink time . i hold u.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      grrrrrrrrrrrr. i typed an ultra long entry and the stupid thing gort problem. dun wan blog le. i hate my com. stupid virus. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ppl. juz came back from woodlands. haiyo...todae long day sia. in the morning went to the sch to meet the sec 3s.. haiyo.. took very bery long/ but nvm. enjoyed it. haix. but kinda kena scolded by mr tan and mrs lim larh..  guess i deserved it.  then after that. it was raining realli heavily ... and very. but the air con could nort be on lor. or else shuang~! haha. but i couldnt realli hear myself speak.. sooo i shut all the doors and the windows in the temp classroom. sorrie to the sec3s, i tormented ya all.. haha. but u all culd sit leh. haha  hmm.. after that. decided to go wifthe sec3s to woodlands. actually wanted to go plaza sing wif zak de.. but the others din wan sooo suit them ba.. saw meisen oso.. hot pink sia>~  sooo we took to woodlands.. had a wonderous meal at Burger king anyway.. lol. luffed lots and stuff there.. reali cracked us up dere man. anyway. suhtyng, michelle, zakiah and me were dere larh.. saw some pretty funny stuff.  picture a boy sitting alone at the corner. he wanted to move away but wanted to leave his stuff on the table sooo he started talking to HIMSELF: "this one gort mosquito one.. dun touch this one ah" dotz.  and there was this scene when suhtyng was eating haha. she was like eating eating.. then suddenly she looked in another direction and looked back and she said "uh oh" and stared at the piece of thing which fell off her burger. haha.. shes soo damn cute lor haha.. no wonder shes my daughter. haiyo.. btw: someone wanted to be my great granddaughter leh.haha.yingchern was like complaining how come nv put her in da family.. dotz.  okay after that decided to follow them around. needed to buy stuff too.. haha. but felt quite paiseh to follow them to go around searching for clothes lor. esp in the ladies beach wear section dere. i was like the onli guy there. and all the other shops oso lor.  but nvm after that zakiah went off. leaving me wif suhtyng and michelle. haha. crapped lots wif them. i was quite picky wif the stuff i bought larh. haha. tormented them totally. suytyng was complaining full time abt me lor. wahhaa.. but finally gort it.. now i need onli one more "ingredient" haha.  oso played wif suhtyng there at the metro there.. lol.. it was like the t shirts hung up dere were too high for EVEN me to reach larh. and even joshua i wuld say.. so i used the normal bamboo stick to bring it down lor.. haha.was very very funny lor.. luves suhtyng's new t-shirt.. had words like this: language was invented becoz of the need to complain, complain and complain.. haha. then the back had onli a few words : COMPLAIN. haha. and its in bright orange. haha vanessa ur fav colour. haha.   broke todae anyway.. ttreated them to a bit of burger king.. den bought a lot of stuff. and went to take neoprint. haha. treated 20 cents more.(i noe im petty)  orhh!!! gort one more thing.. in the music shop in the causeway pt there gort some very very nice small versions of the instruments. u noe the small saxophone was soo nice lor.. if huiming saw it, she wuld totally scream lor.. haha. but its like thiry six dollars. cant buy for anybody lor.. haha. sorrie peepx culdnt lend u all money. nvm. next time then get chee hao to buy for us.. wahhaa. if dun wan buy for us ah.. then we use someone** ahemx to threaten u. haha. looks like everybody noes huh? lolz.  i wan a new bk lor.. it costs thirteen sth.. damn nice chinese san wen book lor.. by zhang xiao man. hk writer. she makes hell lot of sense lor. haha. even mich and suythng agreed wif me todae lor.. haha. okay nvm. shall get my mum to get it tml. wahaha. grr im feeling bored. and a bit sad. maybe its becoz of some stuff. duno larh. juz bored ba.. wanna chat wif some ppl on the phone lor.. haha. juz chatted to jy for a while.. anybody noe how to remove firewall. he needs help.. hmm. tml gonna watch hp wif yijun they all.. im excited lor. haha. though theres a music exchange tml oso.. haix guess im nort goin to go ba.. though i already brought the clarinets back.. grr. so heavy. haha. the tubist oso noe how to bring their mouthpiece back onli lor. sooo gd. haix. but other than cck, and sji oso gort regent and bedok north. u all ah.. what schools oso duno.. for dose who duno.. they're playing "holding the truth" sorrie to jeremy cant be dere to help ya.. maybe next time come and find me lor. friday nort gonna go band oso. maybe onli morning go.. haix very little ppl.. kkies. nvm.. i think i crap a lot lor.. haha. haiyo.. i go le larh. enuff for the day. bye ppl ~ byex.  is loving someone or being loved more fortunate?lolz.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      grr. im pissed . very.no mood to blog le lar. my mum accused me of sth. he culd jolly well hve done it on his own and then, it comes out as i didnt help.. haha. yah. the smaller brother gets everything watx. yah.  Mum says: im addicted to msn whatx. i talk crap wat.  i onli noe how to go out whatx. i refuse to help my brother. she is disappoined wif me. i dun even care abt my brother. i make this whole family a unpeaceful place.  FINE. if so.  kill me then.  juz becoz he needs some help, i hve to help. i was bz helO~? i get scolded. its juz sending an attachment in hotmail. i pointed u in the direction, freak. so u hve to go crying to mum for help. becoz of wat. "big brother didnt help u"  and mum comes out to scold me. and brother sits innocently on the floor watching the fight. grr. im pissed. very very very. cant he take some venturing. i duno dreamweaver.  my brother needs to use. mum call me do. i duno kena scold. simple as dat. USELESS BRAT I AM HOR.  so basic stuff i do : eat (waste money) sleeeep (waste air-con) go out (take money) side wif frenrs (dun help family) make this family un-warm   so tell me shuld i go or nort? since frenrs and family dun understand me le. i tried to help. i teach u maths, dear brother. i offered u help. U??? wahaha. u dun even bother to cover the blankets for me when its cold. u dun even close the windows when it's raining, late late at nite. u dun even bother to wash the plates, clear the table, make breakfast for urself? or even do a project without mama's help. ya sec1 ma hor? dun need do larh. need help for everything... haha. i dun think i was dat pathetic in sec1. who will it be when ya all need the photos in the digitial cam for ya project. it'll be me. nvm.  and so in the end what am i? worthless breed.  haha. smiling? that'll hve to come after ive finished being pissed. sorrie if this doesnt sound like the normal wenjie. the normal me was gone a long time ago. eradicated since my sec3 life started. no quote for todae. bye. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha. todae is one rare day when im alone at home lor. haha. my grandparents went out. soooo i have the morning alone. haha. wanna blog earlier de but couldnt wake up. lol. haix. nth to blog in the morning leh haha. haix. been watching tv~ hmmm had a wonderful breakfast i made for myself lor.haha haha recipe: 1) Spread garlic spread on two pieces of bread. 2) Toast. Leave to cool for a while.This is essential because if we dun do this, the oil from the garlic spread will mix wif the peanut butter and form a ugly suspension. 3) Spread peanut butter on the two pieces of garlic bread. 4) Add a piece of cheese on each piece of bread. 5) Add another layer of peanut butter onto the cheese. 6) Put the two pieces of bread together and dig in!   haha. i think it sounds disgusting to ya all.. like cheese is sour and peanut butter is sweet. but u peepx go try larh. last time home econs chuanjian they all say nort nice. but when they tried it, they almost finished everything haha. contradicting. see dun believe me.. haha try it, its nice~  arghZ i wanna go orchard. i juz wanna get out of the hse lor butttttt my mum dun allow lor. haha. grrr. haiyo.  godz.im bored.bored.bored.bored.bored.  anyway. gonna watch hp on thur wif sec4 peeps. lol. haix. dats all for now ba.give a longer post later ba.. haha.  see ya.~    *the greatest barrier on earth isn't life and death. e greatest barrier is that im standing in front of u and u duno that i love u*  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so its finally out eh. after the confession from someone. haha. so okay i noe its nort meant to be after all. i guessed it all along  ANYWAY . nvm. i shant bother at all.  Looking on the brighter side, I went SEntosa wif the sec3s todae. haha. though i din realli enjoy it but since it was sunny and all, brighter side than. Brighter as in literally. okay nvm. lamez. Okay shall wanna clear up sth here. Cheryl has nv had me as a bf larh. its juz playing ya? haha. secrets actually smsed me hor??? haha. nvm.. i shall luv ya too~ yeah shes my GF too.. haha.  to secrets: she wun get jealous becoz she doesnt exist.ya. dun worry. haha. and its nort even her anymore. yeah.  my stupid com has a virus lor. haix. cant read my mail can im too lazy to on the other com. haix.idiotic com. icant sleepwell.if u actually called last nite sleep. nvm. basically was soo tired but kena bothered by some stuff. meaningless stuff.STUPID> i havent watched harry potter anyway.nobody realli waited for me larh.. haha. must be the put off from my normal ego. but wateva. heard it sux sooo i duno. shuld i watch or shuld i nort watch.? orhhh i rmbed. who wuld wan to watch wif pathetic me rite.. wahaha.nvm.i rather watch wif juz cept hes nort free.but nvm the sec4s gort me wif them soo guess i'll go wif them instead of the normal gang. haha. thanx man~ ni men hai shi the best!  orhh one thing. tml. shuld i go for SJI prac.. have ta get tix from mr yea. haix. early morning. i feel like sleeping plus i dun feel like goin there. its juz like another amkps. where everybody's so close but ya're nort inside. nobody bothers to intro. okay nvm. since i've decided to be antisocial, it doesnt reali matter.  lee hom gort new album lor. nort sold in s'pore. haix.another ppl flying to  urlLink japan  lately. help me get kkies. i prefer his jap songs to his chin songs.haha. tokin abt discs, sorrie to nich. i din noe it will spoil oso. haha.  share something wif ya all:(to a certain someone oso)  ??????,???????????????? ???????, ??????????????? ????????,??????????????? ??,???????,???????????????????? ??,?????????????????? ?????????????? ?????????????? duno what to say le larh. i tink its nice. haha. gort it off a bk. haix yah.. nth much to say le lor. decided nort to go SJI le larh.. haha. i duno.    *the greatest barrier on earth isn't life and death. e greatest barrier is that im standing in front of u and u duno that i love u*  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay. juz went out wif siva, nich, yuzhen and huiming. the concert was okay larh other than edwin *wif his classmates nort huiming ah* making a lot of noise,huiming luffing all thru out, siva and nich talking, lack of attention from the crowd and me being sad, i'll say it was quite a success. in any way, cheryl u do rawk.. haha u still luv me rite. althou i'm your 5th bf rite. lol. anyway. cheryl (u noe that cheryl tay from amb, yesh her, u're nort seeing things) says she gort her first bf in pri 4,haha. then still gort a longest relationship which lasted for 2 years leh. ai qing chang pao. then now juggling between edwin and me. so saaaad. haix.  quite irritated durin the concert actually.  due to a few   reasons  : 1) lack of money. cheryl i bought a $20 worth of flowers for u kkies betta appreciate it. 2) recieved an sms from someone. or rather was waiting for dear SOMEONE to reply me. appartantly dat person din bother larh. 3) lamez but the music actually moved me somehow. haha. to irritating mode (one piece but forgot what le) strange what music can do nowadays. 4) nobody to go out wif after the concert. okay this is realli bad i noe.. nort blaming nich and siva but haix. nvm..  and sorrie to Juz who tried to get me out. haha. but u enjoyed urself anyway rite. without me.  and heard that some ppl will go on somewhere and enjoy themselves and basically if i din ask, i'll be left out rite. without me. again  and juz the other day. i was left out for sth. and they said they enjoyed it, it rawked. okay okay soo i waited for them and after that. they went off. without me again. this is getting too qiao~ to be ignored.  第一次，我告诉自己， 可能你们太忙了，忘记了我，我不怪你们。 第二次，我告诉自己， 可能当时的情况不允许你们这样作，我不怪你们。 第三次，我告诉自己， 当朋友的，不要太计较。 第四次，我告诉自己， 我可以大方地体会。 第五次，我告诉自己， 我可以尽量去明白 。 第六次，我告诉自己， 是我太敏感了。 第七次，对不起， 我已经找不到任何的借口了。 你们的确在take me for granted.  haix.. sorrie for the sudden change to chinese. i luv chin anyway. juz feeling kinda sad ba. with or without me, the world will still go on.  即使我不在了， 太阳会依然地照耀着大地， 风会依旧地吹遍千山万里， 花儿依然会开得灿烂无比。 因为我的离去并没有任何价值。 就算我走了， 你也感受不到我的离去。  feelin kinda poetic anyway. nvm. all crappz.(juz as the sitename) hmm. ya larh but that's realli what i feel. haha. think i type quite long le larh. shall go off now. byex ~     *the greatest barrier on earth isn't life and death. e greatest barrier is that im standing in front of u and u duno that i love u*  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay. i woke up at 8.30 again. haix.okay cancel that. nvm. haha. b4 i forget. MY BDAE IS ACTUALLY COMING LEH> rmb kkies.  haiyo. supposed to be doin hmwk but lied to my mum that i need ta check mail from mr tan. which is quite true but he din reply me. hmm i supposed to go offline now, but since u noe 'supposed' soo heckx.  hey. thanx to vaness hor.. haha for the testimonial. thanx for announcing to da ENTIRE WORLD abt the colour and lee hom thing. haha.hmmmmmmmmmmmm.im booorreed.  later shall go out by my boi boi to hougang mall 1st lor.. haha. this guy ah. always so paiseh one but can crap soo much. he has his father character woOhOO~ but i hve nv been to hougang mall b4 lor and the bus goin there runs on a stupid loop service and goes onli like one way. sooo i basically have to go the whole round b4 reaching the first stop when its actually soo near. daMn 21 stops u noe.  err. btw anybody gort any nice band songs pls pass to me hor. in the mood for new ones. other than persis and jap series larh lol.  hmmm. other than all these. kinda hope tmr can go out wif someone. haha. u all duno de larh keep guessing.  to yuzhen and nich: u two hve no mama yet larh. but haha. papa's working h@rd.~!  errr. share a joke here. haha. contributed by jinjun actually: a racist one though but since it's racist, naturally my entire class noes. yeah~  what do u say when u agree wif a indian? > > > > > > > > > > > > > > > > > > > give up/       ERRR. u hve a POINT there.. dose ppl who get it gd. haha. dose ppl who dun. too bad too sad.OKAY i saddist.  haiya.. think nth more to add le lor.. haha....... shall go off to chat on msn le.. bye & smilez :P     *the greatest barrier on earth isn't life and death. e greatest barrier is that im standing in front of u and u duno that i love u*  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      orhh helo ppl.. wahah. i finally gort my own blog lor. after quite some  urlLink time . but i muz realli thank my frenr for dat. lazy me wuld have nv started on a blog lor. hey.. thanx hor. are u secrets or vicky.. haha.  sidenote: the author is nort a good writer hor. pardon him for his lack of vocab and language.. ya larh. as if anybody will read.. haha kkies.  hmmm.. todae totally slacked at home. i mean i'm supposed to study larh. okay in the morning was actually quite hardworking. gd start man.. but that was all.. i woke up at 8.30 (for the 1st time this yr) yah.. studied a bit of chemistry (10 minutes) then went off to watch TV. haha. i actually watched peach gal on channel 8 lor.. at 12. ppl catch it. lee hom's song ' aidejiushini ' as main theme song lehx! wOOhoO~! okay lame  -____-"  hmm..in the afternoon, haha, slacked thru again. haiyo. when im like supposed to do physics.. okay. i noe im realli lazy but juz cant help it.   err. recently heard a quote in a workshop larh.. juz wanna share it here wif myself (ibetnobodywillreadmyblog)haha..  here goes: "Everybody dies but not everybody lives."  okay larh.. it's like realli true larh.. but somehow my class wasnt too inspired by it. okay i admit im innocent wahaha.. innocent pig! haha.. betta than meisen le. she ah. onli noe how to famei. (sorrie.inoe u dun use net that's why attack u wahha)  hmmm.realised a lot of ppl are sad recently.. so ppl CHEER UP!!! rmb what i say: smile big big..  steps to make urself happy: 1) pull urself away from the tissue box. 2) walk to the bathroom and to the mirror (any reflecting surface may do larh) 3) kkies. i noe it sounds stupid. but it works for me larh.. ya... now  JUX SMILE !! keep the smile. think of the happy stuff. look into the mirror. see the real u.  kkies. lame~ nvm larh. follow this.. i noe this doesnt realli work.. but promise me.. nv take ur life away okay? sorrieZ  NVM. crapz a lot le.. tml oso goin out .. again haha.. wif my son and gal. haha. oh ya did i mention my  urlLink family tree  again? okay wait: i hve one father. i hve  NO  mother. (she ran away from us lor) i hve 3 sisters. i hve one nephew. i hve three daughters. i hve one son. haha.  hmmm. maybe dats for all todae. need ta send  urlLink mail  to mr tan le. abt band camp. hope he approves~  byex and take carez smilez.      *the greatest barrier on earth isn't life and death. e greatest barrier is that im standing in front of u and u duno that i love u*  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi! This is Wen Jie. Yup.  No really! Believe me. This is Wen Jie typing. =D  If I am an imposter, I'll kill myself -- uh I mean Wen Jie will kill me -- for impersonating me -- or I should say, for impersonating Wen Jie. So you can see from the above sentense, I am really Wen Jie. Yes. No kidding. Who else will type so weirdly?  I know I know. You all don't believe me because I'm typing weirdly now but that's because I'm making an effort to type proper English with capitalisation and all. So ya. This is Wen Jie. Wen Jie is the only way you should address me by. For I will not respond to any other name you call. That is because,  I am Wen Jie.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>