<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A broken bridge   Times like these wish I were dead, Drowned in gloom, in hatred red Locked in chains tied to my bed Oh to what misery, have I been pledged?  The gloom and doom of painful nights Have locked me in this dreary plight My wings are broken, can make no flight Blackness covering, and blinding my sight  Wicked words and evil deeds Poisoning within, this mead Planted carefully, of blackness this seed Oh to where will this dark road lead?  Someone help me! Please assist! This anger growing like a cyst! Light a fire, clear this mist, Clenched hard like rocks, are my fists  For love and hatred do not mix One or the other, you must pick This broken bridge, this heart must fix, Like holy water no wolf can lick  by norain isa   A new beginning  Sneak a peak through morbid eyes See the fire that rages inside To act ungodly is a sin What devil, what satan lies within  I wish someone would take me high Upon the clouds, see heavens bright Release me from this deadly lock And dress me in a pure white frock  by norain isa   Me  If I could swim away, I would To explore the hidden sea Secrets written across the sand, Unknown to you or me  If I could run away, I would And caress the sandy peaks A world of laughter, happiness and joy Hidden away, for no one to see  If I could fly away, I would And join the birds so free To learn the myths, stories untold And find the inner me  by norain isa   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    meeeeeeeeee&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      to the beings that seem worthy and true can only be met with despair the hard hand of tyranny and injustice backlogs years of care and repair  the ambitions and dreams of one soul determined prayers and hopes are uttered unheard a long winding road,destroyed and deserted makes each moment, a harder lesson to learn  my attempts at peace,in vain and futile faliure caused only by my own contemt,my own actions i cannot surpress,emotions conflicting a little black man forcing every reaction  a series of cries,of screams and of moans reflect on a story,a story untold locked away by the sinews within harder than diamond,reflecting my sins  red bubbling poison,rises within a coarse,fiery demon fueling it further wildly taking over,my soul and my spirit something keeps it inside,cold this benefit  a glimpse of my anger which simmers inside hells raging fires seem so cool and mild a black heart,for one black soul could this mean the end?there's more in store?  a white streak of lightning across the skies can seem so beautiful in my very eyes a rumble of thunder,not unlike my chest a scream in the distance,it comes from the west  today norain holland
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my dream car&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my best fren rachel june sim&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    graduation in tchsd 2004 me and tatty&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello every one i noe i have been boring you with poetry and all that...its just my way of expressing myself....my favourites are the romantics like william blake and lord byron......im kinda new to this stuuf...i have been writing 4 about 2 years.....ill post some of my better stuff soon...as soon as i can locate them...ill be starting photography soon.i saw a blog recently and it was some really nice pictures....he was pretty good...i would love to catch the essence of the world around me....it would be nice to keep track of this rapidly changing world we live in....i dunno why i have suddenly become so passionate about everything nowadays....its so surreal suddenly...like im up in stage..i noe it sound weird.. but its true.....its like...i suddenly have an ambition in my life...i have something to dooo....being cooped up at home doesent mean i have to waste my life away...there are so may thing s for me to doscover and rediscover...my soul...my Religon..i bought these tapes recently..it was about the lives of the prophets(peace and blessings upon them all) and it is soo cool !!! Islam is not  about what newspapers say...it is not about terrorism or killing jews...its about patience and submission to God...it is a simple religion really.... u get freaks in every religion.....so u cant judge the religion from what you see on televison...it is beautiful really...every law has a good reason.....we may not know it but God knows whats best..... i thank God that i was born a muslim....i wouldnt wanna convert to anything even if you put a gun to my head..i put my trust in God anyway i gtg now.. ill keep u posted
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      she walks in beauty,like the night   of clodless climes and starry skies; and all that's best of dark and bright   meet in her aspect and her eyes: thus mellowed to that tender light   which heaven to gaudy day denies.  one shade the more,one ray the less,   had half impaired the nameless grace which waves in every raven trees,   or softly lightens o'er her face; where thought serenely sweet express,   how pure,how dear their dwelling-place  and on that cheek,and o'er that brow   so soft,so calm,yet eloquent, the smiles that win,the tints that glow'   but tell the days in goodness spent, a mind at peace with all below,   a heart whose love is innocent! 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the day i die dont be by my side for i will forever love you till my last breath  the day that i leave you dont let me go for deep inside me i know you are the on efor me  the day i fall in love with you please fall in love with me too for i know you need me untill your dying day  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      of all the souls i have come across yours is the most pure and clean untarnished by the oxides of life still new and still so shiny  slowly u discovered the world taking sstep by timid step seeing thing that you should not scarring your memory forever  i watched you turn yourself around staining your pure white mind if a drop of ink can ruin the milk a drop of this world will ruin your heart  the most beautiful are watched and admired a mistake as small as ash is seen as big as the earth a slip like and ants step,is felt like a giants stride
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The reason why remains unknown why God created this emotion this despair and hurt is solely my own what good does it bring,this poison  this feeling inside,useless and futile it only brings hurt and despair a look on the bright side,how i have tried life among mortals will never be fair  take one last look within my soul the door lies though my morbid eyes i have fallen down this balck hole my lies hold no emotion  no good has come,ive been led astray my heart,my soul has fallen i never even felt anyway true love its called,will be lost forever    
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it was rachels bd yesterday.she was really depressed...im broke so i couldnt buy her a gift just yet....i sent her 2 e cards though...very cool...very nice.....happy birthday rachel!!!!this blogging thing is getting quite cool.although the only ones i read are mine and rachels...sometimes i probe into the lives of others but i really dont give a damn....i like reading the political ones..i like reading other pplz opinons about contraversial topics..it gives me ample warning about what ppl are gonna say next so i can think up a retaliation...i hate being wrong...i am very self opinionated...i like confrontation....especially when im right.well i gtg now...i willl be posting some poems i wrote up here tell me wat u think
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was an ok day....nothin new really..every day is kinda boring...same shit ..my life is so monotonous..i can barely wait till the day i get home. batoool called me today...man she has changed..ssshe seems so smug about her being in the uk and dissing the A level system thinkin that IB is soo damn cool.well sorry to say but A level is more recognised andd more cool.huh. shamsan had a football match today..with satwa..his team won of course...i spoke with ana on the phone..she told me never to leave shamsan.she said it is so hard to find somebody who loves you i am so scared to lose him..i love him so much...he is amazing...kind gentle generous understanding(most of the time)......words cannot express how i feel about him...i can only pray that both him and i get accepted into nus or ntu...i wannago home and be with rach..i have frens here...but its not the same..there is ana but she understands how important rachel is...she evem asks after her sometimes..... i was supposed to watch harry potter today but i came home at half past one last nite after an all girls party that i kinda passed.it was nooras graduation party..it was really fun...it was right on the boat at al boom and we danced on deck while the dhow sailed on the creek...there were all these hot guys on shore so we couldnt resist taking the oppurtunity to..ehm ehm..lool it was really cool..in both senses of the word.surprisingly it was cool up oin deck.considering it is stifling on land.i guess it is the night breeze. amazing...how people can not believe in GOD amazes me,.....how can they be so stupid?? i mean His creations surround us..what further proof do we need...how the sun floats in the sky?how mountains and icebergs have roots like teeth.....omg... anyway. am tired now rach is not online at the mo...she is basically the only reason why i come online...noone else is really worth it..i guess i miss talking in singlish to everyone else..i guess im totally homesick...  OMG...guess who added me to his msn...ali cobra..it has been a year i ignored at 1st but he added me at another addie...desperado lol...we chatted and he seems ok...not so much the jerk i knew 1 yr ago...he seems to have changed but past experiences tell me otherwise...ill keep my guard up. gtg am tired  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.hi5.com/i?l=NCO1T2FQ  thats my hi5 link.do wateva u want with it.kool'
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was as uneventful as ever. last nite shamsan and i had a fite which lasted till like 3.30 in the morning.i cant recall what it was about exactly.but it was dumb....i feel so bad coz he has to work from 3 pm to 11 pm today and he is gonna be in a room controlling all police activity....he is a policeman..inspector...insspector sexy i call him lol welllllllll i gtgnow everyone is pesterin me keep ya posted
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just have so many emotions bursting inside me.i never knew that many emotions could exist at the same time. im happy sad amazed exited reluctant expectant all at the same time. i just cant wait to go home.i cant wait for uni. i cant wait to pick my outfit every day and have an excuse to buy clothes and makeup. i cant wait to make up for lost time with rach and my other frens. i cant wait to go down to malaysia n e time i want. i cant wait till i can afford a vespa.its gonne be pink..with a picture of the grim on it.Inshallah. that means god willing.Inshallah for everything. i hope everything will be ok for me.i just keep praying.it only just hit me this year when i started my a level course this year.....my life is just beginning. i can only pray for the best. even thogh i have been away from home for so long i have learned so much. it is satisfying to know that although unwillingly, i have learned alot the past 2.5 years.i met different types of people.dubai is a cultural melting pot.so many nationalities though mainly arab or indian subcontinent. its nice to know that i have one experience noone else will have.well tired now. doday is the start of the rest of my life
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i must be so boring. all i ever talk about is going home.i miss it.its boring me to death here in dubai.thepeople are fake,lazy,boring the weather sux the shopping sux.the stuff they serve in food courts are a miserable excuse for food.........ugh the movies come out weeks too late........terrible i hate it here some things are ok.the guys are really hot but they are sooooooo narrow minded and they only think of one thing...***..u noe wat i mean welll enuf complaining for now  keep posted 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well hello i decided to do this blog stuff coz ma best fren rachel in sg gave me the idea. she was online yesterday afta so long.man i miss her. i cant wait to go home. i miss her so much.i miss my home.but i love my bf though.i hope he can come home with me and further his education with me. i really want him to meet rach. im so homesick.i hate it here in dxb.its ok but i just miss home.i missed my teenhood.i should have been in sg not in dxb. i haf so many regrets keep ya posted
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i have had this new blog for sometime now.....come visit me..... www.tabulas.com/~ainjiwa
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i have had this blog for quite some time now.....feel free to visit me at my new adress www.tabulas.com/~ainjiwa
     
    
</post>


</Blog>