<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today, at work, we had an asian waiter working instead of a usual girl. He was waiting a table of about 10-12 men, all of which are your typical "I hate the blacks, Jews, and Mex-ee-cans. WOOO! White power!" type guys. They, together, had a $100 bill...The waiter, being Asian and not white, got 50cents as a tip. That's just really shitty, yes?  And then, when a different table was payign at the register, the guy paying couldn't even look the vendor in the eye because he was hispanic.  Sometimes I really fucking hate living in the South.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I'm off from work early, which is great because I'm tired as hell and I want to take a nap...  Good god, I've turned into my grandfather...  Anyway, I'm getting really fucking tired of rain. It's been raining here pretty much all week, and we're having flash flood warnings around the clock...  And, to top it off, I don't have any TV thanks to shitty SBC Yahoo/Dish and Roadrunner/Time Warner Cable.  Acutally, I've got the only TV, that does have channels on it, in my room, so I get the joy of having my stench-filled brother in my room if he wants to watch TV. Oh joy...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah...apparently, I'm a poet, but I did know it.  Well, I try to do poetry. here's my latest, if anyone happens to read it and feels like commenting, feel free:  Euthanasia  The tulips rise into the sky And reach their interweaving petals to the heavens In search of life, Only to be given that, From their heart underground. They sulkily sleep to untrained eye, But to me they are alive, Asking me to just touch them. To hold them and show them they are loved. To give them what we all essentially want. Their hearts beat, Pumping pigment into their thin skin shell. Green, Complimentary to our mammalian red, Spreads the color to the eye catchers, The petals. Their shade, Dependent upon the sun's rays, Gives direction for my pupils to follow. Standing over this creature, I can see the fireworks are going off inside its arms, Slowly getting brighter and more powerful, Until someday, Those arms are spent, And start to wither, And start to flail, And become limp, And fall onto the ground. But me, I can't let that happen. It is my obligation, As a witness of this display of chroma, To cut this being's life now, While it still has its dignity, While it still has its color, And while it's not in pain. And I do. I take its stem, And make a clean, swift cut, Tearing this being from its heart underground. I take this tulip home, And place it in a vase, Where though it's dead already, Its beauty overpowers The darkness of any room  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So here it is...  I finally broke down and got a blog, much to the chagrin of the Amish community, thwarting my efforts to run with the mainstream, and to always be different. Yet, I can't help but feel that I can now say what I want to say, when I want to say it, where i want to say it, and to whom i want to say it to.   So for those that see this, you should expect to see rants and occasional drunken diatribes in the near or distant future.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I've been in Alaska, washington, and Canada for a week and a half, which would explain my absence on here for 10 days...But as for the days prior to this? erm...a journal is a very easy thing to forget about.  Anyway, a new poem I've got:  The Writer of Poems, with himself would sit,  Until his work was full of wit.  Though never able to make of it,  That single greatness we all need.   In that room with somber eyes,  He left a breath of worthy cries,  And never thought to realize  That he will not succeed.   His life was left to be so grim,  Waiting for muses to come to him,  And beckon to his every whim,  Until he did his deed.   A single candle showed the light,  And helped The Writer in the night,  But never gave the gift of sight,  To those too blind to read.   The only muse that ever came,  A tiny moth too small for shame,  Was taken by the guiding flame,  More than willing to feed.   This single moth showed the strife,  Of every writer's lowly life.  And The Writer of Poems took his knife,  And made his poems bleed.   In that dirty, placid room,  Full of dark, and shaded gloom,  One can find his resting tomb,  Full of shameful greed.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      New Poem. This one, from others and from myself, is believed to be very good, with a funny twist at the end.  She sits there in her skimpy dress, Hair unfurled and in a mess, Only there to impress, With her sexy silhouette.  A youthful boy, of all the guys, Would catch a glimpse of hazel eyes, And suddenly, to no surprise, “Perhaps you'd like a cigarette?”  “If you insist,” a reply would be, “But have a seat here next to me.” An eager face would let her see, His thoughts of her in love.  She'd inch closer, to feel his heat, And slowly make his red heart beat, And there they'd stay, in the lonely street, With voyeur stars above.  She'd bat her eyelashes, and giggle delight, Whisper lovelies in the night, Lightly nibble and gently bite, And promise him her flower.  For thirty minutes, the games they'd play, In that lonesome bus stop sleigh, Until, at last, she'd slowly say, “It's two-fifty for an hour.” 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>