<Blog>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everyone.   Just thought I`d drop you another quick update before I leave to go skiing for the week (yeah baby!!!).  Christmas here was a blast, so much food, so much wine, so many people, so much food, oh yeah and did I mention the food.  Seriously I haven`t stopped eating for like 4 days.  It`s been pretty interesting.  I even went to a French Church Service on Christmas Eve at Midnight.  Wow Eh!  It was the first time I`d been to church in about 10 years.  I was relieved i didn`t start foaming at the mouth (exorcist style) when I walk in the door :-)  So all the songs were in French, all the bits where you answer the Priest were in French, and the Lord`s Prayer (or whatever it is) was also in French.  So I basically just kept my mouth shut.   One of the hardest things about Christmas though, for Marc and his family, was the fact that Suzanne`s (Marc`s Mums) mother is dying.  She came to Christmas night here at Marc;s house - so Marc, Myself and his Uncle had to go pick her up from the nursing home.  She is in a wheel chair, and can only move her fingers, and her face a little bit.  She can still smile and make a little noise like Yes and No..But other than that, not really a lot.  I`m not to sure what she has, but the basic gist of it is her central nervous system is deterorating..and eventually her lungs will stop working.  Its been very hard for Marc and his family to watch such a proud woman succumb to such a cruel disease.  Especially given that just two years ago, she was playing golf and exercising at the gym as fit as a fiddle.  However, it was a pretty moving experience to talk with her, and see the reactions on her face.  Her brain is 100-percent with-it...It`s just the body that is not co-operating.  For me it was the first time I`d ever had to go into a nursing home of this type (basically a hospital for old people who are going to die.)  It really opened my eyes to some things, that luckily I`ve never seen anyone in my family go through yet. So, I am now little wiser on these matters to say the least.   Anyway hope I didn`t put a dampener on things...But on the bright side I got SOOOOOO many presents for Christmas from Marc and his family ...it was incredible.  I certainly did not expect such generosity from a family I`ve only just met.  I got about 10 boxes of chocolates, some monkey slippers, wine, food, an alarm clock, a sweater, the new Sarah McLachlan CD, Dr Phil`s Guide to good food (to help me once I`ve eaten all the chocolate), and a bunch of other things.  I think his Dad`s present was one of the best though.  He gave me two lift passes for the best mountains in Quebec. (about 200 bucks worth).  So I was pretty stoked.  He`s also lent me his 1000 dollar ski suit, and a pair of skis.  How good is that.  So yesterday I snapped up a pair of second hand Ski Boots for a cool 70 bucks (and I didn`t have to pay tax) also got poles and goggles thrown in....soooooo I`m officially ready to hit the mountain (hit being the opporative word there).  I think most people will be wondering why someone with such good ski gear, is tumbling down the slope on his ass.  LOL.  Which in reality is probably what will happen, as I`ve never skiied anywhere in my whole life (Gulp.)   Anyway moving right along.  For boxing day we went to Marc`s Auntie`s chalet at Mount Saint Sauveur about 45 minutes out of Montreal.  I got to walk on all the ski slopes, for the first time.  It looked so so so fun, and I was all excited like.  `Lets ski now now now now`.  But I couldn`t because I had no boots then, and also I had to go sign the lease for my apartment.   Which brings me to my next news.  I now have a place to live.  We signed the lease for the apartment yesterday.  So we move in on January 5th.  Then I officially start looking for a job.  So that`s the next big challenge.  But for now I`m just breathing a big sigh of relief that I can start my new year in a new apartment.  Especially because Marc`s family have been so gracious...I really didn`t want to wear out my welcome here.  So, I can now say I OFFICIALLY live in Montreal, Quebec.  How cool is that.  I`ll forward you all my address for the endless house warming presents I know I`m bound to receive from all my friends. :-)   Ayyway have to go now, my suitcases are packed, and I`m off to go skiing in Quebec city for the next week, with Marc`s Dad and his brothers and sisters.  Hope everyone had a wonderful Chrissie...all the best for the new year.   Love  James :-) 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The good news is, my PR work appears to have paid off.  We got the first apartment we applied for. And they even through in a washer, dryer and fridge.  WAA HOO!!!.   So it looks good.  However we haven`t actually signed a lease yet....so I`m not going to count my chickens until I`ve got a legally binding egg. (so to speak)   But just thought I`d say, it looks like I`m no longer homeless...(fingers crossed)   So that`s 1 down.  Now I just have to find a job.  Here is my list of potential new careers in order of preference.   1.) Evil Dictator (have seen a vacancy in Downtown Baghdad)  2.) Toy Boy (I`m pretty sure I could let some old rich lady have her way with me for the right price)  3.) Advisor to President George W Bush (I heard this vacancy actually never got filled in the first place)  4.) The third and more masculine sister of Paris and Nikki Hilton.  5.) Whitney Houston`s cocaine dealer.   What do you guys think?   More news as it comes to hand   James 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Heya..   Well we've had record snow falls...(trust 'me' to invite this type of  weather).  So unfortunately skiing today was cancelled because of the  strong winds.  So it looks like I'll be learning this at a later stage.   So today is Sunday.  We have to go and look at some apartments, as  we'll be moving to Montreal in January.  This part of things is a  little difficult, as I have no job, and not a lot of money.  So Marc  and me, and Carine (our flatmate to-be) have been figuring out ways to  'cook the books' a little, so that we look like dutiful and responsible  tenants.   Marc is wearing a suit today (haha), its the first time I've seen himin  anything other than cargo pants and a ski jacket....ever!!.  I, on the  otherhand, may just have become the youngest ever foreign  correspondent, or maybe I'll be a young entrepereneur traversing the  globe, setting up some sort of technology I'm yet to invent.  Needless  to say, we will be stretching the truth a little on this issue, or I'll  be sleeping in the park.  And -15 ain't to comfortable at the best of  times, least of all when it's on a park bench.   At least I can say all those years in the media (all 3 of them) have  taught me something.  IMAGE IS EVERYTHING.  The other thing it has  taught me to do, is to lie well -- and how to....what we technically  like to call in the industry 'beat up the story'. So with these  invaluable skiils hopefully we'll be able to snag a good apartment (not  the easiet thing to do at this time of the year).  I just have to do a  little PR work, and smoochzing with the landlords -- lets hope they're  bi-lingual (gulp!!)   On a brighter note, I've also had a couple of people put my name  forward to a few of the TV stations here.  So we'll see what happens  (fingers crossed).  Otherwise maybe I'll get some work as a waiter,  cleaner or a toy boy for some old dame (hey I'll do whatever it takes)   Anyway better run, Marc has nearly done a Michael Hutchence in his attempts to put his tie on.   (Hmm, we are very different people in some ways :-)...namingly fashion.   Take care, have a great Christmas.  Will write soon.   James 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everyone...   I hope you`re enjoying your spate of hot weather.  I`ve had a couple  of emails from a few of you saying that most of the days this week are  in the high 20`s / low 30`s....  and from a few sadistic people I`ve  even been emailed pictures of a few of you lazing around on the beach  in bikinis and board shorts. :-P.  Looks like I`m missing a good  summer.   Anyway, despite a lot of snow...things are going really well up here  in the Northern Hemisphere.  Yesterday I joined the gym that Marc`s  family go to.  Marc`s been pretty busy with work, so yesterday his Mum  and Michelle took me to the health club where we all did a work out.   I`d forgotton how unfit I was.  Needless to say, I am now very very  sore today.  But it was good to start doing exercise again (something  that has eluded me for the last year whilst I`ve been working to save  for this trip.)  I`ve also been studying more and more French.  Marc  tells me that I`m over-doing it...but I am determined to get good as  soon as possible.  I must admit it is one of the more difficult  aspects of living in Montreal -- not speaking the primary language  that is.  Whilst on one-hand it is forcing me to get my ass into gear  and study a lot, on the other hand it continues to isolate me from  conversations when we go out with Marc`s friends.  And it`s the  everyday things like not understanding TV or Radio programmes, not be  able to say what you want over dinner, and not being able to ask for  directions or instructions from locals (something I often need to do  when I`m on my own ).   Every now and then I feel disheartened, and feel like I`m not picking  things up as quickly as I could be.  However, on the bright side, I  refuse to let myself become negative about `what I don`t know`, and  instead remain positive about the things I do know.  So this is not  really me complaining...but I guess more me trying to explain the  downside of what is otherwise a great opportunity.   So to change the subject...I heard they nabbed Saddaam Hussein eh??   That must have been a fun day in the newsroom.  For those of you who I  worked with (at Nine)...Tell me what were the words in the keyshot for  the story that night.  I`m willing to bet they read something along  the lines of `WE GOT HIM`...let me know how close I was.  And as for  FOX FM...what time did this story break?  Was it a busy breakfast  shift...tell me tell me, I`m having `breaking story` withdrawls.  LOL.   BUt seriously, it actually was a bit frustrating the way I found out.   Marc and I had just been to his father`s cottage (aka holiday house)  in the Mountains about 4 hours North of Montreal.  So we were on our  way home from there (in the biggest snow storm this year apparantly)  doing 20 km`s an hour on the freeway when the news flash came on....IN  F**KEN FRENCH.  So hear I am going... `What`s happened`, `What`s  happened`...`Have they Got him`, And I`m just making out bits and  pieces of the story...Like `Caught south of Tikrit`....and then I hear  a few grabs from Bush and Blair.  Poor Marc was saying....Shut up  while I listen, and then I`ll translate for you.  It was pretty  funny....but also a little frustrating as well, especially for someone  like me.  The other big story in Canada was that they just got a new  prime minister `Paul Martin`...so that`s been all over the TV on every  Channel with his swearing in ceremony.   Moving on...I hope this email isn`t to long, but for those of you who  are bored...don`t feel like you have to read everything if you can`t  be assed. I`ll just give you a little account of where I`ve been since  my last email.  As I did mention we went up to the mountains to Marc`s  Dad`s place (really really magnificent).  It`s right on the snow  fields....tucked away from everything.  So we drank lots of good  french wine, had the open fire going, and went for `snow shoe` walks.   I`ll email the pictures when I get my laptop working (damn Canadian  power sockets...I have the wrong plug).  It was really cold in the  mountains -20 and very windy.  We have had the biggest snow fall so  far this year.  I spent last night shovelling the snow out of both  Marc`s Mum and Dads driveways.  All the cars are snowed in, the roads  are slow.  And Marc told me the traffic reports on the radio on the  way home from the mountains said something along the lines of, ``Stay  home, don`t go anywhere, the roads are to dangerous...and the accident  list took about 5 minutes to read`.   The other place I visited on the weekend was Quebec City.  It`s about  3 hours from Montreal.  And its so so French.  Like, absolutely no-one  talks any English at all.  But it was a truly enchanting place.  The  city is up on a cliff top overlooking the St Laurence River.  Marc  said it was the first city founded in Canada (dunno if that`s right)   But anyway, you can imagine the buildings.  I`ve never been to  Europe....but that`s what it felt like.  It was a maze of cobbled  streets, grand cathedrals, christmas lights, and brass lamp posts.    The whole city looked just about as festive as I`ve ever seen a city  look.  They had a famous shop that just sells Christmas decorations  all year round.  In short...Great City, can`t wait to go back.   Anyway, this week maybe a little boring for me.  Marc has a lot of  work to do.  I am going to the Museum of Contemporary Art on Wednesday  to see an exhibition on `The 70`s`...so that will be good.  But in the  meantime, it`s back to my homework.  If I never have to conjugate  another French verb for the rest of my life it will be to soon.   Miss you all heaps.   A Bientot  (see you later)   James 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Everyone...   Thought I`d write a second email as I`ve got a little time up my  sleeve.  A little has happened since I last wrote home.  First thing  was Marc surprised me by getting home 2 days early...that was pretty  good.  So we`ve had the weekend catching up and him telling me about  his trip.  Unfortunately he`s been a little sick (and the doctor thinks  he may have caught a parasite in Mexico.)  But he only gets sick for a  couple of hours a day...and the rest of the time he is fine.  So I`m a  bit worried...But hopefully it will pass.   On a brighter note...His family are so so awesome.  I can`t even  describe how these people have embraced my presence here.  I already  feel like one of the family (despite the fact only his sister and his  step-father speak a little English).  Anyway I`ll tell you a little bit  about them.  His Mum`s name is Suzanne...She has no English at all.   His sister Isobelle is 16...she is a amazingly attractive girl...who`s  really shy and mature.  Most of the time she`s studying.  She`s really  into art and politics.  HIs little brother is Jean-Michael, he`s your  typical 14 year old guy.  He spends his time skiiing, playing ice  hockey, snowboarding.  He`s taken me out snow boarding....which was  great fun.  He forced me to go over this jump at his house....so funny.   First of all I landed flat on my ass in the snow, but by the end of  the night...I wasn`t too bad.  His step father is Michael (pron.  Michelle).  He used to be a school principal.  I think he`s been my  greatest asset here, and he`s become my French tutor.  We are spending  a couple of hours a day speaking French...and I find myself always  going to my books to read more, or to learn new words, or asking what  signs say, or saying `how do you say this is French`...or `what did  he/she just say.`  I`ve become like a curious two year old.  Actually  I`d say learning French is the hardest thing I`ve ever done in my  entire life....but conversely, it`s also the most rewarding.  I am  having little conversations with everyone...asking questions, ordering  food in restaurants, telling Marc things.  It`s great because everytime  I attempt it...I get a little smile from whoever I`m talking  to....generally everyone is really impressed that I`m picking stuff up  so fast...which is a good motivator to keep learning more.  There`s  always those little mistakes that stuff you up along the way though.   Like a funny one yesterday night...we were in a Computer store just  before going to see Matrix 3, and Marc asked me in French If I liked  playing a particular playstation game...to which I replied `I don`t  like orgasms`.  Marc`s jaw just hit the ground...and he`s like...`OK...  now that was very wrong`.  Damn all these words sounding the same...the  possibilies for mistakes are just endless.   Anyway, I`m doing a lot of reading, a lot of study, and going for a lot  of walks.  I`m enjoying sleeping in, and not having to be anywhere in  particular.  This weekend we`re going to Marc`s cottage in the  mountains where I`m going to get to use a ...wait for it....SNOW  MOBILE!!!!!  For those of you who`ve seen me on a jet ski...you`ll know  how excited I am about this.  And there is so much snow...already I`ve  become so accustomed to it.  It piles up to the door, and when you open  it, it comes tumbling in.  Everytime you start a car, you have to  scrape all the windows.  There`s lots of funny little everyday things,  that you need to do to copê in this environment.   Well, I`ll stop boring everyone now.  Hope life in Australia is great.   Thanks to everyone who wrote to me and told me how hot it is in  Australia...you can all get fucked.  :-).  I have two pairs of jeans  on, and two jumpers, a jacket and a beanie.  But I like it, the  atmosphere from the people here is still warm.   I`ll try and take some photos soon to show you where I`m living   `A la prochaine`   JAMES 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello Everyone.  Hope everyone is well.  I`m finally at Marc`s good friend Emilie`s house an hour south of Montreal in the countryside.  There`s frozen lakes, squirrel`s running around.  It`s all very `Fargo` or `Snow Falling on Cedars` to compare to it to a few movies.  But anyway, now that I`m not paying by the minute to use the computer, I can sit down and actually try and recount my first couple of days here.  So here goes.  Well first of all the flight from Melbourne was delayed by an hour because we had `technical errors`, so as you can imagine - i was sitting there in my seat with images of the plane`s engines failing half-way across the Pacific, and me coming to an untimely end in the middle of the ocean.  However thankfully it was not the case.  My attempts to get a business class upgrade (by wearing a nice shirt and slacks) weren`t quite successful - however I got the next best thing, the elusive exit row seat next to the window.  YAY!!!.  So needless to say the flight over was incredibly comfortable, despite being long.  However the hour delay in Melbourne had consequently made me late for my connecting flight to Montreal, so after a quick dash through customs and befriending an LA gangster who showed me the way from terminal 4 to terminal 2 (about 10 km`s for anyone who’s been to LA airport)  I finally dragged my ass and my overweight luggage to Air Canada, and made the connection by 15 minutes.  Phew! Very close.  The flight to Montreal was pleasant (5 hours)  And I got to Dorval airport about 7.30 at night.  Next was immigration.  I swear I must have got the only immigration officer who was doing his first day on the job.  He tried to tell me my Visa was only valid until next April....However, after me explaining that the 12-month VISA letter was called the 12-month Visa because it was reminiscent of the amount of time I was permitted to spend in the country, he finally accepted that I was most likely correct, and reprinted it with an amended date.  So, to cut a long story short...I can stay for 12 months now, if finances permit.  So by this stage, the whole airport was empty...My baggage is spinning round on the carousel by itself (thank god it hadn`t been stolen)  And Marc`s friend Emilie was still dutifully waiting for me at the airport gate.  So finally I walk outside into my first Montreal winter night.  My first word`s to the city...`Jesus fucken christ it`s cold`...(Sorry Mum, but unfortunately I can`t lie.)  Ok for those of you who don`t know what -10 feels like.  It is damn damn cold.  Like I`m talking the feeling you get when you go into the fridge at Liquorland to buy a slab of beer -- except even colder.  And I had like 3 layers of Jackets on.  Anyway, after quickly realising I was going to need some serious thermals...we then headed for my hostel.  But first a quick detour past Emilie`s theatre class.  It was really interesting to spend my first couple of hours listening to a French reading of `Douze Hommes en Colére` (12 angry Men).  Very very funny.  I understood like every 100th word, but was surprisingly able to get the general idea of what was going on -- which was mostly a lot of yelling.  Another interesting thing was that no one at the reading spoke English...So they were trying to communicate with me, and me with them.  They were very friendly...But sheesh it is so intimidating to be the only person in the room who can`t speak the language.  Character building to say the very least.  Ok I`ll skip forward a bit, to save everyone from the inevitable boredom of recounting my steps move by move.  Went to the hostel Yada yada yada -- its really nice.  Lots of great interesting people.  The next day Emilie was busy with homework so I took to the streets of Montreal on my own, the temperature a `balmy` -6 degrees.  However the sun was shining, so altogether it wasn`t too bad.  One of the funniest things I quickly discovered was that you can`t stay out in the street for more than about 10 minutes before you have to duck into a shop to unthaw.  The temperatures in all the buildings are so well controlled, so most of the time you feel just right inside, even if you are wearing a couple of thick layers.  The other really amazing innovation that the people here have come up with, is this entire underground shopping complex that links about 4 or 5 blocks of the CBD.  It really is fantastic.  It also joins up with all the Metros (stations)  So on the really really cold days you can avoid going outside altogether.  The city itself is really cosmopolitan and so, so charming.  It’s got a great European influence, but with all the mod-cons of a typical Canadian city.  It’s French through and through from the cutesy little signs, to the cobbled streets, to the clusters of ball shaped street lamps and in many places there’s beautiful old buildings, and great historic architecture...but at the same time it still feels like a busy, fast paced business hub - an ironic combination to say the least.  The city itself rests on the banks of the Saint Laurence River, which is mammoth, and has one of the largest shipping docks in Canada.  At this time of the year its partly frozen, so it looks absolutely spectacular.  The dock is right near a place called (Old Montreal)  which is basically where the city was founded, and still has all the really old buildings.  This part feels extremely European, and is basically entirely French.  I have had a few chances to give my pathetic excuse for the French language a go...with some somewhat amusing results.  For instance the waiter in one restaurant looked at me bemused when I mistakenly asked him for `12` forks instead of two.  And for some reason I got the words `suitcases` and ‘sunglasses` mixed up which also produced a few perplexed looks from the hostel staffs.  But generally, I am still speaking in English once I get past the whole `Hi`, `How are you`, `How much is this` part of the conversation in shops.  But that little luxury is gone as of today...for I am now in an entirely French country town, which speaks no English what-so-ever.  I got the bus here today, and I couldn’t even ask the bus driver to tell me when I got to the last stop.  So sometimes, the language barrier makes you feel isolated, and all round... pretty bloody scared.  Especially when you`re on your own.  So that’s basically `it` in a nutshell.  Things a good.  I really love it here. It really feels like a proper winter seeing all the snow, and the squirrels running around, the baron trees along the partially frozen river, and the throngs of people dressed immaculately in their fur winter coats, and those Russian looking fur hats (I so gotta get me one of those.)  You can basically wear anything you want on your head (a whole yak`s ass if you think it`d keep you warm) and nobody would bat an eyelid at you.  I think everyone is pretty much in the same  boat of just trying to stay warm. And its only going to get colder – around -30 in January which to me is just a joke not even worth contemplating.  I think I might consider a drive down to Miami when the temperatures plummet down to those depths.  Anyway, Marc gets home from Mexico tomorrow night.  For those who don`t know he`s been there for 3 months living in a tiny little village (with no running water or electricity).  So he`s pretty excited about getting back...but I spoke to him on the phone yesterday and he says he`s really grown fond of the place and his host family...and was actually very very sad to be leaving.  He says living with such poor but remarkable people has changed him irreversibly.  Which was quite a profound thing, and has made me think twice about how easy I actually have it.  So tonight I get to spend the evening with Emilie and her parents (who don`t speak English)  So once again I`ll get another chance to try to improve my French.  Thanks to everyone whose been writing to me.  I promise I`ll get back to everyone eventually...its just I have been pretty eager to get out and explore.  Will let you know how things are getting on, and how my hypothermia is.  At this stage I just have a cold (runny nose and cough)...but it’s not that bad.  Miss you all heaps, and you can all get fucked for having so much sun.  Damn.. I was on the beach 4 days ago (WHAT AM I DOING!!!!) haha  Much love James 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, After 20 hours on a plane I am here.  And let me assure you -10 is  definitely as cold as it sounds.  The first thing I did was go out and buy  new gloves, new beanie, new scarf, new thermal underwear.  My cotton cargo pants felt like I was wearing ice blocks down my legs.  Anyway, I'm in a bit of a rush because I have limited time...but I'll give  everyone the brief run down. The plane trip was fine...I didn't sleep much, but other than that it was good.  Los Angeles airport still sucks..and I nearly missed my flight because the Nazi'a at US customs took so long.  But I just scraped in there.  I got to Montreal quite late, and had a little trouble with my VISA...but  I finally explained things properly to the immigtration officer (so  everything is A-ok now).   But other than that everything is going surprisingly well so far.  Montreal is an amazing city...it has a real atmosphere about  it. The French is extremely prevalent...but at the same time it's comforting to know that if I can't say what I need to - I can just slip back to  English.  Anyway, its lunch time now...so I',m off to go and explore.  Just wanted to  let everyone know I got here ok.  I am in great spirits, and that I'll write a more detailed email when I'm not paying so much for internet access from a cafe.  Thanks for all the well wishes, and the great going away party.  Please  write back when you get a chance.  Merci, au revoir.  James 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, will keep this short.  I just had my first day at work.  Really, really great.  Great company.  tonnes of paper work. (just the usual stuff they want your first born child and a vial of your blood to hang around their necks....nothing more than what most companies expect these days.)  I made a mistake on my first day (I didn't wear a tie).  Ooops.  I thought I could get away with it because I knew my fasion sense was better than everybody elses.  Alas, individualism is not part of the company model, and I was asked politely if I could wear a tie tomorrow.  Sooo.....Since I had no ties, I had to go and buy 10.  And since I can't wear cheap ties because I'm allergic to them, I had to buy expensive ones.  Oh well I'll just have to sell more computers.  One thing I will say seriously though is I'm getting some pretty damn cool training.  They give us product seminars everyday, I'm learning about networks, servers and software licensing.  How to source my own clients, how to sell really well, how to f**k people over for thousands and make it look like I'm doing them a favor, how to build big accounts, etc.  The great thing is we have these things called 'spiffs' where a company...say IBM for instance pays us money to sell their product.  And heaps of companies do it...so there's heaps of commission and sales to be made.  The bad thing is Canada only has 2 weeks annual holidays a year.  JESUS!!! WHAT ARE THEY THINKING!!  I had 5 weeks paid in Australia.  Ok I know I promised brief, brief, brief...but there's always so much to say.  I'll finish by saying it's been so so so so cold.  Like so so so cold.  I had my first taste of -40.  And on my way home tonight it was only like -5, and I actually found myself saying "Oh what a lovely evening, it's so warm tonight."  I think I am officially losing the plot.  Keep me posted. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gone are my days of cargo pants and runners, as I prepare to begin my life as a `Corporate Whore.`  I start work on Monday as a Sales Executive for one of North America’s largest online IT companies (sounds impressive hey…don`t worry I`m sure it`s not).  The area I will be looking after is on the East Coast of the US, covering New York to Massachusetts.  So I`ll have some pretty big clients which will be great.  It will also give me a chance to build on my business skills which are still in their infant stages.  I have a 4 week intensive training program which also comes with a Sales and Marketing accreditation, (bound to look good on my otherwise luster-lacking CV.)  One outing this week did lead to quite an amusing little story which I`ll tell now.  It started with my business wardrobe, or lack thereof.  I`ve only got a couple of nice shirts with me from Australia, so Marc thought that it would be a good idea to buy some more business clothes 2nd hand  This way I wouldn`t be wasting money on items that I`d only need to use this year.  Reluctantly I agreed (no easy feat for someone like me who`s been known to spend in excess of $200 on a single shirt.)  So it was with great courage and humility that I turned a blind eye to downtown Montreal`s plethora of high-end fashion stores, and proceeded on to the Salvation Army`s 2nd hand clothes outlet.  However…my frown soon turned to a grin when our car pulled up at what must have been the biggest second hand clothes store in the Northern Hemisphere.  My elation was further amplified when I realised that most of the clothes in the store were from well known designers like Yves Saint Laurent, Banana Republic and Pierre Cardin. (all at a fraction of the price I`d normally pay)    I raced through the racks like a kid in a candy store gobbling up what I naturally saw to be the most exciting clothes sales since the day Daimaru closed it doors.  Pretty soon I`d accumulated an entire shopping trolley of business shirts and pants (all at the tidy sum of $3 to $4 a piece.)  Needless to say Marc`s little exercise in `cost effectiveness` backfired dramatically, and he looked at me with disgust as I lobbed my haul to the register.  Marc`s friend Marie-Pierre (a veteran of the Vintage Clothes trade) was heard to remark that she`d never seen anybody plough through the racks with such voracity.  And the little old lady who served me looked equally as bemused as she clocked up what must have been her biggest sale in history.  To sum up -- old habits die hard, and clothes budgets are like religions -- they’re well and truly ingrained.  So when the clothes got cheaper, I simply did what anyone in my shoes would have done.  I adjusted the quantity accordingly.  Thus my winter wardrobe is now complete, and I’ll kick start my corporate life looking the part.  (Keeping in mind the journalist’s code of ethics: Never divulge your sources.)  Hope you’re all well  James 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone.  I just thought I`d touch base because I haven`t written in a while.  I was going to wait until I had a job, and then write to you.  But it looks as though I`m very close now...so I thought I`d update what I`ve been doing at late.  First thing first.  Montreal has been going through what we affectionately like to call a `dague de froid`..which in laimens terms means, A whole lot of very bloody cold days altogether.  This week has been one of the coldest Montreal has seen for years.  The temperatures (when you include the wind factor) have plummeted below -30, and even down as far as around -37, -38.  Which, to my great pleasure has coincided nicely with my week of job interviews.  So, in short, I`ve been trudging through the snow from one employer to the next, in my best suit and tie, trying to avoid freezing to death (by no means an easy exercise.).  And because of my long-existing case of hair vanity I was even trying to do it WITHOUT my beanie.  Fortunately common sense got the better of me, and I resorted to just doing my hair again in the employers bathroom before going into my interview.  (that is except for one extreme case, where in an act defying physics my hair gel froze in its bottle.)    One loud mouth New Yorker at the bus terminal was even heard to quote.  `63 YEARS...IN 63 YEARS I NEVER SAW WEATHER LIKE THIS.  NEVER IN MY WHOLE LIFE`.  He then proceeded to rant on like this for another 10 minutes until the bus came -- Ignoring the fact that most of the people at the bus stop spoke French, and most likely didn`t understand him anyway.  I considered punching him to shut him up, but quickly decided I was too cold to move my arms.  So, moving on to the job hunting -- it`s gone pretty well.  I`ve been offered quite a few cushy positions in call centres but have turned them down in the hope of finding something a little better.  It looks as though I will begin work for an IT company as an account manager in 10 days.  They`re just verifying the references I was given before I left (Big thanks to Jonathan and Ken for those), and it looks like that will be my job here if everything goes well.  But I`m not 100 percent sure, so I`ll have to let you know.  The good thing about this job is that Marc is a computer geek, and has been getting me up to speed on the products I`ll be selling.  (150,000 of them in total.)  I know, I know, I`ve sold my soul to the devil and entered the lucrative world of IT sales.  But hey, maybe deep down I`m a geek and I just never knew it.  Marc seems to think so.  Apart from that I`ve been doing night courses in French at the YMCA language centre.  It`s a really great place, and I`ve quickly made some new friends.  The classes have been a little more difficult though, because the teacher ONLY speaks in French 100-percent of the time.  So I`ve been adjusting to trying to understand everything...and am slowly getting better day by day.  The apartment is nice and WARM with heaters in every room, and we`ve all settled in nicely.  Marc starts back at school for his final semester on Monday.  (They have their big vacation in July.)  He also says to say thanks to everyone who wrote back to him about the photos he sent.  (If anyone couldn`t open the attachment, just send me an email and I`ll forward you a couple of jpeg attachments.)  That`s all for now though.  We`ve had snow, ice, wind and a few mini blizzards.  But I`m still alive, slowly finding my feet, and loving every minute of it.  Be in touch soon.  James XX 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK...   So everything was going fine up here in Montreal...that was until last night. Marc and I were driving back from the apartment in Montreal, after a 3 hour trip through what must have been the biggest IKEA store in the northern hemisphere -- (we`d been shopping for furniture for the apartment.)   Anyway, the roads here yesterday were an absolute nightmare.  There`d been an ice storm, so it was basically impossible to brake effectively, as the car just kept sliding on the road.  And the whole day I`d just been on edge everytime we got in the car.  So it gets to about 11.30 pm, we`re heading down the highway after dropping off Marc`s friend off at her house.  The whole trip I was really nervous, just because there was so much snow and ice on the highway.  To make matters worse it was still raining ice while we were driving....so visibility was pretty low as well.   We were about 20 minutes from Marc`s Mum`s house, and I`d just started to relax talking to Marc about the apartment and what sort of job I`d start looking for...when the worst possible thing happened.  The back tyre on the van we were driving (like a Toyota Tarago van) blew.  So we went into an uncontrollable spin at 100 kilometres an hour...fishtailing down the highway.  We then slid across the medium strip seperating the two directions of the highway, straight through all the snow that has built up there, and right into the path of the traffic travelling in the opposite direction.  (the average speed of the traffic is about 120 km/h)   By this stage I`m screaming at Marc, s**t, s**t we`re in the path of the oncoming traffic...DRIVE DRIVE.  So Marc`s jammed the exalerator down, and we`ve skidded back into the medium strip and into the snow.  Not a moment too soon either, because no sooner had we done so than about 10 semi trailers all flew past all speeding...and there`s no way they would have been able to stop on the ice.   So we just sat there, panting, silent.  I didn`t no whether to laugh or cry or what to do.  There were two police cars up the road patrolling the area.  (Apparently the conditions were so bad that there`d already been 6 car accidents that night..just on a single stretch of the highway)  So the policeman shouted something out on his loud speaker to us in French.  And soon a tow truck came and towed as back out of the snow back onto the highway.  So we paid him the hefty 60 dollar fee for his 20 seconds of work and started to drive again.   However... what we failed to realise was that the back tyre had actually blown.  Marc still hadn`t figured our why he`d lost control.  After all we were doing the speed limit, and by all accounts driving fairly carefully.  So Marc still couldn`t control the car when we tried to start driving it again.  By this stage, the highway police who`d been trailing us again told us to pull over.  This time they called a proper tow truck.  20 minutes later the vans winched up on the back of this massive truck and he tows us to the nearest truck stop.   Next problem.  Neither Marc or I has ever changed a tire on a car before -- let alone on a bloddy 8 person van.  For a start we couldn`t even find the tyre.  Oh yes, and did I mention that it`s -10 degrees outside and still snowing.  No I don`t think I did...Ok so its -10 degrees, snowing, we`ve just both narrowly escaped death by a matter of minutes, its now 1 am in the morning, we can`t find the tire...and between the two of us we only have one pair of gloves to keep our hands from freezing.   We eventually figured out that the spare tire on these type of vans is kept underneath the car.  So Marc had to get down on his back (in the freezing snow) slide under the car and losen the hinge so we could get it out.  It took us an hour to change the tire ..not because we couldn`t figure out how to do it.  But because all the bolts on the rim were frozen.  Not to mention the fact that our hands were red raw from the cold.   Anyway, finally the tow truck man came back and helped us out a little by jacking the car up more with his truck...which made things heaps easier.  But needless to say by the time I got home I was in a pretty bad state of shock.  I know it doesn`t sound that bad in an email...but I can assure you the highways in this city are absolutely treacherous.  And it didn`t take long for it to kick in just exactly how close a call we`d actually had.   Anyway, by 4am, we`d both managed a hot shower and a chance to calm down.  I gave Mum a call back in Melbourne, to tell her what had just happened.  I think i scared the s**t out of her, because she had to go to the bathroom twice while we were on the phone.  (sorry Mum.)   Anyway, that`s all I can write for now.  But Marc is putting together a little photo presentation with some photos and the like --  which I will send through in a couple of hours or so.   That`s the latest from here though.  I CHEATED DEATH!!!  HAHA...But it damn damn scary and i don`t ever want to drive again.   Miss you all heaps.  Sorry I`m taking so long to reply to all the individual emails.  Will be in touch again soon.   Love  James  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Hey...   Sorry I missed out on saying Happy New Year, I was skiing somewhere in a far away land where email doesn`t exist yet.   Anyway I`m back now....thanks to everyone for wishing me a happy new year.  (Mum you`re sooo fired because you forgot to email me, I will be employing a new Montreal Mum to replace you :-P)   Well, what can I say about skiing....I`m better than I thought I would be.  HOWEVER....a large part of my learning experience did involve sliding down the goddam mountains on my ass.  But that was only because it was a little bit ìcy`...so I did have an excuse.  On the whole it was an absolute hoot, and I have put `ski instructor` down on my list of possible new careers.  I was thinking of doubling up as a ski instructor who also teaches French.  Marc thinks that this may not be such a wise career move.   Speaking of which...I have been strictly forbidden to divulge anymore details on my ski-trip, as Marc wishes to write the email himself (he says that this way it will be more honest.)  So expect an account of the trip from him in the next day or so.   I will say one more thing though, which I`m sure Marc won`t being telling you....How`s this!!!  I spent New Years Eve dancing to Grease Lightening and the Beatles played from a laptop.  I then saw the countdown for 2004 on the television...(Ab Fab style)  And then Marc drank so much red wine, by the time it got to shaking hands with everyone at midnight, he`d passed out next to the toilet.  So my first few hours of 2004 were spent....holding Marc`s head back while he threw up.  For shame.  I personally would never let myself get to such an inebbriated state.  I was shocked :-P   Anyway more emails on the way shortly.   James  P.S. - I have set my email to automatically reject emails that contain the current week`s temperature in Melbourne 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello from the North…  I hope everyone is well.  I hear your summer down there has ‘piked’ out on you?  That’ll teach you all for teasing me in December about the hot weather you were having.  Now what have you got – floods!!  That’s karma for you.  Anyway, here is another little number from my keyboard (please feel free to delete it if you don’t feel like hearing about my recent observations and experiences.)  To start off with, I have completed my first week of training for my new job and I am now proud to say I’m a now lot more ‘geekier’ than I used to be.  For instance did you know that:  •	switches are better than hubs  •	WANS (Wireless area networks) are made up of LANS (local area networks), and can also be part of MANS (metropolitan area networks.  •	Despite common misconceptions SOHO is not actually a place in London, it’s a “Small Office/Home Office.” •	And as for the meaning of ‘Daisy Chaining’ – well, let me tell you it’s enough to get even your best coaxial cables in a knot.  So there you have it…I may not speak French yet, but I am becoming quite proficient in “Geek-speak”.  Another interesting little thing I’ve recently become aware of, is the radio stations here in Quebec seem to have developed a cruel and unrelenting obsession with Phil Collins.  Here is the format I hear everyday both to and from work.  •	French host babbling way to fast to understand. •	Traffic (even faster) •	Phil Collin’s Song •	Interview with someone I’ve never heard of •	Phil Collin’s Song •	More babble •	Phil Collin’s Song (extended version) N.B – Occasionally Phil Collins may be replaced with Michael Bolton.   I really don’t get it.  Either all the bus drivers are tuned into 101.PHIL or Quebec has some serious explaining to do.  What’s more…I am actually starting to miss Delta Goodrem. (Gulp!)  The last thing I’d like to mention, is the progress (and I use the term loosely) of my skiing.  I went again this weekend in Quebec City.  It was beautiful and sunny, and really hot too (-2)…which actually is warm for skiing.  I was doing so well in the morning.  I did some black run trails, I was keeping up with Marc, and all round I was starting to think “Hey yeah, I’m finally getting good at this sport”  HOWEVER…  by afternoon, I’d torn both my gloves from falling on the ice, I’d stacked about 10 times on this one really slipperly patch, I’d had a particularly unfriendly encounter with a large bush, and in what was my grand finale – I lost it completely doing about 50 miles an hour down a big slope, did two flips, one face plant, and lost both my skis ten metres back up the hill. And it ALL happened right under the watchful gaze of the people on the chairlift overhead.  It must have been bad, because as I tumbled out of control, (images of Christopher Reeve drifting through my head), I could hear everyone above go “OOOOOWWWWWWW” out loud.  Needless to say my confidence was shot, and I retreated quickly to the chalet for a much needed chocolate bar.  Anyone got any pointers on how to stay vertical on ice?  Because I suck at it.  More news as it comes to hand.  James XXX  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi...  Ok, I swore to myself I would never do this due to the fact it is so unbelievably cheesy...but I want to know what everyone on this list is doing at the moment.  So I have only put about 10 names on this list, 1 question each.  Respond when you can  Here are my list of questions to individuals.  Aaron -- Are you going back to London anytime soon?  Candice -- Are you still alive, I've tried to call you 143 times and if you've died and I missed the funeral I will be extremely annoyed with you.  Emma -- Happy birthday.  Sorry I forgot.  I am officially the worst brother in the world.  Mum - I love you heaps.  P.S - Send money.  Michael -- Say hi to Tokyo for me.  I want an update on how many useless electronic gadgets you bought?   Patrick -- How many times have you watched Lord of the Rings (either 1, 2 or 3) since I left?  If the answer is more than 8, then that equals over 24 hours of J R Toklin and you may need to seek medical advice.  Paul -- Did the cat die yet from obesity yet?  And are you coming to visit this summer?  Paul Troon - How's the job going?  Are you and Trevor travelling this year?  Simon -- Call me!!! I forgot what dates you're arriving.  And also how is Pepsi treating you?  Walty -- No question for you because you're not a producer.  :-P  Have you returned to TV yet?  I'm sure Melbourne's programming is suffering in your absence.  Kristy -- Are you rich yet?  I want to see 1440 Productions in the fortune 500 company list by the time I get back.  P.S. - How's your sex life?  and last but by no means least  Adam & Jared -- Have you "been down pub" much?  Say hi to London.  As for me.  Well it's Marc's birthday tomorrow.  So I'm taking him to see Phantom of the Opera in New York for easter, and then we're going to tentatively start planning a trip to South America in the summer which may not happen as we're both poor.  P.S. Did I mention I love you Mum P.P.S - Send money.  Everybody elses Mum's are doing it.  And I'm reasonably sure it's tax deductible. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Everyone,  Well I thought it was time to write you all another email detailing my antics in ‘snow kissed’ Montreal (euphemism for slushy snow filled frozen town of coldness). No seriously the weather has been warming up, and today it was so sunny when I left for work.  It looked great as, we’d just had a light snow shower.  However by the time I left work this evening the roads looked like the bottom of a ‘slurpy’ right before you finish it.  You know, like the ones you get from 7/11 and there’s always that one bit of slushy ice that gets stuck at the bottom of the cup, so you tip it up and it won’t budge, so then you shake it and shake it until finally the ice falls onto your face, or all into your mouth at once and you get an ice-cream headache.  That’s what Montreal was like today – a mud flavor 7/11 slurpy… but beautiful none the less.  I really do love it here and I know for a fact that I’m going to miss it when it comes time to leave.  I was watching a travel show the other day and it said that Montreal was the 3rd most unspoiled tourist destination in the world -- topped only by Oslo in Norway and by some other place that I’ve forgotten.  I think it was Baghdad or Islamabad but I could be mistaken.  Anyway, I finished my 2nd level French course and now I’m onto the 3rd.  I’ve been doing 6 hours a week, twice a week after work.  It’s starting to get fun as I become more competent.    C’est difficile, mais je trouve que je peux dire plus et plus chaque jour.  (It’s difficult, but I find I can say more and more each day)  Yes I know I’m just showing off now, but seriously I’ve even surprised myself.  Conversations are starting to last a lot longer and slowly I can understand what people are saying.  I think the secret to success with language is that no matter what, you can’t give up.  There’s always those disheartening moments when you can’t say or understand a thing, or where you accidentally ask the waiter for a roast donkey and a black sock in front of a table full of French people.  But if you just say in your head, “I will keep doing this no matter how long it takes”, sooner or later you’ll either start speaking French.  Or otherwise give yourself a brain aneurism and die an excruciatingly painful death.  So what have you got to lose!  On a completely unrelated topic, I see this little girl walking with her father at the station every now and then.  It’s quite funny.  So I’ll tell the story.  Not that it’s really a story, but more an observation.  Anyway, I see this little girl sometimes.  She’s always walking with her father in the metro station.  It’s like deja-vu (which is literally French for “already seen” by the way)  Anyway I always see her and I don’t know if any of you have seen the film ‘Schlindler’s List’, but she wears this cute little read velvet duffle coat just like the girl in that movie. (except in this story she doesn’t end up dead).  Anyway…for some reason she’s always crying.  It’s hilarious how loud she cries.  In fact I’ve never seen her do anything except look up at her Dad blubbering in French saying stuff like:  “Pourquoi, Papa?”  – Why Dad?  “C'est pas correct!!!” – It’s not fair   ‘’Pourquoi tu n'écoutes pas? ’’  – Why don’t you listen?  And her father always ignores her.  So she crouches down against the wall with her bottom lip sticking out.  It’s the cutest thing you’ve ever seen.  And the sad part is, at 3, she speaks better French than I do.   But I’ve seen her like 3 or 4 times.  It’s funny how you really start to notice and remember little things like that when you’re away from home.  Anyway I won’t babble on anymore.  Except to say I’ve finished all my training at work.  I’ve been getting some good sales figures and generally like the job so far.  At Easter Marc, me, and a couple of his friends are doing a road-trip to New York.  So I can’t wait to see all the museums and art galleries there.  Also in a few months my friend Simon is coming to visit for two weeks.  So we’ll be taking him around Montreal, Ottawa, Toronto, and hopefully Boston and New York as well.  I can’t wait to see Niagara Falls, I’m thinking of taking the barrel ride down them .  I also thought I might try to find a new job in a bilingual work place in the summer so I can really capitalize on some French (or semi-French) submersion.  Anyway, hope everyone is well.  Please feel free to write back and tell me what you’ve been up to.  I love getting emails because I get lonely sometimes (everyone go… Awwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww”   Nah seriously, it always makes my day to hear from people who can still be bothered reading this jargon.  With that, I’m off to watch Marc’s new Bjork DVD and make myself dinner.  Which will be hotdogs as I can’t be bothered doing anything that requires more effort than boiling water.  See ya  James  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all...  Well I just arrived at my desk for another Monday.  I've turned into a little business beaver... Work all week, travel on the weekend, drink to much coffee, and actually watch the stock market.  Who would have thought hey?  I went to a place called Rigaud (pron Rigu) on the weekend.  It's a pilgrimage sight because appiritions of the virgin mary have been sighted there.  We climbed to the top of the mountain and had the most magnificent view of the St Lawrence River and the snow covered landscape.  I joked to Marc that the power generator on the top of the mountain was used to power the holo-graphic Mary-making machine. (you know like the one they use in Star Wars.) Ahhhh god bless my blatant atheisim.  Marc found it midly amusing :-)  Anyway thanks for all the emails I received over the weekend, it was good surprise to get to my desk and start off the morning reading about what everyone's been up to.  Sorry if the last email was a bit sombre...but sometimes I use this email as like a way to 'vent' my thoughts.  So its possible you might hear all sorts of weird and wonderful things.  (N.B - All statements, thoughts, and opinions expressed in these emails become null and void after 36 hours.)  Speaking of weird and wonderful though, Marc had a ground breaking moment in his English yesterday when he affectionately reffered to one of our quasi-friends as a "Slapper".  What have I done!!! I've created a monster.  Seems my disgusting use of Australian slang is finally starting to rub off.  Quebec will never be the same again  Off to go work now.  Oh and its getting warmer here....(slightly)  James 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I can't believe how out of the loop I am now that I don't watch TV anymore.  I just got home and found out about the terrorist attacks in Spain on the internet.  Then I jumped on Channel 9's website and watched the Michael Usher story from this morning’s news.  It was awful to see the same familiar pictures yet again, and yet sadly, it’s not even surprising anymore.  I think the world is truly a different place.  Marc is pretty shaken up by it, as you all know he was in Madrid last week, and Marc's father's girlfriend just flew out of Madrid this morning.  It's truly sad to think that such an amazing time in history is being so maliciously overshadowed by these cowardly and abhorrent acts.    This is the second close call I've had...My sister was in Bali (and even in Sari Club) just 2 weeks before the attacks there.  It's definitely a scary thought to think how different my life might have been if fate had taken a different path.   Anyway, I hope everybody is well and enjoying the summer.  It's times like these when I really wish I was with you guys.  Well I guess that’s all I have to say.  I just thought I should put ‘finger to keypad’ (as opposed to pen to paper) and say something to record my thoughts. And I hope everyone turns their thoughts to those who are feeling this directly, because once again I realised tonight how easily I could have been one of them  James 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone,  Well it’s been a while since an update of any kind, so I thought I’d enlighten those of you who are still bothering to read these long-winded ramblings.  On that note though… I do feel a slight duty to write these emails, as I haven’t been keeping a journal of any kind (mostly because it’s too much like homework) and hence these emails are my only record of events.  Anyway moving right along.  Last weekend I took my second trip down to Canada’s beautiful capital, Ottawa, to hear the Dalai Lama speak.  It was super sunny and such a great weekend for a short road trip.  The speech was opened with an impromptu performance from Canada’s greatest export – Alanis Morrissette – who sang 3 songs and then introduced His Holiness.  The speech itself was very captivating – a clever mix of wisdom, humor and advice for self development.  I found him to be quite an amazing character.  He had a translator with him who helped him out each time he got stuck with his English.  Each time it happened he’d turn to the scholar and ask in broken English “How say that?”  It was very funny.  But in all seriousness I think most of us felt enlightened with his succinct use of metaphors and ideas and principles to shape our lifes by.  Surprisingly, the title of the talk “Free Tibet” was left largely untouched.  He did have an historic meeting with Canada’s prime minister Paul Martin…but once again the issue of China and Tibet was left for the most part untouched.  I guess that’s mostly because of Canada’s close diplomatic ties with China.  The metaphor in the speech that I related to the most was the one he used to describe how self destructive anger can be.  He likened it to a mechanic who is working underneath his car, who after accidentally banging his head, gets angrier and more annoyed, consequently banging his head another 5 times, and making it worse.  For some reason I related quite a bit with this particular example.  So anyway I guess I should probably move on to the more exciting news at hand.  I’m off to London in 2 weeks time to spend a fortnight with friends and family.  Marc has also donated to the expedition so I can take a train ride to Paris, and live one of my live long dream of visiting The Louvre. In London I’ll be staying with my old flat mates Adam and Jared for a little bit -- who are over there preparing for the British Dancing Championships at the moment and living in a 5 bedroom house.  I’ll also crash a little bit with my friend Michael who I went to Uni with, and also some friends who live up in Leeds.  One of the interesting things I will get to do is see where my grandparents grew up which will also allow a visit with a Great Aunt and a Great Uncle who I’ve never me.  So that’s the plan.  The airfares were so cheap you would just die.  It’s only like $800 bucks to get to London.  The down side though is that I have to quit my job to take the trip, which will mean that I have to come back to Australia earlier than expected.  So chances are I’ll fly back to Melbourne around August.  My other friend Simon is coming to spend the last couple of weeks here with Marc and myself, so hopefully we’ll be able to get down to New York one more time and see the sights for the last time.  When I get back I am also seriously considering finishing off my Uni degree so I can do some post graduate studies in French and or International Studies.  I’ll also be looking for somewhere to live close to the city when I get back if anyone’s looking for a flat mate.    One thing I would quickly like to do is wish my oldest friend Kristy the very best wishes for her upcoming wedding.  I’ve known her for 22 years and will miss her wedding which is on the 9th of May i think.  So i am bitterly disappointed about that, especially following recent updates from the mother of the bride which indicate this will be one hell of an event.  Needless to say everyone here wishes you a fairytale event Kristy, and my speech is in the works and will be emailed through very soon.  Well that's all from the Northern Hemisphere for now. Hope everyone is well and please write back when you get a chance  James XX    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone,  Well I only have two more days of work, two days break, and a weekend separating me and Europe. (Not that I’m counting).  So I am super, super, super excited presently.  Especially given that so many of my friends are in London at the moment.  It’s going to be like a bit of a reunion party - except with more alcohol.  I also just found out this week that one of my best friends from high school, Glenn, will be in Paris at the same time as me.  So we’ve decided to stay together and I’m going to remain there for a few extra days and soak up a couple of extra sites.  I’ll also be able to spend a few extra hours at The Louvre as well which I’m glad about, because everyone I know who has been there says it’s mammoth and you need a lot of time.  Kind of like Disney Land, except the paintings are better and there's less vomiting.  After that Glenn’s planned to come back to London with me on the train…so I’ll have a traveling buddy for some of the trip which will be awesome.    I’m also hoping to travel a bit further north to Leeds and Manchester as well, but I’ll have to wait and see how many Euros I blow in Paris.  So that’s about it really.  I’m glad to be finishing work on Wednesday.  Frankly I could get used to this work 4 months, get up and move countries kind of schedule… maybe I’ll consider a new career as a con artist when I get back. Or maybe I’ll get the job that Paris and Nikki Hilton are famous for….I’ll just have to figure out what it is first.  Oh yeah I remember now being filthy rich sluts.  Yeah that’d be fun.  Anyway, not much else to say except that it’s beautiful and warm here at the moment.  I’m in shorts and a t-shirt basking on my balcony and not missing the snow at all.  The ski boots are in the closet, and I don’t think I’ll be lugging them back with me to Oz -- that said -- I think my little winter flirt with the slopes of Montreal has now officially ended. (much to the relief of my bruised butt).  I should be back in August, late July.  I want to stay until the Sarah McLachlan concert…but that might not be possible as I am predicting a rather substantial drought in finances.  Anyway, please write me back.  Soon I’ll be back in Melbourne, with no job, no money and no life… bugging you all to catch up for coffees.  The unfortunate side of that will of course be that these emails will be coming to an end. (Dry your eyes)  Of course I could still write to you when I get back to Melbourne… but that would be attention seeking and self indulgent… And as most of you know, those are just not qualities that I possess…(pauses for laughter)   James XX 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't recall any such event.  Then again it's not surprising in light of the copious amounts of alcohol I drank this week.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well because I've had so much fun playing with this blog software today, I have decided to extend an invitation to anyone who wants to post stuff here.  Yes, I know, the blog is predominantly just photos of my trips at the moment...however if you have photos or comments of your own to post....just email me and I'll send you a password.  And finally, before any of you say it...Yes, I know...I am such a geek :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Glenn and I -- Lakes District, North England
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Adam and I -- Tower Bridge, London 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "Ground Zero" -- World Trade Centre site
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    New York Stock Exchange
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Time Square, New York City
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    United Nations, New York City
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Broadway, New York City
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    News Corporation Headquarters, New York
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Views from the Seine River
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sunday afternoon in Paris
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Gardens of Versailles 2
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Gardens of Versailles
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Palace of Versailles
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Louvre statue gallery
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    La vue -- Tour Eiffel
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tour Eiffel, Paris
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "Moulin Galette" -- Renoir, Musée d'Orsay
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The canal from "Amelie" -- Paris
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My Street -- "Avenue Pothier"
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    House in Montreal
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Montreal, Québec.  The weather is hot.  I have no work to speak of.  Life in Canada is drawing to a close -- what better time to start my very own blog.  I am notoriously bad for neglecting anything I start, but let us hope that the simplicity of this software will encourage me to at least continue for a while.  At the very least, I'll have a place to post some photos from my travels.  If you'd like to post to this blog as well, send me an email and I'll add you as a user.  The theme of the blog is: “The words that enlighten the soul are more precious than jewels.”  Disclaimer: The user takes no responsibility for any posts, images or quotes which fail to enlighten.      
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Le Monde est Grand
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Everyone...   Sorry it's been so long since my last email -- I guess I've been a bit slack.  But I've been pretty busy over here since I got back from London.  I took a couple of weeks just to relax and unwind.  I got terribly sunburnt doing the gardening at Marc's Mum's house and ended up peeling for 3 days.  The summer over here is beautiful -- although just like Melbourne we've had quite a few summer storms as well.   My friend Simon arrived from Australia at the end of June, and I spent the last week or so showing him around Montreal.  It was great to do the 'tourist' thing one last time before I leave.  We went out for a couple of nights on the town.  We then spent Canada Day in Ottawa with another friend Alex who lives there.  There were tons of people everywhere and being the capital of Canada I think it was the best place we could have spent the holiday.  We also ate heaps of candy and ice cream and generally went out of our way to put on weight.   We then took a walk down by the river -- which turned out to be a big mistake as a massive storm hit as we reached the bank.  Not near any shelter, we got completely drenched from head to toe in the 15 minute downpour.  It was hilarious -- we were soaking.  And it was only the day before that Simon and I had taken a raft tour on the Lachine Rapids in Montreal, which we also got drenched on.  However this time we didn't have a change of clothes with us.  Luckily Alex's Mum lent us the use of her clothes dryer and a hot shower, so we didn't have to spend the day walking around in soggy clothes.  They have a beautiful house right near a huge National Park in Ottawa.  Her dad is currently working for the United Nations in Afghanistan -- how cool is that.  I think I'd like to study something in that vein when I get back.   ***Oh yeah, and I forgot to mention I moved out of my apartment on the 1st of July, so everything's packed up in boxes ready for my return to Oz.  I can't believe how much stuff I've accumulated -- there's no way I'm going to be able to bring it all back.  Just my french books alone take up half a suitcase.***   Anyway, back to what I was saying.  After we got back from Ottawa, Marc and I took Simon to his Dad's cottage in Quebec City for a weekend of booze and hiking (not necessarily the best combinatioin).  We had great weather, and it was also interesting to see all the mountains I'd skied on earlier in the year minus the snow.  After 8 bottles of wine between us all I was only feeling slightly drunk.  It seems all the wine I've drunk over here has increased my alchohol tolerance level to a new height.  Not happy Jan!!! I can't even afford to get myself drunk anymore.   So that's about it really.  Had a great week with Si who is now spending his last week over here in New York City.  I am really getting scared about coming home.  It's less than 2 weeks and I'm back!!!!  The last 7 months has gone so quickly I can hardly believe it.  I know for a fact I am really going to miss Montreal so much.  I've grown so close to it and all the people I know here.  I think it will probably be harder for me to leave than it was for me to come in the first place.  Still, having said that,  I am really looking forward to seeing my family and friends again.  Especially my Mum and sister who I have never been away from this long in my entire life.   Well I guess this will be one of my last emails before I see you all again.  Sorry it hasn't been very interesting -- but my English skills have been polluted.  Actually that is one funny thing I have to tell you about.  When Simon got here he noticed that I was saying lots of things wrong in English.  Mostly because my flat mate and I spoke in French so much, and when we did speak English -- her's wasn't very good so i got used to hearing things said wrong.  So that was the trade off for learning another language -- I nows speaks English not so gooder than I had spoked it before.   So, Marc and I are off camping in Eastern Canada on Friday.  We're off to Gaspe (about a days drive)  and then we're putting the car on a ferry and going to Isle de Magdeline (an island in the Atlantic Ocean) so it should be a great way to end the trip.  Hey, and we're also sleeping in a tent!! Whoa that's a big step for me.  I even taught myself to put it up while Marc was at work yesterday.  That's one thing that Canada has done to me -- it's made me a whole lot more 'outdoorsy'.  Who would have thought eh?   That's it from me.  Please write back if you get a chance, I haven't heard from anyone in ages.  Not even my own Mum!!!!! (yes Mum you big slacker, you've abadonned me)   Hope everyone's well, and I really really can't wait to see you all again.  Right after the 21 hour flight (groan)   James  XXX  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>