<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Because I live at the end of nowhere, I had to cut alot of wood to have when the winter will come. And I didn't finished all, and I'm very very tired. My hands hurt, my legs, my head hurt, my everything hurts :(. I just need a long long vacation. A long vacation ....... When??? A long vacation .... 

						
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Read  urlLink Yep, the monday  

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   People are crazy or they are stupid, or something, it's very strange.  When I stay home, and i watch the TV or I take a shower, I always dream "wow, how good will be now if I would be on a mountain, with flours around me, not any car sound, not smoke, not any strange noise from the neighborhood, just the birds and the plants". And when I'm up there in the top of the world on the mountain, I think "why? why I camed here? bugs everywhere, I don't have where to take a shower, I don't have anything to do, I just get bored, not a TV, not nothing, I should stay home next time when I wana go on a mointain".  And ofcourse, when I'm home the same thing it's happening, and when I'm on a mountain the same thing. Why we are like that? We will never get the answer. 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When I'm at work I am thinking at alot of things doing after I get out from work, in my free time. So, when I have free time I should do those things. I'm not. Why? Dunno why, I just want to get lazy and not to do anything. Curios, huh? Sometimes I ask my self why God made us like we are. Eating, going to toilet, drinking if we are tursty, sleeping, and so one. It's a strange world and some strange people too. 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yes, it was a hard day, because my boss was out of town (you could all say: yupeeeeeeee!!!). No, it's not like that, because when my boss it's out of town I have to do his work and I can't miss from work, and alot of thing.  All the day I was very depressed, something in the morning made me to think at what is the meaning of life. And I didn't found out, a part from my depression is because I don't have a girlfriend., but I'm not in the mood to explain what I thought and what not. This subject I let it for another day.  Ah, by the way, today I had the first comment to my blog :), from somebody called Ron, Thanks Ron :), it's nice to know cuz somebody is visiting your blog once in a while.  Ok, I will close the post for today, because it's showtime and because I'm just not in the mood, the OZ it's begining :). A movie with a jail :)  Good Night 

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The first day from this week. Yep, it's monday. Ah, I hate the first day, yep the monday. Why? Because is the first day to work, and ofcourse because it's monday. Monday I work more like the whole week. Yep, monday, the day when another week of work is coming. Do you have that feeling "of monday" in anothers day? I have that. It's not a nice feeling, a nice feeling is "of friday" or "of saturday". The feeling "of sunday" i don't like that either, because after sunday comes monday, and again, yep it's monday :(.  At work I have a great Boss, yep it's great because he consider me his boss, not him my boss, but he talks alot, and when I mean alot, I mean alot, and he talks about things what I don't care, because he is old, I think he has over 70, and i'm just 26, what I could hear from him, everytime when I have a little break, I run from my work to stay 15 - 30 minutes with some friends, who are working at 2 minutes from me, two brothers, one works 3 days after that the other one works 3 day, and with them I can talk about what I want, and about what I'm interested.  I wait everyday to get out from work, to come online to make what I like the most, surfing :). Surfing nowhere, just I open the google and I search and I search and so one. I stay 2 or 3 hr, after that I go home at my computer and I work at my webpage, at some designs. I look at the time, and wow, it is begining the tv shows, I watch like 3 hr and after that I go to sleep.  I will go a little too surf some more, and after that go home. Why? Because it's monday, yep it's monday. 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wait 5 minutes, to clear my mind, and after a good thinking, knowing a little html :), I looked at my blog and saw the "I power blogger" image, and I put there that crazy link with that crazy image, what gived me alot of head pain, and I removed the last link what apeared on EVERY POST what I made, so  now the blog looks ok ;)  I'm Happy cuz I'm smart :)  Smile, tomorow is another day :) 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Searching for blogs on google to see more about theme, I found a site where you have shares from blogs or something like that, I registered in there and to be active I have to put a url gived by theme in my blog. Here is the url  ah, I don't know I put here the url but on the blog apeared the code not what it should be, and now I inserted the code in the template, but dang the code apears right but on every post what I make, ah, my mind hurts, so tomorow I need to change that, because it looks like dunno what. ON EVERY POST COMMOOOOOON!!!! Stupid me. Tomorow.  Funny, it's my first day when I see the word "blog", and I already have one, right now with this post will be two posts :).  Ps. Searching after blogs I found an IQ test, and I tryied to see how good I am, because in my country we don't have IQ tests or something like that. The result was 122, I don't know if is big or small. (the IQ test was in english and I'm not to good in english, I did my best I think to the questions with images :)) ). 

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Right now is 20:10, I'm at an internet cafe, and I was searching on google deifferent things, and I saw a lot of thing about "blog, blog, blog, blo..., bl.., b..." and I wondered what it is, and I arived at blogger.com and I found out what it is, and right now I made an acount to have my own blog. So that is how I start my blog :) 

						
</post>


</Blog>