<Blog>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so my day at work was well, crappy to say the least. Management at times really sucks, for you people out there that work for management, let me give you a tip on the inside. If your manager it hard on you, realize it's because they are responsible for you to their leaders. And when you slack or don't take the initiative it's the manager's fault. Have some sympathy for your managers and realize they have a lot of responsibility and that helping them helps you.  So on another note, I'm making huge progress in my life. I come from a family of alcoholics and it has dramatically affected my attitude and reactions to life. I just recently got involved with the Al-Anon program, and am very excited for the 12 steps I am about to embark on. If this is something that you might be dealing with, drop me a line, it might be helpful.   thanks for staying tuned
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today has already begun to be a great day. I got to sleep in, which in itself is amazing. My husband is at work all day which means that I get to work by myself today. For those of you who don't know, my husband is the cathedral of the rockies youth minister, I have a position as special events coordinator and childcare director. We basically, work together all the time on everything. So God Bless his heart I can't but help relish in my alone time. I'm about to go to work but I just had to go play frisbee with my dog, and ketch a few minutes of general hospital. Just for the record, general hospital has the best acting and plot line then any soap opera out there. So now I go off to work, can't wait to blog later.  brandy 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey ladies, leif here. just thought id let you know, brandy really thinks you guys have no chance. well, in case you want to compete, let me tell ya, unless you love as much as she does, laugh as much as she does, live as much, and and look as good as she does, dont bother. im too busy thinking about her to listen to what you might mistakenly think you have to offer. sorry!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I've got a great joke for ya (just so you know I'm a big joke teller)  So Mr. Jones get off work one day and decides that instead of going home to his wife and kids and have dinner, he would go to the local bar and get blizzed before he goes home.  Anyhow, after he was three sheets to the wind he blacks out and doesn't remember getting home. He wakes up in the  morning in his bed. He thinks to himself, shit, my wife is going to be pissed. As he wakes up with the worst hang over of his life his wife comes in with breakfast in bed. She says, "Good Morning honey, did you sleep well? Have some breakfast and down't worry about mowing the lawn today I already took care of it" After breakfast in bed, he's thinking to himself, what is going on? What happened last night? Why is the lawn mowed and the house clean? This must be a trick to get me back for last night. So he comes into the living room and sees his youngest son "hey son" he says, "What's going on I thought for sure your mom would be pissed off at me." His son replies, "well dad she was pretty mad at you, but when she started to undress you for bed you said 'get off me lady I'm married!'"
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    take a bite out of crime!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It took quit a time to get to this blog, but I'm glad to say that I can now join thousands of people that get a kick out of telling total strangers about their weird bizarre life. Oh, and trust me..... mine is.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a crazy life. I wish that I could take the time to full expand upon the last two weeks of my life but I simple do not have the patience to expound on all of the funny details. But to make a long story short, my husband and I took 9 kids to a mission to Yakima, WA. We ended up saving an abused puppy whom we named Resy (Reservation). I did my good deed for the month. Our good friend Curtis ended up adopting her. We came home to find out our 2 best friends are taking of to work in Hawaii for 6 months. Poor Guys! There is so much other drama that occurred in that time frame but only those who are privy to knowing me will get to hear the edge of your seat story. But the whole point of this blog, was to say that I got promoted at work!! Yea for me. Toodles
     

    
</post>


</Blog>