<Blog>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jeff Jarvis coins a new term for the extremists out there: neo-nuts. He has some very good arguments to support his thesis. He first mentioned it in response to  urlLink someone who said he was an extremist . He is no extremist in any sense of the word, and he, rightly, took issue with that. He then points out the constant references by the media that try to show how divided we are as a nation. And others  urlLink have responded  to the same sentiments.  Another gentleman by the name of Oliver Willis (a blogger on the left that I read occasionally) also responded to Jeff's comments and had some  urlLink very interesting observations and reactions . Basically saying, you call me names and I'll defend myself. To which Jeff  urlLink responded .  Jeff points unquestionably to the fact that the divisiveness is being promoted by the media. And it doesn't matter if you're on the left or right of the political spectrum, the media big-boys are the ones pushing the extremist zeitgeist. Jeff them makes a call to take back the debate. Have open discussions that are respectful, not to sling mud and demonize the other side - something that I've  urlLink written  about  urlLink before .  Now, I don't always agree with Jeff, but I also don't know anyone with whom I agree with completely and in every case. However, I think Jeff has pointed out what has been bugging me about the political discussion for so long. While I've been trying to call for more even-handed discussions, I have failed to point out why I thought that particular approach was necessary. I failed to notice that while I was so upset about it, there was a driving force behind my feelings. I focused on the results and not the cause. I think Jeff has found the cause. The template has been cast and now the accepted way to success in the political arena is to demonize the other side.  A former politician explained it to me once, and Jeff says the same thing: moderation doesn't sell. You can't be successful by trying to appeal to both sides, and you can't please both sides simultaneously. Rigid extremism doesn't necessarily play well for political success, but it is profitable and it does serve to motivate the masses. But why does it have to be that way? Is it a paradigm thing? Is it human nature? I am going to lean on the side of human nature for now, but I have to wonder if maybe Jeff isn't more than partially correct. If the media didn't hype extremism, maybe the bile wouldn't rise as much. Possibly, if the media refused to peddle extremist views and focus on the chasm or divide or gap they say exists, maybe it would help to ameliorate the current viciousness that permeates our society.  Maybe.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Matt (or anyone who cares to tackle this), I have a proposal to make.   You have stated on the mothership that you think Bush lied to get America to go to war in Iraq, and I have heard that from others as well (the common meme of "Bush lied, people died!). I would like to hold a sort of court of opinion. Since I am of the opinion that Bush did not lie, I leave the opening salvo up to you. Please provide specific incidents where Bush has lied about the war in Iraq. I would like to treat this just like a court of law. Hearsay isn't proof, neither is opinion. I would like to see specific citations linking back to transcripts or quotes from reliable sources of things Bush has said, followed by other specific citations from reliable sources that show why what he said is a lie.   I will then try my best to find citations that show that, in fact, he did not lie. And I will hold myself to the same standards.   And like a court of law, you have to prove your case beyond reasonable doubt, as do I. If it becomes a matter of interpretation or conjecture, then it is a non-case.  If I am unable to refute any of your specific accusations, I will officially change my opinion and agree readily that Bush did in fact lie.  I am always saying that we need to listen to other opinions with an open mind, and now I'm willing to put my money where my mouth is.   The ball is in your court.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Ditto .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There's a few quotes I'd like to point out from this story: urlLink San Francisco rolls out the red carpet for the Clintons .  Hillary Clinton: "We're going to take things away from you on behalf of the common good."   No thanks.  A fan of clinton: ""I've never shaken the hand of a president," said Thomas, who added that he had one grandma who couldn't stand Clinton and one who thought he was the best president ever. "Even better than George Washington," said Thomas.   Like his grandma has any way of judging that.  Hillary Clinton agian: Sen. Clinton was asked what she thought of her husband's book. "I loved it," she replied. "You've got to read all of it."   And you expected her to say, what, exactly?   [heavy sarcasm]Brilliant story.[/heavy sarcasm]
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Some  urlLink Iraqi   urlLink bloggers   urlLink are   urlLink very   urlLink happy  about it.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The Supreme Court finally made a  urlLink ruling on the Guantanamo Bay detainees , at least to some extent. I applaud their decision, in the sense that the detainees will have access to the court system. In my opinion, it didn't make sense that because they were in Cuba, that they did not have access to courts. All U.S. bases and embassies, etc. are considered U.S. soil so how could the administration argue that because the detention "center" was in Cuba they had no right to the courts. You can't have it both ways, either it is considered US soil or it is not. If it is, which is the case, then they may as well be in Delaware as far as their rights under the Constitution are concered. As emotionally charged as this issue is, with the chance that many terrorists are in the camps, these are the times when are rights are tested most. I believe had the administration won this case, then we would all be in danger.   
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is a continuation of a discussion thread on the mothership.  First, Samiam said:  What that moore sayes is truth?? sorry to offend but he is a bafoon in my opinion driven frome birth by overexageration..How can anyone posibly believe him??? He has done nothing but Bash bush since he took office,some will say anything to advance a agenda...his movie is a exageration..of his own opinion  Cactuscat later posted:  I just returned from seeing the movie, and it was amazingly powerful. I think every democrat should take a republican friend to see it!  Which got Samiam going again:  To acomplish what? Im sure that probably all republicans know it is nothing but propoganda! If i went to see it i would probably be sick..I seen what happend on 9/11 and ervryone that did should have the same view, Stop terorist's and there money sources..to manny people died to not do anything,and for moore to make a movie intending to discredit action by i feel one of the only Administration's willing to make a stand!!! No NO nO, maybee a republican should take a democrat by the hand and pray nothing like that ever happens again in this country...To me its not about left or right,its about pay back long over due...Unless others think that we should just allow the building of threats to our freedom..God forbid thousands die again simply because moore said we are wrong....  Then Cactuscat responded with:  I have some questions for samiam. Like "payback long overdue" for what exactly? Since Iraq had nothing to do with the terrorist attacks on the US, what is the payback for?  There was more, but those quotes capture the essence.  Samiam - the ball's in your court.  My thoughts are clearly expressed in other posts on this site.  urlLink Here ,  urlLink here ,  urlLink here , and  urlLink here .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jeff Jarvis (who has been focused on Moore like a laser beam the last week or so) points out a link to what Michael Moore plans on donning next:  urlLink taking on the U.S. Health Care system .  Jeff then has this incredibly  urlLink pithy observation:   Well, the good news is that health care is a subject that damned well needs tackling. It's shameful what's happening in this country: millions uninsured; people trapped in the wrong jobs just because of health benefits; money wasted on exploding insurance bureaucracy; doctors' time wasted with insurance time-wasters; proper and necessary care withheld from the sick; costs skyrocketing; malpractice rates driving doctors away.... Oh, Lord, it needs tackling.   The bad news: If Moore does as blunt and bad a job of it as he did with war and politics in Fahrenheit and gun control in Columbine, it ratchets-up and dumbs-down the debate. What we don't need is more polemic and preaching to the converted and the sick. What we do need is intelligent, well-researched, strongly argued media that will set and change the agenda in both parties. Once upon a time, I might have thought that Moore could contribute to that debate. But that's my real problem after Fahrenheit: He merely seethes and it's too damned easy for the other side to ignore the slob seething in the corner.   He's absolutely right. MM has served a small purpose, that of stimulating debate. However, the approach and tone he takes is so off-putting to some that it just makes it easy to pass him off as another fanatic (which is precisely my approach). While MM's approach is powerful for the believers, it has the exact opposite effect for those he is trying to convert to his side. MM preaches to the choir and the missed facts, the arguments that try to have it both ways ("we shouldn't have attacked Afghanistan" vs. "we didn't send enough soldiers to Afghanistan") are things that get overlooked by the people who generally believe the same things as MM. However, if you disagree with MM all you see is a rabid fanatic who you shouldn't even bother trying to debate because all he'll do is just shout you down (halfhearted! Oil!), and froth and seethe some more.   What he chooses to attack isn't the problem - it's the methods. Some of what he has to say may in fact be valid, but it's the zealotry that makes it so unpalatable.   UPDATE:  Others are saying  urlLink basically the same thing .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Political blogging sucks. I've discovered that I actually don't like it. I really don't. It doesn't feel good, it doesn't make me feel any better about what I just blogged. It hasn't resolved anything. It hasn't made anyone feel any better. It hasn't done anything for anyone else.  So why do I keep writing about political, or at least politically charged topics?  Because I have to say  something . It's like a boiling pot. I see story after story talking about things that just get to me, they push my buttons and make me crazy. I have to do something. I don't want to discuss it with someone face to face, I hate that more than anything. I truly hate getting in arguments. Reasonable discussions I can handle, but I just don't like how I feel when I get in an argument. I don't like seeing how the other person/people feel either. So what can I do? I can post it somewhere where maybe a few people will see it, but nobody will particularly care.  Why is it that politics has to be so damned inflamatory? I need to think about this some more. I've tried to write 5 different paragraphs right here to express what I'm trying to communicate, and I haven't been able to come close yet.  One more time...  I guess what bugs me more than anything is closed minded people. Some may call me closed minded, and I could easily understand why. I'm very firm in quite a number of my beliefs and opinions. But if an opposing viewpoint is presented I will always listen (provided it is communicated in a non-confrontational manner) and try very hard to judge it on its merits. I may quickly discard it as being in direct opposition to my core values or beliefs, but even in rejection I will try to at least understand why someone feels or thinks the way they do. If I can't understand then it kind of makes me evne more disappointed - I have failed to learn and understand.  I can understand on a psychological level why some people don't want to understand - but it really,  really  bugs me when they don't even want to try.  I had a religious argument with a friend once - a man I honestly admired. The discussion began with him telling me that I was completely wrong in my beliefs. After about an hour of discussion I began to see that we were talking about the same things, but we were using different words - it was purely semantics. I had him define very carefully particular terms he was using, and then I would carefully define the terms I was using - using nearly the same language. He would then promptly declare that we weren't talking about the same thing. The best I can guess is that in his mind I was already wrong, it was simply inconceivable to him that I could believe the same things he believed in. I wasn't asking him to believe the things I believed in, I wasn't trying to convert him, I was trying to find common ground to stand on, and he wasn't even willing to consider that common ground might exist.  That's what bugs me about political discussions. A complete unwillingness to find common ground. A ready willingness to assume the worst motives, to find the worst in someone.   I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been loosely folowing the career of bike-builder Jesse James. I'm watching "Motorcycle Mania 3" right now, and I have to say, Jesse is one different cat. I don't think there is anyone quite like him anywhere, ever.   Psychotic, honorable, destructive, creative, independent, hard working, ambitious, loving father, traditional, innovative, at once respectful and dissrespectful and apparently a trustworthy friend.  He's an enigma, and it is no wonder that his bikes are famous, his TV shows are a hit and he's become a counter-culture celebrity. He just fascinates the hell out of me, and the sheer uniqueness of the man makes for extremely riveting TV.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I think I'm done with Michael Moore. I don't like bloging about a single topic so much. I'd rather have more fun writing.  Sorry for the long train of political posts. But sometimes I just can't help myself.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      He's  urlLink bloging Michael Moore  and Fahrenheit again. Key quote:  " Now he's still poking fun but in the immortal words of Billy Crystal, it's not fun, it's not funny. He's deadly serious. He's downright rabid. And that makes him harder to take; don't you always want to back away from somebody who's seething at you? It also makes his role as a filmmaker and political activist different: He's no longer just ridiculing the powerful; he's no longer turning them into punchlines; he's now trying to convince us that these particular powerful people -- Bush et al -- are evil, venal, corrupt, incompetent co-conspirators out to ruin our world. If you're going to try to convince us of that, then you have a different obligation of fact and argument than if you're just trying to make fun of somebody. You should give us legitimate facts and arm us with arguments by showing both sides of an issue and beating down the other side. If you don't do that, you're only shrieking. You're weakening your own argument by ignoring the other side. You're insulting the intelligence of your audience by not giving them both sides. You're just seething. That's what Moore is like now. He wants to convince us he's telling the truth but he's afraid to tell the whole truth. "  Jeff is a big media guy and he's predominantly a Democrat, which is what makes his views so interesting to me. He doesn't take things at face value, and he's really good at seeing behind the PR (he's in the industry after all). Also, his views on the FCC, government regulation and censorship are definitely worth looking at.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      As usual  urlLink James Lileks  has some cogent thoughts:  " Finally: yesterday we had fun with Rex Reed, who's a gassy dolt. Glib Nazi comparisons. Ooh! Naughty. But today we had something different; today Al Gore upped the ante. He coined a new term for the Internet critics of his positions: digital brownshirts. Yes, yes, it's over the top. But it's not the sentiment that raises eyebrows, it's the position of the person who's saying it. We don't expect presidential candidates past or present to indulge in Usenet flame-war lingo. We don't expect serious party elders to call the other side Nazis, and for good reason: it's obscene. The brownshirts were evil. The brownshirts kicked the Jews in the streets and made the little kids put their hands on their heads as they stumbled off to the trains. The brownshirts were not interested in refuting arguments. They were interested in killing the people who dared argue at all.  At some point, I fear, the political discourse of 2004 is going to seem horribly irrelevant and misplaced in the face of some loud new wretched horror; it will seem as oddly disconnected from reality as the Condit / Killer-Shark news reports of August 2001. An indolent luxury.   Digital stormtroopers. Tell me again who's stifling debate? Remind me again who's questioning people's patriotism?  Find me again the story where Bob Dole called the Dixie Chicks 'musical Mukhabarats'? Look. We don't have to agree on the big hard issues, but we can certainly agree that we share common values that set us apart, and that it profits no one to identify the opposition as something outside the American experience. Liberals are not Communists. Republicans are not fascists. We have a nice window of opportunity here where we can come together by choice, instead of being thrown together by events. I say we get a head start on national unity, and turn on anyone who floats the Nazi analogy. Shun 'em. No links, no reviews, no radio interviews, no newspaper pieces, nothing. From now on, the Nazi parallel buys you bupkis. This means that the right doesn't get to parade around the mutterings of high-profile wackjobs as illustrative of the heart of everyone who votes D, and the left doesn't get to do the whole "he's wrong in his overheated critique, BUT" dodge. Enough. ENOUGH! For Christ's sake, enough!"   Yea, verily, truth is spoken.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I think I speak for everyone in America when I say: Monica Lewinsky, go away; far away, and please don't ever show up again.   And, just for reference sake, this story: urlLink Lewinsky feels betrayed by Clinton , is so totally stupid that words fail me. ML is one seriously clueless woman.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Take a gander at this story: urlLink Cheney curses Leahy on Senate floor . I think Cheney will not be the vice-president to run with Bush in the next elections. It seems like he's tired of it and has simply had enough. And I can't really blame him. The constant attacks from the opposing party and from the press would be enough to wear anyone down.   In fact, I'm a bit surprised that anyone would want to get into politics on a national stage in any form. The constant criticism by one side or the other, the constant need to defend/attack - it just seems all so constant and petty. I don't care if you're a democrat, republican, libertarian, green, independent or whatever - you have to have some seriously thick skin to be able to hack it on the national stage, and a healthy ego.  The worst part of it all? It's only going to get worse from here. Baring a revolutionary and dramatic turn-around in the political zeitgeist things are only going to get more and more partisan for at least the foreseeable future.   UPDATE:  Jeff Jarvis seems to be thinking the same thing, but he has yet another perspective that is really  urlLink quite ironic in context .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      With the monsoon season approaching and the wind kicking up today reminded me of a phrase a friend of mine and I used to have: "There's wind."  Now, that may not sound like much in the way of a catch-phrase, but for us it was "the signal." We were both single, and my friend, Wade, was kind of a wheeler-dealer. He always had some kind of deal in the works; a natural born salesman. The deal that made us the happiest was when he traded a few typewriters for a 16 ft. Catamaran. That's right - typewriters. Don't ask me how he did it, but it seemed like he was always pulling some kind of freaky deal like that.  That catamaran got a lot of use. It wansn't anything to scream about, it was old and beat up, and the hulls were sort of a bleached out vomit green color, and we had replaced the original trampoline with a blue one that just didn't look right, and she had lost some of her cleats and pullies but she was still water worthy and a hell of a lot of fun. Because she had seen better days we didn't mind abusing her a little. We referred to the boat as "The Chick Magnet." Every day during the summer was a potential day to sail and monsoon season was simply the best. If the wind was kicking up, I could expect a phone call. A typical phone call went like this:  [ring]  Me: "Hello?" Wade: "There's wind." Me: "On my way."  [click]  Then I'd get in my car and high-tail it out to Wade's house - I left my car stocked with all the supplies we'd need (swimsuit, towels, water bottles, sun-screen, hat) so I could go at a moments notice. At Wade's house we'd hook up The Chick Magnet to the Battle Wagon (neither of us had nice cars - me with a Dodge Omni that I paid $250 for and Wade with a Ford Ranger with just primer for a paint job that I'm pretty sure he paid about the same - we were living the high life) and head for Lake Plesant.   Once at the lake we'd hit the water and just sail around till it was too dark to see. Wind in the Arizona hills around Lake Plesant is a strange thing, it circles and swirls and only occasionally do you get a nice strong breeze that is in a consistent direction. Those were the winds we wanted, and they would usually only last for a few minutes so you had to stay sharp and really grab a hold of them as quickly as you could.  But really - it didn't matter. If we had wind it was just a bonus. It was simply exquisite to get out there on the water and enjoy the peace, grace and beauty of wind-powered propulsion. The smallest breeze would push us along and we'd tool along fast or slow depending on what mother nature decided to give us that day. We always understood that we were experiencing something extrordinary and rare that not very many people have an opportunity to experience.  I'm happy to be maried and have a son and another on the way. But sometimes, when I think back on how darned much fun it was to just take off and hit the lake in that boat, I have just a little sense of loss at the freedom that being young, single and having no responsibilities can bring.  Of course, that was one of the few aspects of being single that had any merit. But it was a lot of fun.   UPDATE:  apparently others have noticed a  urlLink similar trend .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Here is a very interesting story that deserves a good read as well:  urlLink Operation Tiger Claw .  Basic story: a student opposes the political viewpoints expressed by his teachers and decides to do something about it. He has a very uphill battle to fight.  That is one dedicated and personally corageous kid.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jeff Jarvis of "BuzzMachine" (and TV Guide fame) went to the New York opening of Fahrenheit 911.  urlLink Here is what he had to say . It is definitely a must-read.  He also has lots and lots of really goog links from other media people (lots of variety and points of view).   UPDATE:  Damn - how about that. Jeff linked to me off his site. Welcome anyone who happens to drop by off from Jeff's site.   YET ANOTHER UPDATE:  If you haven't seen all of the links Jeff points out, you really ought to check  urlLink this one out . Tony Pierce puts things into a perspective that I admire. I don't completely agree with him, but at least he has some points that are worth considering.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      All I have to say is, "Holy crap." I hope that I never, ever have to be on the receiving end of a critique by Mr. Hitchens.   urlLink Unfairenheit 9/11 - The lies of Michael Moore. By Christopher Hitchens   One key quote among many: " a documentary must have a 'POV' or point of view and that it must also impose a narrative line. But if you leave out absolutely everything that might give your 'narrative' a problem and throw in any old rubbish that might support it, and you don't even care that one bit of that rubbish flatly contradicts the next bit, and you give no chance to those who might differ, then you have betrayed your craft. If you flatter and fawn upon your potential audience, I might add, you are patronizing them and insulting them. "  Or further down in the same paragraph: "At  no point does Michael Moore make the smallest effort to be objective. At no moment does he pass up the chance of a cheap sneer or a jeer."   I make no bones about it - I really and truly don't like Michael Moore. I am extremely subjective about it - he rubs me the wrong way. I have no respect for his work and I have yet to see anyone successfully defend anything the man has said, written or produced. He is a propagandist, not a documentarian.   UPDATE:  don't take the quote above out of context. Take 10 or 15 minutes and read the whole article. The quote I chose is relevant to my mindset - the critique as a whole is absolutely devestating. He takes the movie apart piece by piece, not from a philosophical perspective such as the quote above.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Oh, this is rich:  urlLink Iran Threatens to Resume Uranium Enrichment .   So, you're in breach of U.N. resolutions, and you're about to get a  written  rebuke (Oh, no! Not a mean letter!), so as a way to keep you from getting the sternly worded letter you say you're going to start doing the thing for which the rebuke is being written in the first place.  Iran - the 3 yr old of world governments.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Can anyone give me one good reason why I  urlLink should trust the U.N. ?  Other than a few aid organizations within the U.N. can anyone point out a bonified success of the U.N.? Can anyone tell me why we should even be involved in the organization in any meaningful way, or why they matter on the world stage?   From my perspective they are one of the most corrupt organizations I've ever seen, their policies are a joke and they are basically a huge waste of money and time. But somehow they have a legitimacy confered upon them by people who believe in the concept of the U.N. The concept is nice, but the execution seems to be seriously flawed these days.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Does anyone else see a problem with this story?  urlLink Hamas wants two PA cabinet ministries ? A terrorist organization that has been a major contributor and promotor of humans blowing themselves up to kill other civilians wants to have the cabinet posts as Minister of Education and Minister of Health? This has to be a joke, right?
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, here's your chance Matt,  urlLink The Supreme Court dismisses Pledge case .  Although I am not nearly knowledgeable enough about legal matters to give this any kind of proper analysis, it does seem to be as the article suggest in that the ruling is fairly narrow and doesn't address the case of separation of church and state.   However, at the  urlLink Volokh Conspiracy  (a law professor group blog) they have this to say: Some will say, "Rats, too bad the Court didn't squarely reaffirm the constitutionality of the 'under God' Pledge." Others may say, "Too bad the Court didn't strike it down." Others might say, "Good thing that the Court is taking procedural requirements like this seriously." Others will say, "Well, at least they didn't affirm 'Under God' on the merits, thereby creating a lousy precedent that we'd be stuck with." Others might say other things.  What all of those mean I have no idea - but there you are.  In a response to Matt I also suggested that if you take out the "under God" portion of the pledge, you'd also have to change all of our money as well as the state seals and mottos of half the states. Another issue I hadn't thought of was also brought up at the  urlLink Volokh Conspiracy :   In the wake of the L.A. County seal controversy, some people (including me) have given city names as an analogy -- city names such as "Los Angeles," "Sacramento," "Corpus Christi," "Providence," and the like are religious references, the argument goes, but surely we shouldn't hold them to be an Establishment Clause violation, even if one accepts that the Establishment Clause generally bars government speech that a reasonable, knowledgeable observer would see as an endorsement of religion. Why? Because city names are not seen today as endorsements of religion, but just as reflections of the nation's history. Likewise, the argument goes, with the cross on the L.A. county seal.  But the city name issue, it turns out, is not just a hypothetical. In the early 1990s, James O'Leary sued the County of Sacramento, complaining that the county's seal contained the religious term . . . "Sacramento." In the words of the Ninth Circuit memorandum in this case,  O'Leary alleged that the County of Sacramento's ("County") use of the "sacred holy name (Sacramento) on their county seals have caused him to suffer anger, shame, fright, humiliation, mental anguish, emotional distress and physical distress," forcing him to "go 'underground' with his Christian religion."  The court rejected O'Leary's claim on procedural grounds.   So, the issue is a little larger than just state seals, mottos and money. But for some the scope isn't the issue - it is the issue itself. Religion and the term God must be erased from all public record no matter what the cost.    I am curious what is so "wrong" about having the words "under God" in the pledge? Or, for that matter, what is the basis of the impetus to remove religion and God from every aspect of public life? Where do you draw the line - where does it end? Do we stop with official (by which I mean state-sponsored) realms, or continue on to all public realms (which some are trying to do)?
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Matt should find this a particularly interesting article. Steven Den Beste writes a fairly lengthy blog post about the  urlLink nature of identity and consciousness . It is a must read (and for Matt, you may be particularly interested in following some of the many links he provides). He poses some very interesting questions. He states pretty early on that he is an atheist (specifically a mechanistic atheist), but then goes on to shape arguments and thought experiments that are challenging to almost anyone.  I'm not a big proponent of thought experiments though. The can definitely be used to refine a definition or a belief, but they don't really serve much practically because they are just that - thoughts, there is generally no way to prove or even physically test a thought experiment. Nevertheless, they make for darned good conversation.  Go forth and read. I'd like to know what you all think. And I bet most of you will be able to guess where I stand and what I think.  I've been reading Steven's blog for a long time, and he has some particularly good analysis of stuff. He's a pretty deep thinker and uses critical thinking skill, logic and debate principles about as well as anyone I've seen. He doesn't post a ton (maybe once or twice a week on average) but when he does it is usually worth reading. I'll probably refer to him again.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's interesting, and Colin and I had a discussion about it once before, but people who hold a strong opinion in either direction seem to find more evidence to support the opposite viewpoint than they find for their own. In this case we're talking specifically about the war in Iraq.  Matt and Colin (and Diane I believe) are all strongly anti-war and their perception is that all the media supports a pro-war stance, and most of America is either in the "with us or against us" stance.  I, on the other hand, support the war. (I will not get into a debate of the reasons pro or con in this post) I perceive the exact opposite. I see people in the media taking pot-shots at the war and trying their level best to paint the worst possible picture of what's going on to force an American withdrawal (Vietnam! Quagmire!). I see almost nothing but anti-war.   Oh, I have sources for finding news and articles that support the war - but none of them come from the major news sources (NYTimes, CBS, ABC, NBC, CNN, LATimes, Chicago Tribune, etc.) About the only news source that comes close is Fox news, and they aren't necessarily pro-war (we're talking news here, not pundits - their roles are completely different, one is supposed to have opinions and the other isn't), they're just less anti-war.  So, which is it? Is America pro- or anti-war? How much would you like to wager that the majority of America sees both pro- and anti-war people as extremist nutballs and feel that the war was probably a good thing in the long run but they wish it was over with and hope we can just settle things quickly and get our troops home.   But those aren't the voices we hear. We hear the voices of people who care a little more and want their voice heard. And if they agree with us, we pass over it in a "yea, yea, I know that..." fashion, while when we hear the people who disagree with us we react: "What? How can you be so stupid!" Which reaction will we remember? The one with more emotion involved.   P.S.: I'm not implying in a particular statement above that the American majority doesn't care at all about the war, or even that they care less than vocal minorities. I am saying that they're more willing to let others has it out verbally.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Matt made an interesting comment about children being able to decide for themselves by high school, and if not then our school system has failed them.  I will dispute that by saying, not really true.  Recent research has shown that cognitive development in teenagers is both non-standard and not as far along as we would suspect. The ability to use logic and critical thinking in the way that adults percieve it on average doesn't develop till 16 - 18 yrs. of age. It can develop in children as early as 12 - 14 yrs., or as late as 20 - 22 yrs of age. So, saying that they should be able to make up their own mind is somewhat true, but they are much more likely to be heavily influenced by outside forces rather than being able to weigh the pros and cons on their own.  Other signs that teens are not capable of the type of reasoned thinking adults are capable of: It has also been shown that teens do not accurately recognize facial expressions and the emotions they represent. They regularly interpret "shock" and "surprise" as "anger." The also had difficulty recognizing "anger," "confusion," and "empathy" and associating them with their propper emotions.  The teenage brain is still very much in flux and has not developed the stability and abilities of an adult brain till (on average) near the end of high school or the beginning of college. I find it interesting that so many people assume that a teenager (especially a high schooler) should be able to "think for themselves" - they can, but they are most likely using very flawed logical processes to come to conclusions.   So, when we're talking about objections to people endoctrinating our children, and believe me, I know it goes on for all aspects of the political spectrum, I am speaking of it as a trend that should be recognized in all areas and worked to be minimized if possible.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      For those of you who are authors, here is how to post to the site:  Go to  urlLink http://blogger.com , you will be asked to sign in - if you haven't already registered (if you are an author of the site you should already be registerd) do so. When you click the "Sign In" button you will be taken to the "dashboard" - in the dashboard you will see a listing of current blogs, one of which should be "Hell's Kitchen", that's our blog.  Click on the hyperlink to Hell's Kitchen, from there you'll be able to post to the site. Use the "Posting" tab, then "Create" and you'll be up and running.   I have myslelf listed as the only administrator so I'm the only one right now that can make changes to the template and change the settings, but all the rest of you should be able to post original threads.  If you have any problems, send me a PM on the mothership.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hugh Macleod focuses his writings on the marketing/advertising folks, but sometimes, what he says applies to a lot more:  urlLink Purpose, belief; reclaim them both.   Whatever your passion is, stay focused on that passion - make it something of incredible value to yourself. Then others will begin to value it as well.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A fellow blogger attended an anti-war rally in L.A. he ran into urlLink Gillian Russom , a school teacher in the L.A. area. Read his report, then tell me what you think of this.   NOTE:  Now, before anyone jumps to conclusions, I'm not saying that all school teachers are like this nutcase. I'm just pointing out something disturbing to me.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hmmm...looking over who has volunteered to help with this site, we seem to have a heavy tilt toward the conservative side.  I'm not terribly happy about that. I really want to see a wide variety of opinions on this site - if it's just a bunch of us agreeing with each other we'll have to resort to abusing Tom in order to have any fun.  Not that there's anything wrong with that.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Along with the death of Regan, some folks have overlooked the 60th anniversary of the D-day invasion of Normandy.   Please, don't forget about it -  urlLink remember it  and honor it.  Or, for a wonderful juxtaposition - read a speech by  urlLink Regan honoring D-day .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A very excellent article on the  urlLink roots of polarization . The author, David Brooks, is planning on writing more on the subject. I certainly hope he does.  He approaches it from a psycho-sociological perspective, and his conclusions gel very well with statements I've made in the past. Humans are simply not rational beings. Oh, we can talk about logic and reasoning and even the scientific method - but in reality we all process every scrap of information and sensory input through our brain, and our brain is shaped and defined by our experiences. There is really no such thing as an absolutely correct solution to any problem (especially in politics). The main problem behind partisanship and subsequent polarization is the lack of ability to see a problem beyond the confines of personal interpretation.   Brooks has it right - politics is very much like religion. You form opinions in religion based on a set of beliefs. Politics is no different. And just as certain religions cannot get along despite seemingly similar goals, so it is with politics.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A little sadness, a little relief. He really wasn't Dutch anymore. His mind died years ago. But we mourn the passing of his body, with a touch of relief that both his and his families suffering is over.  Some reaction from around the web:  urlLink here ,  urlLink here ,  urlLink here , and lots of links  urlLink here .  And a very touching personal essay  urlLink here .  This is a repeat of another post I made on the mothership.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This site is officially up and running now, I've posted a link to us on the mothership. Pete and I may be the only ones who ever visit - but I hope that isn't the case.   Anyway - welcome to any AZH visitors, and please come back. This blog is in its infancy and we're still trying to see what works, what doesn't and trying to set the tone.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
           I think the most controversial topic that I have ever run accross on a hiking website was that of nude hiking or being nude in public.  Basically, there are lots of folks who go sans clothes at places like the Verde Hot Springs.  At the time of the debate, I didnt really mind the nudists at Verde and I still dont.  The subject stirred and incredible amount of controversy      I was just thinking to myself the other day what a perspective changer it is to be over here in Germany.  There are naked people everywhere.  No one seems to care or even really notice for that matter.  It's just part of the deal.  I guess I kinda feel sorry for the folks that experience a gut wrenching feeling when ever they see someone naked.  I wonder if it is a big deal to you????    I am going to try to post the picture of a fairly typical billboard from over here.  I would also like some opinions on that.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    Test picture (Bartlett Canyon)&nbsp; urlLink    How cool is this - we can easily upload photos to the blog as well - totally free! Blogger.com rocks.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay - this is brand spanking new, and we're still adding people as contributors. Look for the following things to happen in short order:   As contributors are added, we'll find a place for a short profile for each of them   As contributors are added, we'll have a separate links section for each   We'll probably be updating the layout and other things - so just keep tuning in to see what we do.   P.S.: for any contrubutors - either put a post up of your profile and a list of links you'd like to see under your name, or send me an e-mail/PM - I'll get them up there.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      New research seems to point to recent research showing that  urlLink increased volume in specific areas of the brain is correlated to intelligence .  I'm not entirely convinced of this. We're always looking for the "G factor" (the Genius factor) and hopefully identifying some method of spotting it through physical observation. Einstein's brain was famously sliced and diced appart till very little of it remains today in the search for what made him a genius. Was it the size? (No.) Was it the shape? (Qualified no - more folds in the surface are also semi-correlated to intelligence.) Was it density? (No.) Bloodflow? (Qualified no - lack of bloodflow definitely leads to damage, but isn't correlated to intelligence necessarily.) Metabolism? (No.)  The interesting thing to keep in mind is that very few people could qualify as a genius in multiple fields of endeavor. Genius in one and very competent in another, yes. Genius in one and semi-genius in a related field, yes. Genius in two completely separate fields of endeavor, not really.  Psychology is such a complex science, there are just so many factors to consider and look for. Just as I don't believe we'll ever truly be able to generate artificial intelligence, I don't think we'll be able to pin down things like genius, creativity or personality. Sure, we might be able to go so far as to see how individual neurons interact with other neurons and in what manner and with what chemicals and so forth - but we'll never be able to fully understand why that particular interaction can produce a Beethoven symphony or a theory of relativity, or even the desire to love another.  And if nothing else - even if I live to be 120 or more years old - I'll never see AI or the type of understanding of the brain talked about here in my lifetime. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Cheif Wiggles has some interesting observations on  urlLink the nature of pundit discussions .  I think he's right on.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      An incredibly interesting read if noting else. Stone Mountain says that  urlLink Bush is probably just acting stupid . It sounds a little over analytical to me (like he's beating himself with his own cleverness), but, as I said, it is certainly an interesting theory.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A much more thoughtful response to a  urlLink French Blowhard  than the initial reactions a while back.  urlLink WorldChanging: Another World Is Here: Harry Potter, Deconstructed . Well worth the read. He brings in some elements of social thinking and cognitive early development that actually put some credibility back into the frog's argument.   It's still an over-analyzed, cultural reactionary diatribe - but at least, from a cognitive standpoint (an argument which he doesn't make, btw, it just happens to be a related point through coincidental research compoletely unrelated to his rantings), he can get some traction. Not much, but a little.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Andrew Bolt is  urlLink  pissed   at Michael Moore. Wow. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Michele offers some  urlLink Perspective . It is sobering to say the least. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is in response to this post by  urlLink A Small Victory - Expendable Children    urlLink follow up comments   Abortion is a pretty hot topic, but I wanted to state my position clearly. I am against it. However, I think it is extremely shortsighted and wrong to outlaw it completely. There are certain circumstances where abortion should be strongly considered. Specifically they are in the case of rape or incest and when the health of either the baby (it can be conclusively shown that they baby will not be viable outside the womb) or the mother is threatened. In all those circumstances (which overall are extremely rare) abortion should be an option that can be considered by the mother (in the case or rape/incest) and in conjunction with a doctor (in the health related causes).  I think the phrases of "Pro-life" and "Pro-choice" obscure the debate quite a bit. You could term me a pro-life advocate, but I'm also pro the life of the mother. If her life is threatened through pregnancy she should be able to get an abortion. But overal I would prefer the term anti-abortion. I like to be very clear where I stand and that term is more accurate. That being said, I also don't stand with the radical anti-abortionists. I definitely am willing to consider abortion in very limited circumstances, and I am unwilling to prosecute my views to the point of violence. Pro-choice as a term just offends my sensibilities - you're not pro-choice you're pro-abortion. By saying your pro-choice you're trying to hide an ugly term and sanitize your stance. Call a spade a spade, please.  The basis of my position is that of responsibility. I believe that the power to procreate is a special thing. The ability to create life ought to be taken every bit as seriously as the ability to take a life. Nobody in their right mind says they are "pro-death" - it just doesn't make sense. Life is to be cherished. The ability to create a life should not be taken lightly, and yet that is exactly the position of pro-abortionists. In essence they don't want to take responsibility for that incredible power. If you are willing to take the risk of using your procreative powers in a manner that will create a life, then you should take responsibility for your decisions and take responsibility for that life. I find it telling that more people are concerned with sexually transmitted diseases than they are about abortion. Yet they are both tied to the exact same phenomenon - abuse of the powers of procreation.  Every woman has, within the limits of nature, the right to choose what will or will not happen to her body. Every woman has, at the same time, the responsibility for the way she uses her body. If by her choice she behaves in such a way that a human fetus is conceived, she has not only the right to but also the responsibility for that fetus. If it is an unwanted pregnancy, she is not justified in ending it with the claim that it interferes with her right to choose. She herself chose what would happen to her body by risking pregnancy. She had her choice. If she has no better reason, her conscience should tell her that abortion would be a highly irresponsible choice.  What constitutes a good reason? Since a human fetus has intrinsic and infinite human value, the only good reason for an abortion would be the violation or deprivation of or the threat to the womans right to choose what will or will not happen to her body. Social, educational, financial, and personal considerations alone do not outweigh the value of the life that is in the fetus. These considerations by themselves may properly lead to the decision to place the baby for adoption after its birth, but not to end its existence in utero.  The womans right to choose what will or will not happen to her body is obviously violated by rape or incest. When conception results in such a case, the woman has the moral as well as the legal right to an abortion because the condition of pregnancy is the result of someone elses irresponsibility, not hers. She does not have to take responsibility for it. To force her by law to carry the fetus to term would be a further violation of her right. She also has the right to refuse an abortion. This would give her the right to the fetus and also the responsibility for it. She could later relinquish this right and this responsibility through the process of placing the baby for adoption after it is born. Whichever way is a responsible choice.  Is this position a moral one? Absolutely. But most laws are in essence based on morality. If we were to take off all laws based on morality so that our government could not punish anyone because of a decision or action they considered moral there would be few laws on the books left. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Apparently  urlLink comparing Bush  to  urlLink Hitler  is okay, but making the suggestion that  urlLink Kerry is the man that terrorists want it power  is not.   Okay, I got it. Just so long as I'm clear about that.   P.S.: I completely disagree with either side of that argument - they are both far too extreme for my tastes. Although I do honestly think that any terrorist would rather have anyone in the White House other than Bush, so the Kerry bumper sticker is correct in that regard, but the implication that Kerry is Bin Laden's "man" is going a bit far.    UPDATE:  more on the  urlLink Bush = Hitler  comparisson (a truly excellent read and a well defined comparisson, a must read in every sense).   
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Once again, the left declares that  urlLink Bush is a liar . As Matt pointed out before, lying is a very serious accusation. To say he flat out lied is to say that he knew the truth and yet spoke contrary to the truth. I think the most that can be said is that he had a poor representation of circumstances and presented his case based on that faulty intelligence.   However, I also agree with Steven Den Beste that the President had  urlLink other   urlLink reasons  for going to war that he did not divulge, but those are reasons that I agree with. And in any case, the charge of "lied" is still far to strong for what was done. I am not even sure that "missrepresented facts" is even in there as well. I think he spoke about the things that he knew at the time. It isn't Bush's fault that the intelligence was flawed.   I have yet to hear a truly cogent argument that Bush "lied" about anything.   The truly stupid part of the Ben &amp; Jerry dude is that the effigy shows Bush in a flight suit with the "Mission Accomplished" slogan on the front. That's a particularly poor image to use as the banner and speech in question could be interpreted two ways: 1) the end of major combat; or 2) the end of the mission for that ship and it's crew. Both of whichh are true. All subsequent engagements ini Iraq since that speech have been on a platoon or regiment level - nothing near the level of engagement that the first few weeks of fighting entailed, and nothing that involved a regular army. So saying Bush "lied" about the "Mission Accomplished" slogan is just plain thick-headed.   UPDATE:  even the Washington Post is admitting that  urlLink Bush didn't lie &nbsp;- at least not about one of the primary talking points for the meme. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There is a ton of stuff floating around the blogosphere and other internet news agencies about the  urlLink Sandy Berger scandal . Some have begun to call it "Trousergate" and  urlLink Wizbang  has one of the more inflationary quotes I've seen about it.   I'm not ready to go to the level of "the Watergate for the new mellennium" yet, but on the surface it certainly appears that Berger will have to answer to some pretty serious allegations. With all the spin on this story we're not likely to know the extent of it for some time.   Developing.    UPDATE:  the  urlLink Hambergler  - Very funny.  &nbsp;  MORE:  Now Berger has  urlLink stepped down  as an advisor to Kerry.  
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Here is a story that . urlLink I really like . It certainly seems more rigorous than the crappy "Mozart" study a while back. And there's a link to that old story as well
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've stated it before, but  urlLink this article reminded me  about it again, we will never create a machine with true artificial intelligence. We may be able to create extremely powerful computers, we may even be able to very cleverly simulate intelligence, but we will never actually create a machine that will be able to be intelligent in the way a human is: creative, sensitive and utterly unique.  I doubt very seriously that we'll even be able to create a computer that could show the same intelligence level of a dog.  Macines will always be nothing but a series of commands entered by a programer. Chess computers are a good example of what I'm talking about. They are very good at what they do, and they are very powerful. However, essentially they are still a product of millions of lines of code entered very carefully that does nothing but analyze every possible outcome of a chess game. They also program in every possible strategy to every possible counter move - they basically program in every effective chess move possible. There is no creativity. You can't program the computer to simply understand the rulesof chess and then say "go get 'em!" You can't even program it with general guidelines for strategy - well, you can, but anyone with a rudimentary understanding of chess will be able to beat that computer.   Basically, the computer is able to simulate intelligence in a highly specific domain (chess) but only within the prameters that the programmers have accounted for. That is the limitation, the computer cannot create, it can only extrapolate and analyze based on previously entered data and parameters. It simply has more knowledge to pull from than a human opponent and therefore has the ability to beat that human. Now see if it can readily apply, on it's own, the concepts learned in chess and apply them to, say, Risk (a vastly simpler game).   It is an opinion for sure, but experts have been saying we're "10 or 15" years away from artificial intelligence since the 1970's, and they're still saying the same thing. You can bank on it. It will never happen.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      You know, Blogger.com is just a great site. Since I've been using them (something like 2 years now) they've constantly updated things. Now they have some really spiffy updates to the Composer tool - I haven't used all of them yet, but they look pretty sweet. So far it looks like they include autoformatting for:   Bullets  Numbred bullets  paragraph alignment options  Text colors  More font sizes  Block quotes  Uploading files  Remove formatting button   A pretty fair list of upgrades for a free service.   Google - you guys are cool. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've always been a fan of his writing, and  urlLink here is an interview  about his latest book. Definitely worth reading if you like P.J.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Another gem from  urlLink Stephen Den Beste .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So the original Oil-for-food (which more closely resembled Oil-to-keep-a-dictator-in-power) program has now been linked to the Iraqi "insurgents" and has now morphed into a  urlLink Oil-for-terror  scandal.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This brings new meaning to that old e-mail that used to circulate about what cars would be like if they were  urlLink built by Microsoft .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink This story  certainly gernerates a healthy sense of optimism in our government's ability to protect information.    UPDATE:  Defense Tech is all over this story. More  urlLink here  ,&nbsp; urlLink here ,  urlLink here  and  urlLink here . 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Probably not .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Keeping in line with the unfortunate headline  urlLink this article is a bit odd . Rosie is a bit incoherent. Prohibition = bigotry? And isn't the current vote in the senate on the gay marriage and pretty much their deal, not Bush's? Also, it's not just a religious ideology - it's a moral ideology that some people hold independent of religion. Granted, not everyone holds that moral position - but quite a few do.  It's a silly argument, but one that deserves an honest answer. If you think gay marriage should be allowed, what about polygamy or bigamy? The same moral objections that hold for outlawing gay marriage can also be brought to bear on those two moral positions. They are currently outlawed as well.  I do not advocate any of them. Marriage is between a man and a woman. Yes, my decision is religiously and morally based. I cannot and will not deny that, it is who I am.  The Jared bashing may now commence.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      John Kerry -  urlLink stirring the racial pot .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The popular news source urlLink Knight Ridder gets it wrong .  The "Bush Lied!" meme is losing more and more credibility. I think that about the best that can be said is that the inelligence community failed miserably (which is an incredibly valid criticism and one that hasn't been addressed adequately at this point), but Bush certainly didn't lie.    UPDATE:  Here is another opinion with some good links that basically say  urlLink this isn't the whole story  and there is much more behind the scenes.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I can add nothing to urlLink  this post by Glenn Reynolds . And, in fact, the quotes he cites are self explanatory.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      In a fairly new and very interesting blog, WorldChanging: Another World Is Here: reports that urlLink  scientists say the magnetic field around the earth is collapsing . This is a very interesting story that merits much more attention.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just as it is for  urlLink Victor Davis Hanson .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've blogged about it already  urlLink here , and the questions about the atrocities in the Sudan continue. Here is an answer to my quesion of why  urlLink France doesn't want to impose sanctions on the Sudan . It seems they are heavily involved in the oil there. So, I guess, for them, it is all about oil.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Some thoughts worth considering if you are a  urlLink believer in the war on terror  but yet don't really like Bush all that much.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Rand Simberg has some  urlLink thoughts on party politics  that I think are quite relevant. Except for having never been a Democrat, my experience mirrors his quite nicely.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow. Jeff is on a roll. Now he's  urlLink decrying the stupidity and self importance of movie critics . I can say quite unreservedly that I agree with him. I have never read a movie critic that sounded like the average movie fan. They may sound like a student of film - but that's not the same thing. How about a movie critic who is more in the vein of a movie reporter. Tell us what you thought of it on a visceral level and not compare it to mid-20th century Argentinian civil-deconstructionist philosophist dogma or other such drivel.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jeff Jarvis talks of how the  urlLink old standards of media influence  are dead.   Probably not "dead" - but certainly wounded and staggering around. Jeff and other bloggers like Glenn Rynolds and Hugh MacLeod all make a very good case that blogs and similar media will take the lead in media influence in the years to come. I'm not 100% convinced of that, but they do make a very good point. Jeff and Hugh are particularly convincing.   UPDATE:  Jeff  urlLink touches on the subject  further. And then  urlLink some more .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink This is the kind of story  that makes my stomach turn.   So, the Kerry campaign is embracing "real American values" which apparently consist of vulgar diatribes (because, you know, "Democrats aren't afraid to laugh") and hate filled speeches against Bush.  Sorry, those aren't my values. Oh, and apparently as a non-democrat I have no sense of humor.  Nice generalizations Whoopi. The next time you do something funny, be sure and let me know so I can chuckle appropriately (or laugh with that evil maniac laughter we conservatives use every time we subjugate the poor, cause it's so darned much fun!).   UPDATE:  Even the  urlLink NYT isn't impressed  with the way the "Bash" was handled. More  urlLink here , and  urlLink here .  I hope this story gains some steam. It won't, but I can be hopeful.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Amid all the other concerns (venues not ready, insufficient preparation, security concerns)  urlLink this is certainly  something you don't want to hear about 1 month prior to the olympics.  Does anyone else smell disaster in the air for this summer's olympic games? Not necessarily of a tragic (meaning death or injury) kind, but of the "this is the lamest olympics EVER!" type.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Gene Weingarten can certainly  urlLink pack a punch  on occasion. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      If you did or didn't support the war in Iraq (ostensibly as a part of the war on terror for those who support it, or as a big mistake and none of our business if you didn't) would you support a  urlLink military intervention in Darfur, Africa ?  Would you or would you not be in favor of military intervention from the U.S. to prevent crimes against humanity?   Asside from that, if you say we should, but only if the U.N. approves it, then why did the U.N. approve military intervention in Kosovo, but not in Darfur? One was an ethnic clensing of Muslims, the other is an ethnic clensing of non-arabs. Should the distinction make a difference? Why is France once again opposing any intervention?  These are questions that I'd sure like an answer to.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      First: Mikey Kaus " urlLink we survived Carter and we'd survive Kerry "   Second: Andrew Sullivan (while citing the above slogan by Kaus) enhances the idea: " urlLink I think it's sign of real intelligence that someone can both essentially loathe a candidate and still, for various reasons, vote for him. "  And these are both people that are planning on voting for Kerry.   The roar of enthusiasm is deafening.  I don't want to know why I shouldn't vote for Bush, as with any politician there are some things he does I support, and some things he's done that I don't support. Yes, overall I think he's done a decent job and I plan on voting for him at this point. However, if you're going to convince me to vote for someone else, you're going to have to do better than "Anybody but Bush" - it may be a winning strategy for some voters, but it certainly isn't catching fire with me.  This is just one more reason why I'm registered as an independent. I don't really support any party. I support the people who have ideals that are similar to mine and hope that they can carry them out to the best of their ability.  I was listening to representative Flake on the radio the other day and I think he had it about right. He basically said that he knows it's all a game and that everything in Washington is essentially a power play and a grab for money, but that if you go there knowing that you can do your best to influence things in favor of your ideas of right and wrong and hopefully make a small difference.  I think that's the best you can ever hope for from a politician in today's political environment; that they have ideals and values that you agree with and that they'll go to Washington and attempt to do their best to pass legislation that meets those ideals and values. You'll have to compromise, you'll have to make deals, and you'll probably have to do a few things you'd rather not in order to get support for things that are more important to you. But that's life in American politics. It's been like that since the very beginning of our country and it's not likely to change anytime soon.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink This article in the NY Times  focuses on other aspects, make sure you read the 5th paragraph of the article:   The unanimous report by the panel will say there is no evidence that intelligence officials were subjected to pressure to reach particular conclusions about Iraq. That issue had been an early focus of Democrats, but none of the more than 200 intelligence officials interviewed by the panel made such a claim, and the Democrats have recently focused criticism on the question of whether the intelligence was misused.   They couldn't find any evidence of faulty intelligence, or for the more serious allegation of demanding that intelligence analysts arrive at a particular conclusion, so now they're looking to see if the intelligence was "misused."   This also jives pretty well with  urlLink other stories  coming out of England.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Or, if he's not around, James Lileks will do in a pinch. He's got  urlLink another classic  up today.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Then there is urlLink this article  from  The Onion .  I think that puts it back in perspective.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is so  urlLink ridiculously offensive  in so many ways. I almost didn't link to it, but then it is just so amazing that I didn't think people would believe it if they didn't see it. It is a shining example of how far some people will go to push an agenda.  UPDATE: Here's an  urlLink asinine quote  from a seriously fractured mind. You have to read it to behold the sheer stupidity of it. Honestly, It's unbelievable.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Read the 5th paragraph down in  urlLink this article . Who the hell was  urlLink he looking at ?  According to  urlLink this article , dude wouldn't have been allowed in the courtroom at all. So, what is he doing describing what Saddam looked like?  Idiot.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Of course,  urlLink this is no surprise  to anyone who has been paying attention. The scary part is that if this was missed by everyone, what else does the "intelligence" community have wrong?
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I don't know about you, but I think  urlLink this  is just plain funny.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    This is just a great caption to have on the front page of your newspaper. Not "Saddam Goes to Trial" not "Saddam Faces Charges" - no, we have to point out that Saddam agrees with the liberal POV - Bush is the criminal. Of all the goings on with Saddam today, that was the quote they chose.   Nope - no lieberal media here.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I saw this:  urlLink 56 Deceits of Fahrenheit 9-11 . My first reaction was, "cool, a really detailed account," but then I saw the length of the thing (it is really, really long - roughly equivalent to a page or two of text for each of the "deceits")and thought "why bother?"   Honestly, I'm spent on the subject. Burned out, tired and really sick of the subject.   It's going to be a long summer.   UPDATE:  Steven DenBest has  urlLink similar feelings .
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm pretty sure Lileks  urlLink covered the gamut .  UPDATE: Vodkapundit points out a  urlLink couple of international reactions  that fall in line.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There is lots of detailed coverage at " urlLink The Command Post ."  One thing that does bear mentioning, according to Saddam: " urlLink the real criminal is Bush ."   Okay!  UPDATE: a  urlLink summary of the charges  agains Saddam.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      David Brooks  urlLink paints that picture , and through the devious journalistic practice of actually quoting Michael  Moore.  I imagine you could argue that MM said these things merely to get the publicity in Europe. Which would be a fair assessment as far as it goes. But ask yourself - would you make those same statements? MM is supposedly a man of the people, but he seems to display a high level of contempt for the people he supposedly champions (lower and middle class).
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jeff Jarvis has a  urlLink "Duh!" moment . It's something that I've been noticing as well, we're not really seeing a campaign  for  Kerry, what we're seeing is a campaign  against  Bush. And really, it's a pretty sad commentary on the state of politics. If the DNC feels that their chosen candidate (Kerry) isn't strong enough to beat Bush on his own merrits, what does that say about Kerry? And they're saying just that by putting fort a campaign that focuses on beating Bush. You could say that de-facto a vote against Bush is a vote for Kerry - but that's a pretty far cry from, "Vote Kerry, he's the man we want in there." Instead we have, "Vote against Bush, because anything is better than what we have now."   UPDATE:  I just ran across an online advertising that said "Help make Bush a one-termer" - it was sponsored by the Kerry for President campaign. I followed the link and it was official, but I can't display it because it was a randomly generated ad (which I discovered after I refreshed the page).
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Michele has some  urlLink words to say  about the Saddam trial going on in Iraq.  I agree with her, it is an important day for the people of the world. A murdering tyrant has been brought to a court of law to face his accusers and respond to the atrocities he's committed. I hope that justice is indeed served, and by the look of things, that will most definitely be the case.   No matter where you stand on the why or wherefore of the war in Iraq, everyone should be glad that this man, this tyrant, has been brought to justice.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Holy. Cow.  This article  urlLink MSNBC - Most overpriced places in 2004  - is a hoot.  Read the bottom paragraph about how the rankings can be read - they are on a scale of 1 - 150 (1 best, 150 worst). San francisco is  the most  expensive place to live (150). San Jose is right after it (149) and New York isn't far behind (146). San Jose also ranked dead last (150) for job growth, with San Fran not too far behind (145).   If that doesn't make you want to move to the bay area, I don't know what will.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A little more government numbers crunching:  urlLink MSNBC - Tax burden shifts to the middle   The thing that reall makes me upset is that the whole tone of the article focuses exclusively on what the Congressional Budget Office foung. Apparently the analysis was requested by Democrats who oppose the Bush tax cuts, which brings up an interesting quesiton: what parameters and numbers were used to calculate the "tax burden"? Never forget, not for one second, that when you're dealing with numbers it is all about what you look at and how you report it - numbers (especially when you're dealing with extremely large numbers) very seldom are a complete reflection of reality. We're trained to think otherwise because simple mathematics do, in fact, reflect reality (2 + 2 = 4; always has, always will). However, when you're dealing with numbers so large that your mind can barely wrap around it (can you possibly concieve of how much money even $1 billion is? - with the government most revenue runs into the  trillions ).   So, in the article, one side (the budget report requested by the Democrats) says the middle class tax burden has increased. In other statements made by Republicans looking at different numbers  in the same report  say that isn't the case. WTF?  So, who to believe? You and I may never know. We aren't told precicely how the calculations were made, and we aren't told all of the parameters around the calculations or what numbers the calculations were based on to begin with. Without that information this article is just so much partisan hot air.   One of the more laughable quotes is in the middle of the article where they compare the amount of money the tax cut generated for each comparative income level. The bottom 20% recieved $250, the middle 20% got $1,090, and the top 1% got back $78,460. They tell us the top 1% averages $1.1 million income per year, and the middle 20% earns about $63,000 (I'm extrapolating from their statement that the middle 20% earns between $51k and $75k pre year). So if I have my math correct that means the middle 20% recieved roughly 2% of my annual income back as a tax cut divident. The top 1% is getting back roughly 7% on average. Not a very bad deal considering that the upper tax brackets pay a far larger percentage of their annual income in taxes than I do.   Another thing to consider is that there is a much more broad range in revenue for the top 1% than for the middle 20%. The difference in the mid 20% is between $50 - 70k, (a 40% swing) the upper 1% we are told averages $1.1 million, well what is the actual range? $1 million to several billion (we have quite a few billionairs in America)? If that is the case we are talking a swing of over 90,000% - that's a HUGE margin of difference for the top 1%. So those numbers quoted in the article are averages, which doesn't really do well in reflecting reality (remember in high school how you hated the dude that wreced the grading curve by doing really well on a test? - the same principle applies here: the curve (average) isn't terribly reflective of the true nature of the upper 1%).   Anyway - all I'm really saying is that these numbers are kind of silly to be tossing around. Especially the "top 1%" numbers. Those are just plain stupid. There are all kinds of special tax/income rules that apply to the top 1% anyway so all these tax numbers being tossed around are probably more meaningless than we can possibly realize.  I'm just odd enough to look at it differently to begin with - I have no problem with tax burden being more equitable to begin with. Here's what actually happened: my "tax burden" went up and the wealthy "tax burden" went down, but that's because taxes were lowered across the board. We are all paying less in taxes. As long as I'm not paying  more  in taxes (which I already feel is too much) then I don't particularly care how large or small my "tax burden" is. It could be completely equal across the board (flat rate tax anyone?) - and I wouldn't care. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      With all the stories coming out it seems like the Los Alamos research station could be quite possibly the  urlLink worst designed and defended  "ultra-secure" site ever created by the government.   For a place that handles so much dangerous material, ideas and information - it sure didn't spend much intellectual effort on actually, you know, keeping all that stuff safe and secure.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, not exactly, but certain elements of the Republican party choose values over winability. At least that is the  urlLink argument posited by Eric Sheie .  He makes some interesting points and the commenters to his post also pose more questions worth considering.  One thing he doesn't address enough is that this is the nature of politics. The truly motivated are generally those who have the strongest values and also generally the most extreme and farthest from "mainstream" or "moderate." The truth is that over the long run moderates are usually the ones to win elections. Occasionally a very highly motivated group can excite a base on a particular issue just enough to elect the occasional prominent official (see the "Know-nothing" party of the 1850's). However, once the "base" sees the radical viewpoints for what they are and compare it to what they actually want, the radical candidate will lose the "base."  I don't think his lessons can be applied specifically to Republicans any more than they could be applied to Democrats or any other party. It is simply the nature of politics and the "mob" mentality that occasionally arises. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Apparently the  urlLink California Supreme Court in a 5-2  ruling says that the San Francisco mayor had no right to perform the same-sex marriages and all marriages performed are null and void (the hyperlink has lots of good links to other stories and interpretations). More thoughts  urlLink here .  Can't say I'm surprised. Nor is this very interesting from my perspective. The law said it was illegal at the time and a mayor simply doesn't have the right to overrule state laws. Now, if there is a legal challenge to the law then that is a ruling I might have more interest in.  The primary reason I link to it here is just to point out the fact that this ruling really has absolutely no effect on the national debate except from an overblown symbolic effect. This is a legal matter that was pretty cut and dried. I think it is a good example of the liberal stance of most California courts that there were even 2 dissenting votes to begin with.  Now, I'm against same-sex marriages, but just because I don't support it doesn't mean that I approve of the ruling - the ruling was based on a legal matter and the law is clear in regard to same-sex marriages. They are simply not legal in California. For a judgement to have any lasting effect on the national debate someone has to challenge the constitutionality of the current laws on the books or manage to pass legislation that either solidifies the current legal standards (and survives the inevitable legal battle that the supreme court would be forced to address) or makes it legal to have same-sex marriages (and also survive the inevitable legal challenge which would also make it to the supreme court).  No matter what your views are on this issue, you need to realize that this is an issue that, despite any legislation one way or another, is going to eventually be settled in the courts. I'm not totally clear on the politics of it, but I think the only way to avoid involving the courts in that issue is to have the issue incorporated into a constitutional ammendment. That would be an extremely interesting story to watch the outcome of which is far from pre-determined (see: prohibition). Same-sex marriage is not an issue that will go away quietly and will take a long and protracted battle to settle it one way or another.  Not that I'm saying anything new or earth-shattering here. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Because this story:  urlLink Watchdogs point to "immense" plutonum inventory discrepancies  is certainly nothing to lose sleep over.  [heavy sarcasm]Yes, we're all  perfectly  safe. You can trust your government.[/heavy sarcasm]
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Stephen Green has some excellent thought and reflections on  urlLink the history of war and principles for winning the current war . It's a brief but good analysis.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I see a lot of predictions about what we'll see in the future. Predictions about society as a whole, technology, medical breakthroughs and so forth. Most of them remain decidedly optomistic to me. I try to think of it a little more pragmatically.  For example, since 1950 (over 50 years ago) what has changed? Communications are much faster, but still, a resident of 1950 would certainly be able to figure out how to make a phone call on their own, or send an e-mail with a very short demonstration. They would still be able to drive a car with no problem and navigate to and from where they wanted to go. They would be able to cook our foods and would easily recognize our major appliances. They might be amazed by some of the advances from a curiosity standpoint - a few medical breakthroughs might be somewhat amazing to them (heart transplant for example). But even this wouldn't be beyond the realm of imagination for them. Even their clothes would still fit in - a little geeky perhaps depending on your clothing choice back then, but still essentially the same.  However, if you look at the future that was anticipated by someone in 1950, our world is very different. As someone once said "Nothing is as dated as yesterday's future." Flying cars, space stations, moon bases, aliens among us, ultra-modern, ultra-efficient cities with monorails and such.  Why isn't it here today? We hear people say that we're closer to such things than we ever were in the past, but are we really? Are we really that close to yesterdays tomorrow? Are we really that close to things like true AI, custom grown organs, quantum computing, hybrid cars in every garage or fuel cell vehicles, space stations, viable genetic clones, designer babies, or any of that type of thing?  My guess is, no. 50 years from now (discarding any religious views I may have) will not look all that different from what we know today. The same advances we've seen over the past 50 years will continue to increase: faster communications, more computing power (possibly by orders of magnitude, but there is also a possibility we will have reached a threshold and can't reliably develop beyond that level by then), more ways to keep a person alive, faster, more efficient transportation options, etc. But we'll still have roads, we'll still have communications bottlenecks, we'll still have disease and death, we'll still die of old age (probably with an average life-span of 110 yrs.) there will still be 3rd world economies, there will still be wars and national disputes.  Basically - it will look to me like a denizen of the 1950's would look at today. It will still be very recognizable and not at all alien in appearance or execution. What 100 years will bring may be more significant - but even then I'm betting it will still be more than 90% recognizable.  I'm just not a hyper-optomistic futurist. The future has never come based on the predictions of futurists (at least not the fanciful ones - the boring, mundain, "that-wasn't-so-difficult-to-figure-out" type of predictions do come true though). What makes people think it will come through this time as opposed to 1950?   UPDATE:  Some  urlLink thoughts on Futurism . 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      When it comes to media matters, nobody touches Jeff. Nobody.  Just read his thoughts on the  urlLink loss of control of media by the media .  Or perhaps you'd be more interested in his thoughts on  urlLink what diversity really ought to be about .  I particularly like his thoughts on diversity. I've often thought that diversity was nothing more than a skin-deep, feel-good word. How can you possibly define something as complex as an individual human personality based solely on their color/race/economic circumstance/location of origin/political leanings or whatever parameter you choose to pigeonhole someone.  I'd be willing to bet that at most you'd be able to get a 30% success rate like that. Meaning that by categorizing someone on some convenient surface parameter you'd be able to discern maybe 30% of their viewpoints. However, I imagine that even that success rate would be diminished if you took into account nuance of opinion.  Diversity as defined by government or burocuracy is an illusion. It is something designed purely to give a demonstrable and measureable result - and you can only measure something like that through the most cursory and obvious observable traits. Skin color is a great one - you just have to look to see if someone is a different color than you are - if they are, Huzzah! you have diversity.  What a load of crap. As a psychologist I cannot imagine a more demeaning and shallow way to categorize a person. However, the unfortunate truth present is that type of categorization has become so prevelant that people are willing to let themselves be defined by the parameters of "diversity." And that is all in the name of power - if you associate and groom yourself to fit in with a category that offers certain advantages you deem worthwhile, you'll allow yourself to be categorized.  It's a poor way to run things, but I don't see it ending anytime soon. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was going to blog James Lilek's post this morning, but instead I'll just kill two birds with one stone. Michele has some excellent thoughts on a subject that I've been thinking alot about recently:  urlLink SBHFS: Sudden Bush Hatred Fatigue Syndrome .  Her basic thesis is that in all the years she's been following politics she cannot remember a time when so much hatred was being pushed around. She does have a point that there are far more outlets for that kind of sentiment than there ever have been, but in essence I think that isn't really a factor. There just simply is more visceral reaction and people are more willing to trip the switch toward an emotional reaction than ever before. It's easier, it takes far less thought and effort and it isn't looked on as disapprovingly as in times past.  There is just more room for hate.  It's a development that I'm not pleased with. What happened to responsibility and civility? I don't care if you disagree with my viewpoints, but if you do could you possibly tell me why in reasoned terms and then propose a different solution?  That's what's missing most of the time. Complain and rail, but don't offer counter solutions. Just point out what's wrong with the current situation.  I'm fatigued as well. It's exhausting - and I'm utterly certain that the "other side" feels the same way. There can even be credible arguments made that the current environment of hate began with Clinton and the position taken by the right during his administration. But I don't think either "side" is to blame exclusively or even more than the other. We just arrived at this point together.  What a way to live a life. I used to be interested in politics, but now I'm not sure that I have the stones to deal with the current climate. What kind of pressure would that put on my family? I'm not sure I would be willing to put them through that kind of experience.   UPDATE:  Jeff Jarvis has  urlLink truly excellent and must-read  thoughts on the matter. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    Now that's how you make a mess with a Red Vine!
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    This one isn't ours - but it is a good example of what can happen when you give a Red Vine to a (nearly) one year old.  What a glorious mess. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    She thinks she looks horrible because she is 7 months pregnant.  I think she looks wonderful (she, of course, doesn't believe me). 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    This is my son Caleb preparing some muffins with his mommy in preparation for his 4th birthday. He LOVES cooking. Cooking for his 4th birthday party 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Some  urlLink interesting observations  about presidential intelligence.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I posted previously about the  urlLink SWIFT boat veterans against Kerry , and I said that the story would never see the light of day. Apparently I was right,  urlLink but was looking at the wrong source  for the obstruction.  UPDATE: The Instapundit is  urlLink all over this  
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was busy preparing a talk I am going to give at my church when I ran across a talk that was given by the leader of my church in October of 2001 - only one month after the 9-11 attacks.  " urlLink The Times in Which We Live "  For those who are unaware, yes, I am a member of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (otherwise known as the Mormons). This talk is by the President of our church Gordon B. Hinkley.  Having said that, I'm sure that anyone not of my faith will have immediately moved on to read other blatherings that I have posted here. However, may I make the simple request that you read his words. His statements about the war on terror are particularly relevant.  Excerpts:  You are acutely aware of the events of September 11, less than a month ago. Out of that vicious and ugly attack we are plunged into a state of war. It is the first war of the 21st century. The last century has been described as the most war-torn in human history. Now we are off on another dangerous undertaking, the unfolding of which and the end thereof we do not know. For the first time since we became a nation, the United States has been seriously attacked on its mainland soil. But this was not an attack on the United States alone. It was an attack on men and nations of goodwill everywhere. It was well planned, boldly executed, and the results were disastrous. It is estimated that more than 5,000 innocent people died. Among these were many from other nations. It was cruel and cunning, an act of consummate evil.   Now we are at war. Great forces have been mobilized and will continue to be. Political alliances are being forged. We do not know how long this conflict will last. We do not know what it will cost in lives and treasure. We do not know the manner in which it will be carried out.    Members of the Church in this and other nations are now involved with many others in a great international undertaking. On television we see those of the military leaving their loved ones, knowing not whether they will return. It is affecting the homes of our people. Unitedly, as a Church, we must get on our knees and invoke the powers of the Almighty in behalf of those who will carry the burdens of this campaign.       
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This certainly  urlLink can't be a good thing  for Kerry. However, if it ever gets reported in the big media - it will be a miracle. This will never see the light of day on a national stage.  UPDATE: Well, it has trickled onto the national stage, but the big media certainly hasn't done much covering of this story (unlike the fevered coverage of the non-scandal about Bush's National Guard service record). All I want to see is an admission that there is a scandal and a defense by Kerry's team.  Overall the story is not much of an issue. Even if the charges prove to be true the end result is that Kerry told a lie. [heavy sarcasm]Politician's lie? No freaking way![/heavy sarcasm]. The only thing this tells me is that Bush has a greater tendency to stick to what he says and that you have a greater chance that Bush will tell you straight up where he stands. Kerry not so much.  Again, no surprise there.  I'd rather to see the personal attacks end. Give me issues and plans for the future. That's what I'm interested in. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      If you don't read Hugh Macleod - shame on you. To get a taste of the type of genius that he produces, just read his thoughts on  urlLink how to be creative .  The man knows a little something.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jeff Jarvis is right. All I can say is:  urlLink Amen, brother .  All the "visionary" protestors like Michael Moore have no vision. They focus like a laser beam on one problem. They have the proverbial hammer to solve every problem. The world is far too complex to point at a single source of any problem. If you don't like the way things are being run in the country, the problem isn't one man (Bush). The problem isn't even three men (Bush, Cheney, Ashcroft). The problem is much larger, much more complex. Focusing the debate on one man doesn't solve the problem, because fixing that one thing won't fix the problem.   Take stock in the situation. The world changed on its own - Bush didn't change it and neither did Clinton. They don't have the power to do something like that. All they can do is be a player in the game.   Look at the game and figure out how to play it - don't focus so much on the players and figure out how to bring them down. The game will continue without them.
     

        
</post>


</Blog>