<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      http://www.roanoke.com/news/roanoke/6933.html  I am furious beyond reproach.  Why do college campuses seem to breed rapists?  Why are my fists clenched in a ball right now?  Why do I feel helpless when my friends have been raped?  Whatever we are doing is not working.  Someone put out an idea to make this stop, I swear on my life I will help bring it to fruition to the best of my ability.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I quit bringing a lunchbox to work because everyone looked down upon it and commented on it and asked while I still carried one.  Instead I have been throwing my sandwhich or what have you in my briefcase.  I looked on top of the fridge today at my lonely unused lunchbox.  Fuck them for making me not express who I am because it doesnt look "grown" enough.  I have more education then 2 of my 3 bosses.  So today, my metal lunchbox with Wonder Woman and her golden lasso have made a comeback.  Damn the Man.  Who doesnt love the movie "Empire Records??"  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Check it out:  www.margaretcho.com/blog/blog.htm  While you are at it check out www.moveon.org
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is my last Tuesday at work.  This morning I started to reflect on all the kids I worked with, how I made an impact in their lives, and how they made an impact on mine.  They have a complete journey ahead of them, most of it uphill, and it makes me sad to not be able to share in that anymore.  I mostly worry about the ones where "dad" was around just long enough to donate sperm and "mom" sits in her room all day smoking weed and forgets to pick up her kids from the bus stop or buy groceries and fix them dinner so they can eat.  I know I cant save the world, but I have to try something because many people figure it is up to someone else to fix it...leaving no one doing anything. I challenge you all to make a difference in your community in some way.  Be involved, make your prescence known.   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How much do I love Sophia Murray?  She spent four hours of her own Sunday chill time to help me get my project for work done.  She rocks and I just had to let everyone know, just in case they didnt already!   Today is my last ever Monday working here.  I am getting taken out to lunch today...gotta love free food.  Antoine's son is here at work today.  His name is Najii and he is four..the cutest little man ever.  He keeps coming into my office because of course I am fun to play with and have all sorts of toys on my desk.  How can I resist such cuteness?  Kids can make me so happy.    I went crrrazzy at the grocery store yesterday...eighty dollars later of Fruity Pebbles, Chocolate Milk, Chips and Salsa and Queso...needless to say I can't wait to go home and throw down..you know you want to help too..don't even front.  I figured it was the last time I would go to the grocery store while in Charlotte so why not eat like pure shit and enjoy it.  I think I did get some lettuce and grapes though..green things are good right?    Well all is good.  Peace abounds in my life which is my daily goal.  Thanks to all my Blacksburg/VT peeps who threw down in the comments section in my support.  I love you all.    Do hi yi & tsi lv quo di my brothers and sisters.  (Peace and love)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, I come home to this.  I would like everyone to check out the comments under my "Skye Kennedy, Esq." post.  I was going to delete them, but after a moments thought I have decided to highlight them.  The comments are made by Katie, Skye's ex.  I mean yeah, I understand bitterness, but DAMN.  There is a Chris, I have met him - he is a pretty cool guy as far as straight men go.  Oh and as for Skye's massive bruise (the reason I left work and went to Athens)- Ms. Thing I know you are reading this and if you touch her again I will personally call the police.  For future reference KT, please refrain from commenting on my blog.  I truly do wish you peace so relax, get laid, and have a cold one.    -Stacey  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I wanted to take a moment to reflect and work on my inner peace.  I fell in love with a woman many years ago when I had a sweet innocent baby face and a matching heart.  We became amazing friends and I lost all hope that my love for her could ever be returned. I have never been a believer in fate, yet circumstances have opened my eyes to the fact that I have no control over love.  This woman is now in my life as my partner, by my side.  To see her and look into her eyes when I first awake is a beauty only those who have found their soulmate can comprehend.  I am truly at peace in our love.  Skye, you know I am truly putting myself out there, but I wanted to let everyone know how I feel about you.  Its not "Skye Who?" - its "Skye, my Life."  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahh..its that time of year again where I crave music concerts and traveling.  Traveling to different cities is like going to an art museum for me.  Every city, every block paints a different canvas and sometimes the beauty grabs your right out and takes your breath away.  Other cities, you have to look for the intricate detail to appreciate the art. The oppurtunity to travel to so many different places for lacrosse was one of the biggest bonuses (aside from my tuition being paid and all).    Music is one of my favorite art forms.  However, I have not been to as many concerts as I would like because I refuse to sit in Row ZZ for 50 bucks and not be able to see anything.  I will go see Jill Scott this summer though - trust.  Aundre, you know you want to come with me!  Did anyone go see Melissa Ferrick at DC Pride?  Well Im chillin at work, all three of my bosses are in New Orleans right now...I WILL make it there to see my Mallory at some point.  Its been too long since we've chilled with cloves, Corona, and Whitney Houston dance sessions at 2am Tiny! Ahhh memories...  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had a great night.  Went to the Charlotte Sting game and saw Dawn Staley, Nicole Powell and a suprisingly new, improved, and now somewhat hot Kelly Mazzante.  They won the game in the last second with a drive to the basket by Tyneshia Lewis.  It was tight.  And then, back to the house to watch the Pistons beat up on the Lakers!  Girls in shorts and Kobe and Shaq going down - what could be better?  I slept so well, it was so refreshing.    I started today with some French Toast Sticks from Burger King - a breakfast of champions for sure.  So why am I getting so many complements on my hair this morning?  I got up so late that I didnt really even brush it, just ran some water in it so that afro puff of morning hair I get would go down a bit.  Well nothing deep or brilliant for you this morning, not that there ever is - my brain has been immersed in charting child behavior patterns which is important but tedious.  Just earnin' that last paycheck and all.  Back to work for now. Holla at your girl.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I would like to thank "Anonymous" for their lovely comment and well wishes that I received this morning.  Skye and I are happy and it is so great that you would take the time to wish us happiness in the start of our relationship.    I've had a great morning thus far.  I woke up extremely warm and happy.  I did forget my Marvin Gaye CD that I had planned to bring to work with me so instead I am humming - I feel sorry for those around me who really dont want to hear it through the grapevine.    Im probably going to the Charlotte Sting game tonight - got to see Nicole Powell play in person.  You know the whole crowd will be family - gotta love that.  Well back to work, I'll check back later.    Peace.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So...I just gave my two-weeks notice.  I will officially be unemployed at 5:00pm on June 25th.  Giving notice was a little more unsettling then I thought it would be - it took me a good ten minutes to get the nerve to walk into my boss's office.  At the same time it is a relief, it is a job that makes me miserable at points, working the jobs of 2 or 3 people and definitly not seeing any of that scratch.  Still, it was the routine and a steady paycheck that provided comfort.    By the way, I've been singing the Dukes of Hazzard themesong all morning.  I made my first ever trip to Alabama this weekend.  It was a cultural experience to say the least.  I thought I had seen small town living before - evidently I was wrong.  Im not knocking it at all, just the polar opposite of where I grew up.  Im sure the traffic, massive bridges, and the hurried nature of Washington/Baltimore would be a culture shock to the residents of Douglas, Alabama.    I miss Skye, it gets exponentially harder to leave her every weekend.  Im happy that problem will soon be solved.  We had some great talks this weekend and it felt good to finally meet James - it gave me a different lens to look at her through which I just ate up.  Kenshata, if you are reading this you need to holla at me - its ridiculous that we havent chatted yet!    Adia Jasmine Garrett - I am calling you out - pencil me in!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have just recently began to entertain the idea of going back to school for my PhD.  Then I laugh and laugh and laugh.  They say post graduate work is for those who are truly anal retentive - oh and how I fit that bill.  I am the consumate student, but being broke and working for free (internships) wasnt all that it was cracked up to be.  Im hoping this flickering interest will soon pass.    Well this afternoon I am off on a road trip.  That means Beatles and 80's hair metal belted out at the top of my lungs - nothing else makes the time pass on road trips quite like the nostalgia of "Pour Some Sugar On Me" and "Once Bitten, Twice Shy."  You know you are humming right now.  Oh and I don't particularly find tractors sexy - Skye just wishes I did :)                                    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Missin the summer nights of whip cream twister - I need to take the summer off from being an "adult adult" as Skye likes to label me&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A middle school student, at a school I interned at, was shot and killed a few days ago.  A 17-year-old used a handgun to shoot him in the stomach over a girl.  According to a friend of mine who still works there, this kid didnt want to kill him - he thought that shooting him in the stomach would just hurt him.  I am completely uneasy with handguns and dont understand why they need to be legalized to be carried by civilians.  Im not against all guns mind you - just ones that can be concealed and brought into a home or school undetected.  Let me know your thoughts on this.   http://discussions.roanoke.com/roatimes/news/story168180.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      When you first arise in the morning, give thanks to the Creator, to the four directions, to Mother Earth, to Father Sky, and to all of our relations, for the life within you and for all life around you. Remember that all things are connected. All things have purpose.  You are bound by your word, which cannot be broken except by permission of those who the promise was given to. Seek harmony and balance in all things. It is always important to remember where you are in relation to everything else and to contribute to the Circle in whatever way you can, by being a "helper" and protector of life.  Sharing is the best part of receiving.  Practice silence and patience in all things as a reflection of self-control, endurance, dignity, reverence, and inner calm. Practice modesty in all things, by avoiding boasting and loud behavior that attracts attention to yourself. Know the things that contribute to your well being, and those things that lead to your destruction. Always ask permission, and give something for everything that is received, including giving thanks for, and honoring all living things.  Be aware of what is around you, what is inside of you, and always show respect. Treat every person from the tiniest child to the oldest elder with respect. Do not stare at others; drop your eyes as a sign of respect, especially in the presence of Elders, teachers, or other honored persons. Always give a sign of greeting when passing a friend or stranger. Never criticize or talk about someone in a harmful, negative way.  Never touch something that belongs to someone else without permission. Respect the privacy of every person, making sure to never intrude, upon someone's quiet moments or personal space. Never interfere in the affairs of another by asking questions or offering advice.  Never interrupt others. In another persons home, follow his or her customs rather than your own. Treat with respect all things held sacred to others, whether you understand these things or not.  Treat Earth as your mother; give to her, protect her, honor her; show deep respect for those in the animal world, plant world, and mineral world. Listen to guidance offered by all of your surroundings; expect this guidance to come in the form of prayer, dreams, quiet solitude, and in the words and deeds of wise Elders, and friends. Listen with your heart. Learn from your experiences, and always be open to new ones.  Always remember that a smile is something sacred, to be shared. Live each day as it comes. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just was informed that I had the settings so that only other members could comment - well that is now changed so that ANYONE can state their comments - so have at it! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, good news.  Great news actually.  Even though I am currently going to be unemployed for the moment in the great state of Georgia, I will NOT be homeless.  Skye and I will dwell in this amazing house - email me for the link to look at pictures :) There will be plenty of room for visitors, so I want to hear no excuses my friends.  Im really craving the power, beauty, and energy of the ocean right now.  I can almost smell the salt water if I close my eyes long enough.  My memory and imagination are better than any camera they have on the market. Speaking of the market, I have become quite obsessed with some material objects of late.  Let me share some and let me know if you feel me on any of these:   1.  Toyota Seqouias  - I get this lustful, orgasmic feeling everytime I see one - and trust me they are on every block in Charlotte. 2.  Vinyl  - thats right I want some good old LP's and a record player.  Nothing has come close to that sound unless you are hearing the music live.  Right now Im jonesin for Jimi Hendrix and some Janice Joplin.  3.  Old School Nintendo  - give me that A&B button and Super Mario shooting a fireball out his belly button and Ill be content for hours.  4.   Jet Ski's  - thats nothing new at all - just gets worse in the summer time when I see everyone out on the lake with one.   5.  Digital Cameras  - if anyone has a recommendation for a good camera - let me know 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I have more than a few worries on my chest right now which is making it feel like I had a cage match with one of the Glamourous Ladies of Wresting.  Who remembers GLOW from TV in the early/mid 80s?  Anyone?!  My momma is my main concern.  Shes a tough little thing, but like me has to put everything on her shoulders when she needs to be sittin on a beach sippin on her ice tea lookin for seashells when the tide goes out.  I hate my job because school is out and I dont get to see my kids, Im just chained to a computer doing paperwork which is against my personality.  I have to interact with people to be fufilled at work and not just stare at the keyboard all day.  Who would have thought that when at age 10 I couldnt even look the waitress in the eye when she would ask me what I wanted for dinner...what a shy kid I was.  Now look at me - presenting workshops and helping kids and parents to get along with each other...just a few years ago in my freshman year at college I wanted to do cancer research.  So as I labor on with this entry - let me get back to my point - I think my generational roots are filled with worriers - but the kind of worriers that are active and take care of it - if that is any better than a passive worrier.  That is why I am not having the kids! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Is there a clear definition of home?  I have lived in many different places, but the only thing I refer to as home is my momma's house.  I lived in Blacksburg for six years and still only said "my apartment" - never called it home.  Maybe its because the faces always changed, roomates changed - nothing was a constant.  Maybe home is the thought of unconditional love - of a mother who will defend me to her death, of a family that always welcomes me with open arms, or of a good friend with deep brown eyes who will cuss me out in an instant and then give me the biggest smile ever no matter if I havent seen her in a year.  Maybe home is safety.  God knows I have an issue of never feeling safe, like someone is always going to break into my apartment even though that is ridiculous (I hope).  Well I welcome any thoughts, Im at work but thats a whole 'nother issue in itself.   Peace and love.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me laxin it up&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am on the verge of taking one of the biggest leaps of my life.  Those who know me well know that my biggest fear in life is falling.  Yet, I strangely find myself unafraid.  As a born and bred Yankee city girl, I have begun the process of learning  about and embracing Southern culture into which I will soon be quickly immersed.  Im ok with that just as long as I dont have to be an Atlanta Falcons fan!  So here's to love, jumping in head first, and to new friends. Cheers.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have severe shin splints today.&nbsp; Skye and I went on this 5 mile walk the other day and my running shoes are a bit old.&nbsp; I went to Finish Line to look at some new ones and why are all the ones I liked 99$ and up?&nbsp; I am addicted to my book of Logic Puzzles right now.&nbsp; I even prefer doing them over reading at the moment.&nbsp; Nothing really new with me at the moment.&nbsp; I am in a bit of a stalemate which I am determined to change.&nbsp; There&nbsp;are only so many home improvement shows I can watch on TV before my brain will go to mush.&nbsp; Job hunting is scary but I am beginning to stick my neck back out there.&nbsp; There is a show on the Discovery Channel that I want to watch - Dr. G, Medical Examiner.&nbsp; Has anyone seen it?&nbsp; Im fascinated by that kind of shit.&nbsp; Ok, off to eat.&nbsp; :)&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So things are finally settling down in Athens.&nbsp; Skye and I both got flat tires within the same week...too troubling for me to just write off as coincidence but who knows and frankly now I don't really care other than it set me back 60 bucks for a new tire.&nbsp; Kenshata's pictures of DC she has posted online have really made me miss my hometown.&nbsp; There, organized chaos abounds.&nbsp; The Southern life has really slowed my roll, which isnt a bad thing - yet there is a part of me that misses that fast pace reality that keeps your blood pumping and on your toes.&nbsp; I don't miss the gas prices nor how much it would cost to rent property.&nbsp; Skye and I have painted the dining room and are going for the zen feeling.&nbsp; Notice I said feeling and not look.&nbsp; We need some peace and ever since we painted a Japanese character canvas and hung it in the central location of the house, we have acheived that feat.&nbsp; I promise to be more dedicated to the blog again.&nbsp; It is a definite source of catharsis for me.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am in the great state of Maryland right now visiting my family.  My parents live very close to the Chesapeake and I am so jealous of everyone out on their boats chillin and partyin' it up. But it has been great to see the family and eat some good seafood.  So I have officially moved in with Skye and my mother now refers to me as her "Georgia Peach."  My friends say I need to wear a debutante dress with some long gloves and Tammy went as far to even suggest a bonnet.  I think I will stick with my cargo shorts for now.  It has been great living with Skye.  There was a major snafu with the house about three days before we were supposed to move in so we renewed the lease on Skye's apartment.  We have taken on some home improvement projects to make the place look tight.  It is great to wake up to Skye every morning, even when her alarm goes off at 5:45am!    I am still doing all the paperwork transitioning shit that happens when you move to a different state.  A royal pain in the ass and a finacial drainer to boot but it all has been worth it.  I cant wait for UGA to start up again and take advantage of all they have to offer...I've missed being in a college town.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hmm..whats new...oh I got my hairs cut..a little fiesty haircut that Skye likes alot...umm I despise the DMV, I mean who doesnt...if I ran that show there would be chairs and video games for the kids and the adult kids (DMV would make bank on that), some of those water sprayers like they have at amusement parks so you can get a little refreshed if you get hot and a freakin hot dog/pretzel vender because we all know food cures all ills.  We have a cat now named Clinton.  A litte orange guy that is fiesty as all hell and likes to eat my hair and bite my toes as I sleep..but you know Skye and I are in love with him.  Im hoping after he gets his balls chopped he will calm down a bit though.  Let me know if anything new is going on with you all.  Peace and love.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Growing up Gotti" is a new TV show starting on Monday's at 9:30 on A&amp;E...sad thing is I want to watch it - Its about Victoria Gotti and her three sons..who doesnt want to see how a mobster's family lives? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>