<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink The Cannery Seafood House  Seafood place...oyster! Well Carol said Provence has good oyster too. Got to try both of them!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Cynthia's World 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      http://www.philipglass.com/ http://www.sun.com/software/looking_glass/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Lumiere Restaurant ?? Relais Gourmand   Lumi?re is a combination between European elegance, North American flair and Asian minimalism.   Robert Feenie's cuisine reflects this eclectic style.   For this young Canadian chef, the simplest cuisine is the most complex.   "I hope my food speaks the French I love, the Japanese and Chinese I hear around me in Vancouver and the Canadian I am."   Since it opened in 1995, the Lumi?re Restaurant and Chef Robert Feenie have received accolades from notable food critics around the world.   Lumi?re has been awarded Vancouver's Best Restaurant and Best French Restaurant awards for an unprecedented six years in a row.   In November 2000, Lumi?re became the first freestanding restaurant in Canada to receive the Relais Gourmand designation.   An honor reserved for those who specifically cater to the passions of the art of living, quality, refinement and a sense of the exceptional.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Nintendo Midi Music   urlLink MIDISite   urlLink evilau   urlLink http://www.vgmusic.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Yahoo! Photos - shirley_cwchan's Photos  My best friend Shirley! LOL Look at her nice nice picture albums! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink amarcord.ca  Amarcord ( I Remember ) is a Vancouver restaurant specializing in authentic dishes from Italy's Emilia - Romagna region. Try Risotto! Bigoli al Gambero 15.95  Sauteed Tiger prawns with garlic in a light Pernod cream sauce.    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Share Clip  Share Clip is a small utility program to share the text portion of the clipboard between PC, Mac and Linux computers. This allows you to copy and paste between two computers the same as you would on one computer. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Did some research on the search engine:  urlLink Topix.net Weblog: The Secret Source of Google's Power   urlLink The Google File System   urlLink searchenginewatch.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink International PHP Magazine - Cutting-Edge Technologies for Web Professionals    urlLink Vancouver PHP User Group  The Vancouver PHP Association holds monthly meetings on the second Thursday of every month. Meetings usually start at 6:30, but it is a good idea to show up a few minutes early. The venue is generously donated by ActiveState, and is held in their offices in downtown Vancouver at 580 Granville Street.  Each month a new talk is given with topics ranging from XDebug by Derick Rethans to Rasmus Lerdorf presenting 'Intro to PHP, Tips, Tricks and Performance'. The meetings generally cover technical topics relating to PHP development, deployment and use in professional applications.  There is no charge for the meetings and we welcome anyone interested in PHP to contribute to our open discussion with some of the top industry professionals within the PHP community. We occasionally hold social gatherings which provide a great avenue to get to network with other professionals around Vancouver, and traditionally with guest speakers as well. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hahaha visit  urlLink ehosting.ca   urlLink goldensoldier.mp3 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Incutio PHP Google Web API  Using SOAP to connect to Google API
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink HungryPig.com  Vancouver online food ordering website
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Eyeball Networks Inc.  If you like the video feature of MSN messenger yet complaining about the speed and troubles it brings, try this "Eyeball" video chating program.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink 飛行棋棋盤  今日見到Emily買左塊whiteboard,D megnet有D似飛行棋的棋子,所以上網搵?有無棋盤。好野!有飛行棋玩!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink The lomographic Society International  My friend gave this link to me very very long time ago. You can find a lot of imspirative pictures all from this site.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Got Woot Network Version 2.02 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       上海一只鼎  NO.3 Road (Shopper Drugs Mart 對面) Recommendations: 香蕉高力豆沙,燻魚,小籠包,賽螃蟹,肴肉,醉雞,酒釀丸子
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         urlLink CoffeeGeek.com   urlLink CoffeeKid.com   urlLink Coffee-Expo.com  Hmmm Tim sent me this link that talks about coffee and recipes. I guess Christine will love this site (if she hasn't know about this yet) LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Storyeum   Storyeum is a multi-media, multi-sensory, storytelling experience set in a unique underground theatre in Vancouver's historic Gastown. Enjoy the engrossing, spectacular history of British Columbia; compelling dramas, humour and action brought to life by powerful performers, spectacular sets and spellbinding 21st Century entertainment technology.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Did a little search today and found some funny references:   urlLink Modal Dialogs in JavaScript  Find this function during JavaScript research: a modal window is a child pop-up window that restrict your access to it, before you can go back and touch the main parent page again. Hmmm could be useful yet annoying when people don't why suddently the parent page is locked :(   urlLink kirupa.com - Creating a Borderless Window  Wow now this is call annoying: your own screen will be covered by a big DIV.   urlLink flashloaded.com  Alot of funny and powerful Flash clips. Try the Flash mp3 player! So fast!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today for no particular reason I slept in until 11:30am and late for work for a whole  2 hours 45 mins ! Suck big time :( So embarassed when came back to office.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Octopus Garden  This is a Western Japanese place that sits in Kitsilano. Try the fish sashimi plate! Hmmm Christine recommended the "Catapula plate" (I've no idea what that is instead of seeing a piece of green worm-like sushi plate), "thin steaks on sizzling plate" !_!    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Forum Nokia - Developer resources  Calvin Tong's recommended website from Nokia, a good place to look around modulephone platform program developement thingy. Hmmm may check it out later hohoho
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome to Jeepu's blog. From here you'll be able to find my latest news and investigation of ANYKIND. Hahaha jeepu!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Vancouver Magazine  Load of nice restaurant recommendations  Part of my wishlist: C-Restaurant: http://www.crestaurant.com/ Tojo 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Tiffany & Co. | Home  A website that contains every girls dream
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      More fun MIDI and MP3 sites:  urlLink MIDI   urlLink http://www.dejp.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Skybar - Party under the stars  The best club in town! Wow who wants to go with me?
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink HSBC Celebration of Light  2004 Schedule Wednesday, July 28 — China Saturday, July 31 — Sweden Wednesday, August 4 — Spain Saturday, August 7 — Grand Finale  Location:  English Bay, Vancouver   Start time: 10:00 p.m. rain or shine 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink VhqOnline.ca  This is a new movie rental service that customer can choose a movie online, and then the company will mail you the movie via Canada Post. You can watch the movie whenever you want, no due date. After finishing the thing and you feel like returning it, just mail it back to the company, and then you're good to rent a new one.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Gallery 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.imagestation.com/members/2xme 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink The Sushi World Guide: na -> Canada -> Vancouver    urlLink The 13th Annual Restaurant Awards    urlLink The 14th Annual Restaurant Awards  Well wanna try Tojo if I'm in the mood oneday :P 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink LanguageGuide: French Grammer   urlLink French Audio Dictionary - Introduction and Key to Abbreviations 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Richmond Community Centre Guide  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Carol's Friend's Wedding 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Lego Spidy! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Nothing to say, just look at how cute these dogs are:           
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      2603 West 15th Ave. Vancouver BC 604-739-0555 Speciality of desert and cake, not so impressive for dining. Shirley claims that the service was aweful, so you judge :)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Meadows Corn Maze  Amazing! The Meadows Maze! Go before sunset, or you'll get lost forever!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink UrbanDictionary.com: Define Your World  Open source dictionary system. You can define your own slang and even record your voice.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Pretty funny little movie clips!  urlLink 著數日報的笑笑小電影  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink http://www.ebmyoga.com/  Elise Browning Miller Yoga, it has beginner Yoga poses that are nice to start with.   urlLink http://www.ebmyoga.com/  Bush being your Yoga teacher, what more can you ask for? He's a very good Yoga-er!  Thanks Shirley for giving me the link!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Albums of Malisa  Wow look at this outgoing girl's pics...lots of activities! She's so fit and definitely a good athelet!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Cantonese Swear Studies  Every cantonese should descover their original, and the first step of it is to understand "swearing". You'll be amazing that almost every swearing word has a chinese character. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink The Foam Party Page  You know, this kind of party is really facinating, while you can see all hot girls wearing just their bras or bikinis and dance wildly in the FOAM. Wow so if anyone is interested, preferrably girls, let me know and lets hit one of these parties! Okok guys are welcome too :P
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Our princess Shooting is going to study in France! Everyone in the family went celerbrating ( for her leaving?! :P ) and gave their best wishes to Shooting star. Just looking at how many pic her took with every single person in the family...LOL Bon voyager! GOGOGO!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Peasant's Quest 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Ka  is one of the million Friendster's scam that unlucky Mimi encountered recently. He uses Friendster to get knowing 69 people, mostly girls, trying to get dating with them. Hmmm...read the conversation, what can I say :)   [03:31:22 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ex-ex: opened tutor center.               ex: programmer. [03:31:44 PM] ka: programmer at mircosoft? [03:31:58 PM] ka: which tutor center? [03:32:28 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: iono which tutoring center. my ex-ex's               getting married in sept, that's all i know [03:32:46 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: programmer at some company lor~ not MS....               haha....not everyone can get to MS! if not i'm working               in MS now la hahahaha what the~ [03:33:05 PM] ka: then u 2 are not that good in studying lah [03:33:14 PM] ka: nearly all my friends got into ms [03:33:19 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: haha really? [03:33:26 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: good for them [03:33:30 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: but it's diff 4 yrs ago...... [03:33:39 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ur older than me for 4 yrs.. and this               batch of graduates are different [03:33:53 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: future for IT isn't the same as b4 la~ [03:34:07 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: and.... u said u don't make assumptions               about me.. why do u assume that "i'm not that good in               studying"? [03:34:10 PM] ka: I respect what u think [03:34:14 PM] ka: but we know the truth [03:34:24 PM] ka: I didn't assume [03:34:26 PM] ka: u [03:34:35 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: u just typed it....... [03:34:40 PM] ka: I said that my friend got in [03:34:52 PM] ka: so I thought that he is that good..and should be in               MS too [03:34:53 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ka says:               then u 2 are not that good in studying lah [03:35:11 PM] ka: not that good and it doesn't mean that u are NOT               GOOD [03:35:11 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: haha...how hilarious when u said smthing               and assumed something and won't admit it? [03:35:27 PM] ka: u said that I told u that u are not good [03:35:29 PM] ka: I never said so [03:35:44 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: MS don't just look at grades~ they also               look at certification [03:35:50 PM] ka: I don't know if my communication skill got problem               ..but i am sure that u overlook it [03:35:56 PM] ka: no [03:36:04 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: and i have friends who are working in               MS... some of course have really outstanding grades.               but others, it's just becuz the chance permits it [03:36:04 PM] ka: they look at grades and your interview [03:36:21 PM] ka: if u perform well in the interview, u got in [03:36:29 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i don't wanna argue about this [03:36:39 PM] ka: they may not good in marks but they got brains [03:36:53 PM] ka: u have to go thr quite a lot of intellectual               questions [03:36:53 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: do u think MS gives everyone an               intervies? [03:36:58 PM] ka: no [03:36:59 PM] ka: they won't [03:37:01 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: exactly [03:37:11 PM] ka: but everyone can go in and write the test [03:37:34 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i've never heard of MS has a written exam               for EVERYONE [03:37:39 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: if u know the info u should give me [03:37:43 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: 'cause that's certainly not what i heard. [03:37:45 PM] ka: before [03:37:50 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: exactly. [03:37:51 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: "before". [03:37:59 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: well "before", i'm not graduated. [03:38:12 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: suen la....this is tiring to talk like               this [03:38:26 PM] ka: u were talking about my friends..didn't u? [03:38:34 PM] ka: we never talk about WHY U are not in MS [03:38:41 PM] ka: u just grad [03:39:00 PM] ka: why do u always have to twist what I am saying [03:39:20 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i think ur making assumptions about me               along the way..... but u won't admit it [03:39:31 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ka says:               then u 2 are not that good in studying lah [03:39:33 PM] ka: first..I said that my friends are in [03:39:34 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ...i'll always remember that [03:39:38 PM] ka: and u said that your friends were in too [03:39:44 PM] ka: but they are not that smart [03:39:52 PM] ka: so I explained that everyone could write a test at               that time [03:39:55 PM] ka: that's why [03:39:59 PM] ka: they may have the brain [03:40:09 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: u didn't say "at that time". [03:40:11 PM] ka: then u change the topic..and said that u haven't               grad [03:40:23 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ka says:               but everyone can go in and write the test [03:40:26 PM] ka: u were talking about your friends..who got in and my               friends who got in [03:40:31 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: .... that makes me think that i can still               go in and write a test [03:40:39 PM] ka: u can still do [03:40:47 PM] ka: u want my friend to give u a try? [03:40:53 PM] ka: I can email them for u [03:40:59 PM] ka: some of them are supervisors insdie [03:41:01 PM] ka: inside [03:41:11 PM] ka: u can give me your resume [03:41:11 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: sure, if there's such a chance i would               like to know it [03:41:22 PM] ka: just send me your resume [03:41:33 PM] ka: and your transcript [03:41:52 PM] ka: I can email them right away [03:41:55 PM] ka: which area are u in? [03:42:17 PM] ka: and..mimi [03:42:23 PM] ka: I really have no offense [03:42:39 PM] ka: I am not a kid or young adults like u and your               friends [03:43:02 PM] ka: all my friends and even myself are               professionals..who are working several years out there [03:43:14 PM] ka: pls say things out when u think twice [03:43:26 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ka says:               I am not a kid or young adults like u and your friends [03:43:31 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: that's another assumption about us. [03:43:38 PM] ka: it's not an assumption [03:43:41 PM] ka: that's the truth [03:43:49 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: nice. u say what u "say" are the truth. [03:43:53 PM] ka: haha [03:43:57 PM] ka: u are really funny [03:43:59 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i'm not going to argue about it now [03:44:03 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: this conversation is very tiring. [03:44:10 PM] ka: face the truth [03:44:21 PM] ka: if I say that u are a female, u are [03:44:25 PM] ka: that's not an assumption [03:44:28 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i have friends who are not the bunch of               people who are hanging around me, and they own their own               businesses [03:44:31 PM] ka: that's the truth [03:44:34 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: right.....haha..... [03:44:46 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: whatever. i'm really, really tired about               this now... [03:44:47 PM] ka: of course [03:45:00 PM] ka: most statements talk about majority [03:45:03 PM] ka: for example [03:45:05 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: thanks for offering to help me about MS.               I suppose that's not somewhere i really want to work in               anyways. [03:45:13 PM] ka: hk people are wealthy [03:45:21 PM] ka: it doesn't mean that EVERY SINGLE one is wealthy [03:45:27 PM] ka: if u wanna pick on that, anytime [03:45:31 PM] ka: just shows that u are a kid [03:45:44 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: so, u say that "general statements" are               not meant to be picked on. [03:45:47 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: then why comment on them? [03:45:49 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: it's pointless. [03:45:52 PM] ka: u can pick on every single word if u want [03:46:06 PM] ka: all statements are general statements [03:46:13 PM] ka: if u wanna pick on that, haha [03:46:16 PM] ka: nothing that I can comment on [03:46:24 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: whatever man~ [03:46:28 PM] ka: and IF u wanna pick on the present and past               tenses..all the time [03:46:29 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i regret letting you see my photo album. [03:46:35 PM] ka: nothing that I can comment on either [03:46:40 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: u've never sent me any albums about               urself [03:46:56 PM] ka: it's okay that u regret..I respect that [03:46:59 PM] ka: but I saw that already [03:47:00 PM] ka: too late [03:47:06 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: but my album contains a lot of photos and               about my life.. and i feel sorry for my friends becuz               u've made an unfair "truth" statement about them [03:47:08 PM] ka: pls don't assume [03:47:18 PM] ka: I don't have an album ( that's what u did ) [03:47:28 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: it's ok. i have nothing to talk to u about               right now.... [03:47:45 PM] ka: how can I send u an album if I don't have one? [03:47:48 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: i'm not a person who likes to lie about               myself [03:47:49 PM] ka: pls don't assume [03:47:57 PM] ka: : p [03:47:58 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: so i always think there's nothing to hide [03:47:59 PM] ka: haha [03:48:05 PM] ka: It's really funny to talk with u [03:48:06 PM] ka:  : O [03:48:11 PM] (8)  2xme? ~: ok. thx for the comment [03:48:18 PM] ka: nothing to hide? but u are hiding everything [03:48:18 PM] * ka has been blocked 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink 無聊峰的日記  峰哥乜咁悶呀 :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I spent a wonderful Sunny Sunday with May and Edith visiting the Horseshoe bay, Squamish and Shannon Falls. Here are some pictures we took:  urlLink 2004-Aug-01: May and Edith's Sunday Adventure  I'm sure that Edith had a very good time :P Lets look for pretty scenery again this summer!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>