<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm working 42 hours this week. if i'm an asshole to you at any time, this is why.  i will be happy when i get my 70 hour paycheck.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      slothO0 (1:47:38 AM): and now i have to do this survey because i'm really fucking bored and not tired anymore  YOUR LIFE____ [x] they call me: alex [x] also: franz [x] sex: male [x] my first breath of air: 4:35 on february 14th 1988 [x] status: i'll assume you mean single/taken where my answer would be single, yeah, fuck you too. [x] occupation: cashier / super saver [x] nationality: mostly german  ____REWIND____ [x] most memorable memory: well lets see, there's too many things that stick out in my head, so i'll just say last night, because i can remember it the best and it was a good memory [x] worst?: one sticks out [x] first word uttered: da [x] first bestfriend ever!?: jared foote  ____FAST FORWARD____ [x] college planning to go to: ISU [x] future resident of: ΣΤΔ (comment if you get that) [x] wedding: that's all her decisions, I just agree with what she says [x] children: maybe? i hate kids, but i dunno [x] looking forward to: tomorrow (pre-4PM) [x] NOT looking forward to: tomorrow (4-9PM)  ____PLAY____ [x] feeling: a little better than before [x] Listening: crystal method - high and low [x] Talking: to christ himself [x] doing: two chicks at once [x] craving: acceptance, understanding, my way(for once) [x] thinking of: people [x] hating: sluts  ____LOVE?____ [x] love is: found after a struggle [x] love or lust?: love with the occasional lust [x] best love song: ORIGINAL love song [x] is it possible to be in love w/ more than one person @ the same time?: no, that's highly impossible [x] when love hurts, you: hang in there, hope for the best, crash and burn (at least in my case) [x] true or false - all you need is love: true [x] have you ever been in love?: yes [x] is there such thing as love @ first sight?: somewhat  ____OPOSITE SEX____ [x] turn ons: similar personality, eyes [x] turn offs: people who become loose when they get drunk, and fatties [x] does your parents' opinion on your bf/gf matter to you?: are you kidding? [x] what kinda hair style?: long, not too long though, a bit past shoulder length [x] the sweetest thing a member of the opposite sex can do for you?: be there for me [x] where do you go to meet new people?: they usually meet me [x] are you the type of person to holler n ask for numbers?: i'm going to stab you.  ____PICKY PICKY____ [x] dog or cat: dog AND cat [x] short or long hair: long, not too long [x] innie or outie: only fatties have outies, and i think we've already gone over my views on fatties [x] sunshine or rain: rain in the day, sun in the night [x] moon or sun: moon [x] basketball or football: FRISBEE! [x] righty or lefty: right [x] hugs or kisses: both, but either one is good after a long absence [x] 1 best friend or 10 acquaintances: 1 best friend [x] bf/gf or best friend: gf [x] tv or radio: tv [x] starbucks or jamba juice: starbucks vanilla frappuchino [x] mc donalds or burger king: BK [x] summer or winter:  summer [x] written letters or e-mails: written letters [x] playstation or nintendo: nintendo [x] disney or nickelodeon: early 90's nick [x] car or motorcycle: car [x] house party or club: house party [x] sing or dance: sing [x] freak or slow dance: FREEKALEEK! [x] yahoo messenger or aim: aim [x] google or ask jeeves?: goddamn that faggot english butler  ____MISCELLANEOUS____ [x] can you swim?: yes [x] whats your most embarrassing moment?: ummmm, not my MOST embarrasing moment, but one time I was at village inn and the waitress asked me how i wanted my eggs and i kinda sat there for a second and said "yes" [x] what are you scared of?: losing someone, in any way [x] what kinda roof is over your head?: definitely not mexican [x] do you like tomatoes?: i like romas better than the big ones [x] how many TVs in the house?: 4 1/2, 6 if you count computer monitors [x] how many phones?: 3, 3 cell phones [x] how many residents?: 3, me, brother, dad [x] how many DVDs do you have?: a HECKUVA lot [x] last dentist visit: actually not that long ago [x] last doctor visit: actually not that long ago [x] last phone call: 11:47 PM tonight
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I couldn't explain my problems if I wanted to. It's the same old thing, me wanting something I most likely can never have, and just getting depressed about it. I'm not worth your time.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Andrei impedance meld profession trivium nail gouge drippy administrator costume suit rapid proteolysis argillaceous algaecide brasilia chestnut jubilee decryption pastel conant ambuscade evanescent thomas attendee tete jefferson nih bricklaying dung buses swordtail dnieper cryptography berniece schlesinger hibachi byzantium bonaparte embeddable florin hadn't hindrance fluid lutetium homebound barbital attempt ankle intensify amanita editorial slid mig simpleminded bumblebee dewitt academia niobium pantomimic brown wildfire homo hanoverian chastise numeric deferring seal profession citation corrigendum credulous commiserate zesty laurentian recital anonymity vendible charcoal gymnast feminine dispensary gumdrop corrosive mutatis confucianism anglican measle invertebrate bookmobile purgatory integument acropolis lawgive occlusive cession bursitis selector diligent cpu facade wheelbase beneath burlesque cryptogram babe gerhardt diagnostic scythia hazard declassify molt accusation always columbia luke clandestine amherst colloquia participant regulus ally butterfield medicine moor slurry intend polypropylene vicksburg curia evanston ferrite velasquez feather shrivel evansville nco import curlew necessitate stellar brendan wove surpass consort dare tenneco construe portal venomous hecatomb ulan rate june lookup electoral embellish factorial julep horsehair leer actinide larsen connie cackle warp posteriori initial controlling oxeye blomberg seldom sphinx eldon ambiguity picofarad gritty kosher misogyny amorous flashlight host coronary butternut folksong joliet russ curlicue gene dilettante booby shuffleboard bodyguard habitation naomi scent bellini anaconda werner ceremonial oleander nib azalea diego justine moron podge capo capetown embroil imperil sicklewort case debater appellate hecate horse buzzard gail watanabe contingent chaperon juice freeze anise autonomic fredericksburg simper dogmatism stanley scotsmen stamp hardboiled small elaborate tungsten additional fraction genial handwaving bezel analogue astral bloodshed filament suffice disturb adair appointee contagious prohibitive butyric coleus montmartre burtt breezy chaise prowess albacore comport testament acapulco hap ambulatory ruthenium huck salvageable helsinki sleuth theism lachesis became opportune hatchway vanilla euphoric threesome bronchiolar grass particulate capo cornelia lair beautiful coriander expound dempsey dreamt octave class duel cyclone alvin colette dandelion spayed beginner ames hackmatack lucian height incapable clone larry presumed guidebook seashore agamemnon stubble posteriori puritan generic nonsensical palladia cylinder blunt prolific fossil proven sarah spectrum hybrid sunlight lurk turtleneck contagion demitted crocodile invest hanover convulsive bender demagogue helicopter doubtful muscat frenetic lucretia explicit despondent wake fancy boogie denudation twosome deferral disjunct farthest collaborate mobster invite corridor forgetful parthenon she'll adult abrasive alto lilt pickerel hasten shim value antigen defrock job airspeed fairfax wrest motel suggestive upland bourbon waybill electroencephalograph assai collector rca benelux fee caretaker instrument quadrilateral yoghurt hemlock hidden sweater pocketbook affectate assignation contentious smirk brew pawtucket baptiste preeminent rheology cluster mcclellan rather bourbon reverend purr decker european neuter alsatian brazil crank knotty mandrel antedate shell congest involution ronald subsume partisan retribution anthropomorphic richard economy edwards chipboard pyrometer differ sima shanghai tetravalent neuromuscular inoculate reign libya hutchison plunk thunderclap fanny erroneous illegitimate extensor frustrater beg hessian negligee epidermis possession transgress ruckus mutineer obfuscate duffel letitia manchester cameramen adsorbate nightmare dinnertime northwestern planetaria relayed fluoridate saloonkeeper impale southern bookmobile century burnt inure bradford stock trajectory garvey funereal breakthrough lysine slavish consultant burglary fox harriet laudatory garrisonian degas deanna quizzes assyriology dahl olson mule helsinki great nil angelic manure adventitious decor bristle moldboard offsetting cotta weedy collateral tricky perchlorate gestalt offspring.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's an assignment for all of you:  Prove me wrong about something. Something that I've been really adamant about. This can't be an opinion thing, but rather something based on fact. Amy has already completed her assignment. Now the rest of you have the rest of June and all of July to do it.  Get to it, bitchezzzz.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ################################################ ################################################ ####################MXVVXRRBM################### ##################MVti+tIIYYVRM################# #################RI+=+++ttIIIYXRM############### ################Xt++++=++iittYYIIB############## ###############BIii+=;;++iiitIYY+IB############# ##############WY+==;;;;=+itttIVVIiIM############ ##############R+++;,:::=+t=+iIVVYttY############ ###########BRWVIYYI=::;=+=;==+IVYYIYB########### ###########XY#XXBRRI;;=+t+tIi=+iIVVVX########### ###########VtMRRRRRY=:;iVVXRRYt+iVRXXM########## ###########I+XRXBMRI=:=YRRXRBBRIiIRRXB########## ###########I;iYYRRY+::=XBXXBVXBRItRBRR########## ###########t::;;++=;.,;IXYBWYYVBVIVBBB###WRM#### ##########Mi,..,,;=+;=iIt+VRIYtRXIYMBM##WRYM#### ##########R;,..,:;=+=IIYt;+tIttVYIIRMMMRXRVB#### ##########Y,..,:=,,::;+ti:;+++iIYtIXRXXXRRRB#### ##########I,..:=;.,.,,;=+;,;==ttIIIVBRXVXBRM#### #########Wt:,,=+:,.,:;;=i;.,:=tYIYYVBBVVYXRW#### #########Ri::;t=:;;iIi=ii=..:=IYYYYXBXIYYVR##### #########Y+:;+I++YVRMRYIt=:.:=tYIYVXRVYYXRM##### #########I+;;iIIVBRVXBMRVt+,;+tIYYVXXXRXRBW##### #########t;;=IIIBBIi=VBBBYt,=tIIIYVRYIXRBB###### #########V==+IYVW##MBMRBMVI;;tIIYYVXVYRBRW###### ##########B++YVX##W###WWMVI=;tIYYVVYYVRBB####### ###########I+XXMW#######WRI;;tIYVVYIYXRR######## ###########XtXBM###WWW###Ri,;tYVXXYYVXBM######## ###########MIRRM#W#######R+.;IVXBRVVXXM######### ###########WYRYW#W#WWWMW#V;,=tYRBXIYRB########## ############VItW#WBRVVYXMI:,=IYRBVIXM########### ############Y+tBWBYt+++tY+:,=IVR#BB############# ############Y;iXRVti++++I+::iYXR################ ############I:=IIItti+tYX+,:IXRBWMW############# ###########Wi,;itYIItYRRV+.:YRBM#MBM############ ###########Wi.=iIVVYVXRXI;.=VRB###WMM########### ############i,=+IYVXRVVYI::YRRM#####WW########## ############i.:=itIYVVVY=;iRMMW################# ############i..,.;=+IIt+:iXBM################### ###########Wt....,:;=;;,+VBBW################### ############+:,.,,,::,:+VBMM#################### ###########WI;==;;::;=tXBBM##################### ############V:=iIIItYXRBBBW##################### ############B=:;IVRBMBRRRM###################### #############X=,,;tYXXXRM####################### ##############XYIItYVXBM######################## #################WMBBM########################## ################################################ 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got all these ideas, conceptions, thoughts floating around in my head, I don't know what to follow, what to believe, what to throw out, what to ridicule for even thinking about jumping in my cranium. It's 2:51. AM, mind you. I woke up at probably 10 this morning. Now, to the normal person, that might not seem very bad, but A)it's summer, B)i'm used to 12 hours of sleep (which i definitely did  not  get last night, and C)bagel. Just talked to a good friend on the phone, who was a little out of it but thanked me for listening to the rambling. Anytime. Jicky best get better. Is it true? I could say this to a lot of things recently. None of which I care to share right now. This post has the potential to be a good one. I started making a comic tonight, but when John Stamos got involved, I just about threw up and gave up on life in itself. Work is good, I'm getting 30+ hours a week, at 6.25/hour and after this paycheck I get the "you've worked here for a month and we enjoy that" raise, to 6.50/hour. I found out last night that Sonic owns at making french toast sticks. Better than Burger King's. And that's hard to do. Their syrup containers aren't very deep though, which gets annoying. SoBe Nirvana drinks kick your ass, my ass, and your dog's ass. If you don't have a dog, then it kicks your cat's ass. If you don't have a dog or a cat, then you're a fucking loser. Jesus. Jim Caviezeieazieizieazeail truly is Jesus. No, Eric, you're not. I wonder how many people will actually read this far. My dad's gotten cooler lately, he's actually trusting me to come home at legal curfew (12:30) instead of his bedtime curfew (11:00). An hour and a half doesn't seem like much, but in the summer, any time you can spend with friends makes a difference. I'm not sure why all these spam-senders want to stop my non-existent pain, but go ahead and keep trying to guess my name. (Hint: It's not Pablo Escobar.) I'm not sure what kind of college I want to go to, or where, or what I want to study, or what my major should be. All I know is that I want to go to college. Also, I want to be good at whatever I decide to do. Are big long ranting blogs annoying? Oh well. Maybe in the future I could divide these up into paragraphs. That would be like 350 paragraphs with how much I ramble. Jeez. Jimi Hendrix was a great man, even though he burned up that phat (yes I said phat) guitar. Did you know that guitar picks are just like little triangles of flamitude when you light the corner on fire? Seriously though, I'm not sure what it is about them, maybe the foil or something in the plastic, but Fender picks just explode into 1 and a half foot high flames when you light one on fire. It's really cool. Dan Keesis is an indian. He ranks lower on the indian scale than Chief Spetman. Punk rock doesn't appeal to me at all anymore, maybe because of all the stupid little kids saying "omg I totally scared a squirrel yesterday, it was so punk" and "omg my AOL background is black, thats so punk lol." Ami Hummel is a prime example of this. Damn fat kids. I'm gonna get crap for saying that, but I don't care, she's fat. Booya. Those camel spiders that you might have seen on website  urlLink A  or  urlLink B  really arent that bad, it's just the camera angle that throws people off. Plus, the picture you most likely have seen with the soldier in desert camo holding it up is actually 2 spiders either fighting or held together in some odd spider mating ritual or something. Jeffrey Rowland (the dude who does  urlLink Wigu ) got bit by a Brown Recluse and got wicked necrosis on his leg. It looks nappy. The wigu forums are the coolest. Just like Richard Cheese, bowling, and Travis Archer. That kid is the coolest. His mom's a crazy lunchlady though. When should I stop ranting about random crap? Broadway bowl is so much dirtier than even Lightning. Thunderbowl is the best when it comes to quality bowling, but I know all the people at Lightning, so it's cool. They just need to buy a freaking Smokeeter so they can get rid of that reek. Oh well, it's "the Lightning Bowl smell." Tom Petty rocks my socks. I think, that if I were gay, I might go find him and do him. But I'm straight, so that's not happenin'. No worries, ladies. Speaking of ladies, where the hell are you all? I'm so lonely! I want some birthday cake, right here and now. Or a Lunchables. Cracker Stacker, bitch. My camera isn't that nice but it works. Every month I have the lawn sprayed with classical literature to keep the rednecks away. Alright, I think I'll stop. Note: If you just scrolled through this post because you didn't want to read something big, I hate you and you are a fucking douchebag.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      comment shiz updated, now everyone post something
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      did i kill what little reader base that i had with my other blog(s) by moving here?  a.k.a. comment if you read this
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      slothO0 (6:36:27 PM): or we could see troy slothO0 (6:36:34 PM): lol slothO0 (6:36:37 PM): hahahahahaahhaa Echotallica311 (6:37:52 PM): hahahahhaa
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THIS ONE IS ABOUT: Alex 1. LIVING ARRANGEMENT?: me dad brother 2. WHAT BOOK ARE YOU READING RIGHT NOW?: manual for my stereo 3. WHAT'S ON YOUR MOUSE PAD?: dont have one (optical mouse) 4. FAVORITE GAMES?: counter-strike 5. FAVORITE MAGAZINE? : PC mag, car and driver 6. BABIES?: nein! 7. FAVORITE SOUND? : the sound that prince's symbol sounded like...i can only express it like "pblwop!" 8. WORST FEELING IN THE WORLD? : heartbreak or depression 9. BEST FEELING IN THE WORLD? : opposite of above 10. WHAT IS THE FIRST THING YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING? : i should probably get up now 11. HOW MANY RINGS BEFORE YOU ANSWER THE PHONE?: two, so i can see who it is 12. WHAT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IN LIFE? : love (paul mccartney quote anyone?) and money 13. FAVORITE FOODS? : italian stuff 14. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA : choc 15. DO YOU LIKE TO DRIVE FAST? : ho ho ho yes 16. DO YOU SLEEP WITH A STUFFED ANIMAL? : my pillow gets quite rowdy sometimes 17. STORMS? : relaxing 18. WHAT TYPE WAS YOUR FIRST CAR? : 1992 Buick Skylark (so the sexy) 19. IF YOU COULD MEET ONE PERSON DEAD OR ALIVE WHO WOULD IT BE? : karl marx 20. FAVORITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK? : something with alcohol 21. WHAT IS YOUR ZODIAC SIGN? : aquarius 22. DO YOU EAT THE STEMS OF BROCCOLI??: yeah 23. IF YOU COULD HAVE ONE JOB IN THE WORLD WHAT WOULD IT BE?: automotive journalist...test cars and write about them 24. IF YOU DYED YOUR HAIR, WHAT COLOR WOULD YOU PICK?: probably some kind of dark brown or maybe some kind of highlight thing, i dunno 25. HAVE YOU EVER BEEN IN LOVE? : yes 27. IS THE GLASS HALF EMPTY OR HALF FULL?: what glass, i see no fucking glass 28. FAVORITE MOVIES? : uuuuuuuuhhhh reservoir dogs, gone in 60 seconds, kill bill, dawn of the dead, natural born killers, romper stomper, fear and loathing in las vegas 29. DO YOU TYPE WITH YOUR FINGERS ON THE RIGHT KEYS?: i have my own system that works better 30. WHAT'S UNDER YOUR BED? : my dresser and a chair and a box 31. FAVORITE SPORT TO WATCH? : frisbee's pretty entertaining...that or hockey
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, im gonna write a to-list.  to chris- meeeeeep. to amy- you read this, apparently, and i dont want to fuckin fight anymore, just chill, it's over with to wes- you dont need a new girlfriend. just settle in and be single, it's fun. kinda. to franz ferdinand- i had the name first, but you guys kick ass. to dan- stop drinking. to travis- yeah, i have a blog. no big whoop. wanna fight about it? to alex- you're cool, dont worry about stuff anymore to andrea- you're also cool, we should hang out more often. to chief spetman- poopoo! to grant- crunk.  i feel like doing a survey or something
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I made a new blog, new name, new everything. Dude.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm. Well, not much is on my mind except working and spending my money right now, i dunno. I felt I should update.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ohhhhhhhhhhh, great night. again, me overreacting on the last post. too much to say about tonight. had lots of fun, blew lots of shit up, i have a ton of fireworks in my trunk now, and i almost blew up a corvette. yes. almost.  ask me if you want to know, even though nobody reads this.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i wish i could just make myself not like people, because then it never works and i end up just being depressed.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>