<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Haha...I'm not that happy actually..! HAhaa I PONTENG my skool today ..wait,it's just  GOTONG-ROYONG  day rite??at 2 P.M,I'll go to the public library to do my presentation..the title is SARAWAK.Kinda good.. you know what?Now I'm listening to N Sync-Gone..such a sad song....It reminds me about my primary skool friends!!We really had fun being together..especially after UPSR exams..I remember that we used to listen to radio in the class..and there's one day,we made an impromptu choir~!!could ya believe that??It started when our music teacher,Mrs Norni announce that every 6th graders must enter this competition..but, they sort our names by alphebetical order!!so we must tolerate with that itchy2 boys from other class which is impossible!!so..day after day,everyone started to put a cross at their names..so in this situation,we thought that the contest is off..BUT..when the day comes..Mrs Norni gathered us to sort which group will be the 1st one to perform.to make it worst,MY group became the 1st.so we've chosen an indonesian song [in 5 minutes only].It was fun and of cuz,HUMILIATING.OK that's all flashback things..bubbyeee.....~!unitil the next meeting!!  p.s:I'm listening to bring me to life-evanescence.. Good song..doesn't make me sleepy at all!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi... anyway,here's some of my missionsssss....fer now..  1.get straight A's although it's impossible cuz I'm totally lazzzzeehh... 2.get 85% above in all subjex 3.want the skin like liv tyler's 4.want the hair like scarlet ortize's 5.marrying gareth gates.perhaps raul gonzalez would be ok too.haha!! 6.being featured on the newspaper/magazines[for my marriage with gaz,i think]/or TV..someday!! 7.watch sum movies with muh friends!!  haha..I've been telling a bunch of my punk friendsss to visit this blog.huhuhhh...let's see wuts their commentsss..:>~  kay dats all i guess!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Heh..it's been a long..time since the last post..haha.I've been quiet busy..[Hey..I'm still a student right..?].. guess what..?last sunday..my family went to KT..SOOOO..my friend kude and I went biking to our primary skool....!haha..quiet far from my home but I'd suddenLY got the courage to do that-without my mom's permission..[don't you dare tell my mom.]haha.like you know my mom..it was fun.100% better than my trip last week.and i juz got some of my results..and for now,I got 6 A's and a B.there's another 2..quite OK.. I just watch 3 films..Kill Bill,Harry Potter..and Monalisa Smile..Kill Bill is so violent..!but I really2 love this one..~!Harry Potter is NOT soo good than I've thought.and Monalisa is so wundafooLL!!I really [truly-deeply-madly]hate Kirsten Dunst here~!!! the only SHIT here is that,one of my friends,[OK.not friend LAH]fadilahhhhhh~!!!I hate her so much taht I could tear her into bits~!!she's a LOUSY..gossiper.[HEY HOT NUs~!!]so you guys.MY ADVICE:don't trust her too much!haha..don't misunderstood me,I don't tell you not to befriend her,OK!! Yesterday,our P.E. instructor,Mr Chan,teach us how to play SOFBALL.-[I dunno the english word for this~!!!]you know what?We have to play this game everytime we have P.E!!!What a waste of time..and guess wut?Mr chan said that lefties are the best..my friend,d*la is a lefty ..I'm not.I tried to write using my left but it's no use,hahahah..
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey there..haha..I dunno wut to do here~!!!ok this IS school holiday.but my mom said; don't ever stop reading your skool boox,although its holiday.hullo>???BUT ..how to put photos in here??I'm still wondering..-_*..you know what..when it comes to holiday,I'll start to laze around and do nothing.cool,huh?FUCK THAT.I'm sorry for using UNCOURTEOUS word here~!!that's my habit,ok??when I met a bunch of my friends at tuition yesterday,they asked me; where have you been? haha.they reminds me about my NOT-SO- WONDERFUL-AT-ALL trip.hmm.so I told them that I went to frankfurt.[haha..they believe it~!!]but in their mind-WHAT ON EARTH FRANKFURT COULD BE??lah..that's fine as long as it has  BUNYI-BUNYI OMPOOTEH  la so they'll understand.got up at 8.45 a.m,you know,[Ok.this is just coincidences.]for 3 days since I got back from my trip,I've been woke up at 8.45 a.m in arow.believe it.hey..do you know this song..'I miss u' by blink 182..?and 'this luv' by maroon 5..?I really like them.ok if you had been to Khadijah's blog..ask her about mehhhh..she's my friend.really cute like a cat but she doesn't know how 2 make it's sound..ngeh ngeh ngeh..[don't easily get angry!~] that's not all..I make sugar drop cookies today..don't really work,though.ok..tomorrow my grams will be coming.that's all folks ferr naw~!!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok..firstly,I wanna thank myself for creating this blog..blablabla..]Actually,I dont really meant to create a blog,ITS JUST 4 FUN!!so,you guys out there..do visit my blog~!!!    you know what?I just got back from my trip at tioman island,which is damn..sux.MABUK LAUT,men!I conquered 3 spaces to get some sleep on that "TUNAS" ferry.[lousy name,huh?].this is my worst nightmare.eh? no.no.no.my worst is sharing my meal with a gigantic cockroach~!!waaaaa~!!!  as usual,I'll tell you a lil bit about myself.If you ask my friends about me,they will said,"oh~..that gal.hey,I remind ya.she is the kind of  MAKChIK  you'll find at market," and sometimes my friends would say "hey,that girl is so shy!"  yeah,I can be talkative but sometimes..I'm not.ok that's all for now..   P.S:do tell me if you think my blog's sux~!!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Haha..tonite I'm going to that stupid tuition again.I think I should quit the tuition cuz I'm not going to concentrate on anything cuz I will talk and talk with my friends.cant help it cuz we're not in the same skool-MISS THeM LAa.yesterday I went to the dojo at semambu.We met the Kishi Sensei from Japan.and guess wut.I got his signature~!!Not only his,I also got from other senseis-[but still dunno their names.~_  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hi.Fer your info,today I'll go to my granpa's house.yeah-and it means I'll meet my cousins Hannah..and my sec cousins-adibah and&nbsp;bahiyah.And I think I'll eat a lot of 'telur masin' that I love most.Aki[my granpa] always bring along 'telur masin' when he visits us or when we come to his house.it's delicious!!you should try some~![fer those who haven't].and I think I'm sticked to JC chasez's song-build my world.you should hear this one and the songs I've listed the other day~!I forgot to tell you this one.on Monday i think,two women came from KAO malaysia to give a talk to us-form 1 and form 2]about their brands-the one with laurier,biore,and all those women things.couldya believe that she taught us how to wear that 'THING'?it's hilarious and that woman is so funny.We can't help laughing at her talks.She promised us to give each one of us a free biore facial foam and YOU-KNOW-WHAT.and yesterday pn Latifah came and spread it all to each of us.BUT I hate it when the gals are so 'galak' when the boys want to see the parcel.lah.tapi don't be too over-acting with that.just pretend that nothing had happened.ni nak bising2-WOI LAKI TOKLEH TENGOK.the more we said that -the more misunderstanding they'll be.hey you know what.my new neighbor wants to renovate his house.everyday,the workers will come and make NOISY SOUNDS-like this-BZZZZT~!amboi.berdesing-desing telinge sayyer!but the neighbor had apologised to us,so that is POLITE.Buleh dimaafkan.HAHAHAHA..~!But I was curious.am I going to my tuition centre tonight-for I'm supposed to go to the kenduri.hmm.If I go to my tuition,I'm going to meet Marzuki who makes me furious.haahah.so I hink I'll go to the kenduri instead.   I really miss my frens..fOoxaH,b*loh,p*joh,BliaNa,intan,MyrA and more~!I really miss my primary skool life.Ok this song is dedicated to my frenZ~    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Clear my eyes, it's the morning after  Did I fall in love, or did I find disaster?  Take a second just to breathe  I pick my heart up off my sleeve, yeah   There she goes and I know she knows  By the way she eased out on her tippy toes  Skip the breakfast tea for two  We made no plans to rendeavous, yeah   Someone for everyone but no one for me (No one for me)  Constantly searching for the love I need to...   Basic Chorus:  Build my world around, around  I'll be the lonely one until I find someone  The one I build my world around, around  So, bring the arms of love until I find the one  The one I build my world...   Lazy days, I'm in a hazy phase  Of watching countless ways in which my life goes crazy  Foolishness to blame  Still, it pains me all the same, yeah   Empty faces with empty gazes  In a race of change, I'm losing faith in my pace  Trying to keep my feet before I fall   I'm on this endless road with nothing to see (Nothing to see)  Constantly searching for the love I need to...   Repeat chorus ['the one' replaces 'someone']   A cornerstone of honesty (All around)  A foundation of gravity and freedom (All around)  A clear and concrete understanding (All around)  A love that's best kept safe and sound   It's amazing how we fear the maybe  It's from ourselves we so often run  Abandon fear and consequence of heartbreak  Expose the truth and give yourself to love   We've all been set up to be disappointed  We have to crawl before we learn to fly  It's a blur that moves right into focus  Removes the doubt, aligns your heart and mind   Repeat chorus x 1.5 [overlap last verse/first verse]  (Just say it, just say it, just say it, just say it,  yeah yeah, oh, baby)  So bring the arms of love until I find the one  The one I build my world...  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      mmm..yesterday's aina's bday.kelmarin ahla's.last monday gareth ponyer bday.waa..nit that I forgot ur bday gareth.its just remembering it late.hahah..haha..my bf's 20..which means 7 yrs older than myself.you know what.I'm starting to h8 maznah.dunno la..it's becoz:  1) she alwiz got her art homework done by ms suzi.why her?why not anyone else. 2) I don't like her mimic when she wants to say sumthing she is excited about. 3)she thinks she is always at the center of attention.  there's many things,though.yesterday Aina brought her bday cake.she said she doesnt want to share her cake with boys.but lepas tuh sedap2 je die kasi.pastuh suroh org kasi kat cikgu klas kitorg plak.AINA supposed to make any decisions on that,not her.well-she wants to be a prefect.today I told her I don't really want to be a prefect.she said-laughing,'bagitau lah cikgu yang awk tanak jd prefect tapi kawan2 awk ade yg nak jadi,'[think she'll be the candidate If I quit.]  lawaxx btol aina..today.you know, Aina had been sucha good gal today..~!!there's a guy 'riding on' a wheelchair at 3A.when we're on the way to science lab,cg Azhar n cg halele.cg Azhar asked that guy's friend to get sumthing in the teacher's room.so she asked aina to push the wheelchair for that guy[we're going to the same destination.].haha...~! I juz walked behind her so that I could laugh-and-laugh till we got to the science lab.I HOPED he does'nt hear me at the back.actually I'm laughing at aina for being sucha good gal.-SINCE WHEN SHE LOVES TO DO THIS kerja amal??but the ultimate part that I laughed most-maser nak lalu longkang.tak habis2 ketawa aku maser tuh.ye lah.sampai nak kene angkat wheelchair tuh[dengan die2 skali.]thank god some of his friends came and helped him.he said-'kene bace bismillah bebanyak neh.'haha..gi toku kai JAPAN [karate]will be coming soon~!!so i'll meet those japanese~!!!!yeah..I can't wait for that!!  for students who got 6A's and above,will get the 'wajadiri bestari'award.farah,afiqa,alia,atiyah and me will get that award for our achievements for MId-yr exams.OK,OK-I'm quite happy for that~!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hullo..wazzup??guess wut.huda is here just now,and we make some prank calls~!!umi [but kantoi],ashilah,mizal,and asraf.haha..so funny laa..I was like this to ashilah;hullo.this is your destiny.you must answer this phone.or you will not stop laughing after 5 minutes.hullo.accept your destiny.and it goes like this with asraf-[fyi,he's an 8 yrs ol boy~!!]my friend's said;hey you this is cikgu zaiton.' and many other cheeky things we said.and when we make a call to mizal he kept saying 'hatok ngko'.is he a really shit thing?kohkohkohkohkoh..could ya believe that mizal likes a gurl name Mona,a girl which shares the same name with his father's MURDERER.pity him.mizal's totally sux,but his father-everyone in malaysia knows about Dato' mazlan..who had been murdered by moma fendi somewhere in 1993..haha but I kinda had a crush on him lastyear.hahahaha..but I do hate him anyway~!!serious!!anyway I wanna tell you sumthing about my 'choral speaking' practice...kinda good but i really want 2 do sumthing so that I could make it on the first row!!!my feet hurts a lot when I stand on that lousy old bench..huhu..I'm really scared if Madame wbeebee ask me to take any solo lines..~![what if I made a mistake??huh??]everyone in my skool started to talk about AKADEMI FANTASIA 2.wut so interesting bout dat??I better sleep 24 hours than watching modern teenage muslims living in the same house..wut the hell muslim is that??hadith and koran says that when there are 'maksiat berleluasa',that means the end of the day will come.I dunno.    I dream a lot.I always think about my future home.new zealand countryside.I'll get kittens,goats,cows,and horses.a ferrari 360 spider in front of my porch.cool clothes.and many other good things...~!!!may it comes true.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Heyya..today ade karate-do..bestnyer...adilah ader..asmaa..hanisah ade..kinda good but my right feet's  hurt soo much..OK..Bubbye..ok.it's kinda weird but my sista's calling me and force me to turn off this computer..or else..you know wut will happen~!!!ok...tons of luvs from ol' aliah~!!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       When I am down and, oh my soul, so weary;  When troubles come and my heart burdened be;  Then, I am still and wait here in the silence,  Until you come and sit awhile with me.  You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.  You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.  There is no life - no life without its hunger;  Each restless heart beats so imperfectly;  But when you come and I am filled with wonder,  Sometimes, I think I glimpse eternity.  You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be.  You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;  You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;  I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;  You raise me up: To more than I can be. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      name_aliah azmi aka justin-recent-luver age_13 only maa skool_samurai skool of jujutsu,kukishin-ryu..SMART fave colours_blue,black,white,soft green,fizzy green fave singazz_read my file! fave clothewear_diesel,radio active,anything that's stylish siblings_sarah,sophie,abraham,and luke best friends_foozah,blah,hooda,b*yna,pJ,mairah things I love_menyombangkan sore dlm klas, tido, main game FF, sanosuke sagara, CDs, surat ape2                 kecwali surat buang skola,nerdies,smart people.kewl figurines,anime,cats,dogs,horses,goats,dinos,anything                that's adorable,ferrari 360 spider,megi,Tv,cool gadgets,cool hairstyle.most of                all~chocolate..    things I hate_back-stabbing friends,mat motor,stewwpid guys,alcohol,cigaratte,smoker,prostitutes,homosex,small space,petai.most of all..lipas aka cockroach. ambition_doctor   dats all!~!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm listening to this song again~!!  today is kinda good day to me..nah,I felt very happy..cuz tonite my sista's here..!yeah..I can't wait fer my karate lesson tomorrow..stewwwpid ZOELHILMI!!!![sorry if you're out there!!~_ dah lah mase skool prim dulu kan,die nak angkat bangku batu ngan alvin tetiber tercabot bangku tuh dari kaki dier .kakakakakak...~!!but we're kinda good friends in prim skool TS.we used to be gossipping about  people we hate..till now I don't talk to skin.I'm feeling horrible too about it..but I'm not the one who MAKE SOMEONE TRUST YOU AND BRING YOU DOWN at last.hey,why can't we put a song in this blog??100% satisfying,rite??I wonder what could be happened to my friendz??pJ I think she's studying in SMKTel,nearby her houze.b*lah-SABS..i think she thinks that I was being snobbish cuz I don't call her fer along time..not that I'm snobbish,I'm kinda busy,and everytime I call her daddda's phone,she's not with him.FAIR AND SQUARE,rite??bliana,she's kinda workin' with the rtm radio,being the radio-drama actress..cool huh.foozah is so luckeeee~!!!!she's at MRSM mersing..wuhh MRSMers  senang dpt scholarship,so they could go to oversea easily..for 3 weeks,we form 1 students are workin' on our KH project..I really hate to gergaji kayu2 burok neh....anyway I'm in luv wit justin..kakakakakah..I hate to wear apron when the KH periods.nampak leher..gellieeee...~!! I think 90% of students[and also teachers.]of SMART hate our nu principal -datin hjh maizidah.wuts wrong wit her??she's kinda OK...yeah..we must'nt say anything cuz we don't know what she's up to!! but I kinda hate her,too cuz she makes people chopped down trees at SMART,so  semwe org maken kpanasan lah ..kcian..and then she likes to check our notes.[who cares??] ye lah ,we're not supposed to make notes on math,but our math teacher tell us to make notes from the beginning till now.and that's lot of works!!even mrs Wbeebee don't like her. siap ngompat2 lagi tuh ..but sometime I pity her too when I see her OLD face full of wrinkles..HAHAH..she's soo old 52,I think.hey..I supposed to go to my choral speaking practice but I feel like quitting la.. malu stepek jer ngan SABS nanti .SABS is soo rich.They make a charity dinner every yr.last yr they invited 'teh tarik crew' to entertain people there.this yr they're inviting OAG.hmm..my brother used to be a SABSer,but nw he's in MRSM KT.he's been featured on TV three times, I think.but in paper daa banyak laa gak..my sistas poon dah masok TV and paper..tak lame lagi aku plak kot.heheheh..[BANGGE la jugak] both my sisters are SMARTers.my sister sarah who's studying at russia got 10A's and 2 B's for SPM.my sister sofi is now studying at matriculation.she got 11A's and2B's fer SPM[but still doesn't get any offers.hahahah..]. OK..sakit tangan daa.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Kept rollin this song!!!can't help it~!!!!  this is my top 30 fave songs[not in order..]  1:let's get it started-black eyed pease 2:tearin' up my heart-*nsync 3:spirits in the sky-gareth gates 4:gone spanish version-nsync 5:gone-*nsync 6:when it comes-tyler hilton 7:anyone of us-gareth gates 8-hey mama-black eyed pease 9-wheres the luv-black eyed pease 10-its gonna be me-nsync 11-till I get over u-michelle branch 12-here 4 one-blazin' squad 13-flying without wings-westlife 14-the reason-hoobastank 15-I miss u-blink 182 16-cry me a river-justin timberlake 17-you raise me up-josh groban 18-I'm just a kid-simple Plan 19-addicted-simple Plan 20-stuck-stacie orrico 21-this love-maroon 5 22-here without u-3 doors down 23-the anthem-good charlotte 24-girls and boys-good charlotte 25-the trouble with love-Kelly clarkson 26-you and I both-jason mraz 27-cry-alex parks 28-everything-alanis morissette 29-my band-d12 eminem 30-betterman-robbie williams  there's more..but I cant finish it!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      you know wut??I kept rolling on 'tearin' up my heart' and 'gone' by n'sync today.very sad songs....but 'gone' in spanish is so funny..hahahah..but better than the songs in telenovelas..justin's voice is like the one who sings in 'chuando seas mia'.kahkahkah..terhina justin aku..!!ok that's all I wunna say..!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      actually not so boring.even if my parents and my brother's here makes me feel more..boring...my friend's here..but I still dunno wut to do.this morning,I watched 'mean girls'...bwahahahahah..it's so ..funny..hvya watch it??watch your back!!in that movie,rachel McAdams'es eyebrows looks really weird and she's not as pretty as her old one is 'the Hot chick',rite??Lindsay looks pretty and sumtimes annoying[believe me.heroins MUZ be annoying in every movies I have watched]I always examine lindsay's figure and I wonder what's SOO pretty about her[prettier than hilary]..her face is childish like her old one in 'parent traps' except for her freckles all over her body.and that aaron samuel,is he hot??i need your opinion.i kinda hate him..~! ingat die hensem sgt ka ??but,the best part is when the plastics and cady[lindsay] make their performance at the WINTER TALENT SHOWS..hahahahahah..it really loox like that 'tarian bogel' except for they are wearing SEXY santa's costumes.and I cant help laughing like mad when one of the plastics spoiled their performance.and i realized that I really like intelligent boys..!!and also thick eyebrows one.I wonder wut am I gonna do next..and I can wait to watch 'the confession of the teenage drama queen' and 'nu york minutes'.thanx a lot to fie-qa and izatul@idabol [ name timangan aku kasi,best tak .]cuz give me this CDs..JUST BORROWING  lahh..diorang bukannye bayk sgt ,..kahkahkah..kay bubbyyee~!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Konnichiwa!!How are you there??I'm fine as always..you know wut??yesterday I got into a fight with my friend,skin.wuteva.I kinda cry at first and start saying fuck u to everyone.hahaha..that nik asked me'are you still mad at us??' so I said  'TOKSAH TERGEDIK2 LAH NIk.  'Merajoklah nik ..kakakak..today i went to my friends'es house..aresha's,fieqa's.aresha's room is sooo nice with pink wallpaper and i think 90% stuff in her room are pink..!and there's a black cat in there too.I dunno how does fie~qa's room looks like cuz she doesn't want me to see her messy bedroom..haha..stupid fie~qa spilled MAGGI soup all over my shirt!!pastuh die bwat kitorang lari psal ade org MPK lalu situh.. ponat..ponat ...and dya believe dat fie~qa has been fart about 15 times today!!I tried hard to find a clean spot to sit..an hour before I work on this blog,I played celeb games..it's kinda cool.there are reflexing game,concentrating game,and many more..haha..dya realized that I love to write 'haha'?I REALLY LOVED TO SAY THAT!!thanx fer noticing it..yeah-yeah..tomorrow,kuda and I will go biking again..hey another two days to go!!and my sister's here!!!I kept telling my friends about this especially fatin amira,cuz I used to think that her face is just likemy sister's!!even she is excited as i am to see her!!HOw I miss her soooo much!!haha..[there goes again..!!]..last day I asked KD how to put photo in blogs.she said that we need a kind of software that we need to install in the computer so that we could put our photo on the internet..waaah leceh nye..OK bye..I need to work on muh nu community!!!!!!MUAHHssZZZZ~!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      LYRIXX from me..by justin..  "Cry Me A River" You were my sun You were my earth But you didn't know all the ways I loved you, no So you took a chance And made other plans But I bet you didn't think that they would come crashing down, no You don't have to say, what you did, I already know, I found out from him Now there's just no chance, for you and me, there'll never be And don't it make you sad about it You told me you loved me Why did you leave me, all alone Now you tell me you need me When you call me, on the phone Girl I refuse, you must have me confused With some other guy Your bridges were burned, and now it's your turn To cry, cry me a river Cry me a river-er Cry me a river Cry me a river-er, yea yea I know that they say That somethings are better left unsaid It wasn't like you only talked to him and you know it (Don't act like you don't know it) All of these things people told me Keep messing with my head (Messing with my head) You should've picked honesty Then you may not have blown it (Yea..) You don't have to say, what you did, (Don't have to say, what you did) I already know, I found out from him (I already know, uh) Now there's just no chance, for you and me, there'll never be (No chance, you and me) And don't it make you sad about it You told me you loved me Why did you leave me, all alone (All alone) Now you tell me you need me When you call me, on the phone (When you call me on the phone) Girl I refuse, you must have me confused With some other guy (I'm not like them baby) Your bridges were burned, and now it's your turn (It's your turn) To cry, cry me a river (Go on and just) Cry me a river-er (Go on and just) Cry me a river (Baby go on and just) Cry me a river-er, yea yea Oh (Oh) The damage is done So I guess I be leaving Oh (Oh) The damage is done So I guess I be leaving Oh (Oh) The damage is done So I guess I be leaving Oh (Oh) The damage is done So I guess I be... leaving You don't have to say, what you did, (Don't have to say, what you did) I already know, I found out from him (I already know, uh) Now there's just no chance, for you and me, there'll never be (No chance, you and me) And don't it make you sad about it Cry me a river (Go on and just) Cry me a river-er (Baby go on and just) Cry me a river (You can go on and just) Cry me a river-er, yea yea Cry me a river (Baby go on and just) Cry me a river-er (Go on and just) Cry me a river (Cause I've already cried) Cry me a river-er, yea yea (Ain't gonna cry no more, yea-yea) Cry me a river Cry me a river, oh Cry me a river, oh Cry me a river, oh Cry me a river, oh (Cry me, cry me) Cry me a river, oh (Cry me, cry me) Cry me a river, oh (Cry me, cry me) Cry me a river, oh (Cry me, cry me) Cry me a river, oh (Cry me, cry me) Cry me a river, oh (Cry me, cry me) Cry me a river (Cry me, cry me)   p.s>Best tak?? 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi..u know wut??I really have bad mood today..I really get mad at my friend,farah..actually she had done many annoying things before..but this time I can't tolerate it anymore.OK..she IS soooo pretty like mad..but she really likes to say anything she think.she's just so honesssstt...but that's not the problem..it was like this;Nik said.YOU LIKE him!!! so Farah said;hey ALIAH LIKES HIM!!..I was like..'hey you!shut your hell up!!'I think  BERGEMA2 suara saya .It lasts long until I get back at my seat...yesterday I went for my karate-do lessons..I'm a greenbelter.we learned some of the KUMITE..another 3 days to go...and my sister will be here!!she's studying in russia to be a doctor..most of my family members are doctors..!soon I'll be doctor too..but I want sumthing dat have to do alot of science..suchas pathologist or wut soeva..!you guys out there..do tell me about ur ambitions~!!I wanna know more about you!!   Guess this animal..  It is a reptile. It's green slimy thing. It can walk on the water surface.  guess you don't have any idea who am I!!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>