<Blog>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yahaaaa footy starts today alrighty then:) england are going to win you know it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Picked the flowers for my grandads funeral today, its a heart shape made of white flowers and roses its really nice but it was a bit upsetting talking about how he died.  My mum and dad were at his side when he went and my dad (its his dad) broke down from what my mum said, thing is i have never seen my dad upset ever, so although i knew he would getting confirmation made me realise what i would be like if it was him and not my grandad that died, does that sound awfull it isn't meant to i loved my grandad but i dont know what i will do when my dad goes he is the one who is there when i make a complete mess of everything and makes it all right again.  It should be a good send off everyone is going to be there people i haven't seen for years like my cousins from jersy (although i'm not sure if they all live there now) and my dads uncle john, also people i have never met before are going to be there as well.  Hope its a nice day it would be nice if we could bury him in the sunshine.  oh well grandad if you can see this you were great we all love you and miss you already   phillip
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well the laptop is starting to bugger up, I use firefox and in the last few days I have been getting an error message when I open it up it tells me that I should not use the java plug-in for IE and should go and get one for mozilla? Why do these things happen eh? I have not done anything out of the ordinary in the last few days just surfed and stuff I don't download dodgy stuff look at weird sites or anything and I never open emails from people I don't know, so why does your pc bugger up on you its like its saying 'Right oh I've worked fine for a while its time I pissed him off a bit what can I do, oh I know I'll stick up this error message every time he opens firefox that's do his head in' Well let me tell you it bloody worked its getting right on my tits.  Thing is as I have already said I get broadband in 60 days time and I thought what better way to start with a brand new fast connection than to format and reinstall windows start afresh and there shouldn't be any problems eh,Mind you with this NTFS partition I have to delete that and repartition the bloody thing apparently (if anybody knows different feel free to tell me how to do it).You must know what a pain in the bum formatting is it takes a while to do then you reinstall windows then all the bloody drivers (and there is millions if the buggers) then you need all the stuff that supposedly makes your pc secure antivirus firewall and the like, then when you have done that you need all the updates from MS and dood there are like gazillions of them because old Billy boy likes to make Swiss cheese operating systems with more holes than a string vest, its said that if you leave a fresh installation of xp (sp1) with no patches or firewall  connected to the internet it takes 20mins to get infected with either a virus or Trojan bloody hell just what you need eh you would be formatting every day.....   So what do I do format now and again in a couple of months or wait and put up with it? dunno think it's see how it goes for a while you never know it may fix itself after all it buggered itself up didn't it :)   What about this gmail thing eh what's all that about people are selling invites for unreal prices, I have seen one bloke selling his account for $100 I mean come on its not worth that is it. It is one hell of a marketing strategy they have got people chomping at the bit to sign up (me included but I wont pay for an account) and beg bloody hell people are promising the earth in the hope of getting an invite lol I bet it goes out of beta soon then we can all have one and lets face it most of the top level names will have gone now wont they :).
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The swelling has finally gone :) my head looks normal now (or as normal as it did anyway lol.  football starts sunday cant wait it should be great, comne on england you know you want it.................  just seen some topless mud wrestling on Big brother god nadia is one ugly beast mind she was a bloke and blokes aren't renowned for turning into good looking chicks hahaaahaa  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm fed up today i still look like the elephant man and its getting on my wick now!  it seems to be going down a bit though so hopefully tomorrow :)   not done a lot played on monkey island on the ps2 and got further than the wife has so i'm chuffed with that lol.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok here is a couple of pictures of my house......             
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well i woke up today and could hardley see, my eyes had swelled up too :( took anthir tablet and they seem to have gone down a bit but now all the skin on my nose is flakey, if i had known this would happen i would have worn a hat or something but you dont expect this rubbish with a little sunburn do you?  stayed at home from work today due to it its really bad but hopefully wont last all that long.  I'm at home and bored out of my head been rooting about on the net to see if i could find any Fla movies i could mess about with (what you make swf with) found loads but non i want to play with.  I just noticed that people are selling invites to gmail (the new google email service) its shocking people will buy anything, why not just wait till is released and get an account then? mind you i suppose the name you want may have gone by then..  i get broadband soon can't wait this 56k is diabolicle its so slow you can't download anything thats even remotely big and expect to have it anytime soon.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My grandad died today, he was very ill in hospital and it wasn't completely unexpected but it is still upsetting. He was great and i will miss him but it was for the best because his quality of life was down to negative numbers :(.  Also i remember i told you about my head getting burnt well it has swelled up now on my forhead, i look like worf from startrek now. I came home early from work and got in at the doctors half an hour later (a minor miracle in itself), the doctor had a look and gave me these funny anti histamines (spl) they are not like the ones i have for hayfever they are a bit powerful he said. so hopefull i wont look hideous after tomorrow.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here we are then, my own personal blog. Well lets hope i keep it up this time i have had a few in my time but could never be arsed to keep them going for one reason or another, but hopefully this time will be different.   Euro 2004 starts in a few days with england playing on the 13 june, not bad is it and as the kick off times of every match are after i get home from work i will be able to watch them all :) great.  I am sitting on my laptop writing this and there are prbably a few spelling mistakes, forgive me for those i'm not pefect by any means (but i try). Its monday and i dont work mondays i work tuesday to saturday but i leave at 12 on saturdays so it feels like an extra day off :).   I work in a supermarket stacking shelves, its not exactly brain surgery but it is a steady job and i get paid a decent amount as well as all the government incentives i get we dont do to bad as a family, Did i tell you i was married? well i am my wife and i have been married for 9 years now we have 2 children a boy and a girl 6 and 8 respectivly.  My wife is great although she can't cook chips to save her life lol but i dont tell her she would beat me up :). The kids are ace too my daughter enjoys gymnastics and does it for 3 hours on a saturday morning according to her mum (the wife) she is doing really well but i dont get to see her due to being at work.  my son does judo but he likes to mess about and as he is only 6 i can't really see him being much good yet although he can chuck all his pals about already lol :)  I went and did a car boot sale yesterday with some of the old junk from the attic, it went well i sold a lot of stuff and made 70 quid from stuff we would normally have thrown away, although i have 3rd degree burns on my forhead now cos it was bloomin hot.   I enjoy using my computer and am looking forward to getting a fast connection soon i'm on 56k at the mo but in a couple of months i get 1mbs yea cool or what:).  i will try to root a picture out of myself and post it up i'm not hideous and i scrub up pretty well if i say so myself however although my days of rampant girl hunting are well and truly over you never stop thinking of yourself as a love god do you:)  oh well thats all for now phill.........
     
    
</post>


</Blog>