<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      [This message brought to you by reading some of the posts in the Corporate Wasteland forum over at  urlLink The Boots 'N All website .  I bitch a lot about work. I hate my job. I've basically hated it not long after I started working here, but for this area, and for someone like me (no college degree yet/still in school), it pays too well for me to quit. They also let me have a flexible schedule which I need for school, and I do get free DSL because I work here. I am just so tired of having a job that sucks all of my energy, makes me feel bad about myself, doesn't let me really use my skills or talents much, etc. Now that I have my apartment, I need to be able to pay for it somehow, you know? So I can't just up and quit before I find something else. I wish I could quit, but I don't know where I could go. I would need to find something where the pay is comporable and they would give me a flexible schedule for during the school year. I just feel sometimes like I can't get away from this place and it drives me nuts. :(   It's kind of funny, because now that I am doing this other gig in the deli at $GroceryChain (hehe, when I am at $LocalISP I called it "The Other Place"), I'm remembering what it was like to have a non-office job. Even though I am not used to being on my feet all day like that, I like the feeling of being able to just do a good, solid, honest day's work, get paid, and go home at the end of the day and be me again, without feeling like I have all of this mental/psychic baggage to deal with. With my current job at $LocalISP, I think I've gotten into the trap of letting my job define too much of who I am. I would have to look back over my old journals, but I think it would pretty much show a pattern of me being depressed and miserable ever since I started working here. I am not really the corporate type.   I wish I could find some sort of production-type job where I make decent money and just show up, do my work, and go home. I am actually surprised at how much I am liking working at $GroceryChain. Everyone is extremely friendly, I get to move around a lot, you stay busy, and the customers are pretty nice. I dunno...I just feel so, so, SO emotionally exhausted after the past 2 years of my life that I really think I am just plain tapped out. I need to find a job that doesn't make me miserable for 8 hours, pays enough for me to get by, and maybe get the hell out of here. Now that I have SNS, and I have my financial aid covered for school, maybe I can just work at SNS during the semester. I would so love to quit working here at $LocalISP.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so that isn't a very original title, but oh well. I am in weird emotional-limbo-ville today for some reason - today is one of those kind-of-blue days. :( It's probably just because I didn't get much sleep and am not overly enthused with my M/W/F job or my personal life at the moment. :P  I am working on laptops yet again and waiting for one to finish updating so I can go home. I have to boogie home because my dad is coming over for dinner, and then we are going to the Pirates game. (We have season tickets for the Fri/Sat night home games.) I am not the biggest baseball fan in the world, but it is entertaining enough, and I get to spend time with my dad.  Well, that last Windows Update is done, I am going home! Maybe I'll write later. Bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i actually did get a second job! so i can pay my rent and all....after i get a farking paycheck! which won't be until the end of the month, most likely. so i hope i can pay *next* month's rent on time. and, you  know, bills and stuff. and maybe someday in the misty future, i can afford new clothes, a haircut, the expensive salon shampoo i like, some new shoes, etc. little things like that.   ok, going to bed now! even though i haven't gone to bed yet, and tomorrow has turned into today already! that's what you get when you stay up past midnight, you mess with the whole space-time continuum in your head.  going now...going, going....
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I am back, wayyyy after I should have been in bed! At least I am off tomorrow, so I can sleep in a little, but only a little because I have all kinds of running-around to do tomorrow. Oh well. I'll just think of this as "mental health time".  -----------  So, I am rather belatedly discovering Starving College Student Life. Or, more precisely, Disgruntled Low-Budget Life. I have made a lot of stupid financial decisions in my life, directly or indirectly, and it's all led up to Right Now. All of those decisions are affecting me, here, at 25, when I feel like I should be taking over the world, or something. Or at least being able to exert a little more control over my world.   It doesn't help that since I started working at $RegionalInternetServiceProvider, I've made way more money than most of my friends, and finally started to be able to afford stuff that I actually like and want. I've developed horribly expensive, completely yuppietastic tastes for things like organic food and products, shopping at Whole Foods, going out for lunch or dinner whenever I want, buying things like books/CDs/DVDs whenever I want, etc. This past month, for reasons I will explain later (yeah, yeah, I know - ooo, mysterious! - but really, just too much to write about at the moment. It requires a whole post of its own) I have finally just gotten my first real apartment on my own. (No more psycho roommate, thank-fucking-God!) I had to borrow $BigMoney from my dad to get this place, and didn't even have a full-time job, thanks to my new position at work that doesn't actually give me enough to do on a full-time basis. I moved in here at the beginning of May, and thought for sure that I would have a second job by the end of the month. I am now at a 4-year university working to finish my bachelors degree, so I only need a second job over the summer to help cover my expenses.  Well, it is just hard getting used to a very tight budget again, after having a workable budget for so long. I miss having that financial freedom to do what I want, but if I am really honest with myself, a lot of that came from being in a cycle of constant credit card debt - I'd pay them off and use them up again. So now, I really have to scrimp and save where I can, down to every last penny, so I can pay my rent on time (it's an extra $50 if it's late - and it's late for this month). So I can pay my  bills. So I can eat.  What sort of brought this problem into focus today was something stupid I did - I went to the grocery store right after work, hungry, but with a list in hand, and $35 available on my almost-maxed-out credit card. I needed a few more things to help me stretch until I got paid again, preferably until after I get my first paycheck from my second job. I am completely broke now until I get paid again, not counting small change that I have left. My gas has to last two weeks. I won't be able to afford to get any more canned food for my kittens. I won't be able to run to the store to get anything that I might need in the next two weeks. Granted, at least I have enough now to live on for two or three weeks, even if it is mostly starchy or prepared boxed stuff, but at least I have some fruit and frozen veggies and things now to give me a little more balanced nutrition in the meantime. So at least the extra stuff I did get will help me stretch out about another week's worth of meals, which is good, but I fucked myself over in the meantime! I could have used that remaining credit to get the few things I actually really needed, and then had a little left over for canned food for the furry babes, or gas, or whatever.   I already am $20 short for the amount of rent I owe. I am going to try to explain the situation to the rental manager. When I applied the place, I put down a pet deposit and pet rent for May for my two cats. PsychoExRoommate and I had gotten two cats together, a mother cat and a kitten, and I loved them to pieces, especially the kitten. I am convinced that they were more attached to me than they were to her, but who knows...Anyway, the night before I moved out, she took them around 11:30 or midnight, without even telling me, and left. She took them somewhere and hid them until I moved out, and then probably that night that I moved out she changed the locks so I couldn't come back and get them when she was away. Well, I hope she fucking loses her damn house, for doing that to me. I loved those cats, and leaving them was very painful for me. However, I really had no way of getting them back, so I just had to move on. I'm not very proud of it, but sometimes there are just situations you just can't win.  So anyway, I had paid my pet rent for May, but didn't have cats yet. Well, it turned out that the girl in one of the downstairs apartments had two kittens that she needed to find homes for - her cat had gotten out and gotten pregnant, and had 4 kittens. She'd found a home for one and was keeping one, but the two girls needed a home, so I said I would take them. I am too much of an animal-person to let two innocent little creatures go out into the wide world when I know that I could give them an excellent home and love and provide for them. So, maybe it is one of those mysterious ways of God that everything happened at just the right time (even though it was extremely stressful and painful and just about made me have a nervous breakdown!). The kitties and I are getting along great, I've gotten a second job, and as I keep reminding myself - whenever I have really been in need in my life, God (whoever He/She/They may be - One God, Many Faces, you know!) has always seen fit to provide me with just enough whenever I've needed it, and for that I am blessed and grateful. So, I just need to find a way to control my spending more and get a grip on the areas of my budget that I'm overspending in.  Weeell....it is now almost 1:30 am, and I have a very sleepy kitty on my lap, so I should get to bed. Goodnight! Sorry for the rambling.... Will be possibly more coherent in future posts! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, i have a blog!!! *snoopy dance* I used to have one on diaryland.com (ithilien.diaryland.com - shows you how old that is! No one had grabbed that name yet.)  Anyway, I never updated it, and apparently it is somehow only semi-working in their system. So I decided to go with Blogspot/Blogger.  Well, I am sitting here at work dreadfully bored and under-employed and desperately would rather be at home than sitting here. I am working on updating laptops for my friend X, our lan admin, so at least I have something to do. I used to do tech support for (to borrow from alt.sysadmin.recovery and alt.tech-support.recovery) $RegionalInternetServiceProvider. I did that for 5 years.  Now I am sort of the office bitch. Long story - will explain later. Unfortunately, part of being the office bitch includes being the bitch of one of the quasi-admins, who, while being a really nice guy outside of work, is a complete nazi about our "abuse" database. I am the poor sap that has to call customers and tell them they have viruses like Sasser, or are spamming (regular or virus-laden), have open proxies, are port-scanning, you name it. I HATE IT and I hate how nazi he gets. Probably because he is the sales department's bitch and having me to boss around soothes his male ego. GAH, I say, GAH!  I gotta go....BBL. :(
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't want to work tomorrow! $ISP job is so mentally draining right now, and it still irritates me every time I go in there that The Bitch still works there too. I wish she'd fucking get a new job already so I would never have to see her sorry ass again. I would feel much better in life knowing that I never had to see her again. Besides, I was at that job first. Grr.  Well, today was kind of so-so at $TheDeli. Jason wasn't there so that was good, but we are short-staffed this week bc two people are on vacation, so that kind of sucked. Then, sometime in the morning around 10/10:30-ish, that duet version of "Unforgettable" came on that Natalie Cole recorded of her and her father singing together, and that made me start thinking about my mom. I made an excuse that I had to go to the bathroom and went back there and started crying in the stall. :( Once I start thinking about my mom like that and start crying it's so hard to stop. So, after that I got a bit of a headache, and I didn't get to go to lunch until 1:00, and I had eaten at 8:00 in the morning, so that is 5 hours going without food or even much of a drink. If I don't eat right around 4 hours later I get really spaced-out, dizzy-ish, sickly-feeling, and headache-y. So, anyway, by the time I was done with my lunch I started to get a vicious headache. One of the back-room ladies had some Motrin so I took two of those, but they took a while to kick in. Thankfully they did or I would have ended up with a migraine, it was starting to feel that way.   The rest of the day dragged but I got to leave 15 mins early so that was nice. We also got our paychecks today, and they can cash it in the store, so that was even better! So I got some groceries and went home. Dad ended up not wanting to fight traffic to go to Kennywood, so I invited him over for dinner and it was nice. I gave him some leftovers to take home so he was happy. :) The rest of the night I just relaxed...I got my latest Netflix batch, so I watched The Rookie tonight. (I'm on this baseball kick now that I have gone to all of these games with Dad.) Damn, Dennis Quaid was pretty buff in that movie. ;) It got off to a bit of a slow start, and of course it has that special brand of Disney-made-this-so-you-WILL-feel-warm-and-fuzzy-after-watching-it vibe, but I really liked it anyway. Sometimes you just want to kick back and watch a nice, simple "feel-good" movie that doesn't have an agenda. And besides, it was about baseball. :] So now I have Spiderman and Mona Lisa Smile left to watch.    Well, I don't have much to write about. Some more of my eBay things sold so I am happy - that will give me gas money for this week. It is so nice that I get paid weekly from $TheDeli. I like having extra money when I need it. I just need to curb my spending on convenience foods and pop. I always get a pop and a candy bar on my breaks and that adds up after a while. I also haven't been packing my lunch for the days when I work an 8-hour shift at $TheDeli, so that wastes money too. I have been too tired to pack a lunch at night, and didn't have money to get groceries.  Oh well. It's 12:15 am, I need to get to bed. Goodnight! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, I worked with Cindee tonight, she is one of the cooler people that I work with at $Deli. Well, *according to her*, Jason is a big fucking sorry-ass druggie. :P (Haha, I originally wrote that as "a bug fucking sorry-ass druggie". Well, maybe he is that too! Great typo, LOL)   Like, he used to snort heroin. :-o I don't know if he does now, but that would explain his mood swings somewhat! Christ. She also said that he has a girlfriend, so...so much for that. :P Oh well. He irritates me too much anyway. I think I found him attractive because he reminds me vaguely of someone I used to like. I think I am basically looking for someone who is sorta similar looks-wise but, you know, cuter, smarter, nicer, and not a loser. Oh yeah, and on Monday when Jason was being an ass and I had such a bad day, I heard him say to Linda the mgr. that he was a "nihilist". Oh, hand+staple+forehead! I have a feeling that he sees himself as some brilliant tortured James Dean type and "no one understands him" and bla bla bla. I mean, I feel like that myself sometimes, but I know not to take myself seriously all.of.the.time!   Anyway, his saying that made me think...what would I call myself? Hedonist? Postmodernist? Secular Humanist? Populist? Existentialist?  I don't know...I am intrigued by philosophy, but I haven't delved into it yet at any great length because it annoys me a little. I am irritated by things that aren't very useful to my daily experience in life. That is why I am no longer very religious. Maybe that means I am intellectually lazy, I don't know. I *do* want to take a philosophy class eventually and read some of the classics. I want to start out with reading Plato, Aristotle, Socrates, etc., and move on through the historical philosophic periods into modern philosophical thought. It's just one of those things that keeps moving on down the line in order of importance in my life. Well, maybe when I win the lottery and can retire at 30 I can live a life of leisure and devote my time to the intellectual pursuits. In the meantime, I have more things to take up my time with than reading philosophy to impress some drugged-up twit I work with at my joe-job! If anything I will do it for myself. I have always wanted to start a classics collection for my little library...I've been wanting to read the Mabinogion for a while, since I saw Troy I've been wanting to re-read The Odyssey and The Illiad, and since I saw Quills I want to read some of the works from the Marquis de Sade! Although it will probably piss me off and make me want to throw the book against the wall. :P  Argh... I need to go to bed, I am so fucking tired. I wish I didn't have to work tomorrow. My dad wants me to go to Kennywood with him for KDKA Day, but after I get off work I will probably just want to crash. Sorry Dad. :(   I hope Jason isn't an ass tomorrow or I will smite him.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It would be so nice to win the lottery and invest my winnings so that I could live off the proceeds for the rest of my life. Is it time to retire yet?!?  I got my first job in high school at age 16. I am 25 now, so I have been working for almost 10 years now. And I have, oh, 40 more years to go! That is if I am lucky enough to be able to afford to retire at 65. I am already panicking thinking about things like: *paying for a new car and car insurance entirely on my own *saving money for a down payment on a house *saving money for an emergency fund *saving money for a retirement fund *paying off my personal loan debt and credit card debt *paying back my student loans *paying for grad school *paying for funeral expenses. Since my mom died in December, I have thought about this a lot...Dying can be expensive if you aren't prepared for it. Not too long after mom died, Dad bought me a cemetery plot in the same cemetery they will be buried in, although I won't be beside them. Although it kind of gives me the wiggins to think that I have a grave already, and I know exactly where it is, on the other hand it is kind of relieving in a way. At least when it is my time to go, which I hope is in the far, far misty future (!), that is one less thing to have to worry about! ;) Although, with my dubious Catholicism, I might not be able to be buried in a Catholic cemetery. Who knows. At least once I am more financially on my feet after I graduate and get a "real" job, maybe that is something I can change. I've always liked the idea of being buried in some type of natural way, with my philosophy of living lightly on the earth and all.  Anyway, the list of things I can't afford right now feels endless. I have that book, "Debt-Free By 30", and it is only if I get a substantially better-paying job after I graduate that I could possibly be "Debt-Free by 30". I mean, shit, I am gonna be 30 in 5 years! How the hell did that happen!?!?! ;) ;) ;)  Seriously...I felt like an invincible youngun' until I turned 25, and then it was like, OH SHIT, have to be responsible now!! I just wish I had gone to college right after high school, not gotten myself into credit card debt, etc., because now I am paying for it. I should never have been lured into working full-time at $ISP instead of finishing school, but I was so tired of always being broke that the money was calling my name. But hey, at least I am working towards a degree and bettering myself, and I won't have a useless degree when I graduate. As far as I know, GIS (Geographic Information Systems) is still a growing field. I hope I can find a decent job when I graduate.  I am only one class shy (Intermediate Algebra, ugh) of having my associate degree in Computer Networking. I am going to try and see if I can take it somewhere as a series of Saturday classes or something. I would feel like so much less of a loser if I at least had my associate degree! I would feel like everything I've done so far hasn't been quite in vain. Plus, having that associate degree would make me a lot more employable combined with my experience at $ISP. I get so irritated with myself sometimes because I feel like I have so much stacked against me, against what I really want to do. I have this history of depression that has caused me so, so many problems in my life...I am doing a lot better now, but there are still times (like today!) where I feel so paralyzed by depression and sorrow that I just want to hide in my house and sleep all day.   One thing that has changed, and I know this may sound horrible, is that I no longer have to constantly worry about my poor mom. She was a diabetic and just had so many horrible, heart-wrenching problems. I hated to see her suffering, and we all constantly worried about her because at any given time something seriously wrong could happen to her. It was especially hard for me when I moved out last year. But that is too much to get into right now...suffice it to say that my heart can rest some now knowing that Mom is no longer suffering and is in a good place. So I don't have to devote so much of my life to her...I can finally devote more of my time to myself. I know that sounds awful, like, "Yay, Mom's gone so I can get on with my life!" But really...talk to anyone who grew up with a parent who was constantly, extremely ill and suffering, and they will tell you how relieved they are when their parent finally passes on. That doesn't mean you love them any less, or miss them any less, or that their absence kills you any less...but you start to realize how "normal" people get to live. You find out how it is to go through every day and not worry about life-and-death things on a daily basis. I can't explain  it very well, so I am just going to change the subject for now. :( Like I was talking about before with the mental-partitioning thing, I have a part of me where I can talk calmly and objectively about these things, and then I have the emotional side of me that has all of the feelings about all of this.   Doing this type of thing probably isn't healthy, but it is what is getting me through life right now. It's only that once I let myself start to think about all of the shit I have been through in my life that I completely lose it. I think part of my whole problem in life is that I have so much pent-up grief in me, over so many different things, that trying to get it all out would be almost impossible. That grief is really what I don't know how to handle - I never learned how to deal with it, just how to bury it and deal with it in private as best I could. And that grief, really, is what keeps me so separate from other people. I don't know very many people my age who have suffered like I have. I am to the point where I feel so emotionally and mentally numb from everything I have gone through. All I want to is live quietly, to make enough money to do what I want and get by and be relatively happy, and save for whatever future I may have. (It's looking pretty bleak and lonely at this point without some sort of miracle happening, especially if I never leave Pittsburgh. What a scary thought!) Anyway, all of this shit I have been through, and this cold, numb feeling I have inside...that is what keeps me away from other people my age. Aside from someone with a finely developed sense of empathy, how could anyone possibly be sensitive enough to understand what I have gone through? I mean, for example - Jason. Yes, I think he is cute enough, and he seems smart and intellectual and all of that. Obviously I don't know what he has been through in his life, but I doubt he has been through anything near what I have been through in my life.  My friend X has been through some serious times...His mom died when he was in his early teens, and he took care of his dad for a while before he died in X's early twenties. So he understands somewhat about the suffering of being a caretaker, the suffering of seeing your parent die, etc. But at least from my perspective, he can't empathize or understand where I am at right now. Every day for me is such a struggle to get up and go on and "keep on keepin' on". I mean, my mom only died six months ago, but no one really asks me anymore, "How are you doing?" No one asks me if I want to talk about my mom. I miss her so much, and I feel like I am the only one I can talk to about her, and about her dying and all of the shit with Stacey and everything else. I mean, it's bad enough that my mom had to suffer her whole life, and that she had to die the way she did, and then for Stacey to treat me the way she did was so horrible that I can't stand it. My old friend Liz hardly talks to me anymore...she barely said anything when I called to tell her my mom died because I guess she just didn't know what to say. (She lives in NC so I don't see her much.) When she calls we do the usual "hey how are you doing" bit, but the thing is, she has never and probably will never really want to listen to what I have to say. She has enough of her own problems that on the one hand I feel bad wanting some of her time/attention for myself, but on the other hand, that is what friends are for! And I have really tried to be there for her whenever she needed me, let her rant, lent her money, etc. She has never done that much in return for me. :(   So on top of losing Stacey as a friend, and probably slowly losing Liz as a friend, my friend Andrew couldn't/can't really deal and I don't really talk to him anymore since my mom died. He did something that really made me exceptionally angry at my mom's funeral (long story) and we quit talking for a while. I finally was the one who had to call him, and since then we talked once or twice but he hasn't called me back since, so he gave up on me pretty easily.  I am just so tired of everything. I am tired of feeling like I have to struggle through life for just a few scraps of happiness. That is why I feel so angry at God/Fate/Whatever...have I not suffered enough? What the hell did I do in my past life or lives to deserve the life I have gotten in this one?!?! Deep down all I really want is someone to love, you know? But I never seem to be able to meet anyone who respects me for who I am, really listens to me, shares my interests, is fairly mature and just plain someone *I* would like. I am a little picky, but I don't think I should have to just "take anyone that will have me" in life. I deserve more than that. Maybe I just don't believe in myself enough that I am capable of attracting that kind of person, or that I deserve a true, lasting love. I don't know why it seems to easy for other people and so hard and near-impossible for me. That is why, when someone does come along who admits to liking me, I feel so sad and guilty when I can't return the favor. I know for a fact that my friend X likes me, and two of my other friends think he is in love with me, but there is nothing I can do about it. He is a really, really great friend, I almost think of him like an older brother or cousin that I never had, but I don't find him physically or emotionally attractive in a romantic sense.   And the thing with Jason is that while he somewhat looks the part of the type of guy I am attracted to, I doubt he has the maturity or sensitivity that I am looking for. So who knows. Like I said before, at least maybe there is a chance for some kind of friends-with-benefits arrangement, but if he keeps going all Dr. Jekyll-and-Mr. Hyde on me I may just end up pummeling his ass before I can, uh, do anything else with the rest of him. :P  Ok..off of the serious topics. Speaking of doing things with various parts of other people, I found  urlLink this site  linked from someone else's blog. It is so fucking funny!    Also, my cousin Alissa sent me one of those email forward quizzes. The results are kind of funny. Here is what I got:  AMAZINGLY ACCURATE Whatever you do, don't cheat! CHINESE HOROSCOPE : THE YEAR OF THE IRON DRAGON, WISHING YOU PROSPERITY AND GOOD FORTUNE IN THE CHINESE NEW YEAR   FOLLOW THE INSTRUCTIONS -  DO NOT CHEAT OR IT WON'T WORK AND YOU WILL WISH YOU HADN`T.   TAKE 3 MINUTES  TRY THIS - IT WILL FREAK YOU OUT. THE PERSON WHO SENT THIS TO ME SAID  HER WISH CAME TRUE 10 MINUTES AFTER SHE FORWARDED THE EMAIL   NO CHEATING !!!!  THIS GAME HAS A FUNNY / CREEPY OUTCOME.  DO NOT READ AHEAD, JUST DO IT.  IT TAKES ABOUT 3 MINUTES - WORTH A TRY  1st. Get PEN and PAPER   2nd. WHEN CHOOSING NAMES, MAKE SURE THEY ARE REAL PEOPLE THAT YOU ACTUALLY KNOW.   3rd. GO WITH YOUR FIRST INSTINCTS !!!!! Very important for good results.   4th. SCROLL DOWN ONE LINE AT THE TIME DON`T READ AHEAD otherwise YOU WILL RUIN THE FUN.   1. On a blank sheet of paper, WRITE NUMBERS 1 through 11 in a COLUMN on the LEFT.  2. BESIDE the NUMBERS 1 &2, WRITE DOWN ANY 2 NUMBERS YOU WANT.  DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE NUMBER?  3. BESIDE the NUMBERS 3 &7, WRITE DOWN THE NAMES OF TWO MEMBERS OF THE OPPOSITE SEX.  CAUTION: DO NOT LOOK AHEAD or IT WILL NOT TURN OUT RIGHT  4. WRITE ANYONE'S NAME (like FRIENDS or FAMILY...) next to 4, 5, &6.   DON'T CHEAT OR YOU`LL BE UPSET THAT YOU DID!   5. WRITE down FOUR SONG TITLES in 8, 9, 10, &11   6. Finally, MAKE A WISH!          ARE YOU READY? HERE IS THE KEY TO THE GAME * * * * * * * * * * *  1. THE NUMBER of PEOPLE YOU MUST TELL ABOUT THIS GAME is found in  SPACE 2  2. THE PERSON IN SPACE 3 IS THE ONE YOU LOVE  3. THE PERSON YOU LIKE but your relationship CANNOT WORK is in SPACE 7   4. YOU CARE MOST about the PERSON you put in SPACE 4   5. THE PERSON YOU NAME IN NUMBER 5 IS THE ONE WHO KNOWS YOU VERY WELL.   6. THE PERSON YOU NAMED IN 6 IS THE YOUR LUCKY STAR  7. THE SONG IN 8 IS THE SONG THAT MATCHES WITH THE PERSON IN NUMBER 3   8. THE TITLE IN 9 IS THE SONG FOR THE PERSON IN 7   9. THE 10TH SPACE IS THE SONG THAT TELLS YOU MOST ABOUT YOUR MIND  10. AND 11 IS THE SONG TELLING HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT LIFE  11.. NUMBER 1 IS YOUR LUCKY NUMBER SEND THIS TO A MINIMUM OF 10 PEOPLE WITHIN AN HOUR OF READING THIS.   IF YOU DO, YOUR WISH WILL COME TRUE. IF YOU FAIL TO, IT WILL BECOME THE OPPOSITE. STRANGE HOW IT SEEMS TO WORK.  My answers were: 1. 13 (my birthday) 2. 24 (just a random pick - that was a good year for me, at least until I moved in with The Bitch!) 3. Jason (ha!) 4. Mandy (my best friend since we were 7) 5. Jay (my other best friend) 6. Andrew (one of my best friends, even if friendship is strained at the moment) 7. Trent Reznor - my lifelong lust object ;) 8. "Closer" by NIN - hahahaha! 9.  urlLink "Legion" by VNV Nation  10.  urlLink "Joy" by VNV Nation  11.  urlLink "Leave Me Alone" by The Cruxshadows   I know how these things usually worked, which was why I guess "Closer" for one of the song choices. It's just funny that it went with who I picked for #3! LOL  Ok, zoinks, I gotta get to bed. I might call off again tomorrow, not sure...I need the money, though. :( Maybe I could just go work at $ISP and call off from $Deli. *sigh*   I sure wish I got a paid vacation still...that's the bad thing about being part time. No bennies. Boo. :(   Goodnight!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      np: live - "lightning crashes" - throwing copper ------------------------------------------------  So, I was supposed to work at $ISP today but I just didn't go in to work. I don't know why, but I woke up depressed and feeling slightly sick and *really* groggy, so I decided to go back to bed. That's it! I didn't even call. :o I hope I don't get fired. I've been kind of pushing it there lately, or at least it feels like that to me. However, I am always told I do a good job and everything, so as long as they are happy with me I guess that is all that matters. At the most I might get written up. Hopefully they will just think "Oh, she is usually off on Tuesdays so maybe she forgot that she switched today." No one called me, so it must not be that big of a deal! I WAS going to ask for Friday off, but I just couldn't deal with going in to work today and then working tonight at $Deli. I doubt they would give me Friday off too if I "forgot" to come in today! :P X, X's roommate, and I were vaguely planning on going somewhere Friday, but oh well. There is always time for that later.  I think I am going to call off to $Deli tonight too. I was thinking, I need to go to the post office and mail my eBay stuff anyway, because the other dude finally payed me, so I have enough to mail everyone's stuff. After that I think I am going to drive up to Altoona and visit my mom. I feel like getting away for a while and going for a drive, and I haven't been up to the cemetery since maybe February or March, so I really need to go. I miss my mom so much...I hate it that she is so far away, but that is where she wanted to be buried, so no help for it. :/   So anyway, I ended up sleeping until almost 1:00. 1:00! I went to bed around 12:30. i don't know what is wrong with me that I need to sleep this much. On my days off, whenever I don't set my alarm, I sleep for 12 hours. I woke up and I was *still* tired! Argh! I even take vitamins and crap and apparently it doesn't help. I'm not sure if Wellbutrin makes you tired or not, I'd have to check. It might be allergies too, and/or just mental exhaustion. Who knows!   I am just plain bummed out today. I was having these weird dreams...I had one dream with Craig Wilson in it playing baseball, but that was about it. ;) Then I had a dream that I was dressing up in these beautiful goth/vintage clothes getting ready to go somewhere with a dark-haired gothy-type guy...I don't know who it was but in the dream I liked him and wanted him to notice me but was too afraid to say anything. It may have been Jason or any other combination of people I've liked in the past. But there was someone else waiting who I was supposedly going to marry or something. It was strange. I just remember feeling so sad in the dream because this person who was the one I really liked wouldn't seem to notice me at all, like I was invisible, even though I looked great and had these beautiful clothes on and everything, and looked exactly how I *wanted* to look for a change. Weird! My dreams are always so random.  Well, it is 2:00 in the afternoon and I work at 6:00 at $Deli, so I should really call them. I always feel so chicken about calling off when I don't really need to. I can never think of a good cover story that doesn't sound totally lame when I finally call. I was thinking I could just call and say that I had to go out of town this evening due to a family issue, or something. The whole thing with lying is that you need to tell part of the truth so it comes out better. *sigh* I could also say that it is because a family friend is in the hospital - Mandy's grandparents were in recently, but I don't want to jinx them! But you just can't really call in to work and say, "Hi, I need to call off because I am overwhelmed and and depressed and my mom died 6 months ago and I really need to go visit her and today is the only day that will do."  I hate to do it, but I do call off way too much at $ISP. I just get so mentally exhausted from that place sometimes and I don't get enough of a break from it. One thing, though, I absolutely need to get more sleep. Period. I will never make it working all of these hours if I don't get enough sleep!  Ok...I need to decide what I am going to do here. I always feel so guilty when I call off, but if I don't I know I will just feel like crap all day and wish I had called off tonight. The bad thing about working this many hours is that you can't be spontaneous. :P I'm also leery of calling off from $Deli bc I am still new, but the managers think I am doing really good so far so maybe it will be ok. I just feel always feel guilty calling off if I am not so sick I am barfing my guts out, because technically I *could* work. *sigh* However, it would be so nice to have tonight off too and actually be able to do something *I* want to do. Well, I guess I can make up for it by just doing a good job the rest of the week, maybe.   Argh. Part of me wants to call off and go to the P.O. like I said, and then go to Altoona. Part of me wants to just call off and do my errands, maybe get some dinner somewhere, and then come back here and veg the rest of the night. I could probably go back to sleep again. I am still tired. Maybe I just need to get out of the house.  You know, what probably brought this on is that I had a shitty day at $Deli yesterday, and Jason snarked at me again and I snapped out on him. I was freaking yesterday - I was in such a bad mood, it was really busy, we didn't have enough people, etc. I was so overwhelmed and the other lady I was working with is so slow. Then for Jason to go and bitch at me in the middle of all of that was just too much! So there I was, all happy about Jason being so friendly from Sunday, and then he has to go and be shitty to me yesterday. I'm such a moron...whenever I have even the slightest suspicion that someone likes me, it's like the world is suddenly this wonderful place full of possibilities, etc. Then when something bad happens that makes me doubt that, I fall back down into reality with a thud and get all depressed about it. Grr. Why can't life be easier!?!? Why does it have to be so fucking hard for me to find somebody to be with? For some people it is so bloody easy...Then there's me...the people that like me are not people I can possibly like back, so I feel guilty about it, and the people I like just ignore me or think I am a joke. I hate my life sometimes.  Cripes. I need to take some Advil and call off and then figure out what to do.   ---- Damn it, I keep finding silverfish in my apartment. They are so gross! They are usually dead, thank goodness, or else veeeery veeeery slow. I pick them up in a paper towel and flush them. Yuck!  Okay, I am stalling. I need to go call $Deli. Argh.  I need to get away for a little bit. I feel bad leaving the kittens here by themselves so much, though. :( 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      np: U2 - "The Fly"/various mp3s ------------------------------  Hello! I am waiting for my dad to come over because we have a game tonight, so I figured I'd blog a little in the meantime.   So, I had a pretty good day today! I had a good time going out the other night- my friend X and I went to Eat 'N Park (affectionately known as "Eat 'N Barf") around 10:45 for some late-night grub. X's roommate showed and we just sat and gabbed for a while. It was nice to get out for a bit and be somewhere that isn't work! :P  Yesterday I got paid so I mailed my rent check - that felt good! - and after work X & I did some running around. We went to K-Mart, Office Max, the Festival Foods grocery store, and had dinner at The Sacred Olive, otherwise known as the Olive Garden. (I had an old old net-friend who loved that place as much as I did, so we always called it the Sacred Olive :D) Very tasty. I don't get to go there much anyway since my mom passed away, and Jay (one of my best friends) moved to Philly. I went to Office Max because I've been needing to get one of those hard plastic mats to go under my computer chair. It was digging holes in the carpet and also stained it from some kind of goop in the wheels, which pissed me off. I will have to try some Oxi-Clean or something on the spots to see if that will lift them up. If it's not from the chair then it has to be from one of my pieces of furniture or someone's shoes from when I moved in. After we ate we went to Festival Foods so I could get the girls Swheat Scoop and kitten food. So far I am not entirely sure about the Swheat Scoop. I think it aggravates my allergies a bit, but it is so much better for the cats and is environmentally friendly. The only drawback is that the pee-clumps ends up stuck to the bottom of the litterbox, but I think I haven't been putting enough in - it says to leave 3" in and I usually leave about 2-2.5" bc they are tiny still and I hate to waste litter. (They get it everywhere!)    np: The Cruxshadows - "Leave Me Alone"/various gothy & 80s mp3s ----------------------------------------------------------------  Ok, I'm back. The Pirates won, yay! *snoopy dance* 5-3, and it's their 8th straight win. Woo hoo! I got to see my Wilsons, too, and my man Craig got a Grand Slam, aww yeah! We got free Fourth-of-July flag-themed hats too, but I am totally not a baseball cap person and I don't know if I will ever wear it. I think I look silly in hats.  This whole baseball thing has crept up on me - I actually like it now, even if I still don't always understand what is going on! If I was talking to myself from 7-8 years ago my old self would be horrified to know that I like something so un-goth as baseball now. ;P And I wore a Siouxsie T-shirt, a pair of dark blue jeans with a flower-y motif on them, and my mom's old brown Birks. I'm turning into such a hippie. :D I dunno...the older I get the more the whole goth thing just seems kind of silly. I like wearing colors and jeans and stuff like that. I'm more of a goth hippie anyway - a hippie that wears lots of dark-colored clothing. Plus, the whole fat thing makes it kind of hard to be a sexxxy gawth chix0r. :P I so can't wait to get back in shape and start being able to look and feel sexy again. With me having much more confidence than I did back in high school, if I just looked a little better better and felt better about my appearance, I would totally get some ass on a regular basis. I am starting to lose weight a bit - all of this running around is doing me good. I am feeling a lot better physically, too, aside from the being tired. I can fit into two pairs of paints that I haven't been able to wear in a long time bc they were too tight for me before, so that's good! I just need to keep it up. I think I am just going to use up the rest of the junk food I have and really try my best not to get any more. I am going to try to just keep making iced tea and drinking that and water. I also need to try to find time to start doing my Power 90 tapes and work on a meal plan again that keeps me around 1500 calories. The last time I was cutting back on calories like that and doing Power 90 I did start to lose weight.   I will be so excited when I can get back into a size 24 jeans! Then I will know that I am really on my way. I have been telling myself for a while now, I am not worried about getting thin overnight. I just want to be able to wear a size 20/22/24 again in pants...eventually I would even be cool with wearing a size 12 again, or heck, even a size 14/16. Ideally I'd like to get down to about 125 or even the 135 I weighed before I moved here - that is a good weight for someone my height. I don't have to be super-skinny but I just want to be able to wear sexy clothes and look good again. The day when I don't have to shop at Lane Bryant anymore will be a glorious day for me! No more dumpy clothes that don't fit the way I'd like. I honestly think that if there hadn't been a Lane Bryant in Ross Park Mall back when I started to gain all of this weight, I would have tried harder to lose weight instead of thinking, "Oh, they have all of these clothes that will fit me, so I don't have to worry about watching my weight." I just wish that I would have tried to do *something* once I noticed that my weight started to creep up. I won't say what I am now, but when I started at Nauticom I weighed like, 150/160. After I weighed 180-ish that should have been a wake-up call for me.   Now I weigh so much more and it makes me so miserable about myself. I feel so gross and disgusting. I wish so much that I could feel like a normal girl again and date and go clothes shopping and not constantly feel like I am this ugly, foul, repugnant thing. I don't even really try to flirt with cute guys because why the hell would any guy want to go out with me when there hundreds of pretty, thin little yuppie princesses around this area? I can't compete with that. So that is why I want to get in shape again, as much as I possibly can and as soon as possible. With the way I am feeling lately, it finally feels like it is time to start working on that aspect of myself. I don't want to live this way forever - single and miserable about my looks. I never realized how secretly vain I was in high school...I personally think I am pretty enough, but was so tormented in high school that I couldn't quite believe that I was pretty without excessive outside validation. I didn't feel pretty compared to everyone else, and I thought I was so fat when I really was just average-sized, but I always liked be able to dressy sexy-ish and go shopping and flirt and all of that regardless. I only dated sporadically and the guys I dated were pretty much chumps to begin with, but at least I *could* date. If I really think about it, a lot of people hit on me or expressed interest, but I was so insecure at the time that I either didn't notice, read it wrong, didn't take advantage of it, etc.   I'm rambling. :P   (np: Siouxsie & The Banshees - "Christine")  Anyway, I never finished what I was starting to write about earlier today. When I got home yesterday I did laundry and hauled all of my nasty, smelly, week-old dirty dishes upstairs to Pat & Tim's apartment and used their dishwasher. :D While I was waiting for everything to get done I cleaned up in the kitchen a bit. I made my lunch, made a pitcher of iced tea, filled up 4 empty 2-liter bottles with filtered water, cleaned the litterbox, etc. I feel like a slob for leaving the dishes for so long, but when I get home after working so much, I either want to get right in the shower and then go to bed or else do something that doesn't involve standing or work! I swear, if I can swing it out of my student loan refund in the fall, the first thing I am getting after paying my bills is a portable dishwasher! I hate doing dishes. I didn't mind doing the dishes when I was living at the bitch's house for some reason, maybe just because of the other-person-to-deal-with factor. I am usually a neat-freak too - my place might not be, say, entirely dust-free, but things are usually picked up and put away, neat, etc. Lately, though, I have been letting the dishes go until I have most of an afternoon or evening off, and the past few days I haven't made my bed. I feel so decadent. ;) I just noticed today that my radio is all dusty and grody from who-knows-what, so I was like, yikes, must clean soon! Maybe Monday - I work 9-2. I'm really trying to keep up on the housework and stuff when I can. I have totally slacked on cooking and stuff, but having a messy house just aggravates me.  So anyway, I was saying that I had a good day today! This morning sucked, I SO did not want to get up. Thankfully getting my stuff ready for today last night helped - I made my lunch and laid out my work clothes for today. Once I got to work I started to wake up and it was slow enough to not be annoying. Jason worked today, too. ;) He was being really friendly today....he was bopping around and singing the Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood song this morning. ;) I told him it was abnormal for someone to be that cheerful that early in the morning. ;) He's a strange guy. But, damn it, he's a *cute* strange guy. I lurrrrve me some cute strange boys. I can't help myself, he *is* cute. And the strangeness is endearing. He has dark hair, dark eyes, a nice shy smile, and he's tall. I love guys that are taller than me...it kind of makes me feel like "Here's someone who can take on the world for me, and give me a break from doing it all myself."  I think I am starting to like him. ::blush:: At least when he is being nice I feel like I could really get to like him if I knew him better. When he gets snarky I just want to smack him upside the head. But hey...maybe he just has a temper or gets irritated easily. I am the same way. I can't read him very well, though...that might be part of my whole no-self-esteem-in-the-personal-department factor kicking in, but based on my limited experience from back in my cute-and-thin salad days (ha!), I think maaaaaybe, maybe maybe maybe, he might like me a little too. You know when you first meet someone, you do that quick mental appraisal, and if you like what you see and think they are kinda cute, and your eyes light up and you do that whole sheepish grin thing? Well, that happened. That has to be a good sign! I think he must be at least as strange and weird and antisocial as I am.   I don't know. I am probably just getting my hopes up. I mean, I *want* to get my hopes up. (No jokes from the peanut gallery!) I *want* to have someone like me again, I *want* to date people again. I want to have some good luck for once and feel like a normal person instead of a social outcast/leper. The way he was acting today, he was being really friendly and talking more. I don't know if he picked up on how shy I really am or not... he probably just thinks I am antisocial. I just freeze up around someone I think is attractive, because I feel so wretched about myself that I feel like anyone who actually realized I liked them would be totally grossed out by me.   :( I don't want him to think I am gross! :( So I don't know what is going on yet...it's too early to tell. I kind of suspect that he might be a lot like me in the personality department - he seems very smart, critical, maybe a little shy/aloof. More like moody! He seems like your typical geek, and I don't actually know how old he is, what he does outside of work, etc., so I don't know if he has dated much at all. Somehow I can't really see him having a girlfriend, but who knows. He seems like the weird loner type. I hope things work out and we can maybe get to be friends at least, he seems like he'd be cool to hang out with outside of work. But oh, it would be so nice to have someone around again who I actually found attractive and liked and who liked me back. I have been so alone for so long. Maybe things are changing for me in the respect? Who knows. It's nice to have daydreams and all, but I have to be practically, really - I don't want to get my hopes up and then be bitterly disappointed. I will just have to play it cool and not try to let on that I think he is cute, and just be friendly and see what happens.   One of the things about being Wiccan/Pagan, if you do anything to develop or encourage your "sixth sense", it doesn't always give you helpful information. Jason "feels" like someone I could *really* get to like and trust and get along well with. He's the first person I've found who is interesting enough and cute enough to make me want to date them. I feel like I could trust him, eventually, if we got to know each other. But I've felt that around other people too and gotten screwed. So I don't always go along with my feelings anymore, sad to say. I don't want to get burned again. That is the last thing I need.  Speaking of weird and antisocial....It's so weird. Everyone always tells me how friendly and bubbly and nice I am or seem. I am like, Customer Service Dream Girl or something. But it's really only a big cover for my gut-wrenching shyness and self-doubt. I've just learned how to not let it affect me as much when I am working. I really do like being a nice person, I like being friendly and in a good mood and I like helping people. I like being helpful because it makes me feel useful. But inside I am so wracked with self-doubt and self-loathing. I have very little confidence in myself and I usually dread direct confrontations with people. I prefer to do things in the background. But with all of my jobs, I've been literally forced to deal with people and find a way to deal with the shyness part...So I've developed this sort of ability to turn parts of my personality on or off as needed, or block them out. I think that is why I do have such a hard time meeting people and getting to know them. I am so used to hiding parts of myself and trying to cover for the shyness that I can't really be myself sometimes, or else I don't dare to even try at all. It makes for a very lonely life. I'm somewhat in a prison of my own making, but I can't see for myself how to break free from it. :( The only thing I can think of is to lose weight and start looking better again.  As much as my friend X always says, "Image shouldn't matter, bla bla bla", but it *does*. NO ONE likes to admit that, but it does. Try going from being a passably-cute thin girl to a she'd-be-pretty-if-she-lost-X-amount-of-weight "fat girl", and see how image matters then. When you are heavy in this culture, it is like being a leper. You are a total outcast. People aren't as friendly to you, they only notice your size and not who you really are, people's eyes slide right over you...You are the embodiment of what many people fear the most - fat! I mean, how many girls have you heard say, "I would rather die than be fat?" Sometimes I can't help but agree...being fat has cost me some of the most potentially fun and enjoyable years of my life. I have got to find a way out of this.   So, at least having this second job is a good start. I can already fit into a pair of pants that I haven't been able to wear in a long time, and they are even loose on me at that! So I just have to keep this up. I am going to drag out all of my fitness and diet books and really try to plan out a workable diet-change and exercise plan for myself. I will be so happy when I really start to *look* thinner. I just can't live like this anymore, and even though I don't really like to exercise, I just have to do it, just like I had to get this second job. And hopefully the results will start to show sooner rather than later!  Back to the whole dating topic...I was thinking about this at work today. It would honestly be near-impossible for me to date anyone right now. I have serious trust issues. I have been hurt for so long, in so many different ways, let down, taken advantage of, treated like shit, ignored, neglected, etc....someone would have to jump through hoops before I would completely trust them with my heart and my innermost feelings. Not to mention feeling so love-starved that it would be really hard for me to resist *wanting* to love someone, even if they weren't the right person for me at the time or weren't good for me. I mean, I would not sneeze at a good shagging arrangement if I found the right person for *that*, but for serious relationship material, I would have to find a specific type of person to really get that far.   I was also thinking today of how much pent-up anger I have in me. I keep such a tight lid on it that half the time it doesn't even really register, but I am so angry about my past and that needs to be dealt with too. I don't even know where to begin on that.   ....  Oy. I dunno...this is all a lot to think about. However, I am extremely tired and really to fall off my chair in a deep sleep, so I had better get going. Hopefully something good will happen in the cute coworker department eventually. ;) But at least in the meantime I can admire the cuteness. ;D   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      you know, i was thinking this morning...stacey should be the one who feels ashamed and embarassed to show her face around the office. i am tired of feeling bad about this. if i see her, i will just laugh in her face at how ridiculous she is.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a very. long. day. I swear, I thought today would never end. I am so fucking tired...I have been home since 6:45 and my feet still hurt! :( I am so tired but I still need to do laundry and play with the cats and go through my mail that has been piling up for two weeks and do the dishes....yay, me. :P   Ok, I need to rant about this assclown I work with at The Other Place, aka The Deli. His name is Jason and he works in the back doing frying and cooking and other stuff like that on some really frighteningly greasy, gunked-up contraptions. The thing is, I do think he's kind of cute, but he's just so...surly is a good word for it! Totally ruins the cuteness factor. He seems immature for his age though - I am guessing he is a few years younger than me, maybe 20-22. Guys that age are generally ridiculous. However ,I will say though that if I had to work back there day after day after day digging bloody chicken parts out of a bag and deep-frying them in oil that is $Deity-only-knows how old, on equipment that probably hasn't seen a good cleaning since it was installed, well, I'd sure as shit feel like it was my very own version of Dante's Inferno! I can't even imagine the smell. :P Eww. So maybe that is *some* excuse for his total shite attitude, but he pisses me off, and therefore, I must rant.   So, one of the other deli ladies, Bonnie, had put a pizza in the oven and told us to get it out when it was done, because she was leaving for the day. It was really busy when the timer went off and I was running around like a (sorry for the pun) chicken with my head cut off. I don't know what I was thinking, I should have just grabbed it out of the oven and then asked what to do with it. But Mark, the other night-turn guy, was in the back talking to Jason, and he is sort of the "shift supervisor". Since I am new, I figure, you know, better to not step on any toes or just assume I know how to do everything, so I always ask if it's ok before I do anything new, just out of habit. Anyway, I gestured in the general direction of the oven and said something like, "Hey Mark, the pizza is done, what should I...?" and he said he'd come over and get it. I was moving towards the oven and Jason came over and said "Jesus, you can't even figure out which one the oven is?!?!". I swear, I wanted to punch him right in his smarmy little face then and there!   This is the third or fourth time he's gotten snarky at me. I don't know what his goddamn problem is...if he gets shitty with me like that one more time I am just going to confront him and ask him what his bloody problem is with me. Last week he got shitty with me because he said I was leaving the cooler door open too much, but I have seen other people there do it too! So now when I leave the cooler I slam the door good and hard so he gets the message. The other time, I was getting ready to cut something for a customer, and asked if they'd like it sliced thin or thick, because invariably if I do it the way I think I should, they will want it done the other way. So I always ask.   The guy said, "Just regular" or something stupid, and Jason goes out of his way to be a dick and said, "You don't have to ask them every time how they want it, just slice it!" I retorted back, "Well, *I've* never worked in a deli before so *I* like to ask them to be sure I am *doing* it right." He didn't say anything to that so I don't know what the hell his problem is. Another thing, when we were getting trained on the new Delallo products by one of the company reps, she was talking about familiarizing ourselves with the various products. We were all talking about some of the ones we'd had before/heard of/not heard of/prepared differently elsewhere, etc. I made some little joke like, "Oh, my family is (are?) all Irish Catholics, so I don't know what half of this stuff is!" because it is mostly various types of Italian meats. (I mean, Delallo? Duh.) He was all like, "What does religion have to do with it?" WHO FUCKING CARES! I said, "I was being sarcastic" and he just muttered something. I don't know what his damn problem is but I wish he'd vent his spleen on someone else.   Sometimes he will seem nice/friendly and sometimes he's just a prick. The only thing I can think of is that the manager, Linda, who incidentally is a very cool person, thinks I am just the bees knees and always takes time to tell me I am doing a good job and whatnot. (Today she called me her "star pupil"! ;)) Maybe he is envious or something? Who knows. I mean, I usually feel embarassed when my work is pointed out in front of other people I work with, so I try to just tell her thanks. It does make me feel good to know that they think I am doing a good job for someone who never worked in a deli before - it really is a lot to pick up all at once. I still ask a ton of questions when I work, and it makes me feel stupid because I haven't picked it all up yet!   So, that is my rant. At least about him! The thing I don't get is that I kind of got the impression that he might have liked me a little when we first met....maybe this is a negative attention thing? I dunno. If he'd quit being a prick and I could see how he was outside of work, I'd maybe hang out with him a few times. He's definitely not boyfriend material but he could be shaggable, who knows. ;) But I won't put up with that kind of nasty attitude from someone. That is honestly why I haven't dated anyone in so long...I don't feel like I should have to lower my standards to any old guy who might think I am the slightest bit attractive. I won't go out with someone who I feel isn't worth my time, wouldn't/couldn't understand me, is a Republican, or would constantly be making me feel stupid in some way.   I think a lot of younger (or just insecure-and-unenlightened) guys do that because they can't stand a female not looking up to them in some way. Guys are raised from birth practically to feel that girls are beneath them, and the way high school girls are these days - I mean, I have only been out of high school for 7 years, and high school girls have always seemed to me to be socialized to be totally submissive to any guy that wants them. I don't play that game anymore. I've had two close guy friends basically admit they are in love with me in the past 5 years, but they were in love with who they saw me as, or who they wanted me to be. They never really accepted *me* for who and how I am. I could never even begin to feel that way towards either of them because deep down, they didn't really respect *me*. They always discounted my opinions in some way, always had to be right, etc. That makes me crazy. Even one of my best friends, who happens to be gay, can't always even see me for who I am without trying to "other" me in some way. He will treat me sometimes in this "aw how cute, the little woman is worrying her pretty little head/doing something dumb but in a cute way, etc."-type manner, and that just drives me up the fucking wall. It doesn't help, either, that I have had to claw my way into Minor Self-Esteem Land, and I constantly feel like anything I do is wrong. I am already shy enough and too self-conscious as it is. When someone treats me that way, it just makes me withdraw more and second-guess myself, and then I *will* do stupid things without thinking because I feel so self-conscious that I am almost paralyzed by it. It always makes me resent whoever is treating me like that as well, hence the vigor with which I am denouncing Jason!   So, tip out there for you guys - don't be a jerk to shy, quiet people.   But I'm not bitter! Nooooo...not me...nothing to see here, move along....  ...  Well, in other good news: I have enough money to pay my rent on time! Woo hoo! Because otherwise, if I pay it late, it costs an additional $50, and I have already had to do that once. I don't want to have to do it again! If I keep paying my rent late like this I will be in a constant cycle of being in the hole. That is definitely not good.  So, I almost started crying at work today thinking about all of this. Some days I feel like my life is just "too much to be borne". I was thinking today, my mom has been dead for 6 months. I have gone 6 months without my mom. That seems impossible to me in some way....how can the world keep on going without my mom in it? Why do I have to keep on going when I feel like all I want to do is scream and scream and scream out loud because my mom is gone?! How can it be 6 months already?! And then I think, why did Stacey have to treat me so horribly....she was supposed to be one of my best friends. I was in her wedding. I was there for her when she had all of that crap go down with her ex-husband, and she did one of those cry-for-attention swallow-a-bunch-of-pills suicide attempts. I trusted her to keep things on the up-and-up when I moved in with her - I mean, I moved in to help her make her mortgage payments, and because I needed an inexpensive place to stay. I not only paid $300 out of my own pocket for the carpet, I paid $70 towards getting the cats fixed that we got together...I always paid her the rent ahead of time for the semester instead of monthly...I got the majority of the groceries. On and on...do you think she appreciated any of it? I doubt it.  Everything went downhill after my mom died....I just don't understand why she turned on me the way she did. I have never really been betrayed by a friend like that, and it hurts me so badly. I mean, this has all made me really angry, and it pisses me off to no end that I really have no way of getting back at her - there is nothing I can do to her of the magnitude of what she did to me, nothing I can do to hurt her on the magnitude she has hurt me. But what she did to me hurts me more than makes me angry - the anger is more of a surface reaction. It just bewilders me completely. I really *do not* understand how you could get mad at your roommate over the housework after their *mother* has died. Hiw could you?! It's despicable! Honestly - that is the whole entire thing that she was mad at me about (or at least that is what she tells herself to justify how she treated me). After I moved out, she had to play Little Miss Drama Queen and blab to everyone at work how she "kicked me OUT!" and how I "wanted her to be my maid" and all of this other crap.                                                                                      The thing is, I DID do my share of the housework. I don't get where she thinks I didn't do anything. I was *constantly* picking up after her, doing all of the dishes when they needed done, regardless of whose they were, etc. When she would do dishes, she'd do hers and leave mine in the sink. The one time I asked her about it, and she said "she got distracted". My ass she got distracted! She never one said straight to my face, "Let's portion out the chores" or "let's make a schedule of who does what and when". Never. All she ever said was that she felt each person should do their own dishes, and we could take turns with the garbage. That was it. Not to mention, after I told her numerous times to tell me when she needed money for the utilities, and she never once asked me for money. So the week I was moving out, she tells me that they are all about to get shut off because she is so past due on them. Well, dumbfuck, whose problem is that?!? She never asked me for money. I am not psychic. I will not know you need money unless you *tell me* you need money. What is the big fucking deal with that?   She just turned on me out of the blue, it felt like, and she was *so* nasty it was just incredible. I mean, what a way to be there for your friend after their beloved, sick mother dies! Ignore them completely! Treat them like shit! Don't even try to empahtize at all! I mean, the *whole entire thing* that she was mad about was...drumroll, please....the *housework*! These were her exact words: "I'm sorry your mom died and all, and I didn't mind helping out with the housework for a month or so, but after that it was just ridiculous and I felt like you wanted me to be your maid, and I felt like I had a    child    in the house." That just boggles my mind. I mean, how would she have felt if I said to her, at her lowest period of her life, "Oh, I'm sorry your husband treats you like shit and all, and I don't mind you being depressed for a month or so, but you're not being a good enough friend and you need to snap out of it because this depression thing is just really annoying me. And besides, we all told you he was a jerk and you married him anyway so it's your own fault if you're miserable." It's a total slap in the face. That is exactly how I felt when she said that to me.   It's like, gee, thanks a whole fucking lot. I am going out of my mind with grief and shock and barely finding the will to get out of bed in the morning, and she's mad because she actually had to lift a finger and help out around her *own fucking house*?! Gah! And the way she acted when she "asked" me to move out was ridiculous. (Side note: i can never again write or say that word without thinking "Riddikulus!" and Professor Snape jumping out of a closet wearing Neville's grandma's clothing. :D) Ahem. Anyway....she gave me a note asking me to move out instead of saying it to my face. She was going to let me take the two cats we had gotten together bc they were very attached to me, but the day I asked her for the remainder of my rent money back for the month (which she had already spent), she took the cats that night and hid them until I moved out. I cried me eyes out begging her to tell me where they were, or to at least let me say goodbye to them...that night was when she really turned on me and went from silently-ignoring-me to being outright fucking nasty to me. So, I moved out and that was that.   She never refunded my money, never made a peep about the carpet or the money I paid for the cats. She still has some of my things and won't answer my emails, so I doubt I will ever get them back. She accused me of stealing some of her things. I did accidentally pack some of her kitchen things, because my mom had a lot of identical items and I thought they were things I had gotten from her. At least when I moved out, there was hardly a crumb of food in the house and she was going broke. I even went back the day after I moved out, while she was still at work, to try and get the cats...She had already changed the locks. That made me so fucking mad, because I had paid her ahead of time in good faith, and she owed me that rent money back. She tried to claim "damages" on my room and that was her excuse for screwing me out of my rent money, which I really needed at the time. So anyway, when I went back, I pushed in the back door and the lock popped right off (ha! take that, bitch!). I was standing in the kitchen with the cats in the cat carrier when I realized, sadly, that with as crazy and unbalanced and vicious as she is, she would stop at nothing to cause trouble for me if I took the cats. So I had to leave them there and I bawled my head off the whole way home. She had the nerve to accuse me of "breaking and entering" and she was going to call the cops on me, bla bla bla. She also had to the nerve to say that "she had hoped we could be friends still after this" (!!!) but that the door was "unforgivable". I was like, sister, what the hell is wrong with you?! What reality does your brand of logic come from? Can she really have no comprehension at all, or no ability to think that hello, maybe I had enough to be angry about? And that she should probably be glad that the *only* think I did was pop the lock off of the back door? With as angry as she made me, I think I showed admirable restraint in not totally losing it and wrecking the place. I was *trying* to keep things on the up-and-up, and *she* is the one who took it to that level. I even asked her, "Why didn't you just tell me you wanted to keep the cats?" Do you know what she said?! (Oooh, this makes me so mad I just want to get a voodoo doll of her and stick hot pins in it all day...) She said,   "Well, every time I'd try to talk to you, you'd just end up breaking down and we'd never get anywhere." Like, oh, I didn't have anything to be upset about. You know, my mom's only dead, what's the big deal? Jesus Christ.   The thing is - and look, I have two friends who are bipolar, and I've had clinical depression for years myself, so I am definitely an advocate for the mentally ill - she was diagnosed with "borderline personality disorder" after her little suicide attempt. She always seemed so normal that I thought the psychiatrist had diagnosed her wrong or over-diagnosed her depression. Well, after living with that psycho bitch for 8 months, with her being off of her anti-depressant, I can definitely see how mentally messed up she is! She's a fucking nutcase. I was constantly walking on eggshells living with her, and I don't think I was that intensely miserable since I was in high school. Those 8 months, especially the 4 months after my mom died, were complete hell. I just wish I had taken my student loan money and moved out in January when I had the chance. I should never have moved in with her in the first place.   So anyway....I am Super Tangent Woman this evening, apparently, oops....this is my life. My mom died, I had to take a semester off of school, someone I thought was one of my best friends betrayed me and kicked me out of the house when I had almost zero money to my name...I've been pretty much broke for roughly the 2 months since I moved in here, because my work couldn't give me full-time hours over the summer, so I had to get a second job. I work 50+ hours a week and just started getting paid last week, so at least now I am finally getting on my feet again. I had to borrow so much freaking money from my dad to get this apartment, and my friends paid for a U-Haul van for me, and they and my uncle helped me move, God bless 'em all. I am just so relieved that the nightmare with Stacey is mostly over. I still have to work with the stupid bitch, unfortunately, but at least she works downstairs and I work upstairs, so thankfully I rarely have to see her, only her car. I sure hope she is miserable and broke and her friends are shunning her. Even her sister was appalled at how she was treated me and said she was "such a bitch".   I am just so relieved to be in my own place and feel like my own person again. After two months I am finally beginning to mentally relax and feel like I am on my feet again emotionally/personally. She was such a negative, manipulative, and ultimately vicious person that living with her really did a number of me. Well, as my uncle and one of my other friends always says, "Life will pay her back." She probably feels all high and mighty, but some way, some how, she will get what she deserves from this situation. All I can hope is that she gets a better job and I never have to see her again. At least I got rid of everything that reminds me of her. I wish I could erase my entire friendship with her from my memory and pretend it never happened. That is how much I despise her now. I just wish that I could get over this anger and the hurt and the disappointment and the desire for revenge. I hate being made a fool of and being taken advantage of, and I am always too ready to be nice and trusting...I will never forget what she did to me and I just wish I could pay her back someday! But I need to get past this somehow....I don't need this kind of anger and resentment hanging around. I am doing a lot better in that respect now, but it's hard to just let something like that drop and move on. I can't help wanting to get even (hey, I'm a Scorpio, it's in my nature!). But I will be the better person for moving on and just getting on with my life. I know I should try to forgive her, but it's hard. I am working on that. It would piss her off anyway. ;)   Oh well....that was a gigantic tangential rant....I don't have issues, no, not me! ;) I need to get going...Meeting a friend for some late-night dinner. Bye! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink An article from ABCNews.com: "Why Are Pregnant Women the Victims Of Murder?"   Our society is so fucked up. You shouldn't have to be worried about possibly being *murdered* by your lover, boyfriend, spouse when you are pregnant! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      np: The new Cure album, again. :) -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  I'm back!  I have some good news - my frigging school *finally* posted their new tuition costs on their website, and I was able to figure out what my financial aid is going to be. People can rip on my school all they want, but it is so cheap that it is almost criminal. I figure, hey, as long as I study hard and get good grades, my degree is just as valid as one from a more expensive school. I went to  urlLink Chatham College  for a semester, and I really think that the quality of the classes I've had so far at $StateU surpasses the quality of classes I had at Chatham. I mean, Chatham really is more of a liberal arts school, so I can't really fault them for their technology programs. but it's expensive as hell, and I couldn't see paying so much more money for a degree that was so generic for the field I (currently) work in.  I already have a large loan from my one semester at Chatham, and I want to keep my school costs down as much as possbile - that is why I transferred to $StateU. I mean, hell, I can pay for a year at $StateU versus one semester at Chatham! Their tuition is so much lower, the professors are excellent, and they have an IS program with a concentration in the area that I am interested in - Geographic Information Systems. I am hoping to work for an environmental org. if possible once I am done. My entire life I have been passionate about the environment, but I sort of "fell into" my IT job. I am only one class shy of an associate in networking, and after working at an ISP for 5 years, I have a good entry-level resume, and I hated to just negate all of my technical background to pursue a different degree. I also did not want to start over and have to be in school for another 4 years.  Right now it is looking like I will be at $StateU for another 2 years, hopefully not more than that. I am behind now because I took a semester off after mom passed away, but I really needed to. I am going to take it easy this semester - just take 12 credits at $StateU, get my easy liberal arts reqs out of the way, and take my last remaining evil math class at $CommunityCollege so I can get my associates, finally! I am so bad at advanced math that I think I have a phobia about it....I mean, I've put off taking that math class for 2 years! Yikes.  Oooh, that is another thing about the whole situation with the bitch that pissed me off.....I had signed up at Westmoreland County Community College to take the math class I needed, then transfer it to CCAC. As soon as I can get that math class out of the way and have my associates, I can get into a shorter program at $StateU for the field I am interested in. Shorter program = less money to have to pay back = happy me!  So that brings me to my intended topic - financial aid! I got enough financial aid to cover all of my expenses this school year. If I could continue to keep working full-time during the semester and take evening classes, then I could use this semester's refund to COMPLETELY WIPE OUT MY CREDIT CARD DEBT! Then, I could use next semester's refund to wipe out most of one of my student loans!!!!!! That would be a fucking miracle for me!!!!!! I would feel so much better to get all of that debt out of the way.  And the thing is - I think I have a way to do it! A few years ago, $ISP started an offshoot org that did online sports broadcasting, and I was the original person to handle the position of tracking and editing the game feeds, and troubleshooting the connections with the radio station board ops and the broadcasters in the field. Well, the company was mismanaged and it went under - we were laid off three days after Christmas of 2000. :( (Bastards! But I got a nice severance package though.) Then, in another stunning example of my bad luck, one of the kids that *I* had trained was hired for the job by the company that bought $SportsDept. He worked there for a long time, but was either laid off, fired, or quit back in May of this year. So, I contacted some of the guys there that I used to work with about that position, and they said they'd turn in my resume, but weren't going to hire for it until the end of the summer. So, as long as it's not a conflict with $ISP-Job, I think I have a really good chance of getting back in at $SportsJob.  I am hoping that they would only need me on weekends - I couldn't work full-time there, part-time at $ISP, and do full-time school, I would lose it pretty quick doing that. As long as $SportsJob only needs me 2 or 3 days a week, I can handle doing 2 @ $ISP and 2 days of classes @ $StateU. I wouldn't have much free time, but I think I could handle it better knowing that I was making so much progress with my debts. It sucked working at $Deli this summer because I was getting paid peanuts and not really making any headway, just staying afloat. I think $SportsJob might pay equal to or better than what I am making now @ $ISP - that kind of extra money would mean a hell of a lot to me. I would have so much extra money each month without those damn credit card payments, and my one personal loan that I had to get for school has a payment of $100 per month, but I usually pay $150 because that keeps the interest down. I am getting close to having it under $4,000 - two more months and I will have paid off $1,000 of it! So if I can get that job at $SportsCo., I can use this semester to pay off my CCs - bam, $BigSum less in the hole. Next semester, do the same thing, and pay off $3K of my personal loan. Bam - $BigSum less in the hole! Plus, if $SportsCo would pay me enough, I could probably pay off the rest of the personal loan during the semester. Then all I would have is my regular expenses and my student loans. That would be *amazing*. So, it would take a lot of coordination and hard work on my part, but it would be so, SO worth it. So I am really hoping that $ISP won't tell me it's a conflict of interest, and that the terms are agreeable at $SportsCo and they hire me back.  Oh, it would be so nice to not be in debt anymore!!!! *crossing fingers* I hope this works out.  Well, it is 3:00, and I have been slacking this morning since I got up at noon (I reserve the right to sleep in ridiculously late on Saturdays *grin*), so I had better get going. I need to do my laundry and clean my apartment. I can't stand slobby, messy places, so I try to just keep my place "picked up" (as they say here in the 'Burgh) during the week, and I clean up every weekend. I like to do things that my mom used to do - I try to keep up some of her old rituals. Like, Sunday used to always be fancy-family-dinner day, Thursday was Italian day, Friday was seafood night, Saturday you cleaned, etc. :) That's one thing I've found myself doing....I feel so nostalgic for things from my childhood now. I've tried to make my apartment nice and homey... it is probably so un-hip, but I like it. I have my books, my grandma's antique furniture, my knick-knacks, etc. I leave the oldies station on for the girls when I am not there - Mom listened to oldies all the time and it reminds me of her. I don't really mind it anymore - I used to hate listening to oldies when I was younger, but now it is just music to me.  Well, I am gonna get going - not going to get anything done today if all I do is write in my blog!  Oh yeah- about the DNC: Barack Obama, the Clintons, and Kerry rocked my socks off!! Obama is incredible. Ii hope he runs for president someday, I would totally vote for him. What an inspiring man.  I missed seeing the wives and Edwards, but I am sure they were ok.  I have some links to share:   urlLink Air America Radio  Listen online with RealPlayer, on XM Radio Channel 167, or through your local affiliate if there is one - you can search on their website.   urlLink Kerry Meetups   I also joined my local Kerry list on Yahoo, and am going to try to keep going to these meetups. There is a Dems meetup this Tuesday down on E. Carson somewhere that I am going to try to go to. I need to get more involved with this campaign!  Ok, I am leaving now, honestly! See ya for now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      np: Alice in Chains - "Would?" (This music is exactly fitting my mood this week) -----------------------------  Ugh, I didn't get to bed until 1:30 am last night, and I slept in until 7:15 because I was so tired. I just threw on jeans and an $ISP shirt and packed my breakfast. I was still late! I am late every day. I am terrible about getting up on time and getting to work on time! I made myself stay later today to make up for being late...I really need to go to bed earlier so I can get up earlier. I technically should get up around 6:00-6:15 am if I really want to look nice, do my hair, makeup, etc.  Argh, the kittens are running amok today, especially Luna! She is usually a good girl but she is driving me crazy! ...  Ok, nothing a little play-time won't fix. ;) It's so funny and cute - I have these two long streamers on sticks, and one has a tuft of feathers at the end. I wave it around and they will jump 2-3 feet in the air and twist around trying to catch it. They run around chasing it with their little mouths open and it is so dang cute! :D They get themselves so worked up that they start panting with their little tongues hanging out, then invariably they flop on the floor for about 5 minutes to catch their breath, maybe go play with something on their own for another 15-20 minutes, and then about 1/2 hour later they are snoozing. It's great. :)  ....     Ok, I started writing that earlier and now it is 11:50 PM. Well, I had a just  lovely  evening. Around 8;00-ish maybe, Pat calls me up asking if I had a little cat dish to borrow, because the  downstairs   neighbor 's  cats got out, AGAIN. She and her boyfriend are maybe 2-3 years younger than me, but they are such immature spazzes sometimes - your basic partyer type who doesn't always give much forethought to things, like consequences! Well, my two kittens are the sisters to her kitten and she still has the mama cat, Jingles. After most of the kittens were given homes and the boy kitten, Bristol, was pretty much weaned, of course she got into heat again and was constantly trying to get out. So what does Chastity do? Leaves the windows open and the cats unattended, and I swear Jingles was getting out every time you turned around, and of course she got pregnant again. Sometime before I took the girls, I mentioned to her that Animal Friends here in Pgh has a low-cost spay/neuter program based on your income. She could have called the number and looked into that and been responsible, but she went out camping/partying a bunch of times and spent a lot of money on beer (she was complaining about it the one day about how she blew all her money drinking). She never bothered to stop and think, "Hrm, if I skip the beer/camping for a month, I can afford to get Jingles fixed. And in the meantime, maybe I should keep the windows closed so the cat can't get out." You know? Basic common sense.  So anyway, Bristol was stuck up in a tree down the hillside a bit from our parking lot, and Jingles was nowhere to be found. Luckily as we were trying to get Bristol out of the tree, Chastity and her boyfriend Kevin came back, and Kevin climbed the tree and got Bristol out. Pat was out cleaning out his car, so I figured, what the hell, might as well join him since I needed to clean my car too. (It hasn't been cleaned since before I moved in! Bad me, bad!) Chastity came out to talk to us after a while, and don't get me wrong, she is a nice person and can be really friendly, but sometimes I just want to shake her and give her a smack upside the head! I think she is still in that phase of not really wanting to accept the responsibility/reality of living on your own. She was saying that she hoped Jingles stayed away and someone else found her, because "she has been such a pain in the ass". Well, you moron, if you'd gotten her fixed she wouldn't have tried to get out constantly to obey instincts she had no control over! Now the poor thing has to have another litter of kittens after just having had a litter in March, and those poor kittens will need to have homes found for them. Hopefully the people who adopt them will get them all spayed and neutered, and Chastity will get Jingles spayed. If she doesn't I will do it myself! If I can afford it, maybe I can pay to get them all spayed/neutered through the Animal Friends program. It just breaks my heart to think of how many animals across America are treated exactly the way she takes care of hers. People just don't think sometimes.  Pet overpopulation is the saddest thing, and no animal deserves to have to go through that constantly. There are millions of animals killed every year because they couldn't find homes.   Ok, so anyway, to continue....she was bitching because Kevin did a bunch of car work for a friend of a friend in lieu of owing one of them a bunch of money, or something. They were counting on the car-owner to pay him for the work, because they were going to use that to pay their rent. Well, they aren't getting it and are broke, and got their 10-day eviction notice today. They keep doing this - are late on the rent and make excuses to the landlord and scrape it together at the last minute. But they are still planning on going camping this weekend! I just don't understand people like that. Well,  that got us to talking about friends who don't hold up their end of their bargains, esp. with money, and that kinda got my back up because Pat is the one who said that, and I thought he was making a jab about me owing him that money from when he helped me out with rent money back in June. I had just gotten hired at $Deli and hadn't gotten paid yet from there, so he lent me $300, which I was going to pay back when I could. So that kinda made me mad. The conversation drifted in and out of other topics, and then Tim (Pat's roommate and our friend) came home from work and the three of them started talking and went over to her car. I kept working on my car, and they were over there talking with Chastity, because, of course, they are single guys who will do anything to see tits or ogle a pretty girl, and they always talk about Chastity whenever they get a "look" at something. It really makes me sick sometimes the way they talk (they both sound like dirty old men), but I think Chastity knows they check her out and probably thinks it's funny.  Anyway....  That kind of got me even madder, because shit like that always makes me feel about  this big . With the way I look right now, there is no way I can compete with a girl like her, and it makes me so mad! I just hate how our society pits women against each other, and how much it feels like the backlash against women has succeeded, esp. for younger women my age and under. There is SO MUCH PRESSURE now to be a thin little hottie who wears a thong all the time and looks like they just stepped out of a Cosmo ad. Pgh is overrun with so many little yuppie princesses who can afford to look perfect that someone like me just has no chance. It makes me so angry, angry for more than one reason, because no one would give me a second glance with the way I look right now. I also get so angry at myself for letting myself get to this point....but that is where my struggles with depression and low self-esteem and my ridiculously fucked-up life come into play. You can only go through so many hellish experiences before they break you and you give up on caring about anything, including yourself.  I feel like, "I don't deserve to be passed over all the time", but then I have to face reality - people don't like to "settle" for someone who looks like me when there are so many girls out there who are willing to go the extra mile to look good and be attractive. I understand that a person is only going to be attracted to a certain "type", and maybe I am just not that type. Maybe it is my personality, too, or I am too shy to make a move when I think someone might dig me, despite my size. I don't know. I have too much of a reflex now to protect myself from being hurt and embarrassed, so maybe I flinch away from situations now where I could meet people. That is one thing my friend Pat doesn't understand - Gods forbid he ever reads this blog, but he prides himself on always telling the truth, so maybe he could appreciate it - if you don't take care of yourself, and expect someone to like you, that's just not going to work. For all that people think "it's what's on the inside that matters", that is definitely true, but if you aren't even slightly attracted to the person's outside, then nothing is going to happen! At least for me, I have to find *something* attractive in a person for anything to happen. With Pat, he wears schlumpy clothes, doesn't do anything with his hair, doesn't try to look good, doesn't watch what he eats, etc. He is paranoid about people making fun of him because his left arm is shortened by birth - it only goes down to a little past the elbow. (I think his mom was given that drug that caused all those birth defects - I can't remember the name offhand.) But no one really cares about his arm after they meet him. I think if he lost some weight, did something with his hair, tried to look nice, etc., he would look a lot better, and maybe then someone would want to go out with him!  That is why, although I try to look nicer now and take care of my appearance, I am overweight enough that I have to be realistic that it would probably have to take a miracle for me to find someone who would find me attractive right now despite my weight.  Another thing that irritates me is that Pgh seems to be overwhelmingly full of jock-type guys. I love smart, nerdy guys, and I have a weakness for goth boys. :) I'm still a goth at heart, but it is hard enough being fat where I live that being a fat goth will just get you shit on that much worse. So I try to be minimalist about it. ;) I still wear lots of black, still listen to the same music, etc., but I toned my look down a lot because I was so tired of the negative attention I got. A thin goth girl is considered sexxee by most guys, but a fat goth girl definitely isn't. :(  Anyway...I keep getting on these big tangents!.....when they were over there talking to her, that made me feel crappy and I got angry, so I finished up my car and drove off to go to the car wash, then I decided I would drive around a little and listen to my new CDs. (Still doing the Alice in Chains CD right now!) I also decided I would stop at a mac machine and get Pat the money I owed him and slip it under their door when I got home, just to make a point. (The points being twofold - a.) here's your damn money, and b.) don't piss me off!) When he got back from going to the carwash himself, he figured I was pissed off and came down to talk to me. So we started talking and then I got all upset and started crying, just because I feel so overwhelmed with stuff this week.  Part of it is about Mom, part about Stacey (The Bitch), part this I-am-so-tired-of-feeling-unattractive-and-socially-shunned-and-being-single phase, part of it money worries....I had to ask to get the balance on my new credit card raised to cover my balance transfer and the few things I bought, and then I had to go and run the card back up that I did the balance transfer on, because I had all of these bills come all at once. I had to pay $228.59 for my health insurance (it went up about $40), and I had a dentist bill come that I had forgotten about for $100. I also had to pay for my first installment of my rental insurance, my phone bill, I needed cat supplies and groceries, etc., etc. I have to pay my rent two weeks late to boot. :( Well, they gave me a hefty balance increase, and I had enough on it to get Pat his money, so I figured, what the hell. I am already in debt up to my eyeballs between my credit cards and student loans, so at least I might as well pay Pat back and have one less thing to prey on my mind. Now I only have to pay my dad back, and start a payment plan for these CCs. At least on my new CC, there is no interest for something like 6 mos. to a year, so that's good!  I have to schedule my classes and am still waiting to hear if I can get any grants from the state, but hopefully I will get a good refund this semester. If I can swing it, I will pay my rent and health insurance, get my books, and then whatever is left I will throw on my CCs. I have (eeek!) three to pay off. :/ I know, bad me! I just never seem to have enough money to go around, and then I get hit with a big bill for something, and that is why I keep having to use my CCs to cover what I am not making in my paychecks. At least, I cut the one up, and I think I will try to pay that one off first. After that I will cancel the account. Then I will pay off my first CC, and pay half of the one with the non-interest. I should be able to chip away at it during the semester, and then with next semester's refund, I can pay it off. I want to get down to just one CC with a low balance, maybe something like $300. It is just way too easy for me to get into massive CC debt and buy things I can't afford. I have been in this cycle of credit card debt for probably a good 8-10 years now, and I just can't afford to live the rest of my life like this! Heck, even if I have to pay my health insurance out of my pocket during the semester, if I can just cover my rent and pay off my major CC, that will be a huge step in the right direction.  This of course does not mean that I don't have a ton of other things that I have to pay for and can't afford, but that's another deal for later!  Ok...to finish my little saga, Pat came down to try and give me the money back, and like I said we started talking and I just got all worked up and started crying about all this stuff. I think Pat was kinda freaked out in the "oh-no-helpless-man-crying-girl" way, but at least he listened and tried to offer some constructive criticism.  *sigh* My life feels so overly complicated at times, and ridiculously simple at others. I think I just need to find someone compatible and have a friend-with-benefits. There's (almost) nothing wrong that a little sex can't help! ;)  Oh man, one of the kittens just took a shit and it is stinking up the whole apartment....ewwww! LOL...ok, gotta go do potty duty and then take a shower and go to bed. See what I mean about not going to bed before 1:00 am this whole week?!? Bad me, bad, bad, bad.  Night!  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I swear, I will not get to bed before 1:00 am any time this week! Bad me.    I wanted to write about something kinda funny - remember Quasi-Admin Boy from my first post to this blog? Well, I think Quasi-Admin Boy has just noticed that I have breasts and am, like,  female and stuff. ;-)   Since I am doing the front desk now and working upstairs full-time, I have been trying to dress nicer for work, instead of my usual jeans-and-a-shirt combo. I have a few shirts from Lane Bryant that are scoop-necks or v-necks, and since I currently am rather well-endowed in the bosom department, you know, those kind of shirts make things, ahem, more apparent? So I was sitting downstairs in Admin-Friend's office working on a laptop again (still trying to finish getting those old ones wiped and updated!), and Q.A.B. came in. He was talking to Admin-Friend but I kept noticing him looking in the general direction of my chest....Every time I would glance over he would look away really quick! So I don't know if some portion of his brain was like, "Wow, Cathy has tits...." or like, "Horrors! Cathy is actually female and actually has tits and I just noticed, bad thoughts, bad thoughts!" (Considering how I have been treated by some guys in the past, I don't really hold my hopes up that any one would actually find me attractive. Most guys, in my experience, don't like smart, fat, slightly-pretty girls. Can you tell that I desperately need to find a different crowd to hang in?!?)  So anyway....QAB's sort of knee-jerk look-there's-boobs reaction struck me as really funny, because normally he seems like the type who would never do something like that consciously in front of a chick, at least not unless he was at a bar or something!  Well, today I was dressed up again with one of my lovely cleavage-enhancing shirts, and I had my hair loose instead of tied back like I normally wear it at work. I've been growing my hair out for at least a year or two now and it has gotten extremely long - it's probably 5 inches above my behind now - it's so long! :) I was standing at the fax machine faxing some contracts and he stopped and asked, "Hey, have you been growing your hair out?" I said, "Yep, for a while now! But I usually keep it tied back." He said something to the effect that he never noticed it was that long before and that was it. I smiled a little about it, though. I felt like, wow, *someone* is finally noticing that I'm female along with being a computer geek, you know? It feels nice to be noticed for my (ok, admittedly usually well-hidden) feminine side for once instead of just "Cathy is the computer geek/ the brain/whatever". When you are fat, most people, especially guys my age, sort of uncomfortably try to ignore the fact that I am female, or at least that is how it feels to me. You are invisible, like a neuter - you can hang with the guys if you can keep up with them, but they won't acknowledge your femininity. It's like, I feel like I had to sacrifice that side of my self to succeed in the tech side of things at work and be respected as a techie, and that makes me mad sometimes.  Anyway, I digress. So, today QAB was giving a presentation on DNS and mail. I figured I would go and listen because I sometimes handle the abuse-related callbacks (ppl with viruses, businesses being blocked by the various spam filters, etc.). He kept looking at me *the whole time*. I would look up and notice that he was looking at me and he'd look away. It was so awkward. I don't know what is going on here!  I feel so awkward trying to play the flirting game because of the way I look now.....I have got to look so unattractive and gross because of how overweight I am. I haven't dated any one "in so long it doesn't matter anymore", and although I have been trying a bit harder to look nice, I have a loooooong way to go to lose the amount of weight I want and reach a weight where I feel comfortable in my own skin again. I am sure I am my own worst critic, and maybe someone out there would like me despite my size (someone I would find attractive in return, hopefully!), but I feel so uncomfortable trying to be flirty at all. I just want to huddle in a corner somewhere and be unnoticed. I mean, anymore, being fat in this culture is like being a leper, what with the "War On Obesity" and all going on currently. You might as well shoot yourself and spare yourself the misery. So I don't try to flirt, don't try to show I am interested, etc. Yet my damn ego still wants to play delicious little games of attraction and have someone spellbound over me....I want to seduce someone! There's that Scorpio thing again!   LOL   So, Lord only knows what QAB is up to. I am probably misreading it wrong, as always, and just making a big deal out of nothing. But he *was* looking at my chest the other day! I am probably confusing the poor boy.   I swear, if I could get over my self-esteem issues and get in better shape and actually feel confident about myself, I could knock some socks off. In the meantime I just have to concentrate on improving myself as best I can.  Ok, I am so tired I am started to feel sick, must.peel.self.away.from.computer!   Goodnight! (Again!)          
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       np: The Cure - "Labyrinth" - new album (yay yay yay yay!) ----------------------------------------------------------------------- Well, shit, I haven't written on here in ages! So much has happened since I wrote here last.  Best.News.Ever: THE BITCH GOT FIRED!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  She sent me an email from a Yahoo account titled "ihatework2005@yahoo.com", and the username was "tech supporttech" - can you even type, you moron? The gist of the email was: "Rumor has it that so-and-so is going to be promoted to X_position in X_month_of_year. I recall that you put in for X_position last year and were denied. The official reason was far different from the one given behind closed doors. Apparently no female techs were considered.  Could it be that $Employer is on a precipece (sic) of toeing the line between legal and illegal discrimination towards female techs?  Concerned."  So, I print it out and show it to my manager - I looked closer at the headers and saw that Yahoo shows the originating IP now...and just take a WILD GUESS whose IP it was?!? Yep, you guessed it - she sent it from her work computer, *during work hours*. And we work AT AN ISP!!!! How much of a barking moron do you have to be to do something like that?!? Why the hell would she think I would want to fucking help her in the first place? I have no idea why she would send that - my first guess was that she was trying to trap me into saying something bad about $employer, and then would use that against me. I can't believe that she would actually think I wouldn't be able to figure out who sent it (the style/wording, poor typing, and misspelled word all screamed that she wrote it), and honestly - did she think she could appeal to my feminist side or something for help? Good grief. Part of me wonders too if it was her pathetic attempt at trying to maybe make amends in some way - too chicken to apologize to me herself, so she tries to appeal to my sympathy with a poorly-concealed anonymous email to get me talk to her again? Who freaking knows. I don't care.  The sad thing is, thanks to the cushion of time and distance, I was starting to feel less angry towards her a little bit. Of course it is a sad thing when you lose a friend...but when you are betrayed and turned on by someone you considered one of your best friends...you never really forget that. Any time I would start to feel like I was softening up any, or feeling nostalgic for our friendship, I only had to stop and think of how wretched my life was thanks to her, from the time surrounding my mom's death up until only a month or so ago. Those 5-6 months, I wouldn't wish on my worst enemy - which is probably her at this point! Even thinking about that time period makes my insides writhe in anguish. That is why I have thought all along, there is *nothing* I could possibly do or say to make her feel as wretched as she made me feel....  But she went and handed the solution to me on a platter!  Ah, glorious day!  I think the email was the last straw for her, really. She had gotten written up once in March or so, while I was still living there. (I was renting a room off of her in her house.) Then, after she "kicked me out" - the Monday after I moved out, in fact - she blabbed to everyone in the tech dept. about how she "KICKED (me) OUT!" and all this other crap about me - basically being little miss Drama Queen. The tech mgr. had to take her aside and tell her to "knock it off"....plus she was being watched by the dept. due to ongoing mistakes (which, after being there for 4 years, she ought to know better) and due to attitude issues. The performance and attitude issues were why she was fired. I think the email was just the icing on the cake.  One thing that really made me feel better was that the tech mgr. told me that she thought I really handled the situation well, "with dignity" was how she put it. That meant a lot. Goddess knows I have been so furiously angry over this whole situation, but I really did try to keep it cool at work and not spread it around the office. Anyone I saw who she might have talked to, I just pulled them aside quietly and told them that if they wanted to hear my side of the story they could talk to me privately. I did tell a few people, maybe 3 or 4 who I trust, and the managers of course.  I am just so relieved that it is over! I wish I could erase the whole friendship and living at the house and all the bad shit from my memory. I swear I have post-traumatic stress from it. She has turned into this bogey-moster in my mind, and I hate it that she was able to affect me this way. I still to this day, 3 months later, feel so wretchedly, painfully hurt by what she did to me. My sympathetic/empathetic side keeps wanting to feel sorry for her/pity for her, because I really think that all of her problems stem from whatever psychosis she has - and she didn't get strange until she quit taking her antidepressant, then the real person started to show. After she quit taking her antidepressant, it went downhill from there, and of course after my mom died, that was really the end of our friendship. I hated her for the fact that she was so pathetically unable to do anything for me or be there for me after my mom died. In the letter I wrote back to her in response to her "Dear Jane, move the fuck out" letter that she wrote me (yes, she *wrote me a letter* asking me to move out, she was too cowardly to face me and talk to me about it like an adult), I said that the way she treated me after my mom died was "unforgivable" and that "death was apparently an inconvenience to her". Then there was the shit she pulled with the cats, and her refusing to pay me back for the carpet I put in, or the rest of my rent money, etc. After all of that, only a fucking crazy person like her could think that I would ever in a million years lift a finger to help her.  (np: The Creatures - "Say Yes!" - Hai)  All I have to say is this:  PAYBACK'S A BITCH, AIN'T IT?!  She got fired last Wednesday, and every day since then has been so great. Maybe it reflects poorly on me to feel such glee that she finally got what she deserved, but you know, so what. It's so nice to go in to work and not have to worry about her being there. I feel like I can go into work and just relax and be myself now. I just hope I can shake the taint of this whole miserable experience sooner rather than later, and get on with my life. I still feel caught in some way, like I am still expecting her to do some other hideous thing to me, but she can't now. I am so glad, so glad this is all over finally. I hope she has to work two jobs like I did....Mandy (my best friend) was like, "I hope she loses her house!" I am trying to be the better person here, so I don't really want that - I think losing her job is the best payback/justice I could ask for. I don't want her to lose her house or car or anything else - all I really hoped for was that a.) she would find a different job and quit, and b.) something would happen to her to make her realize how terrible her actions were and how much she lost by her actions, and c.) she would regret what she did for the rest of her life! (Ok, maybe that's a little dramatic, but hey. I will have to live the rest of my life with the hurt and the memories of how that bitch make my life a living hell when I was already going through the hell of losing my mom. I literally can't think about losing my mom without also thinking of how she treated me and how much worse she made everything. When I think of that....that is when I start thinking really vengeful thoughts! But to be fair and not wish too much bad karma on her, I just hope she has to work, like, 2-3 jobs to get by and struggles all alone like I had to, and realizes how her actions have come back on her full force.  Honestly, she really must have had some hubris to think that she could just keep fucking up at work and coast on by, and no one would notice. You'd think for someone who was living paycheck-to-paycheck and already struggling with bills, and who had a house to pay for, that she would have tried harder to find another job, or else check her attitude at the door when she got to work and just did what she needed to get by until she *could* find another job. What a dumbass!  So, anyway, that is my 'Saga of the Bitch Getting Fired'. I am still awfully tempted at times to send a "neener-neener" email, but I won't. I refuse to contact her or show any reaction at all. My friends and I are dying of curiosity to know what she has done since she got fired, but I will never know and I don't really care anymore. I just need to quit obsessing over my lust for revenge and get on with things. I think I have gotten the best revenge that I could - seeing her get fired!  That's one thing to keep in mind....don't piss off a Scorpio! We may have to bide our time and wait quietly for days, months, or years until our vengeance is complete, but when it is, we will make your sorry life miserable, and you will have to pay the piper, sooner or later! I just think it is great that she did this to herself. Now *THAT* is poetic justice!  ....  Ok..whew...I think I have finally talked myself out on this subject! I think I need to do some kind of banishing spell to get rid of any lingering connection - it might help me get over the hurt of it. I just need to quit obsessing on it - that is one of my bad tendencies, to worry at a problem/situation like a dog gnaws at a bone. It is in the past, and nothing I can do will change it, make it better, make it hurt less, etc. I am just grateful that she is gone for good and I never have to see her again. Thank God/dess for small mercies.  Well, I have to go get ready for bed - I'll try to write more tomorrow maybe! I need to keep up with this. I still have a lot to say about the DNC and the Kerry campaign. :)  Goodnight!         
     

    
</post>


</Blog>