<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I met a boy. He is very handsome. I starting talking to him in a very ackward way but whatever. Well I wasn't going to explain this but I think I will. He was sitting at a table in a pub by himself. I thought he looked attactive so I went up to him. Maybe now is a good time to say I was quite tipsy. ANYHOW- I went up to him and said, "Are you lonely?" ugh - doesn't that sound horrible? I felt like a dirty old man. Really though I was just going to ask if he wanted to join my friends and I but it came out badly. After I said that he looked at me like I had 3 heads and said something like No- I am not lonely I am just having a beer. I walked away feeling rejected and humlimated.  I thought that was over when I was leaving the bar to hit another joint up the street. He was outside smoking and I went up and apoligized for being such a loser. When he actually starting chatting with me. He came with me to the next bar and we chatted somemore. Eventually, we kissed with a promise of a phone call.   Now when most times the "promise of a phone call" does not always work out but this time he did call. He asked me to go to his "studio" to watch him "jam". Incase you didn't clue in he is in a band. So I went we hung out and it was all very comfortable. He is quite nice. We hung out a few times since and it is nice. BUT   We were out the other nite and he said he has "Something to tell me" I start freaking out in my mind. What the hell is this something???? Could he have a girlfriend? Be married? Be Gay? What the hell! I ask him what it is and he tells me. He is 19. Now when we first met, he told me he was 22. I am 26 and thought that was even a little iffy. BUT 19? That one is hard for me to handle. I don't know what to do? I have seen him since and it is nice but everytime I am not with him I have thoughts of how big of an age gap that is. Really I have done a lot since I was 19. I am now a totally differant person!   I am going to take it slow. I mean I am leaving in October anyway headed for scotland so it is not like it is going to be long term or anything. We will see. The more time I do spend with him though, the more I like him.   Well that is enough for now,  MJ
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well- I had a good weekend. I did work at my part-time job both Saturday and sunday night but that's okay. Saturday was such a great day. It was sunny and not too hot (but I did get a bad sunburn!) I had a great brunch at a wonderful huge patio with my sister. Then we went for a long walk and for some reason there was bands playing outside everywhere we went. We bumped into this huge event at a park and we hung out there for a while. It was nice.  I went to work after that and had an okay shift. After which I went home where my sister and friend were waiting- drank wine - a lot of wine and then we went out. It was so fun. My friend and I danced at this late nite club until 5 in the morning! Lots of groddy men there were trying to hit on us but we didn't care and we just danced and danced. Great NIGHT!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am back at work after taking 2 days off. I did actually get really sick. I missed two glorious sunny days while I was coughing in bed too. damn. Now it is almost the weekend though which is nice. I am going to go to Scotland in September. I am going to do it which means I have to save save save. Saving money is a very hard thing for me to do. I don't know why it is so hard. I don't know where the money goes to be honest. I really have to quit smoking. That is where I waste money. Why the hell do I smoke anyways. It is so nuts. It is stupid! Anyone that starts smoking now, in this day and age must be fucking insane. (I started smoking when I was 16 that was almost 10 years ago) Holy shite I am getting old.  My work is very boring lately and there is a woman who sits by me who screams on the phone! How annoying. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God- I hate having colds- especially in the summer. It is 32 degrees outside. I only have to work a half a day today (I am taking 1/2 a vacation day because well there is no reason) and lo and behold- I feel like shite. I have a horrible cough that I try to calm down with smoking but for some reason that is not working very well.  I haven't eaten since lunch time yesterday and I am still not very hungry but my stomach is making a lot of strange noises. I think I may break down and eat some carbs today. Some comfort food.  Anyway- I am going to try not to let this get me down! I am still going to make the most of this day. Maybe it will pass in the next 2 hours.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just seeing if is how you work this thing. Testing :)
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello there world. This is pretty exciting. I hope I will be better at this than I am in my written Journal. I guess I am going to start off with a question and I rather odd request- here it goes: Currently I am sitting at my desk at work- pretending to do work. It is a slow day so I am not feeling particularly guilty  (which is an emotion I am very familiar with) To the untrained eye one would think I have achieved quite a bit at this point of my life. I have gradated Uni with my BA in International Development- I worked overseas in South East Asia for about 9 months- and now I work at the non profit which inspired me to go into development work in the first place. That sounds pretty good. What is my deal you may ask?  I have no freaking idea. I do not feel very content in my life. Currently, I am also working at a waitress in a funky little Thai restaurant to save up money to go traveling in UK and Europe in september which means I will leave my job to become a bum. ahhh well.   What I want to know is IS THIS A GOOD DECISION FOR ME? I do want to state at this point that I am not currently at the position I want to be at in the organization if that makes a difference.   My goodness, why does my first Journal entry have to be so depressing. I will stop going on now - If anyone comes across this and has any insight let me know! Because this is new and exciting. I may write more later on today.   Love ya later, mj
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I notice my last blog was speaking of the boy I met. Well, that is over now. It turns out he was an drunk. I mean listen to this.  We were going to the movies in the afternoon with some of my friends. The boy comes to my house just finishing a mickey of whiskey. Now come on, is that really necessary? Also I am leaving for Scotland soon so I didn't want to start anything too crazy. OH and the biggest shocker- this lead singer of this band was a .....VIRGIN.  Now I have nothing against virgins but at this time in my life I really don't want to be anyone's first.   TYPE SOON MJ 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>