<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (((Sigh))) Well, here it is a Holiday weekend & I thought I had plans...several diffrent ones actually, but a couple fell through & the last one (which is the one I was lookin the most forward to doin) isn't lookin to well either. But I'm still hopin'.  I can't really beleive I'm gonna lay this out there like this...but..hey..I guess that is what this blog thing is all about. But right now..& quite frequently, I feel soooo alone. None of my friends would ever guess that I feel this way. (I tend to cover it up pretty well) See, I'm one of those that doesnt like to let people see what some people call, the weak side. But I'm not sure really where the lonliness comes from. It started gradually when I met someone. & only GOD knows why I am attracted to this person. lol But, over the last few months I have had to admit to myself that I am really in love with this person. & the sad thing is..is that I know, & have known, that there is absolutly no future for either of us in this relationship. We've known this from the begining. & no, he's not married.  Thats about as much as I can talk about it right now...if I go on, I'll just end up sitting here crying for hours, & beleive you me, I have about enough of that shit to last me the rest of my life. lol   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Well, I jus found out today that, (not really sure what to call him,19 months ago, he was my boyfreind). Ok, let me start at the begining, lol.     I was dating this guy, we had been dating about 6 months, when he was sentenced to 5 yrs(only has to serve 1\3) for something that happpend b4 we were together. I managed to stay faithful for about a year and a half. (That is when I met Cap) But that is a whole nother posting)    Anyway, its 19 months later (since he went in) & I jus found out hes getting out tomorrow. Not sure how to explain the mixed emotions.     But Trouble,(muh side kick) jus sighned on and her box is flashin, so I will finish this later.     
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ben 13JuL69~23Apr/04  I'll C U @ the Crossroads...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Muh Baby Doger&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me n Captain&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        But one thing that does make this a whole lot easier...is I know I'm not in this alone. I am one of the lucky ones that inherited somwhere along the way, a bull headed best friend, that, despite her own trials and tribulations, still manages to put in just as many, if not more hours, on my research then I do.  Well, her lil screen is flashin at me so I better answer it....Cause ...hahahah she aint that far away from me right now...and when she calls....lol...Well, I think you know.     ong>  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hmmmmm...Well, here I sit, again.  Not sure where to start...I'm sure no matter where I start from, I will surely loop back around several times.  But then that should put us all on about the same page..(you'll be just about as confused as I am)..I said..JUST ABOUT.  However, there is one person out there that I know of, that not only will she be able to keep up with all this confusion, she'll even be able to explain it to me. lol...{{{you know who u are}}}      WHEWWWWWWW!!!! With all that out of the way, I have now decided that I really don't want to get into all that mess right now..lol...So I think I'll go back to surfin the net, & tryin to keep muh mind off Cap. (again...I promise to explain it all later)  lol 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Dannnnnnnnng it....lol.. I can nebba remember muh sign on name or password .  Takes like 30 minutes for me to get here, & by that time, I'm not in the mood to post anything of substance.  LOL..not that there is much of that in the first place.     Welllll...let's see, what have I been up to lately?  Well, I am back on AOL again..hee hee,  & I'm really enjoying chattin with muh old roomies again,  didnt know how much i missed them...till I returned.  lol...& I'm also REALLY enjoyin the new roomies to.   (uhhem)  Lmao...I'm gonna let THAT  go at that.....for now....hahah..      Well, thats about all I have time for right now,  I need to get off here and go pay muh phone bill...or I wont be on here very much longer.  lmao                                                 LaterZ...          Till Then,                                                                             Miss Dondi         
     

    
</post>


</Blog>