<Blog>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The bank will still be open. It makes me so mad that we had to be open today even though the PRESIDENT himself told people to observe President Reagan's funeral by closing. The Post office is closed, the stock market, and other federal government offices - so why not the bank? Everybody and their brother was calling today too asking if we were open...I wonder what these people are thinking when they actually ask me "Are you open?". Well, nothing closes the bank, except for holidays. Once, there was an electrical wire on fire in the street that was attached to our bank, but did we close, or even evacuate? Hell no...On September 11th when people were sent home from their jobs was I one of them? No way...I figured the terrorists would bomb banks before the E-Check. (Well, I won't tell you WHAT I think should be done with the E-Check)Like I said before, it could be full blown Armageddon, with God and Satan fighting each other outside the front doors, with the sky raining fire,the four horses of the apocalypse, and the righteous being taken to heaven, but the bank will STILL be open! Well, I guess it won't matter to me, because when that last trumpet sounds...I'm outta here!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's some things I've noticed I've been doing since working at the bank:  1) I tend to put all my bills I have in order rather than shove them in my pocket or purse in no order. 2) I have all the bills facing the same way, and in some cases, in order of their issue date  3) I count back money like a teller when I'm out in public 4) I wonder if the business I'm buying something at has a checking account with us. 5)I look to see if old boyfriends, girl friends, teachers, friends, etc, have EVER had an account with us. 6) I now appreciate my bank teller. 7) I love the ATM, because it gives me less work to do. 8) I've opened numerous amounts of accounts I don't really need. 9) I've grown more humble 10) My tongue hurts more since I have to bite it all the time to keep from saying something that could get me fired. 11) There are a LOT of cute guys with NO money 12) There are a LOT of ugly guys with TONS of money 13) The bank isn't out to get all your money 14) I file everything now at home and at work 15) I'm anal retentive when it comes to my teller window being clean 16) I will probably be one of those "lifers" 20 years from now
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just received a tip from my boss on what to put on today's blog. Money, and how filthy it is. Everyday, I probably have thousands of dollars passed through my hands and I'm surprised I haven't died of a funky disease yet. Do you really know where that money's been? Well, first of all, lemme tell you what kinds of money I've gotten. Of course, there's dirty money, money that is stained with coffee, sticky pop or koolaid, or even ice cream. Next would be wet money. I used to work at an amusement park that's well known and lemme tell you - money from the customers in the water park tends to be wet. Then I've had sweaty money - money that's been in a gym sock or in someone's back pocket (Let's hope!) Then there's the blood stained money...I feel like I need one of those biohazard suits to take bills like that..what's worse is when your customer is bleeding and gives you the bills tainted with their DNA. I've also received stapled money, money taped up with duct, scotch, packing, and even surgical tape. Then there's smelly money (This could also be linked to the money that's sweaty), this money reeks of cigarettes mostly, but sometimes coffee (especially if your boss spills their coffee on a $2000 pack of twenties), mold, moth balls, old mattress, and even marijuana. You sometimes are getting a secondary buzz off these bills. And speaking of drugs, I was told once that there's approximately 1 gram of cocaine on $20,000 worth of $1 bills. Well, we have a customer that brings in thousands upon thousands of dollars worth of $1 bills (they own vending machines) and we have to run them through our counter to make sure they're right. So...in review of this, and if that urban legend is true, we're all probably high at work..No wonder *sniff* I always *sniff* feel like I'm *sniff* going through withdrawal *sniff* after work! LOL :)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm sort of stealing this idea from David Letterman, but I thought I'd give it a whirl. Top 10 complaints I've heard this week:  10) Why do I have to have an account here to get something notorized? 9) Why do I have to write a check to myself to get cash out of my CHECKING account? 8) Why am I on Chex Systems? I don't even remember having a bank account... 7) Why do I have to be banking to park in the bank's parking lot? 6) Why can't I just give you all this loose change? I know how much is here... 5) Why don't you all have a drive-thru? 4) Why aren't you all open longer? 3) Why aren't you all open on Sundays? 2) Why aren't there more of your branches in town?  And the number one complaint of the week: 1) Why do I have to pay a fee to cash my pay check here? My job has an account with you guys?  Thank you...I'll be here all week...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was boring. Nothing special. It felt literally like I had cobwebs or better yet mold growing on me in my teller window. Every once in a while, spirits would lift if someone accidently brought a cicada in with them but that was about it. Sometimes, between the hours of 3 and 5 I swear I can hear crickets chirping because it's so quiet! We were working with a skeleton crew today too; a lot of our people are out of town. Lucky people...watching grass grow might have been more exciting than sitting there staring at the same stupid pictures I look at everyday.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Do you know how many times I hear that in the course of a day? Too many times to count. How is it that a couple of numbers are so hard to memorize? What makes me sick is those who NEVER know their account number. I have a customer, let's call him Savings Account man, who comes in EVERYDAY to take money out of his savings account. Our bank CHARGES him every month for too many withdrawals, yet does this phase him? By no means! And it's petty amounts of money...why can't you just withdrawal it all at once and pace yourself? AND HE NEVER HAS HIS ACCOUNT NUMBER. To make matters worse, I know his account number by heart. How pathetic is that? Well, Thursday last our computers joined the 21st century by getting high speed internet. That meant the computers were down for about an hour or so. This one guy came to teller006's window and didn't know his account number. As Nelson Muntz would say on "The Simpson's"...HA HA! He was spazzing, cause he needed money. Oh, boo hoo, that's why we tell you people to take the account number card and keep it. Not because we don't like to look up your account number, but because of something like this, a time where the computer's are down. Another girl came in with her ATM card and her valley girl voice speaking something like this, "Uh yeah, I tried to use the ATM to get my money...and it like doesn't work...can you give me money? Uh...no Alicia Silverstone lookalike...unless you have an account number! The best smart aleck remark I gave someone one day was this: They told me they didn't know their account number. I said, "Well, I know my account number...why don't I put your money in my account!" They took an account number card...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There are cicadas in the lobby of our bank! And these would be the 17 year ones that come to visit, are loud, and are horny! I crunch on at least one a day since their untimely invasion. And the customers are bringing them in! And what do they do? Flick them off, and boom! They're on the floor of our bank. Imagine what a cicada is thinking: I've been waiting for 17 years to have sex, and now, I'm going to die in this bank lobby. What a life! I tried to talk a live one into opening a 7 day CD because of his short life span, but he never answered me. Hey! I can get referral points for that you know! I'll put your name in our referral book. Is Cicada spelled with a C or a K? LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's a good rule of thumb: Don't date your customers. Now, that man might look hot cashing his paycheck, but you have no idea what you're getting into. What makes it a whole lot worse is when feelings get involved. I went out with one of my customers once. Now, a customer is a person that you cash their check, put money in their account, and take money out. Cuties that come in for change I don't count ;)Er, uh, I mean, well, let me get back to the story. I decided this guy was dating material for some reason or other. But my co-workers (God bless them) didn't see that. Well, in a nutshell, I got hurt, and I haven't heard from him in a month. And they knew about it, but let me get hurt. He always screwed up his account too. That should have been an indicator of bad things. My one co-worker, teller006 suggested that I look at a man's stock portfolio before I decide to date him. :) Now, that's a nice suggestion, but I just need to be wise next time. But I'm so over the ex customer. Infact, I can say that with honesty. He hasn't been back to the bank since!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      More to complain about since last time. I really hate it that just because I work at a bank, I automatically need to balance my mom's checkbook. I can't even balance my own, and I work there! Infact, it's been almost 2 years since I've done that. Why? I work there, and I can see what's cleared. But her checkbook...yikes! No one can pay me enough to do that! There's all kinds of additions, and it never comes out right anyway. Besides, she has a money market account that bears interest, and she never ever includes that. Even though it's only like 9 cents a statement cycle, it's still money. Well, it doesn't matter anyway, because her math is never right. I almost hate telling people I work at a bank. They start to talk to me about annual percentage yields or some other mumbo jumbo. Hello! That would be the loan officer's job. I especially love the phone calls I answer. The one's that win the emmy of course are the ones after you answer the phone the customer starts rattling off a bunch of numbers (who knows - it might be their account, social security number, date of birth, how many times they've had sex this week?). First and foremost: Our bank no longer gives out account balances over the phone. Why you ask? Well, there's this lovely thing called the Patriot Act that was passed in November of 2002 I think that says, in a nutshell, that the information is private and can't be given out over the phone. I don't know that's you or not. What if you're an identity theif? LOL...I just love those Citibank commercials. Rest assured, I don't work for them, because I wouldn't have mentioned them by name. But it's true. All they need is an account number, or even better: a social security number and BINGO! I'm gonna buy me some stirrup pants and the mudflaps with the naked ladies on them...ooh mama cita! Well, anyway, another myth about people that work at the bank: we have all kinds of money and/or we take the fees the bank pulls from their account. WRONG! I barely make enough to survive, let alone save. There is no 401K for me, and barely a pension. I think to date, my pension is about 2 months worth of pay. Now I do make more than I would at a burger joint but not much. But to suggest I make 6 figures is ludicrous. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright, I'm back. Lemme tell you about Mr. Big Bucks. I won't give him a name to protect his identity but I'm sure there's more than one of these people, so I'm safe. He has millions of dollars in the bank, there's the first strike against him in my book. Forget about the FDIC rule..there's always over $100K in his account. He ALWAYS wants an account balance, to gloat about his money. He talks about his money. He wants to transfer his money. Wire his money. Get money from a wire. He's a big time business owner. Some big time company; he's the CEO. The bank treats him like royalty, because of his money (Now THAT part makes me sick! How discriminatory!). He gets stuff for FREE because he has money! I never quite understood that, why the ones with money don't have to pay, but the ones without pay through the nose. But Mr. Big Bucks called me today. He's very demanding, wanting to speak with his "private banker", who coincidentally doesn't pick up the phone. Everyone walks on eggshells when he's nearby. I personally get a lump in my throat everytime I see him, afraid I might say something to piss him off and therefore close all his accounts. Does anyone else know someone like this, or is it just me?
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, ok, this is my first post and therefore my first complaint. Lemme first start by telling you the basics..I'm overworked and underpaid...well, who isn't really? I work in a really ritzy neighborhood as a bank teller. Teller number 4, that's me. I endure some of the dumbest people I have ever imagined, and some of these people have millions of dollars. Others, well, I can see why they don't have any money. This is a definitely humbling job, and as a result, it seems like I've gritted my teeth down to nothing. (Just kidding) I see probably close to a hundred people every day, some are VERY attractive looking, and others, well, we need to basically hose the place down after they leave. I try to make humor of my situation, such as this blog writing I'm doing. I can't seem to imagine life without a checking account now, and my once fun job has turned into how many accounts I can sell to Joe Schmo, who has no money and really doesn't need to overdraw his account. The only good thing that happens to me is when I can escape for only a few minutes, to get lunch at a neighborhood restaurant, or sweets at the local ice cream place. A lot of times I get conversation from these countless number of faces I see a day. It seems to me that a counseling degree would have been helpful with this job. I hear everything from divorce (which I went through by the way), to surgeries, to pains in places I've never even heard of, to the desperate and dateless (which is what I also am). All this and money too! Well, there'll be more to complain about soon I promise. I just have to lay the foundation for my complaining, so I don't receive complaints about my complaining. Get it? Good...
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink My friend Sameh's website   urlLink My friend Abby's (wife of Sameh's) website   urlLink If you're a flirt, and a girl, get your FREE email here! ;)   urlLink If you need to know where we all met, click here!   urlLink My dad's band   urlLink To Order Pizza...   urlLink To order wraps...   urlLink And some website I happened to stumble across that I thought was funny...   urlLink Titanic in 30 seconds..and reenacted by bunnies! LMAO! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      To be high when you come into the bank? Today I was sitting there and in comes this man that's had an account with us for a while, and he's higher than a kite...now, I can sort of understand the gen x'ers being stoned...but this man's gotta be at least as old as my dad...mid 50's range...he comes stumbling in today confused (well duh..) about his atm card not working. Here I find out he's put the wrong pin number in, and after 3 times, it'll lock up and not work, because it's for security reasons. I'm surprised as high as he was he even knew what an atm card was...as far as he knew he could have been sticking that card in the doorjam. Well, I fixed the problem and gave him directions on how to fix it himself. But with this man being in my teller window so long I was getting a secondary buzz off of him! I had to literally walk away after he left so I could clear my head. But he's not the only one - a lot of people, young, old, black, white, yellow, red, male and female have come into the bank under the influence of something mind expanding. If not marijuana, it's beer or hard liquor. (I especially love the smell of those people). And I think I might have even seen one come in on an acid trip...of course, my mom was a hippie, and I believe she still has flashbacks...so it's not a big deal...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, today was Tuesday, boring as usual. Nothing even remotely exciting happened, unless you want to count someone being mad at me because I couldn't cash their check. We have a subsidary brokerage corporation that has our logo and bank name on it, and people naturally think they can cash their check here. Well, I'd love to, I hate turning people away, but we have no way of verifying the funds on it, so therefore, we can't cash it. But that's it. No good juicy stories. Oh wait...I did see someone that works with the ex boyfriend/customer I had written about previously. I told him that he (the ex) dumped me and to tell him what I thought about him, in nice colorful metaphors! And you know what? It was VERY cleansing! But that's it. Sorry to the few people who actually read this. But you can tell your buddy's that I'm single! ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Are a pain in the ass! Today, I was informed by our compliance department I hadn't filled one of these out correctly. Oh, by the way, for the person not working at the bank the currency transaction report is something that the government has us fill out when someone brings in over $10,000 in physical cash or cashes a check for over $10,000. And they want to know EVERYTHING about you too. But, needless to say, I didn't fill it out correctly, and that was even with the boss standing over my shoulder to make sure I did it right. First of all lemme say: Who the heck wants that much money on them at one time? If I have only like $300 in my wallet I'm spazzing. But the other day, I was dumped with a ton of money that needed this report. Some people don't like to fill out the form, and they'll either deposit just under that amount (which then would consitute a suspicious transaction report) or they'll flat out leave the bank. But I LOATHE filling out any forms of these kinds, because it's not something that's done all the time, and it's fuzzy to me. But that's my groan of the day, not much more happening in the wonderful ritzy world today. Guess it was too hot to be getting money out or something...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've decided instead of venting, I'd like to share with you something that's happened to our branch this week. One of our customers (and my boss' best friend for that matter) died on Monday night. He was not even 42. But it's been such a shock to us all, because he was what I'd like to call one of my "dailies"..meaning, he used to come into the bank every single day, either to go to lunch with my boss, or to make deposits, or just to drive us crazy! He was a really sweet man, and we're going to miss him terribly. Infact, I just came back from the layout. I wish he knew how many people loved him, and how many people showed up for him. Today even, one of the managers said she thought she heard him in the branch. For all we know, she probably did. I still feel his presence around, and I definitely felt it tonight at the funeral home. But this blog is my tribute to him. So wherever you are, I want you to know that I'm still your flirtygirl, and if you really want to know how I got that scar on my knee, I'll be sure to tell you, but only when we're alone ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love our security guards! All of them..because they do their job. Our bank has a parking lot behind it, and we share it with a realtor, and an eye glass place. The bank owns the lot, and it's considered private property, and not property of the city. Therefore, we have signs posted EVERYWHERE that your car WILL BE TOWED if you are not in the bank, the realtors or the eye glass place. (Well, there's only 2 spots for the eye glass place, and that's for the owners). What's so freakin' hard to understand about this???? Obviously, to the people that are in the ritzy neighborhood, it's about as hard as trying to figure out the pythagorean theorum! Some people think they are "immune" to this rule..because they have an account with us. True, if you're IN THE BANK! I had this person come in the other day, do their banking business, and then left (or so I thought). 20 minutes later, our security guard came in and asked if anyone knew who had this certain car. Well, none of us knew, the person never came back, and the car got towed. And once the car is hooked onto the tow truck..oh well, too bad. And it's about $85 to get it released back to you. Well, about 45 minutes elapsed...and the person came back..and asked me where their car was...and I told them..they about hit the roof! I was cussed up one end to the other...and told to get the car back for them! LMAO..I'm sorry, I have to laugh...it's just too doggone funny. I was also informed by this person that I knew where they were..(they were in the square making jewelry) and I knew what car they had. That's right..I keep track of every customer's car. Well, this takes the cake, and I was informed that they were planning to close their accounts..and that they had more than $100,000 in their accounts..If only I could REALLY tell them what I thought..I would say something to the effect of..."Well, who do I make the check out to???" Well, to make a long story short (too late) the customer never did get their accounts closed, and in fact, gave the manager who drove them to the towing lot a bunch of cupcakes to thank them. But I just love those days when a car gets towed..and we get blamed...even though there are about 150 signs posted...LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is a holiday for the bank, although I really don't understand that, because it's Monday July 5th. Yes, July the 4th was on a Sunday, but the bank's not opened that day anyway, so why the extra day? Anyway, because of a Monday holiday, we'll have like 4x the work to do on Tuesday. That, and a lot of people don't understand holidays when it comes to fund availability and Monday NOT being a business day. It just seems like it's more than it's worth somedays. And tomorrow will be NO exception. One good thing about today: I'm getting paid for 6.5 hours even though I'm not there. And when you work at the bank, you get EVERY holiday aside from Valentine's Day and St. Patrick's Day off. What's wonderful about this year...Christmas Eve falls on a Friday this year, and the bank will be closing at 1pm...mark that down in your calendars now so you won't be crabbing when you hear the news again...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Is when a customer comes up to my window when I haven't asked them to! Today was a classic example of this. I'm in my window doing some transactions that my manager gave me to run, and this customer clearly sees that I'm busy, comes up to my window, and lays his stuff down for me to do. Hello! I did NOT ask you to come up, nor did I say the classic, "May I help you?" Why is it so hard to stay in the lobby until I call you up? Coincidentally, this was "Dude, where's my car's" husband...so consider the source..if you haven't read "Dude..." read it...it's hilarious! Today, at around 3:45, we had the singles man come in...ah, the singles man, I haven't told you about him yet. He owns vending machines, or something..(Could be laundring money, who knows) and he comes in EVERYDAY with thousands of dollars in SINGLES and they all have to be counted in our pathetic 1934 counter we have (I don't know if it's that old, but still)Anyway, he comes rolling in an hour before we close with (get this) thousands of dollars in singles, fives, and quarters! For the love of GOD! I wanted to die! So, for the rest of the day, I was pulling apart these bills (they had hot fudge and God knows what...*see the one on money*)and venting about this man...I'm sure I'll have more to say about him...but what a pisser to the end of the day! :(
     
    
</post>


</Blog>