<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: White vest top, school trousers, odd socks, black net glove.  Listening to: Leader of men-Nickelback Feeling: A lot of things.. Cuts today: just one.  -+-  I trod on one of the kitten's feet today, and he ran of screeching...so mum and dad had a go at me, and I was in floods of tears..something like 'fuck your feelings, think of someone else for a change!'..then my breakfast made a re-appearance..  We had 3 CAT tests today..and if that wasn't enough, one of the questions had a 'kitten' answer, it was all I could do to keep from burstng into tears in the hall..  And I spent my history lesson using a safety pin, trying to cut into my wrist. They're sharp, so it takes alot of pressure to draw blood. So now my wrist is sore and red and painful looking..then when I got annoyed at my lack of will power, I started crying. I cried and cried all lesson, and then after class ran off to sit under 'my' tree. Will came and found me, tried to talk to me, even though I started snapping. In the end I showed him what I'd been doing...and my day got better since. He held me for a while, still talking to me, and trying to pursuade me to go see our head of year and talk to her.  So I did. After school, I went to have a quick chat with her, about most things..it wasn't very long because she had a meeting, so I've got to go back tomorrow morning. My stomach feels all funny..I'm scared what she's going to ask me..but I'm going to see if there's anyway I can see the counciler without mum finding out..(her office is right near reception where mum works --+).  But cat seems okay now..he's not hurt, and being adorable, play fighting with his brother. Still can't tell them apart, grr..  So, that's it. That was one of my better days. Oh I'm pathetic...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Green shirt, black trousers. Listening to: Last resort-Papa Roach Feeling: Hayfeverish, annoyed, tearful, bored, angry, scared, paranoid, depressed. Yes, all at the same time. Cuts today: 3  -+-   Hayfeverish  Grah! It's flared up again today. Not nice. I'm blowing my nose every 2 minutes, sniffing like crazy, my eyes are red, sore and puffy, and I can't strokes the kittens. I'm highly allergic, so it just makes it all worse. Tablets don't seem to have worked today.   Annoyed  I'm such a bitch. People are just trying to me nice to me, and antics I'd usually find funny, and join in with I'm finding highly annoying. So I'm annoyed with certain people around me, and myself. Great start...   Tearful  I've burst into tears over nothing twice today. Once at break when TinTin slapped me on the back, I burst into tears and ran off..then in english when I had to put up with some wanker making comments all through the lesson. And then when I got home, I was on the verge of tears becuase I thought one of the kittens had escaped. False alarm, though.   Bored  I have nothing to do..well, really I do. I have UG shop orders and homework to complete, but I lack willpower and inspiration. I can't be bothered. I really really really can't. It's amazing I've even managed to write this...   Angry  Angry at myself. For being so stupid and nasty and snappy with everyone today. I just..feel like if I don't keep them away, I'll end up getting used, hurt, betrayed...like the super trollop used us all. I hate her. She's a user and a cow and she'll get another back-hander if she  ever  comes near me or my friends again.   Scared  I'm scared...and also disappointed with myself..I found out we have a school counciler, but when I'd been trying to get my courage up enough to ask my head of year if I could see her...I just, couldn't..I feel so ashamed, so stupid..but I'm terrified mum will find out, because I don't trust any of the teachers...they'll tell her, and say it was in my best interests...   Paranoid  Just..grr..I feel like keeping everyne away, so then they can't hurt me..I've hand remindeders of Michelle, and I miss her so much..and that in turn reminds me of how trollop used us, and Michelle...I miss her so much..i dreamt about her, and it upset me so much..   Depressed  Still. Generally. I need to find out about the health centre in town..I hate being like this! I hate snapping at my friends! I hate havbing to monitor everything I say so I don't upset anyone...but still end up doing...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Green nighty, bandana. Listening to: Disney start-up theme. Feeling: Amused. Cuts today: None. I'm laughing to much to cut.  -+-  Okay, okay. Now today at school i just got by, very quiet but... Will did promise he'd come with me when I go to the health centre in town. Other than that nothing major happened, still moody and depressed.  But when I got home er....mum took me aside and confronted me..*hysteric laughter* she's convinced I'm pregnant..who can blame her really? I've been moody, hormonal, I'm no where near skinny, and when me and Will were an item we were practically living in each other's pockets...so I told her, "pregnancy normally involved sex first mum!"  *sigh* so, nothing major to report today. sorry about that.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Red top, black trousers, bandana Listening to: Tourniquet-Evanescence Feeling: Fat, ugly and depressed. Cuts today: 12, shallow. 2 from cat, also.  -+-  Today has not been a good day. First lesson I had some arsehole making snide comments when I was talking to the teacher about Japan and EGLness.. Second period we had PE. High-jump. Can’t do it. Just…can’t. I’m such an elephant I can barely get my fat arse of the floor, let alone into the air. Third lesson we had art, and someone put paint all over my back. And messed up my portrait of Ekco, which I will have to do all over again now… Lunchtime some bastard year 7s were playing rugby...with a plastic bottle. And when I binned it I got loads of abuse hurled my way...I know it’s stupid…but I just seem to have lost me shield…usually it wouldn’t effect me, but I feel so vulnerable and weak and useless. Forth lesson we has science. I called someone a twat so him and his ‘posse‘ put pencil shavings in my hair. And I stressed at the teacher and got told off. I know they’re just little things, but it’s really doing my mood no good… Last lesson I was in tears the whole way through. I hate me. That is why there are 12 new cuts...because I’m just not coping well.  I tried to get up the courage to ask around for the school councillor, but I bailed on me. I don’t know which adult I can talk to who won’t tell my mother…who works in the school office. I’m so fucked. Fuck fuck fuck.   *sigh* at least when I got home I was able to relieve some on my stress on my pillows and then play with the kittens…and I uploaded some poetry and pixels. And I’m no closer to working out this FTP than I was yesterday. Meaning I have no idea were to start. And my squishy-friend doesn’t seem to be around to help. *pines for her anti-whoosh queen* 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: School uniform. Listening to: Kirsty and Anna arguing. Feeling: Anti-life...  -+-  Made my appointment. After school..so I have to fake I'm at an art club. Hopefully I won't get ratted out...*crosses fingers* But she's going to tell me to tell my parents...*sigh*  I feel yet again, fighting to live. I really don't like being like this, moody and unsociable, snapping at everyone, but I do. *beats self over head with keyboard*  -+-  Good news though...well, ish.  Madame X  is hosting me! So I finally get of crappy angelfire and move! Go me! Only I'm so used to having text input instead of uploading HTML files, which I'm not used to dealing with..and I feel really stupid and embarressed having to ask  Madame X  about everything...ah well, guess I'll just have to swallow my pride and for once actually accept that I don't know how to do everything.  And Mikey & Sully are as adorable as ever. They both fell asleep on me at about 5pm last night, and I just kinda lay there for about an hour and a half while they purred away, then when they started to wriggle I went to get a shower..and when I got back downstairs I walked in on Mikey pouncing on Sully... ^-^  Arg. Class now. Probably have another rant tonight about how my appountment went.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: School uniform. Listening to: Teacher talking. Feeling: Crap.  -+-  Arg. I have a splitting headache…not nice. Science class are dissecting hearts so I’m in the IT room with the lower group, looking up the moon-landing hoax…in other words, I’m doing jack and writing this blog entry.   The kittens have been named-Sullivan & Michael, AKA Sully & Mikey. They almost escaped last night too..but they were hiding under my bed.  Still considering going to a doctor. Have to make an appointment. In fact, I may well do that at lunch-time. And I really wish I could find a councillor or something…but I really find it hard to talk to someone I don’t know, and who I’m afraid will just treat me like an attention-seeking brat…  But I seem to have my muse back. I have ideas for ficcage and am writing a poem. Go me. Now I wish I had some aspirin…  The UG doesn’t seem to want to work...grr…so I can’t RP…*cries*   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Black zion-fleet top, black trousers, odd socks... Listening to: Changes-3 doors down Feeling: Not very happy.  -+-  Woah. I'm still here. I'm still alive, as unhappy as I am. And I think I have  Madame X  to thank for that...it may have been just one comment, but it let me know, despite everything you've got resting on your shoulders at the moment, you still care. *hugs* That comment saved my life.  I'm considering making myself an appointment with the doctor. But he can't prescribe me anything, because my parents would have to get the subscription, and he's going to tell me I should talk to them about it anyway...but I hate being so moody and depressed and angry for no reason. Thankfully, I have enough willpower to not take it out on those I really love, most of whom are online friends.  -+-  Actually managed to get something productive out of my foul mood too.   urlLink --CLICK HERE--  Which translates as:  And I know they don't care I know they don't see  what they put me through They make me bleed So I bleed and I bleed So I bleed and I bleed And I try to breathe But no air for me.  Could well be the makings of something...hope so.   And on another positive front, we have new editions to the family.  urlLink Pic 1   urlLink Pic 2  They're both boys, 8 weeks old, and we haven't named them yet. And ofter 5 minutes I've got scratches... 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Clothes. Listening to: Nothing. Feeling: Title says it all.  -+-  It's all too much again. Every time I feel I'm getting better something happens to ruin it all. I was clean for over a month..and now, well, my arms are red from everything. It's worse this time. It's so much worse. I haven't told anyone about anything recently...I've lied through my teeth. "Oh, I'm fine, just perfect. I'm sooo hyper! Eeeee!" fucking eeeee my arse!  My friendships are crap. I have one friend who doesn't want to know me since I told her I was bisexual, another 2 friends at war with each other with me trying desperately to stay neutral, and one I never see anymore! Sometimes I just want to walk away from the whole fucking friendship group! I really hate seeing insults being thrown each way, with me in the middle. They don't see, or care, how much it's hurting me... My online friends aren’t much better. But I will not go into detail here. But it really hurt..it really did hurt...  Love. Is it even real? My RP character seems to have love, but I'm doubting it's very existence. There is no-one out there for me. I'm an ugly, repulsive, fat, worthless, depressive shit with no social life! Who in their fucking right mind would want me? I told Leah I liked her. As more than a friend. But she's got a boyfriend..so I have to sit there and listen to her talk about getting fingered in the woods and pretend I want to know the gory details. Fuck fuck fuck.  My parents are giving me hell. They still haven't realised that I'm cutting. And dad won't even lay off when I've got PMT. He seems to think I'm not allowed to be a teenager with mood swings! And my stupid fuck of a sister keeps getting me in the doghouse. "Muuum, Abi did this! Daaaaad, Abi hit me!!" when I do fuck all, or she starts it!   And I feel so...repetitive...like my little life is going round in circles, and i can't get out of it. And they're nobody there to help me. Everything I do is crap, and it's all about the same things. Why am I so afraid to try something new? I can't say nobody cares, because I know there's at least one person, perhaps 2 who care about me. But I don't want to unload all my problems on Madam X at the moment, she's going through too much.  I looked up the symptoms of depression. I fit a heck of a lot of them. I even plucked up the courage to ask for a councillor...only to have it thrown in my face and told I didn't need one-I'm being melodramatic. I have yet to ask my parents to see a doctor...I don't dare. And I had another athsma/panic attack second period. I haven't been getting them recently, but everything seems to be piling on top of me. And most of the class decided I was faking it.   I sound so stupid, eh? Some teenager who's just jumped on the self-harm bandwagon. Well, perhaps that's what I am...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: school uniform Listening to: a ringing phone Feeling: hayfever-ridden  -+-    Why is 'orgasm' a six letter word?  ---It's easier to spell than ' ohohohOHYESOHMYFUCKINGGODYESPLEASEMORESHIT YESOHOHPLEASEMOREDEEPERMOREYES OHOHOHMOREMOREMOREYESYESYESN OFUCKINGGODNOHARDERYESYES!!!'  XD I am strange.  Troy. Oh my fucking gawd. It was amazing. Orli looked the vision of hotness is armour...lucky wench getting to snog his face of! I got the distinct inpression Achilles liked taking his clothes of..yes. And I must applaud Eric Bana for his preformance as Hector..breathtaking. But still in shock from the sheer Orli-hotness. Could have killed some of the ocupants of the screen though. One couple got up and left half way through, really load. And some bitch next to us wouldn't stop playing on her phone. It ranf and she answered it. So I told her 'they tell you to turn it off for a reason!' then it went off. Yay me! Honestly, silly woman. Grr.  Class now. See you soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Black skirt, white strappy top, Egypt rose glove. Listening to: Broken-Seether/Amy Lee Feeling: Hot, bothered and annoyed!  -+-  Fuck. It's too hot. Every single classroom is like a desert, bar the IT room, which has the god-send of air conditioning! So I spent lunchtime in there..but the rest of the day was horribly hot and stressful. Not to mention the fucker formally known as Steven being a super prat. Whhhhhy does he persist in annoying me?  Not only do I have to cope with the heat, but my hayfever is at it's worst. I've done nothing but bloody sneeze all day, my eyes are red, sore and swollen and they itch. My tablet hasn't worked, eyedrops done...I can barely see..  Added to all that, yesterday's double tec lesson was productive. Oooo yes. I spent 20 minutes getting the blade out of my pencil sharpener, and the next hour and a half decorating my arms. Gah. I've been clean for about a month or so now, but things are really getting to me. And When I got home I was in a seriously odd frame of mind, I took pictures of my arms. Sick fucker aren't I? Ah well, I kinda find it quite...pretty actually. Tell me I'm stupid, go on, because I already know that.. (((You a sick fucker too? Good for you! Don't click if you don't want to see.  urlLink Pic 1   urlLink Pic 2   urlLink Pic 3   urlLink Pic 4 )))  This is not a cry for attention. If I wanted attention I'd cut my arms and use the blood to paint 'NOTICE ME!' on every wall I could find...so..it's not as bad as it seems. They're not deep at all, just surface scratches.   On a nicer..but still weird note I had an..odd..dream last night. I dreamt me, Jo and Ekco were dildo shopping! Jo had short hair and took to a rather large blue one with a rabbit face on it, Ek stuck to her many bumps and spikes with multiple power settings, and I was looking at green double-headed. This dream was totally weird, because I am no expert on vibrators and dildos, and have certainly never 'encountered' one..I think I need to replace my brain..  No forward on the Nickelback front. *sobs and sulks*
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Green trousers, royal blue nightshirt, black hat with devil horns. Listening to: Silence Feeling: Worried  -+-  Such a crap day..boring lessons, and then I go and forget my key, so I'm locked out of the house for an hour. And then mum desided I can't go see nickelback *cries* not faaaaair! My sister's just been to Alton Towers (£25), and my brother's got a new memory card for the PS2 (£20), and I can't even go to see them! I'm willing to pay for bloody both tickets, but mum's the only adult I can go with and she says 'next time..' if she won't take me this time she won't take me next time, will she?  And we have PE tomorrow.  Great. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Blue trackies *gasp*, black vest top, bandana (can you tell my hair gets in my eyes?) Listening to: Blade 2 in the background Feeling: Happy(ish) Cuts today: None. Not even cat scratches!  -+-   To prove to everyone that my life is not full of hardship like one long anst-novel, I'm updating with my fairly enjoyable Thursday.   I got up about 10ish, did some jobs around the house, listening to my music on full volume (I was home alone). The kittens escaped once XD so I just let them roam around the garden for a&nbsp;bit. They went absolutely bonkers in the flowerbed, and even more bonkers when Will turned up in his&nbsp;nice new&nbsp;jeans and nice new cosmic blue hair. Soooo...while Will lay on my bed, both kittens decided to lay on his chest, purring in his face. Took a photo-the&nbsp;3 of them are absolutely adorable. Watched KillBill,&nbsp;corny jokes about Kill Will &nbsp;ensued...desided we hadn't had a good snog for ages..then he had to go to football training, and I was left bored. So like my usual self I sat on my arse on the computer, randomly licking and poking people. And yes, I realise how wrong that sounds.   Going to see Spideyman 2 tomorrow, even if it is with my annoyingly boring cousin. I'm only going becuase she's paying for me! XD Evil I am...if she's that desperate and stupid to spend time with me...  Saw Garfield the moive, it's rules. Got me back into reading all the old garfield comics. He's so like me. Fat, lazy and cynical (and proud to).  Annnnd going to see Shrek 2 a week on Saturday with Abbi, who's coming down for 3 days. Yay!   Not much else to report.   Oh yeah, mum seens to be relenting on the whole internet thing.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Blood red 'Lestat' shirt, black trousers with holes on the thighs >. Listening to: She will be loved-maroon 5  Feeling: Shitty.  Cuts today: 7+2 insect bites+1 cat scratch (plus lots extra from yesturday)   -+-  &nbsp;  Woopeedoodaa. Last day of term today, and I only wish it could have ended on a high note. Wankers kept insisting that Will got off with some trollop in our class. He swears he didn't, and I want to believe him, but it wouldn't suprise me. I mean, I'm not much to compare to really. She's pretty and all, but still a slut..and now with my face all cut up and sore..well, he's more likely to want to kiss the bottom of someone's shoe.  &nbsp;  Oh, the whole cut up and sore face thing is from yesterday. I was walking Ella in her pushchair across the park (after returning from Alton Towers), and some bastard rudies I'd never met before in my life desided to give me hassle. They must have been drinking, because they had a bottle. When I tried to get away I got it smashed across my jaw. I think I was the most scared I've been in my life..not for me, but for Ella. What tosser attacks someone when they're pushing a 2 year old in a pushchair?! Thank fucking god some guy walking across the park ran over, got them to piss off and helped make sure there was no glass in her pushchair while I got he to stop bawling. He was going to call an ambulance because I had glass in my face (cheek, jaw) but I just got dad to come pick me up. I told my parents I got it thrown at me, so they wouldn't phone the police. I can't remember what they looked like, and to be honest I don't think the police could do jack anyway. Took a drip down the the NHS emergency drop in thing to get the glass out. Then I went&nbsp;to bed and cried. So it's only 4 cuts, but that's not the point.  Mum is considering not letting me have the net on my computer now. So not only does that mean i wont be able to do jack with my website because she wont let me install anything on her computer, but my internet time is going to be....basically none existant. So at this rate i might just have to pull out of unplugged all together, unless I can convince her otherwise (which is not an easy task.)&nbsp; I'm pretty&nbsp;fucking screwed really.  I've tried&nbsp;for too long to&nbsp;pretend&nbsp;all the names and shit I put up with doesn't hurt, like it's water off a duck's back. Bollocks. I'm breaking down now..I'm not coping, and I'm not letting anyone help me. Will still doesn't even know about Friday night. I can't tell him. I just can't. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing:  Listening to:  Feeling:  Cuts today:   -+- &nbsp; Oh god I'm stupid.. I've just cut my wrist twice with a kitchen knife.. it's so much more painful than my little razors..thank shit it's shallow..Jesus, I thought I wanted to die, I really did want to..but I'm still here. I don't want to leave those I love because I can't deal with things. Fuck..I'm not really composed enough to type something long..but I'm sorry to those close to me, I am...but it won't end here. I'll still be here. I'll pull through, I'm strong enough..I am..it'll stop bleeding soon.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Pink/white top, black skirt, bandana, lenseless glasses. Listening to: Cher-that one about the gypsies... Feeling: Headachey. Cuts today: None.  -+-  Well I've not had an internet connection for just over a week. Mum's got a new computer and that's the one connected to the broadband box, so I have to wait  another  week to get the net on my comp. Sooo...I've been getting back into the sims. Nyehe, killing sims rules.  Gah. Lots been going on over the past week. Helps if I could remember it...to be honest I don't really remember anything before Friday. I went to Macey's on Friday-it's this ultra townie under 18's nightclub. I only went because it was a birthday party. It was humiliating. The fuckers found it funny to lift up my skirt. Twice. I cried in the toilets for over an hour, and when I came out I went crazy. I wrote all over my arm, and I mean all over. Stuff like: bitch, whore, slut, cow, fat, unimportant, crazy, weird, different, odd, insane, i hate myself and want to die, depressed, suicidal, hurt, unfaithful, untrusting, selfish, dog, lowly, fucker, ho, prossie, i wish I was dead, kill me now fucker...and more I can't remember. And I threw fizzypop around, and was super hyper. The rest of them are sure I'd taken drugs..hyper as in shouting, being nasty..and not myself. And then I could barely keep my eyes open on the way back home...and Lesley slept over and said I was a bit wierd all night..what does she expect? I think I'm having some kind of mental breakdown..or maybe it was the fact we watched Grease...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: 'Weapons of mass distraction' tee, green trousers, glove, bandana. Listening to: Could it be any harder-The Calling Feeling: Numb Cuts today: 38, scratches  -+-  My day has been crap. I woke up late, had to rush to get ready, with my mum stressing at me to hurry up. That's were the first 5 came from, long ones on my leg. They bled all the way to school. Lied, said I'd cut myself on my bed.  I was fine after that up until 3rd lesson, when the head teacher cornered me and stressed at me for a) my jacket (it's not a propper school jumper!) b) my glove (this is NOT school unform) and c) my boots (those are not school shoes.) Fucker. They're plain black, sensible..more sensible than some of the heels the tarts have. And they get away with buckles, sparlkes, flowers, staps up theit legs...fuck I hate him.  After that, the usual playful poking the yr 9s have got on my nerves. And I stressed at Callum, them i had to go to the office where mum had anothet stress about my uniform. FINE! If I'm not allowed to wear my effing glove to hide my scars then I'm not fucking hiding them anymore!  I stressed at Zoe too, which was out of order. She was being playful and I told her to fuck off, and Katrina desided to stress at me, so I had a go at her. I did apologize to Zoe though..but Katrina won't get an apology. It's been boiling away for ages, she deserves it. She got all indignant about me telling Zoe to fuck off, then telling her to leave me alone, going off on 'don't talk to me like that!' Er, so she's allowed to talk to Pippa and Anna like that, and worse, but I'm not allowed to, once in our 'friendship' in a blind rage?! She's no friend of mine.  So I ran off crying. Lied to the history teacher when she tried to comfort me. Went to the toilets..35 scratches and reopening the wound on my wrist later, though still in tears I went to afternoon registration.  I'm fucked up, and I know it. I'm a danger to myself, I'm falling apart. And so are my friendships..Will's in Ireland..I feel so lost without him here to talk to..  Good news: Ms Brader has sorted out appointment with school nurse. And Laura, Katy, Joanne, Lindsey, Louise, Adam, Alex, Paul, Tom and me are all going to Rock City with me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: White 'everything is copyrighted (c)' top, black cords. Listening to: Behind blue eyes-Limp Bizcuit. Feeling: Headache-y Cuts today: Noooone. Woot.  -+-  Well, i went and had another chat with my head of year. Talked about things, and she's getting me hooked up with the school nurse. I'm glad I did come to her..she seems to understand were I'm coming from, and understands how I feel about mum finding out. It feels like a weight's been lifted of my shoulders, and I can breathe again..  Not much else to report. Accept I walked home last night with Will, in the rain, and he asked if we could give 'us' another go. ^-^ So that has made me happier! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing: Black 'i fucked your girlfriend' vest top, witch skirt, red alice band. Listening to: Nobody's home-Avril Lavigne Feeling: Sick, twisted, fucked up in general. Cuts today:  -+-  Hohum. Haven't updated in a while. Thought it was time I expressed myself before I do anything stupid again.  Firstly, I had a little accident when I was shaving a while back. It was 100% accidental, but I'm still sick. Like My normal twisted self, here's pics. (contains blood, though they're very blurred and don't actually look too bad.)  urlLink http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v169/crystar/foot1.jpg   urlLink http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v169/crystar/foot2.jpg   urlLink http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v169/crystar/foot3jpg   urlLink http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v169/crystar/foot4.jpg  Yeah, that's my sketchbook/paintbrush in one of those pics. That's because it bled so much...I mean loads. The cut wasn't anything at all, i just knocked the top of an insect bite..but I lost alot of blood. Before I told anyone I sat and let it bleed, and painted in my sketchbook with the blood. But then I started to panic, because the toilet floor was covered, and it was seeping out onto the landing carpet. So I had to get mum, and she panicked so much..it took a few hours for the bleeding to stop, and the carpet's still stained.  From then I got really low. 3 days I felt like shit..so much so I didn't even go near a computer at all. I sat in my room most of the day, cutting myself, drawing, sleeping, crying, trying to write, listening to my depressants...only leaving to get ice cubes, chocolate, and when i thought i better make my presence known, as to avoid sucpicion. When mum asked why I was in such a mood I just said I had major PMT. I'm so glad we're having shitty, rainy weather, it means i can wear long sleeves. Even caught myself thinking how many painkillers it'd take to kill me.  If it isn't obvious already, I've still got depression. And that school nurse didn't help. She acts as if she knows everything, but she doesn't. She doesn't know what I feel. Nobody does. Yeah, others have depression..but not exactly how i feel, in my circumstances. Sometimes I want to be left alone completely...but I do want people to care..I'm not going to say I don't want pity because I do..I need to feel loved. I'm so close to giving up..  ---  The less twisted stuff: Mikey can use the catflap now, though Sully's still too gentle to push it hard enough. Ella has a new phrase: "Here we pum!" ("Here we come!") She was bringing up clean washing for me to put away yesturday saying it. Very sweet. I start summer school on Monday. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>