<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i want to update you on the status of my current existence.   its been a week or two, regents are over, school is over, and i am indifferent. its not that i just MISS school its just that i dont care about it bieng in my life, or not. I think this summer is just a transition into next school year, if you think about it summers like two monthsish, 8 weeksish. thats short, after last year and before next year i would prefer something more. next year will be hell. AP's SAT's SAT II's and any other random letter arangment you can imagin. I dont want to go to school. but thats not for me to decide anyway. i mean who wants to end up pumping gas on the corner while your wife works on the corner? Perplexing. I want to go to sleep for like 4 days and wake up bieng as refresed and new as a newborn child. I need sleep, i started sleeping late, really late, like waking up around 1 in the afternoon, its nice but i dotn like it, i waste so much time in the morning when i could be doing something interesting, important, productive and anything else. Waking up 10 every satruday for work is gay. But its $$$. Thank god for veterans day next week, the first saturday in a while i will get to sleep late, hopefully not until 1 but late. I've been thinking about religion lately, i dunno why, probably because this morning some people came up to my house when we were leaving and started preaching to us to follow thier religion etc etc etc etc. These people once wouldnt leave my grandpa alone, i told my parents to send em to me next time. I would love to have a debate with them. See what drives them to go to peoples houses sunday mornging and bullshit. Have they met god? did God tell them to do this? Or did some guy at the church make them. I get so much enjoyment to see people act like zombies. Zombies who do what thier told as long as its one of gods orders. One of the gods, i wonder how many there are, theres the ones chirstains pray to, the jew's god, Jesus, Allah, Buddha (he was worshipped like one but he really wasnt one) probably more. Lets say your taking a test, really hard, you think you failed, yyou get it back and see that you got a nice high grade, do you thank god? WHY!? did GOD make u bubble in the right answer on the sheet, did GOD make your guesses come out right? did GOD make you pass? FUCK NO! you did yourself, you should THANK YOURSELF!!! When an elecrical fire causes your house to burn down do you go "WHY GOD WHY DID YOU DO THIS TO ME?" god didnt do it, the electrician who didnt do his job right did it, the unfortinate chain of events that brought the fire did it, im so sure god went down to ur basement, crossed a few wires, and whent back hiding behind his cloud snikering at what he has done. Like a 10 year old playing ring and run. BULLSHIT! FAITH IS BLAME! who do i BLAME WHEN SOMETHING GOES WRONG. its always THANK GOD! or  WHY GOD? your either blaming or thanking, thats not faith, faith is bullshit unless its in yourself or a REAL PERSON. you go I have faith in myself to do good, to succeed, Or i have faith in my family to get through a tough situation. Faith is god is mearly the shifting of blame or thanks. By praying you do nothing but assure yourself that a third party (god) is working with you. You lose your dog, you pray to god that he comes back. Sure enough your nieghtbors find him in thier yard. Do you say GOD did it? NOOO!!!!! your nieghbor did it. The dog followed instinct and attempted to return to 'home'!!!! god didnt tug on his leash. Feel free to post a comment you religious people, feel free to call me or im me. i love to argue. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Physics hard global easy  im too lazy to type a long post, or to think, so heres some retarded humor.  Conversations out of the ordinary:  An Atom: I think I lost an electron!! another Atom: are you sure?? An Atom: Im  positive   if only i remebered this on the physics final, lol 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Its been while, My bad. A few things happend, finals were over, did pretty good, and another thing, since i started with this blogger thing i realized how popular i made it become. I've seen two people start it and a third telling me they will. anyway, like i said this is alot better than that xanga crap.. So back to real life, Physics regents on wednesday, im planning to stay home on tesday to study most of the day and go to work the other part of the day. Physics isnt much to worry about anyway.. One thing i dont get is why people are scared of leaving school early, not comming to school on the last day. For isntances when my global teacher SPECIFCALY said "If i dont see you your not here", implying she doesnt care if we leave early there were actually people who stayed back, SOME for Legit reasons, such as, Rehersal after school, activity after school. Why did others stay back you ask? No reason but the fear of cutting. This cuttafobia is the dumest thing yet! I mean if teacher A told studient A to cut why shouldnt student A go home. Anyway, i got a ride home after 8th from Marianna to miroslavs house, watched soccer, then billards, then made my way home to realize more people now how a blog! So here i am sitting wonderig what to do now. Im prolly gunna go to the park today and get some fresh air, much needed since i spent all of last week studing. Finally over the summer i will have time to go to the gym, go play tennnis and soccer everday, relax sleep late. Im glad summers here. But then again i kinda liked sophomore year. Better than freshman year, High School is gradually becoming more entertaining (and harder) year by year. although Junior year is nothing to look forward too. Heres something to think about, 'Mosh Pits'. My motto: "If u cant dance, then wave your arms around and hit people!" WHY ON EARTH DO MOSH PITS EXIST!? Can music influence your mood and persona in such a way that you become almost violent?! That means theres something wrong with you. Some kid told me that they were normal and i laughed in his face, i mean, who would entertain themselves in that way. THE END!  ill try to post more often with more productive posts, enjoy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was an interesting day, Starting with the physics final. That was probably one or the 'hardest' test I took, Hardest bieng defined as  Difficult to get a high grade on  yet easy to pass. I wonder, what it would be like to be someone who settles with a 85. On a different note I am wondering, why do most girls not give out thier wieght or anything but then again have thier tags on thier clothing stick out, I mean, does danny care what 3rd world country your shirt was made in? Nor does he care wheater your a medium or large, even less what designer it is. Work today, was good, nice, easy and slow. Speaking of work I was reading Dude Where's my Country by Michael moore. http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0446532231/qid=1086741995/sr=2-2/ref=sr_2_2/002-0988896-8612021) can be found there at amazon really cheap. This book is about Bush having ties with Bin ladens immediate family during the time of 9/11, things that the public should have read and taken seriously, etc etc. I would reccomend it to anyone who wants to learn. This book, although really really really one sided (so far). Anyone with any political interest should read this. We should start now as most of us have less than 3 years till we can vote. I guarantee you'll be laughing once u read the first page, even before the dedication. Anyway, math and spanish finals tomorrow and work till 8 dont mix well.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Its monday, the first day of the end of the year. ALl this week I have finals in every single class. I keep wondering why do I have to take a test on all of the stuff i learned already? Whats the point? I passed every test in the class do you need more assurance that I do really know basic physics? Oh well, back to studying. I've never really sat down and "studied" for anything, yet. So far all i did was basic review before the test, I think i really crammed for a few tests throughout high school, soon to be more with regents comming up. And work is killing me even though a friend is starting to work with me in a week or two which is cool. I never really have time to go out during the week, or play sports or anything. I cant wait till school is over and I can do whatever i want during those two months, between studying for SAT's and what not. 4 real days left, 3 and a half nights of hell left. Especially with work till 8 tomorrow and a math final the next day. I wonder if people are studing for physics at all... This term hasnt been too rough. Well its 9, which means i should finish my physics questions and figure out whta i forgot. By the way this is alot better than that xanga crap with those gay eprop things... Good night.  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Im back. Long time no post. I went to Cali for a week saw many interesting things, it would give me a headache remebering them and a finger ache typing them so lets not go there. It was fun. I am edjubulant to come back to SI and three days of straight full working days...yea ok. I got my raise while I was away which was an entire 50 cents! Now I can afford that extra piece of gum... Considering the amount of hours I work it is a considerable incriease. Ok, now what will i talk about you ask? Another heated religiond debate? a war on drugs? No, though I have a few more interesting points to make on relgion. So if you still have a shred of belief in any relgion after reading my previous posts please see me for your daily dose of reality. lol nah im not going to waste my time. I just finished reading The Lovely bones a short while ago, It was a good book on the contrary to what people have told me, i took out 1984 by George Orwell at the library today hoping it would be somewhat interesting to me. I really wish I had more to write about at the moment.&nbsp;Alright against my previous statement it turns out i will indeed be making a comment on religion, though only for people to comment because they disagree with me.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Most Ideas of ancient man have been disregarded and thier inventions looked at as obsolete. From weapons, to ideas about nature. Relgion on the other hand has stayed, not because its so true but people are brought up from birth to follow it. Others turn to relgion because they are weak people in need of 'guidance'. Who belive that god will make thier life easier for them and thier afterlife happier. They are the ones who need to pretend someone else is in control of them, or helping them control themselves.  All right, now that is done... Im going to go.&nbsp; Hopefully my next post will not be as short as these two last ones and even possibly it might entertain you. Btw, for those who have never heard of this site  urlLink http://maddox.xmission.com/ &nbsp;is a funny site written by an amusing person.  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Another post, finally. The relgion debate posts unfortunatly are moving down a few spaces to add more variety to your entertainement. Well, its 10:30 and I got home from work today around 8:30, on the train i was thinking about people who do drugs, not people who have fun once in a while and experiment with thier friends on a friday or saturday night, but people who 'do' drugs, like wasted on a tesuday morning. Basically, to escape from something. I have strong feelings against people like that, If one has a problem they should do everything within thier power to correct it. Not temporarily 'escape'. NEWSFLASH you are'nt escaping from anything or anyone, you are bieng ignorant. If you need a drug to temprorarly solve something for you, I truly dont understand you. Animals (humans including) tend to solve thier own problems, some fighting like bucks for terretory, others running away like zebra, humans the more evolved of the three can solve these problems by what we call 'communication' say it everybody. good job. Back in the day when we swung from trees (some of us still do) there was no such thing as escaping your problems, males  would jump around and intimidate eachother to solve thier problems...getting off track here.. ok.. If you are a person who smokes weed and drinks practically on a regular basis, weather it is once a week or every day, should be hit with a large, preferrably metallic object. We are taught to solve our own problems from birth, atleast we should be, we are taught the art of communication, I hope..      Anyway that was just a reality check for those messed up people who do those sort of messed up things. Im tired..      another thing, Im proud of myself that I have debated many people to the point of them bieng speachless about my favorite topic, relgion. (that statement was made because its true and dont bother making this post into another religion debate as it has come on gone on this blog, feel free to IM me though) I wouldnt like to end this post as it is short(er) compared to my other ones...But then again I dont have much to say, so to entertain you for the time you wouldve been readign my long post I give you the challange to read this post twice without closing it. good bye 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Of all of those who dont know already in my last post I bashed religion, of course once one would attack the ideas of another he gets lovely, funny, and amusing comments. I am here to clarify details and respond to a critic of my thinking. So here is the Critic in all its interety.     "you see danny you are wrong, you can bs religion all you want because it does seem ridiculous but never doubt that there is not God (An inferior being)! You can be atheist if you like but how can there be no God when our world is filled with so many marvelous things. Big things like the sun and the forests and the mountains. Little things like birds, bugs.  Ingenious things like how bats use sonar. Eels that make electricity. Wasps that make paper. simple things as life nears its end it is the small things that we often focus upon, things that we take for granted. How else can these things be explained?  "Those who support the theory of evolution feel that it is now an established fact. They believe that evolution is an 'actual occurrence,' a 'reality,' a 'truth,' as one dictionary defines the word 'fact.' But is it?... IT was once believed that the earth was flat. Now it has been established that for a certainty that it is a spiracle shape. That is a fact. IT was once believed that the earth was the center of the universe and that the heavens revolved around the earth. Now we know for sure that the earth revolves in an orbital around the sun. This, too, is a fact. Would an investigation of the evidence for evolution leave one on the same solid ground? interestingly, ever since Charles Darwin's book the origin of species was published, various aspects of the theory have been a matter of considerable disagreement even among top evolutionary scientists. 'to their chagrin scientists have no clear-cut answer, because chemists have never succeeded in reproducing natures experiments on the creation of life our of nonliving matter. Scientists do not know how that happened. Scientists have no proof that life was not the result of creation' said Robert Jastrow astronomer. (SO DANNY EXACTLY WHERE IS YOUR SCIENTIFIC PROOF THAT THERE IS NO GOD? IM CURIOUS AS TO KNOW WHO DISCOVERED THAT WITHOUT ALL THE SCIENTISTS IN THE WORLD AREN'T AWARE)" Haaa I have soo much more I can qoute for you to make you know you can't be right. Danny with over 81 million different living things on the planet and human kind can't even create a single one, how else could it possibly get here?"    First of all, all living things were created through a complex process called evolution. Single celled organisms have been evolving since the big bang, So here youve got fred, the single celled organism, time comes for fred to asexully reproduce, Suddenly his offspring are not single but dual celled organisms. In short, this is what happend until organisms became very complex and lived in water, then these creatures living near land evolved to amphibians and were the first to see the land. Ergo, they never reterned into the water evolving more tword the feet instead of fins side. bla bla bla BILLIONS of years pass, and BANG youve got your different types of species and birds. MOUNTAINS were formed by continetal plates rubbing agaisnt eachother pushing ground UPWARD. THis process is seen today, no god included. Bats use sonar because they are blind, same way our eyes absorbe light to see, that is evolution, evolution is again, seen today, and yet again, no god included. Go to the library, get a book encyclopedia and look up these creatures and it can explain how they evolved, just because you can copy and past from a relgions shit website or some pamphlet doesnt mean that it is final.. The earth was belived it was flat before there was Technology to explore it, there is TECHNOLOGY to explore evolution as it is seen today. Dont compare 1400s to 2000s. We cant duplicate natures experiment because nature took millions of years, humans only have decades until they die. Humans cant create anything exept a few unstable elements, EVERYTHING CAME FROM NATURE AND NATURAL EVOLUTION!!! maybe you should think before you copy and past some shit like that. Wheres your OWN answer??? 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I am currently in a conversation with someone. This is no ordinary conversation, this is one where you want to shove your head into the monitor and let it come out of thier screen just so you can see if its THEM typing because they are saying the most obscene, supeflous things.  Ok, here it goes. Im going to try to replicate the conversation in its entierty. For the protection of the creater of the idea I will not mention her name (yes I know I said her, we never discussed me not giving out her gender). From now on I will relate to her as Mrs. Hitler, you will soon see why.  Mrs. Hitler seems to think that all people with downsydrome, those who are 'special', mentally retarded, and other hereditary disfunctions, should be sent away. To an island to example. Now me bieng a calm person I held myself back from bursting out in laughter at that comment. I felt a mix of emtion actually, one of disgust. How can one think that? Were they brought up by wolf's? Whats more is that Mrs. Hitler said that they are a burden to society? Hmm, isnt that what Hitler himself thought of the jewish people, as well as other minorities? Now I am sure you all are thinking "Who is this?" or "How can Mrs. Hitler say this!" Unfortunatly we have a little thing called freedom of speech, which George Bush is doing his best to take away. If I had power in this situation, I would send Mrs. Hitler and other people like her to an island. If you agree with me just comment.  Mrs. Hitler seems to think that Mentally retarded people are a burden to society... Im sorry Mrs. Hitler but unlike you these people have love from thier families no matter what they are. I am sure that if a family has a retarded son they will not hate him and be dissapointed, rather accept the fact and move on with life. Mrs. Hitler also asked me to find a purpose for them! Let me ask you Mrs. Hitler, whats your purpose? Saying stupid things similar to 'send the specail people away'?  Heres what Mrs. Hitler has told me: "save them the trouble of being made fun of and send them to an island "  Maybe YOU should be made fun of for saying that, why dont you meet a special person for once. Watch when Mrs. Hitler will have kids, and one of them is born retarded she will learn.  In conclusion, if you have anything to say or add to what i just typed, feel free to leave a comment.   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wish this was more like my own website, because I really want to change the layout and what not. I probably will after this post is post-ted.   As you may have noticed The title of my blog. This means that everyone religous, drug doing, and stupid...is wrong. Leave your opinion at the door. Hmm thats catchy, Patent pending. Anyway Recently I have paid specific attention to a small, erm...I would hate to say this but LARGE group of people. 'Stupid People'. As nice is it would be for them to be a minority you still need people who will one day grow up and deliver my pizza's, clean my garbage, etc. These people are so stupid you probably need a hammer to get your words into thier heads. I mean, after repeating something a number of times, not something you want them to believe but something factual. Like your telling them something that is real and true, not just your wrong opinion. And then these people sulk about the crap they believe instead of listening to the truth. I want to shoot people who are stupid. They should be given childrens toys to entertain them. Or better yet give them something to believe in that will take up all thier free time and corrupt their mind into doing stuff a way that people thousands of years wanted them to. What was that called again? Oh yea, Relgion. Maybe treatment of forcifull faith is a little harsh.  Stupid people deserve to be kicked, not just kicked, but I mean with steel toe boots by a fat rocker. They also get my stomach churning.  I would love to talk more about stupid people but I forgot what else I wanted to say. Now I want to mess around with my site layout, colors, and go to sleep.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>