<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am now in Pennsylvainia (sp?) Reading is the town... Im staying with my mother for 2 months... Last night i went to a youth fuction at her church (i dont usually have anything to do with churches) and it was decent the event runs all week and is called Teen Week (wow they sure are imaginative!) but it was cool they went to a LARGE park..  and played capture the flag... i got tagged out fairly early to i just hung out in the "prison" and chatted with the other 3 guys... finally i got out and  guarded my teams flag (less likely to be tagged...) all together it was a decent event but i will not get used to the Humidity... it was 78 yesterday but i started sweating immediately... So once i got home around 9 or maybe as late as ten i went to bed and acctually fell  asleep only to be awoken by rain onthe window and in Roberts House (bob is my moms husband) is very old... and has no central AC or screens built into the windows... so i had to pull both screens out and shut the windows...then the lightning started and the thunder rolled in... so needless to say i was up till around 2 last night  man im  tired...  hopefully me and Bob can install an AC unit in  one of the windows... (this will cool  my room and keep rain out while letting air in...) So i am hoping to do that  tonight... hopefully  the storm is long gone and i will sleep well tonight so i can go out and look for employment tomorrow...   Tonight is a Volleyball tournament at the church (drools) and theres gonna be bored games and other things to do... (Im taking  a camera :D)  well i must sign off now. ill try to post again soon.  Goat Out
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow in less than one hour i will be done with New Tech High... Holy shit! im gonna miss all my friends... god this sucks im just not seeing that im acctually not gonna see them much... i mean im goin into Sacto. JobCorp... damn  oh well Newtech rocks! (eventhough it sucks ass)  ha  one hour... wow  Goat Out!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahahaha Ok so i got some links up i have to put in the Horizontal rule and i need to change the font... But yeh it worked... oh damn i need to make it link out... GAH!!! stupid shit... hmm oh well ill change that later not like anyones reading this or visiting the links...  Ok im almost out of school im out at 12:15... yay More later...   Goat Out!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to get a new  template cause i need to add links... grrr i need links!!! ok i guess ill go fuck around with the template code... hopefully i wont fuck it up... oh well wish me luck...  Goat out!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well ive been in class for over an hour and a half...  i got mr. harris to play slipknot... He played Duality and Wait and Bleed... GOOD SHIT! um so yeh we had to watch parts of two movies... some sea thing and one about surfers... Gah  oh well im goin to Biology next and i got a final in there... damn i hate tests but im not expecting to pass it so i guess i cant let my self down...  im bored... oh well ill post later if i can...  Goat Out
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok well i think i just pissed my friend off... she just wasnt chatting about anything interesting so i was like ok well im just done ill see you later... but she started bitchin at me about me bein mad at her. (i would know if i was mad and i wasnt) so yeh that went on for like 5 mintutes then she was all Fine ur an ass! (and she signed off...) shes not gonna be at school tomorrow... Damnit i did it again! i lost another hella cool friend... (If ur reading this Plase forgive me im just tired... and i wasnt really needing to be on AIM) Oh well...  um now im going to go to bed im freakin tired... and im about to catch a flight to PA on saturday so i need to rest as much as possible... and yeh um... where am i? wow im tired... Good Bye Net Folk... Ill post something interesting tomorrow...  Goat is OUT! (Like a Light)  *ZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz*
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate chatting online cause when ever i ask if people like Mushroomhead  they always come out and fucking say that Mushroomhead copyed slipknot... ommfg!!!! are you kidding me? mushroomhead formed in 1993 and slipknot formed in like 1995 so whos copying who? not to mention they have completely different sounds (mushroomhead is more mellow less HATE hate Hate!!!) and yet all the maggots feel that its their duties to diss on a band thats been around more than 2 years longer and   WAS COPIED BY SLIPKNOT!!!   im soo tired of people saying mushroomhead copyed slipknot! get your fucking facts straight before you try to make a point... further more when i correct the Maggots they respond as if im full of shit or im making it up. wheres that come from when someone corrects me about something im uneducated on i give them the finger an walk away i dont make it a longer debate...  ok i had to rant and now i feel better hopefully someday slipknot and mushroomhead will bury the hatchet (correy taylors forehead)and even share the same stage... but until that day comes ill simply tell every maggot i meet how wrong they are... life is grand...  Goat out!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well Lets see... I'm Stuck in Mr. Proctors Computers class For another +looks at watch+ oh god... 2 Hours!!! aaahhh oh well I dont much care... I'll just get some work done... hmmm ok so yeh...  I cant wait until saturday, That is the day that my adventure officially starts! I will be flying out to PA, to see my mother and her new new husband Oh Rapture! hah I make my self giggle like a school girl...  +Straightens and Stops giggling+ ok sorry about that...  hmmm I need to go out of this class and Do Something!!! AAAHHHH! I need out! well i give up im gonna go do work...  Goat Out
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well iam at school and im here till 12:15 so its not all that bad... but yeh i cant wait for school to get out (thursday)...  Ill add more later!   Goat Out
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ha im tired... Today was lame so i get to go sleep and look forward to tomorrow (likely to be even lamer) WHOOO HOOO! Um i get to do a half day tomorrow, Wednesday and on Thursday iam done with school for this Year!!! WOOT! hah i win!  You know what? i dont like your attitude! +punched self in the head+ OH Yeh? Yeh! +socks self in the gut+ OOF! hah ok ow now i need a bandage...  um where am i? ?__? Ok so yeh im tire... +SNOOOAAARRR+  Goat is Out!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, Welcome to my blog... prepare for a freakin crazy ass ride cause Iam more fun than a barrel full of Iguannas Injected with Crack cocaine! So if ur not into the random and often just stupid... Leave... Go somewhere else...   So if ur still here Enjoy cus its about to get odd... 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>