<Blog>


<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No llama burgers!    And this would not be a kinky spooning.  This would be a horrific, painful, torturous spooning.  Unless you are a masochist in which case I would merely tease you with the spoon.  Mwaha.    And whilst we are speaking of the spoon, here I have a gift for Rachael--the product of much boredom and insanity:    urlLink Fear the Spoon   I was planning to post the picture itself and not just a link, but either myself or this site is stupid.  Let us say that the site is stupid and would not allow me to put a picture in my post.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Glad to see somebody just had to screw with some of the setting when they had no idea what they're doing...*cough*  Even though my name isn't on the list of allowed users, I would just like to point something out.  In the event of a conflict between any of the four people that have the power of the Spoon, Rachael always trumps all of the other members.  Just in case such a situation should ever arise...  Mmmm...llama burgers...  A horrific Spooning?  Sounds kinda kinky.  Me likes.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've decided to make a few changes, namely with the power of the spoon. I'm granting power of the spoon to a few other people, just to make sure that there is a cabinet of competent people, and because the spoon is extremely potent it takes more than two people(even though the Gina and I are more than capable). So I think that while Amy is 2nd in command there might be circumstances in which Gina isn't there to excercise the power of the spoon. And I also think Jennie should have power of the spoon as well, so the members of the cabinet don't use to force of the spoon for evil.  So here is a list of people who have power of the spoon. 1. Rachael- duh did anyone really think i wouldn't have power over the spoon. I do own the workd, and  the spoon is mine 2. Gina- to excercise any punishment needed in order to protect the Llamas. 3. Amy- to preside over any issues that coincide with laws for hookering and in case Gina hasn't yet heard of the injustice that was done. 4. Jennie- to ensure that the spoon isn't used for evil forces.  Now many of you may notice that a certain name isn't mentioned in the power of the spoon. This person who will remain unnamed has threatened to eat certain protected animals. If this threat happens again then all power that this person has obtained will be stripped away, and given to someone better suited for the job. I think that's all for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gina is delighted at her appointment as Official Protector of the Llamas and at receiving the Power of the Spoon.  She thanks Rachael most sincerely and welcomes Amy as her second-in-command.  She finds herself wishing that this site accomodated avatars, for then she could make herself a nifty OPotL badge.  But alas, it does not.  Nor does it accomodate signatures.  She find this rather sad and frowns upon this site and it's hidden agenda to oppress the expression of the individual.  She is more than just a name at the bottom of a long, silly, frighteningly insane post.    She considers using the Spoon to punish the Llama-eater, but refrains, for she is a merciful and forgiving God... er... LLama Protector.  But she warns him that any more mention of ingesting the Great Ones shall indeed lead to a most horrific Spooning.    Gina must go for now, for she has run out of things to say.  Now she must go and ponder the Great Mysteries--specifically, why in the world she just wrote this post entirely in the third person.  Perhaps she should seek professional help before one of the other people living in her head decides to take over completely.  Wait...  Oh, no!  Dear God, no!  The other one... It has a spoon!  Arrrghhhhhh!  *ahem*  Gonna go take my medication now....   Mmmm... Thorazine...  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay...this is confusing without names...lol.  It's BWOKEN!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saying there was "no hookering for Amy" is denying that I'm a hooker, Rachael. Duh. :-P And no, that doesn't mean I will sleep around for free. My shirt was not closer to my elbow than my neck...there is a picture if anyone doubts me...Rachael--my bad...GENEVIEVE--was a bit drunk to be trusted to remember correctly anyway. On the other hand, I was sobering up a lot by this point that night. And, no, there will be no women for Amy--that is just out of the question and wrong. And what makes you think that I would need to tie a man down to have my way with him--are you saying that I couldn't find a guy who would want me so I would have to tie him down? Please give me a LITTLE credit here. :-/ *sigh* I'm not clearly confused...just clearly unloved. :-(
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You may have not claimed to be a hooker, but did you deny it? I think not. Now to be honest I'm a little confused. Does that mean you would do it for free? If so then it makes no sense as to why you wouldn't help Dave with his situation? Also just to tell everyone Amy's shirt was already off the shoulder so when she pulled it down to "irritate her mother" it was closer to her elbow than it was to her neck.  I also couldn't help but notice how in your statement about not wearing a giant banana suit and not seducing a sleazy man you wouldn't mind finding an unsleazy man and tying him down and having your way with him, of course she also didn't rule out the factor that she wouldn't bring a woman home either....so i think Amy needs to be a little more descriptive with what she will and will not do to get some action.  Since Amy is clearly confused I think I made a rather smart decision by withholding the power of the spoon (who knows she might use it on her unsleazy man or woman).  However she must have known that since Gina came up with the Llama campaign that Gina deserved all the power.  Although if I feel safe with her handling the spoon power may come to Amy eventually. I think that's about it for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok...let me explain once again to you people. New Year's Eve...I didn't claim to be a hooker. I did not. My mother called me a hooker...and ONE man...not men...threw several CREDIT CARDS...not money...at me. I did not, however, accept them. He was declined. There was no hookering for Amy. Now Dave, apparently upset by missing out on having sex with Amy, was counseled by Genevieve to approach my mother about remedying this situation...but she told him that she didn't think it was a good idea. Genevieve then told him that perhaps Jamie would accomodate him...but he, disheartened by his previous failed attempts, did not approach her about the matter. It is true that Amy did pull her shirt slightly lower on her shoulder to irritate her mother as she was agitated by the hooker comment...but she did not strip as was also alleged. People who were not there really have no right to comment on that night...especially if they didn't even get the drunken messages Amy left them. *cough*Josh*cough* Anywayz...that is about all I have to say about that night. As far as Gina's allegations...they are not true. I do not have any desire to wear a giant banana suit. Sorry. I also don't have the desire to seduce sleazy men from bars. Moving on...I am more than happy to head the "Llamas Deserve to Read Too!" foundation. I am slightly saddened that I can't punish people with the spoon...but I'm not bitter. That is all for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is for Gina, and Amy, and Rachael...   "Walk the Llama llama" ~Rascal Flatts   Walk The llama llama Walk The llama llama Take in the panorama Walk The llama llama - llama llama Don't have to be a drama Walk The llama llama - llama llama No one could be calmer Walk The llama llama Walk The llama llama Double L.A.M.A   Fluff up your fur Stick out your chest Walk The llama llama Now your looking your best Keep out the wind Keep out the snow Wool by llama from head to toe   Walk The llama llama - llama llama Take in the panorama Walk The llama llama Walk The llama llama Double L.A.M.A   Cool in the summer Warm in the cold A perfect fashion statement For the young and the old A cloak for the priest A hat for the farmer You could be looking at the emperor's pajamas   That's way the llama walks so proud That's way the llama holds his head up in the crowd All of us applaud his generosity He's more than just a passing curiosity He covers up our pride And all those things we have to hide In any civilized society   Walk The llama llama   yes, i am a retard, but as i told Josh, leave me the f*ck alone, this is not my day and i am so not into being picked on today... if you have evil/mean comments, keep them to yourself... i've got a lot on my mind, and the llama song got me off of it for a few min!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am sad... so i came to say hi. by the way, life stinks sometimes
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well obviously i missed a lot over break. Oh well, better late than never. I agree with Gina; it's no secret that Amy wishes she wasn't innocent, and to be honest i'm kinda confused that she is, because at New Years she claimed to be a hooker, and men threw money at her. So take that any way you'd like.    And as the owner of the world i proclaim that there will be no eating of the Llamas they have been through enough oppression without having to worry about being eaten as well.  Mr. Brick needs to realize that he has no power over the llamas. Nor will he ever. I feel that in order to maintain everyones love of the llamas, that i appoint Gina as protector of the llamas, being as she was the one who brought the issue of the llamas to everyones attention. Amy is SECOND in command, and head of "Llamas deserve to read to" foundation.  If anyone has issues with the fact that llamas are unedible now they will have to face the spoon. Oh yeah i give Gina power to use the giant spoon as punishment in any way she finds necessary.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okie dokie pokie... I am still tired, but fed... Fed cheap food.. Yes top ramen rules again... anyway, i just thought i would let you know not to worry, i am not hungry anymore!  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I am way too tired for this stuff... I wanted to read all of it, but I got lost somewhere in the middle... somewhere between eating and reading llamas... besides I am hungry.  I would like to take this point to tell everyone I AM A MORON!  Yes, it's true, a moron.  See, I remember my parents telling me that they paid for me to be able to eat when I came back to school on Sundays, and then all week long... Cept they must have forgotten to tell the school... or to tell me that just because they pay for meals, doesn't mean the cafeteria will serve them... Anyway, I AM SOOO HUNGRY... DAMN THE SCHOOL... 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am just lost. The end. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uninnocented by beavers? No. That's just wrong in any possible way it can be interpreted. About the llamas...I'm with Gina on this one. I think we should form a school for the llamas. Illiteracy is very upsetting. Reading is very important. We need to teach them writing too. That's important as well. As far as what Josh is gonna make next...I'm not telling. For once I'm on the knowing side of the secret. :-P  Yes, I'm a dork. But y'all love me that way! ;-) And I'm tired and I think I've had too much cold medicine, so excuse me while I go pass out. lol
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's break and I'm doing  homework  .  I do less work when I'm at school.  *sigh*  Don't llamas taste good too?  I would love llamas a lot more if they started trooping to the back door of the cafeteria to offer themselves up for slaughter, because we really don't get enough meat as it is.  I propose an "Eat the Llamas!" campaign.  Anyone not interested in reading to them may join me.  BYOB (and knives).  You may all rest assured that Mr. Brick will not be making any babies.  The other three are all much more likely.  Amy knows, but whether or not she chooses to tell everyone is up to her...  Amy's nickname, before she was yelled at by [censored] was "Twig," so it only makes sense that she would be into wood.  I haven't eaten yet today, so I think it's time for nourishment.  I can't get back soon enough.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi...This is Jennie.  I don't really know what's going on except for beaver fornication...And Amy? In regards to that, if its a real tree chewing beaver? Ew. But in the case of men....Georgia anyone? lmfao I believe that's enough to make Amy into a dendrophiliac for life. I think you have to be in on that one to get it.  Yeah...So anyway, I just wanted to say hi, and that I'm here too! Bye bye everybody! :) Ps- I miss you all because its spring break for you you. :( At least on my spring break, I'll be with all of you you! Start counting down! :-D
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Musings on the Subject of Amy's Innocence:      Being who I am (Gina--Great Knower of All Things Worth Knowing and Some Things Apparently Not Worth Knowing Until You Know Them and Then Come to Realize That They Were Truly Worth Knowing All Along), I know the truth.  Amy is indeed innocent.  Yes, it's true, she really is as innocent as she claims to be.  On the surface, that is.  However, deep down, the inner machinations of Amy's mind are anything but innocent.  She would never tell anyone the debaucheries she of which she dreams--seducing a man she just met at a sleezy bar, taking him home, tying him down, and having her way with him, all whilst dressed as a giant banana.  Yes, she may appear and act innocent and pure, but her thoughts dwell in a dirty, naughty gutter that is anything but.    Musings on the Subject of Llamas:      I express my deepest thanks to the owner of the Red Room Which is not Really Red for her support in my great Llama Literation campaign.  As for Amy's views on llamas, some of them are indeed antisocial.  These poor creatures suffer from a wide variety of psychological maladies, due in part to their lack of reading abilties.  Another contributing factor is the long year of oppression their species has suffered, being used as meer pack animals.  Donkies have suffered the same, but have the status of their cousin, the horse to comfort them.  Camels have been rehabilitated in zoos and given the honor of making many a child happy.  Llamas have no such comfort.  They are bitter.  Also a source of much bitterness and a contributing factor to their unhappiness is the alpaca.  The alpaca is very similar to the llama, but for some reason has gained more attention, even having their own television commercial.  Having suffered such oppression and living in such obscurity, it is only natural that the llama would be a bitter, unhappy animal.  People have not been kind to the llama.  I hope you shall take this to heart and bear the antisocial llama no ill will.  I shall end my musings here, for now.  I could easily continue with the subject of cookies and beavers, but I shan't for I grow weary of time and grow frightened of my own musings.  But rest assured I shall return soon to enlighten and terrify all of you.  :)    Until then, I eagerly await the offering of cookies and ponder precisely what else Mr. Brick is planning on making...  Brownies?  Pie?  Babies?  Weapons of Mass Destruction?    Schmoogle...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *whispers*  Amy was uninnocented by beavers.  And there will be no more cookies until my triumphant return from home.  I'm sure I'll be hungry for cookies THEN though.  Plus I have some other things in mind that I could make...stay tuned.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Personally, I kinda though I would know best if I was innocent or not...but ok, you all can debate it. *shrugs* (Y'all know I really am, so ok with me if you really feel the need to make up stories about me) ;-P  Anwayz...llamas are antisocial...at least the ones at the cornfield maze by your house are Gina...but it could be jealousy of my ability to read which made them behave that way. *shrugs again* Back to studying...or perhaps it is S&S break time.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe Amy isn't as innocent as we all thought. Gina would know best, because she has known Amy the longest. And yes Josh and Amy get crackin' cuz Gina deserves cookies to.   And as for literating the llamas, that has become the worlds priority, because llamas are very cool. And we can feed them corn. so yay!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What?  Amy's not innocent anymore?  ::shock::  Is this true?  For if it is I shall laugh heartily.  If it is not I shall still laugh, though not quite as heartily.    I fear the spoon.  Well, on second thought, I don't really fear the spoon but I fear the horrible tickling with which I will be punished should I not fear the spoon.  And since I fear the tickling, I thereby, by default, also fear the spoon.  In a roundabout way.  For that is my way.  I am round and I get about.  Not really, but it sounded funny.  And I'm sure it made you laugh.  It's ok to lie if it makes people laugh and following their laughter you then inform them that you were, in fact, lying.  The Morals of Gina--lesson one.   I want cookies.  You all should know that my taters are rather irked by the fact that I am not present among this motley crew and therefore unable to enjoy the cookie goodness.  I have no cookies of my own.  I think you should mail them to me.    And now for something completely different...  Did you know that llamas are illiterate?  I find this terribly sad.  So sad, in fact, that I have decided to make it my life's work to rectify this problem.  I have found my cause.  Screw the whales, they can save themselves.  The environment, while I care, there are plenty of environmental activist.  But the llamas...  They need me.  I urge you all to join me in my cause.    LITERATE THE LLAMAS!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While that may be true, that was an entirely different situation. Amy was sitting right there, and laughing at what i typed. You had no previous approval to say that about Amy.   SO THAT MEANS I WIN!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would like to point out that I was not the one who told a certain someone that (quote) Amy is not "innocent" anymore. (endquote)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's low Josh, really low. I might have to suspend your powers for being mean.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You should fear the Law.  I AM the Law.  Bwahahaha...  *cough*  And my dear Owner of the World, I'm afraid you DID make a typo there.  But I know what you meant and will get on it as soon as possible.   AND WHAT HONOR?!? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I fear neither the spoon nor your law...which I think you typed differently than you meant to.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amy needs to fear the spoon. Who knows, if she doesn't she may need the spoon to defend her honor one of these days. And if she doesn't fear the spoon it will not defend her.   If you don't fear the spoon, then perhaps you will fear the law i've created for not fearing the spoon.  The law for not fearing the spoon: By order of the owner of the world anyone who doesn't fear the spoon is forced to undergo hours upon hours of tickling by the All Supreme and Cool Dude. If the individual runs away from the punishment they will be bound at the hands and feet and thrown to the mercy of the beavers.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I do.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't fear your spoon.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cookies can be made any time, because I LOVE COOKIES!!!!! As a matter of fact, i'm making that the worlds national food. Cookies are to be eaten as regularly as possible. However, if one does not like cookies, they are required by worldly law to give them to me. That's the only exception to the law.   Yay! i'm glad you fear the spoon, however there will be bodily harm if you are lying about your fear of the spoon. The spoon knows who truly fears and who doesn't.  And the spoon will tell me if you are lying. SO BEWARE OF THE MIND READING SPOON!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can handle that - no more Mountain Dew for Josh at mealtimes.  I DO fear The Spoon, so that is a small sacrifice to make to ensure that it does not inflict bodily harm upon me.  When am I next making cookies?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cookies and sex together wouldn't be a bad thing. You'd just have to be really careful. And i thing that you shouldn't be able to have any  Mountain Dew until Lent is over, because I can't have any. So you should be a part of the misery to.  Also instead of being hit with lightning bolts I think it would be better if people were drug by horses instead, because they would be put into much more pain, and pain is good for bad people. But they wouldn't get punished for bringing food into the Book Room, because I might feel the need to do that and since I'm the owner of the world nothing I do should be against the law.  And Josh, having seen the spoon, you should be in great fear of it. Who knows what punishment could be given with the spoon...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like my Lenten sacrifice - it's so easy.  Cookies + sex = bad.  You want crumbs in the plumbing?  I'm thinking not.  We need to take care of our house, here.  The food has to stay in the giant vault.  If anyone brings food near my Book Room, the Owner of the World will (hopefully, pending approval) zap them with lightning bolts.  The first bolt will tickle, the second will sting, the third will kill.  It's a chance to flex your muscles, OotW...  AHAHAHAHAHA, or like taking pizza away from a homeless man?  That's great fun too.  I have no pity for homeless people.  Luckily we won't have any in this home.  Hm.  So does this mean no more MD for me or just that I have to keep it in my lap or something?  That program causes no little fear in me...  I have seen The Spoon...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't make lasagna because Meijer doesn't have the right kind of sauce. *sigh* I'll have to make it while I'm home and possibly bring some back. Or maybe just get the sauce while I'm home and bring it back and make the lasagna here. Hmm...Nice to see you posting on here G...that should certainly make it interesting. Mika, I will make the cookies with no chocolate chips...I promise. I'm just not sure when. I know it's not me that you're referring to with the mountain dew thing...cuz I gave up ALL pop and cussing. And honestly, I'm not doing it for the right reasons anywayz...so oh well. I'm doing it to prove I can to myself...not to "sacrifice" for the church's sake. Oh well, I believe it's already been determined that I'm going to heck..see ya there! lol ;-P
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want some lasagna... You should bring lasagna to your poor little roommate/past roommate who will be spending her night writing until her hand becomes blue and numb... :)    I think instead of bar cookies, there should be the cookies requested 2 weeks ago... yes, I think that souns  good... No chocolate chip cookie dough.  Lack of chocolate chips always makes me happy!  Today Rachie and I wake up in bad moods.  Mostly because ONCE again, we have no shower... The man had to get 2 people because it's so bad... Yes, what a way to start your day, NO SHOWER.  We thought about going up to the 3rd floor... but it's such a walk... So for now we are grumbling away.    p.s. I want lasagna! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i think you may have a point, but Amy wouldn't let me give up something pointless. That's why i didn't get to give up candy. Because i never eat candy, so i'm not "sacrificing myself", but it would have made it that much easier.   As for eating cookies while having sex, that's kinda ironic, because there are many other things called cookies that are not chocolate chip cookies so it'd be kinda funny, in a way.   Damn not being able to have Mountain Dew, and it's not getting any easier, because SOMEBODY puts it on their tray every fucking day at lunch. Damn the people who flaunt what others want but can't have. It's like eating a sandwich in front of a homeless person.  As owner of the world I'm instating a program that if anyone does this they will be killed with my giant spoon. If anyone has any better ideas feel free to post, and if there any good I might consider adding that punishment as well
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude, this rocks!  Sex rooms and cookies!  Mmmm....  Hey, those are too of my favorite things--sex and cookies.  Perhaps I should combine the two...  Have sex while eating cookies...  ::ponders::  Hehe... yeah...   Will the sex rooms come with toys?  I like toys.  >:)  Whips and chains and paddles... Oh my!  Mwahaha.    In other news, I can drink as much pop and curse just as much as I damn well fucking want.  No Lent for me!  Yay!  And if I observe/celebrate/participate in Lent I'd give up something silly like socks.  Or maybe pants.  Yeah...  Ooh!  Underwear!  That's what I'd give up for Lent.  Hey, maybe I should take part in this whole Lent thing...    Woot!  No undies!  Schmoogle!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Josh, I thought you said you wanted a sex room? You're describing a food room! lol Anywayz...no! Not F Lent! No pop and no cussing. I'm being a good girl. O:-) And Josh has voted for bar cookies next, what do you think Rach? And also, I'm currently planning on making lasagna tomorrow...which is going to require a trip to the store. Wanna come? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dude if someone invented a hose that dispensed Mountain Dew i'd say, "Fuck Lent", Mountain Dew is good. i think instead of the whole Cheese Turd, thingy it would be better if we invested in cookies. i like cookies, and by the way i'm almost out, i think someone needs to get crackin'. lol 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I could probably run some sort of investment scheme.  Or we can use the money that I'm gonna make from selling my "Cheese Turds."  This house definitely needs a huge library with big leather chairs and sofas.  Know what I always wanted?  Remember Scrooge McDuck's giant building of gold coins?  I wanted one that was full of Doritos.  lol  If we could get a hose that will come down to the ceiling that dispenses Mountain Dew, that'd be great too (as soon as Lent is over, of course).
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes! sex rooms for everyone! Just post what you want, and they will put it in there! Of course someone needs to win mondo amounts of money. Or someone needs to rob a bank. Any takers?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want a sex room.  :-(
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, i've finally done it! The craziness of Rachael has been set loose online. But there is no need to fear the insanity, instead everyone should embrace the madness. It will make like that much easier and, anyways why would you want to?  Anyways if you people feel the necessity to criticize me, it doesn't really matter, because the odds of me changing anything are so small you'd be more likely to win the lottery.  Wouldn't it be awesome to win the lottery? I'd buy a house, a mondoly huge house and everyone who lived there would get a sex room. Lots of fun. Oh well i guess that's it for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      30 minutes of riding a Tilt-a-Whirl, non-stop.  That URL is screwy.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is this ride you speak of?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd like to see someone actually try to force me to take the 30-minute ride from Hell.  It would not be good for that unlucky person.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i'm feeling quite satisfied with my decision for a punishment. Maybe now "someone" will be satisfied that eating llamas is illegal.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know who I used this analogy with, but I feel it very accurately describes my feeling concerning the tilt-a-whirley-gigs.  Alcohol.  You know you'll have great fun doing it, but as soon as you're done and you step back you get slammed with a headache/hangover, disorientation, etc.  I paid for that ride with a wicked headache that I actually took meds for as soon as I got back.  30 minutes?  *faints*
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know  I  enjoyed it.  :D
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Perhaps. But I do believe he enjoyed that...:-P
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i don't like this non-fear of the spoon. Perhaps riding the tilt-a-whirl for 30 minutes non-stop would do the trick.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am feeling a distinct lack of fear of the spoon, Rach. lol 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I never denied anything, so there was never an argument to win.  But, as I told Amy last night, fine.  I will let her win.  I'm not going to sweat over punishment at the hands of Gina, seeing as Gina's hands are many, many miles from here.  I'm not going to sweat over punishment from  anyone .
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I love this song.  :-)    Sometimes I get so weird I even freak myself out I laugh myself to sleep It's my lullaby Sometimes I drive so fast Just to feel the danger I wanna scream It makes me feel alive  Is it enough to love? Is it enough to breath? Somebody rip my heart out And leave me here to bleed Is it enough to die? Somebody save my life I'd rather be anything but ordinary please  To walk within the lines Would make my life so boring I want to know that I  Have been to the extreme So knock me off my feet Come on now give it to me Anything to make me feel alive  Is it enough to love? Is it enough to breath? Somebody rip my heart out And leave me here to bleed Is it enough to die? Somebody save my life I'd rather be anything but ordinary please I'd rahter be anything but ordinary please.  Let down your defences Use no common sense If you look you will see  that this world is this beautiful  accident turbulent suculent  I'm feeling permanent No way I won't taste it  Dont wanna waste it away  Sometimes I get so weird I even freak myself out I laugh my self to sleep It's my lullaby  Is it enough? Is it enough? Is it enough to love? Is it enough to breath? Somebody rip my heart out And leave me here to bleed Is it enough to die? Somebody save my life I'd rather be anything but ordinary please  Is it enough? Is it enough to die? Somebody save my life I'd rather be anything but ordinary please I'd rather be anything but ordinary please. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn! i do believe Amy has won the argument. And if memory serves me correctly if anyone is caught eating llamas then they are subject to punishment given by Gina. (ha! my memory is better than Josh's)  *now Josh has a legitimate complaint about someone making fun of his memory.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd be a brat whether I was eating or not, wouldn't I? And why pout about the truth? You know that you have no memory...you even admitted it in the post you put up before that one. :-P
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't say I would MAKE anyone do it, just that I would take people out to eat.  You would be more than welcome to sit there and be a brat.  It'd certainly save me some money.  *pouts over the insults to his memory until he forgets why he was pouting*
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Your memory is shit. lol And you can't make me eat llama!! You can't make me do anything. No one can.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... Well... The only reason I can't think of a place that serves llama off the top of my head is because my memory is so poor.  But as soon as I DO remember/find a place, I will immediately report it back and take everyone out to eat there.  lol  As long as you eat LLAMA!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, actually, I can honestly say that I've never seen llama on a menu.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was a stretch, so sue me.  Can't eat llamas?   I already  have .  Have you never seen llama on a menu?
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And i thought it was a waste of space to have something up that didn't work. So i deleted it The last time i checked that wasn't faking reality. I think Josh is just saddened that he can't eat llamas.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't fake reality, but what's the point in leaving up a picture that doesn't work? I never tried to hide the fact that I tried to help Rach post what she wanted to post, but it didn't work, so she deleted them. *shrugs*
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Your supposed Matrix pictures are not working.  Nicely done.  Or, when something doesn't work, pretend it didn't happen, right?  Fake some reality?  Change all of the stories, newspapers, and books to reflect the "fact" that you never tried?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay for me!!! I did it!! :-P *Does happy dance*
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ha! Amy figured it out! So Josh loses
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, but who will be the first to figure out how I was able to do it all?  It should be obvious to anyone with an intelligence greater than say...a llama.  Since, however, the llamas are less than astute academes, they should be put to the only rational alternative - feeding third world countries.  And me.  Re:  Persons other than myself winning.  Perhaps this one will make more of an impact, since it is phrased in a nicer fashion.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You may complain about my threats, but obviously they worked, because you posted pictures. So ha!  I WIN 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yes.  I forgot.  This is the Picasso that I'm looking for.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Re: Threats made to my image due to circumstances that are being exploited and twisted to evil purposes.    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that will speed up the process considerably. LMAO. Though that's just my humble opinion, of course. Which Josh will deem irrelevant as I'm sure it won't coincide with his. He. He.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that I've had some time to think about it, I've decided that Josh is definately in trouble. If Gina were here to punish i would leave it up to her, however Gina isn't here so  punishment is up the all-knowing and all-powerful Rachael     And here is my decree:    Until Josh reveals his knowledge of posting pictures he will be known as the man who led girls straight to gay porn.  .  I think this will speed up the process of knowledge.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uh oh. Josh is in trouble, methinks. He. He.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So is this the kind of person Josh has become? a person who offers knowledge but doesn't deliver,   a spoiled brat who refuses to share?  If this is so, then i'm saddened. Perhaps some punishment from the spoon is necessary.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm just going to breathe a sigh of relief and keep that knowledge to myself.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, you shall not get in trouble, for the Knower of All is humble and willing to admit that, in spite of her vast wealth of knowledge, her title is misleading--there are, in fact, things she does not know.  I am sure this comes as a shock, but it's true.  And so, I shall not beat you mercilessly or anything and instead shall welcome your offer of knowledge.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Will I get in trouble if I mention the fact that I know how to make it post pictures?
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      See? I told you that you wouldn't/couldn't slap me
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not the tilt-a-whirl!  NOOOOOOOO!!  *edited in the interest of saving the appearance of the page*
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You wouldn't slap me. Need i remind you of my tilt-a-whirl punishment? I think not.  Oh by the way our gang is called the "Screaching Limes", i may have spelled that wrong, but you get it I know. Well at least i hope you do. Bye all 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I could slap the next person who calls me old.  They're already calling me Old Man at work.  Kevin, behind the meat counter, said "Yeah, you're gonna feel REALLY old tomorrow morning."  I've only had...three glasses of wine?  Not sure...I shared, but it was a big bottle and it's almost empty, lol.  Current mood:  grapey.  And Grandma still owes me a bottle - w00t!  Typing is definitely not up to par...so I think it's time to stop.  Mucho lovin' to my...gang members...what the fuck is our gang called?  REPRESENT!  REPRESENT!  REPRESENNTTTTTTTT  No more typey for Joshy.  Bye bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, happy birthday to Josh! now you are officially old; how does it feel?
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      :-D  Nothing like a birthday to bring a little color to the scene.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Happy birthday   to you.   Happy birthday   to you.   Happy birthday,   Wittle Joshy.  Happy birthday   to you.  Don't have *too*   much fun!  Happy 21st! Love   ya!!;-P   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yes i did see the love from my fellow Buddha, and it brought mondo happiness. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      :-(  I missed a call from my Buddha.  Immense sadness.  Hopefully my Buddha saw at least ONE of the IMs of love that I left her though.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I figured I would just let you know that I'm leaving for FL really really early Wednesday morning so if you wanna say goodbye before I go and I'm not online, you can call here. I don't expect any calls, just wanted to let you know. Since I'm still in depressed mode, I'm probably not gonna be very fun to talk to so I wouldn't call me if I were you, but I'm not you so do what you want. Maybe I'll start the whoring in FL, right? Don't worry, I'll stay away from Dan. lol Nah, don't worry. To be a whore you have to be wanted. lol So there will most likely be no whoring for Amy. Ok, I'm just getting whiny and really pathetic now. Time to go "sleep." (Like I'm getting any of that lately...:-\) Yeah. Byezers. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* i miss all you guys too! lack of communication is bad. Thank you Amy for talking to Dan (a.k.a. princess)lol. I talked to him that night as well just on the phone. so yes i know he doesn't hate me. (like he ever really did, but moving on)I'm sorry that your dog died, you can have one of mine if you like. they are a pain in the ass though, but i don't think you would mind. you would have to have the girl puppy, cuz i like the other 2 too much to give them away. So you should just tell me, and i'll drive you a dog. Don't ask how i'm gonna drive you a dog as i dont' have a car, but i'll get it done. lol okay i'm done for now, byes everyone! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone distappeared! :-( I miss you guys all over again. lol I was starting to get used to the aloneness and then you guys came back for a couple days and now I'm missing you again. lol Rach, I talked to Dan today--he said that he missed talking to you so I told him to write you an email. I also informed him that if he was expecting any more letters/cookies from me that he'd best get writing cuz I was serious about getting a letter from him. lol He asked me what to write. lol He also threatened to send me pictures of naked old men. It didn't occur to me at the time to ask why such pictures would be in his possession, but that is an interesting point to me now that I think about it. *shrugs* Anywho...I told him he'd better not cuz I'd get even. lol So yeah. In sadder news--my doggy died today. :'-( He got runned over. :'-( Anyway, I will talk to you guys later. Ttfn. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually no I'm here so I can't be there. You are there obviously though. Okay I'm done being a smartass for now. I miss everybody! I haven't seen anyone in forever. But yay for me cuz Amy is coming to see me today so yeah. That is mondo happiness. Anyways I've got some amazing news. I actually walked up to a guy and asked him his name. Yeah me Rachael. Odd huh? Actually if you knew the whole story you wouldn't think it odd, but I'm not typing the whole thing out so you can ask if you really wanna know. *sigh* now I have to go work. blah. Byes for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *poke* Anyone in there?? ;-P
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      :-P Boo! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>