<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday night after bible study - contemplate studying for a methods multiple choice/short answer exam, and write a cheat sheet for it Outcome: On the computer downloading music, fight videos and chatting until about 1  Saturday afternoon after chinese school and piano lesson - contemplate finish typing up notes legal studies exam and write cheat sheet for methods exam Outcome: On the computer downloading music, fight videos, typing blogs and talking to Yolanda  Sunday afternoon after church - contemplate notes for legal/cheat sheet for methods Outcome: watched Shrek, Legally Blonde, Spanish Moto GP and a bit of the Canadian GP  Monday - contemplate studying for methods and legal Outcome: wake up at 1030, go delivery with dad, go for BBQ lunch at an old friend of mum's. Now I'm at my cousin's house for a party of some unknown reason  Moral: a totally wasted effort, partly on my behalf. I was thinking of studying. I made a promise to both methods and legal teachers that I would be very confident walking into the exam room and ready to complete the exams easily on any given day. Pfft... sif!  Seriously though, if the subject matters, study for it - it will only benefit u in the long run - not anybody else
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is the main use of a computer? According to www.dictionary.com, a computer is "A device that computes, especially a programmable electronic machine that performs high-speed mathematical or logical operations or that assembles, stores, correlates, or otherwise processes information."  According to Rich, a computer has three integral fucntions that ensure the survival of man and ensure that men have a good time whilst alleviating boredom: CHAT/EMAIL, PORN and MP3S. In this post, I will outline how these 3 facets of the computer are the most principle of it's existence, and why this post is no way whatsoever demoralising women, defamation is not my contention for such a post. Any chances of male chauvinism will be eradicated upon request and this blog will be deemed unfit for a woman to read.   CHAT/EMAIL: Email, an electronic medium of communication between two or more parties, with communication being the transfer of information, ideas and feedback in order to reach a certain destination or accomplish a certain goal. [Nick Korfiatis, Business Management 3&4, 2004]. This is some what a plausible definition for chat/email.However, we must divulge the benefits and disadvantages of email, although right now I don't see any disadvantages. One benefit, is that it saves money. Why waste 40 cents on a phone call, or waste 15 cents for 30 seconds [depending on your operator], plus a 25 cent flagfall, when you only have to say one thing? The money can be more usefully disposed. Perhaps a fork or straw at the Haileybury canteen? Also, are you able to share English essays, or Chemistry Prac Reports over the phone? I dearly think not. Without email, people like John Hak or Peter Tao would be deprived of their homework sharing services. As you can see, chat/email serves as a great medium for communication, and is great for those assignments due the following day, in an attempt to escape the wrath of detention.  PORN: Ahh.. porn. Porn can actually be a great thing for everyone to enjoy - IF the stereotype and stigma placed upon it as a burden is removed. How is everyone supposed to enjoy porn if we are denied mainstream access, or if there is such negativity towards it? If it is perfectly fine for two ladies to indulge in the pleasures of physical and sexual attraction, then why is not perfectly fine for us to see it? And why is there such a commotion about female homosexuality anyway? If they enjoy it, and want the world to see it, then by all means let them! Come on! Oh, and what about this "what if my kids see it?" business? Well, referencing my last English essay on cencorship - "Children who are exposed to reality instead of living a life full of fantasy learn a far better lesson from a computer or television, a lesson that far exceeds what is being taught in the classroom." In saying that, I don't mean that we should let them see "Debbie does Dallas" instead of teaching them how the uterus is stimulated by the penis. If we prohibit access from them, it will only make them more curious to explore its greatness. If a child is able to procure porn, they will be ready for their first experience when they are older, no need to search for that dreaded "World of Science" textbook that was so unsatisfactorily taught by Ms. Crook in Year 7.  MP3S: What can I say about mp3's. Well, it saves money. Why would you spend $25 dollars on a CD when you can download it? "Oh but what about the cover? And Lyrics?" Well, a quick "Google it" [another benefit of a computer - no need to travel to a library to find ONE book out of MANY on anything] can find discography's which readily stock front and back covers of the original cd, and www.lyricstime.com provides a good source for lyrics so you can sing to the music.  Well there you have it. I think it is clear that the main functions of a computer are not viable without the use of "Internet". This very clever creation has most definitely improved the lives of many around the world, mentally, physically, socially, spritually and sexually.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah that's right YoLaNda - U sMeLL. Just because you work at Shark Fin with Becky doesn't mean you have the right to say that I smell! Pfftt.. Sure mate! I'd say something about Chemistry but then I think I'll get bashed! :P LOL! Yeah well this took me about 3 minutes to write because I had to get rid of some crazy shit. So your lucky!  Peace out  Rich
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many a time, we are faced by pressures that arise from anything. Whether it be parents, friends, teachers or anything, there are always certain instigators of our stress and depression. How do we cope? That is the big question. Some are just mentally capable of usually their own will power. Some are not so fortunate. Some contemplate suicide. I can tell you now that it got to a time where it was an option I was contemplating.  Myself like some, decided to take up smoking. For a while it worked, and for a while it didn't. But it did get addictive. And let me tell you, that's not a good thing. I know quite many people who smoke and everyday they tell me that they hate it. Then why do it? Well its like Pringles - once you oop you cant stop. But luckily for myself, I have limited it to 2 decks a week to a one or two here and there every once or so weeks.   People, don't smoke, don't try any drugs, and most of all, don't do anything crazy. I've been there and trust me, it's not a path that you want to cross. You will meet people who seem ok at first, then drag you in then thats when you're fucked. The best way, I think to cope with stress, is to do what I'm doing. Make a journal or a diary. Write. Let your emotions run wild.   If writing isn't your forte, then the next best thing is to talk. Talk to someone. Your best mate, your girlfriend/boyfriend, the guy next door, anyone who is willing to listen. It's good when you have someone to listen. Even if you think it's the last person you thought that would listen. At school, it's Ms G. Shit, sometimes I even skip class to go and see her. Well she is a psychologist so it does help!  If you think your going to have trouble getting that TER you want, or getting that 50/50, or you're thinking that you're going to fail something, your talking shit. If you are studying, then you're doing something. Your only going to fail when you say so if you're sitting on your ass watching tv saying it. Anyhow, I'm crapping on, and I really hope you take what I have to say seriously, and if you are like me, struggling to cope with the pressures of life, just always remember that God is always watching over you - so that means if you want to get in the good books, don't try any crazy shit
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone! I decided to do one of these things after reading Peter's. It seemed quite interesting. I've always looked for something for an outlet of expression. Perhaps now I have found it...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>