<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That is all that is going through my head right now.  Why does it have to be like this?  Why didn't I do this or that?  Why didn't she say this or that?  Why?  Why?  Why?!  This is the most awful thing I have ever been through in my life.  Maybe I'm just being overly dramatic but maybe I'm not.  All I know is that it sucks, it hurts and I wouldn't wish any of it on my worst enemy.  I wish I had all the answers or at least knew what to say to make it all better....
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was telling Stacey the other night that until October of 2001 I had never known anyone in my life that I could stand to be around 24/7.  October of 2001 was when my friendship with a certain Ms. Fowler began.  She's someone that I can be around every second of the day and never think that I need to get away or have a minute to myself.  I know everyone needs some "me" time every now and then, but I've needed less of that since I met her.    That says a lot if you ask me......    Funny word of the day:    urlLink callipygian 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not that I didn't know this before....but this crappy experience has only reinforced what kick ass friends and family I have.  Thanks for being there for me and listening to me babble.    Word of the day:    urlLink maladroit   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      How come I can see it all from a new perspective now?  I feel like I'm seeing things from her eyes for the first time.  Does that make me a bad person?  Or was I really just that stubborn?  And does she really believe me when I say that I can see it from her perspective?  I don't think she does.  It would  have  to make a huge difference if she did.  I feel like I need to scream or break something.  I know it won't fix things but I'm so frustrated right now.  I also feel like I'm going to go crazy.  Every e-mail and phone call I've received in the last week has brought a faint hope that it was her writing/calling to tell me she had changed her mind and that everything was going to be OK.    I still can't believe she is doing this.  It's not getting any easier.  If I wasn't half numb right now I don't think I could even get out of bed.  It is a true living hell.    Word of the day:    urlLink clairvoyant 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I always thought I was one of those solitary people that could spend the rest of their life alone if they had to.  I've definitely learned in the last year or so that is not the case anymore.  There is one person I want to spend the rest of my life with.  It's totally my loss that she doesn't feel the same way.  I almost feel like I'm starting to go on and on about all of this.  But at the same time I feel like crap and need to get it off my chest.  I'm sure she's getting sick of hearing it, so I'll just continue doing it here for now.  Another thing I've learned the last week or so is how unimportant some of the little things that bother me really are.  (Example:  In the last week or so I've probably been cut off 5 times driving up and down the highway.  In the past that would have pissed me off.  Did it this last week?  Nope.  I realize now there are better things to focus my energy on.)  She tried for the last two years to get that through my thick skull.  The thing that I didn't get was how it affected her too.  Guess I should have listened, huh?  It's terrible that it had to come to this to get me to truly look at things from her perspective.  It makes me feel like I'm going to vomit.    Word of the day:   urlLink misanthropic   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got the Pauline Reese CD I ordered in the mail today.  It's called  urlLink Trail to Monterrey .  Remember me saying I bought it because KVET was playing a song of hers I really liked?  The name of that song?  Don't Leave Me Standing Here.    Of course that was the first song I listened to when I popped the CD in my computer.  I guess I hadn't really listened to the lyrics very close up until tonight.  Seems those lyrics do a really good job summing up how I feel right now.  I'll get those written down and post them a little later....  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ OK, it's Tuesday morning and here are the lyrics as promised:   Don't Leave Me Standing Here  Billy White Jr.  Don’t leave me standing here Wanting to hold you dear If I can’t have you near I’ll be fallin’ apart You tell me have no fear And you sound so sincere But if I can’t have you dear I’ll be fallin’ apart  I don’t want to lose you We’ve worked too hard to stay And I just can’t face the thought Of you goin’ away Let’s work this together As we have in the past Just one can tear love apart It takes two to make it last  So don’t leave me standing here Wanting to hold you dear If I can’t have you near I’ll be fallin’ apart You tell me have no fear And you sound so sincere But if I can’t have you dear I’ll be fallin’ apart  Why o why Can’t we work this out Lord don’t you know That’s what love is all about  Why tell me why Can’t we work this out Oh don’t you know  That’s what love is all about  Don’t leave me standing here Wanting to hold you dear If I can’t have you near I’ll be fallin’ apart And you tell me have no fear And you sound so sincere But if I can’t have you dear I’ll be fallin’ apart  So don’t take your love my dear You’ll be breaking my heart
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Over the course of the last four days I must have asked myself a million questions.  The one that really kills me is one that I can't even answer.  Why didn't I do a better job letting her know how damn much she means to me?  Why?!  Why?!  Why?!  The only possible explanation I can offer is that I am an idiot.  I absolutely hate myself because it had to come to this.  I hope she knows my life wouldn't be the same without her.  Here are some of the other things that have been running through my head the last few days:  Does she know how much  I love her ?  Does she know how much I love that smile? Does she know how much I love those cute little dimples? Does she know how much I love that beautiful auburn hair? Does she know how much I love her beautiful blue eyes? Does she know how beautiful I think she is? Does she know how much better my life is since she walked in to it? Does she know how much better my day gets the instant I see her? Does she know that I can come home in a crappy mood and it instantly disappears when I walk in the door because I know she's on the other side of it? Does she know how much my world lights up when I get that smile and wink from her? Does she know how much I love to lie there and watch her sleep on Saturday and Sunday mornings? Does she know how much I love those mangy mutts?  ;-) Does she know how much Poopie loves her? Does she know how much I love our little "family"? Does she know how much I was looking forward to expanding our family with her? Does she know what a wonderful mother I think she is going to make? Does she know how great I think her family is? (They're the reason she's the wonderful person she is!) Does she know how proud I would be for her to share my last name? Does she know how much I appreciate every single thing she does for me? Does she know how much I wish I could do more for her? Does she know how much I wish I could ease all her pain? Does she know how much I wish I could take back any pain I have caused her? Does she know how much I wish I could erase every bad memory she's ever had? Does she know how much I wish I were more of a gentleman around her? Does she know how much I wish I had been more appreciative when she gave me a compliment? Does she know that I wish all my idiosyncrasies didn't drive her up the wall? Does she know that my world revolves around her? Does she know she is my best friend in the entire world? Does she know she will  always  be one of my best friends? Does she know she is the kindest human being I have ever met? Does she know that I wish I was as good of a person as she is? Does she know that the thought of living without her kills me? Does she know how bad it kills me when she doesn't call me "sweetie" or "honey"? Does she know how secure it makes me feel to know she is sleeping beside me? Does she know that I would do anything for her? Does she know how much I worry about her safety when she is not by my side?  Most importantly, does she know how much  I love her ? (I'm afraid to answer this one.)  God, I pray she knows....
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If this works out I'm buying a few lottery tickets because I'll be the luckiest man on the face of the planet....   Word of the day:   urlLink abhorrent    Bonus word of the day:   urlLink nauseous   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It really, really sucks......  I hope she knows I love her and that I would do absolutely anything for her.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Something I just thought of.......if you guys haven't been to see  urlLink Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  get off your butts and go.  Summer and I saw it last Saturday and we both really enjoyed it.    If you saw the first two and liked them you won't be disappointed with this one.  If you haven't seen the first two, get off your butts and rent them.  They're not just for kids!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Guess what I got? I just bought it this evening at the brand new Apple store at Barton Creek Square Mall. I'm still trying to figure everything out, but so far it kicks ass!  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This one was taken just a few minutes ago. I told you the grass didn't look as bad now as it did last summer!  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got an  urlLink Evite  from Paul on Thursday.  Seems he and Parker were itching to plan a little Clint reunion.  They decided Austin was a central location (central between Ft. Worth and Missouri?).  This is all scheduled for the weekend of July 10.  The plan is to hit the lake during the day and  urlLink 6th Street  at night.  Paul has invited a crapload of people so this should be one interesting weekend....  I've known about Evite for quite some time now but this is the first Evite I've ever received.  To be a big ol' geek, I also sent out my very first Evite earlier this evening.  I invited the fam to go see my friend Robyn open for her brother  urlLink Bruce  at  urlLink Gruene Hall  on June 19.  Not bad for a hick from Clint, huh?  In unrelated music news.....I've found a new local artist I really like.  Her name is  urlLink Pauline Reese  and she's got a really nice voice.  I've heard her on with  urlLink Sammy & Bob  several times but never really paid much attention to her.  That was until they added one of her songs to the  urlLink Genuine Texas Music CD  and started playing it a whole bunch.  I decided that I liked that song enough that I ordered her latest CD off of her website today.  I need to get the GTM CD also.  Lots of good songs on it...    Word of the day:    urlLink asperity 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is where we live! This picture is from some time last summer. I promise the grass doesn't look that crappy anymore!  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not entirely sure what to think of President Reagan's death. It's pretty sad but I think that we all knew this was coming sooner rather than later. After all he was 93, right?   I know many people didn't agree with his policies but I think we can all agree he was a genuinely good person.  And you’ve got to admire the  urlLink relationship  that he and Nancy had.  We could all be so lucky.  Summer and I watched his  urlLink  state funeral ceremony  on TV last night and it was all so surreal.  At the same time it got me really choked up when Vice President Cheney escorted Nancy to his casket.  The scene of Michael approaching the casket, saying a few words and then saluting was also a very powerful image.  Those are two images that will stay with me for a very long time.  I was born while Ford was president but I have no memories of him or Carter. Ronald Reagan was the first man that I can remember seeing and saying, "That's the President of the United States of America." To me this man was the presidency. That's why I can't help but feel somewhat emotionally involved in his death.    I believe it is safe to say heaven is now Reagan Country. We'll all miss you Ronnie.....       Word of the day:    urlLink quietus  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK, first things first.  Y'all are going to ask where the I got the URL from and what it means.  I only choose the "Viandante del Cielo" part.  Where did that come from, you might ask?  It comes from me being a big dork!  Unfortunately,  urlLink http://skywalker.blogspot.com  and  urlLink http://darthvader.blogspot.com  were taken so I had to settle.  Click  urlLink here  and it will be self explanatory (or at least it should be).  If that link doesn't work, please let me know.  The second thing you will probably ask me is, "Why did you decide to blog?"  Well, I've been keeping up with a few blogs over the last year or so and have come across some very entertaining stuff.  February 19, 2004 was the first time I really thought "hey, that might be fun to do!"  What happened on February 19?  Go  urlLink here  and read all about it (that is Summer's boss for those of you that don't know).  Even after being inspired by Rex, nothing happened between February 19 and today.  What really gave me a push to do this was my big sister.  I've enjoyed reading Stacey's  urlLink blog  since she started it on May 13, 2004, and finally decided I was going to try too.  So here we are....  You might also ask if I have a Mission Statement for my blog.  The answer is yes and no.  I'll expand on this a little more at a later date.  Another thing I think I'm going to do here is a word of the day.  Why?  Because I am not happy with my vocabulary and have decided I am going to make an effort to improve it.  Will I keep up and do a new word every single day?  Probably not.  But I'll try to do one each time I post, which I'm hoping will be at least 2 to 3 times a week.  I still haven't decided if I will post a definition each day or leave it up to you guys to look it up.  On to today's word......   Today's word is   urlLink deign   (v) :    intransitive senses  - to condescend reluctantly and with a strong sense of the affront to one's superiority that is involved  transitive senses  - to condescend to give or offer   Oh yeah....I'm an engineer not an English major.  So please forgive any gross grammatical errors or misspellings.  I know that's not a very good excuse, but I'll do my best.  One other thing I almost forgot....I decided to code all the links I post so that they open in a new window.  You'll need to disable your pop-up blockers if you want to keep up with what I'm linking to.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In keeping with yesterday's theme, here's  urlLink something  that had me, Summer, and Stacey cracking up last night. Enjoy....    Word of the day:    urlLink munificent 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a great  urlLink website  that you should all check out. Make sure you watch the video&nbsp;titled  Kerry Iraq Documentary .......     Word of the day:   urlLink animadversion 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    As if we haven't spent enough money lately, Summer and I  urlLink bought  a couple of bicycles last Thursday. We decided that since we have lived across the street from the  urlLink Veloway  (scroll to bottom of the page that opens) for over a year, it was time to check it out. The bikes are the  urlLink Sedona  model made by Giant. So far, we're both really impressed and happy with them. My bike looks exactly like the one above and Summer's is merlot and charcoal.   This is part of our new commitment to do some different things and do more stuff together.  Hopefully, this is something we'll stick with.  It certainly looks promising at the moment. urlLink     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For those of you that don't know, Summer came home on Saturday. It looks like we have resolved most of our issues, but we still have a few we are working on. So far, so good though!   There is no way I could possibly make you guys understand how happy I am!     Word of the day:   urlLink efficacious     
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's done!&nbsp; My application for the  urlLink P.E. exam  got turned in today at 1:30.&nbsp; Thank God that whole process is over!&nbsp; I guess it really wouldn't have been so bad if I hadn't dragged so much ass.&nbsp; Oh well,&nbsp;it's done now.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  If I remember correctly, it's 105 days until the exam.&nbsp; My plan is&nbsp;to start studying 100 days&nbsp;out.&nbsp; I guess I'll start out with an hour or so a day and work my way up as the exam&nbsp;gets closer.&nbsp; I'll also devote a couple of whole weekends between now and then to studying.&nbsp; Hold me back!&nbsp; I'm having so much fun!  &nbsp;  Now I feel like I need to sleep for three days straight.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let me do my best Howard Dean impersonation....... aaaaaarrrrrgggggghhhhhhh!!!!!!!! I am so damn glad I won't ever have to prepare this damn P.E. application again. What a giant pain in the ass! If I finish this by Friday, it will be nothing short of a miracle...    Word of the day:   urlLink procrastinate  (as in Cole is the biggest procrastinator in the history of the world!) 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was just doing a little reminiscing and thought of some dates that have become very important to me over the last 2-1/2 years.  I’m not going to share what these dates are (were), but she knows.  I’m also pretty sure she has some she could add to this list.  These are just the ones I thought of off the top of my head.  I will not soon forget these dates....  Jan. 16, 2002 Jan. 22, 2002 Jan. 29, 2002 June 7, 2003 June 17, 2004    Word of the day:    urlLink loiter 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am by no means a Woody Allen fan, but I came across this today and it made me laugh. I've felt like this many times throughout the last 2-1/2 years...    "I was nauseous and tingly all over. I was either in love or I had smallpox."  ---Woody Allen      Word of the day:   urlLink hebetude  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just finished reading about Stacey's Fourth of July  urlLink weekend  and decided to share how sad and pathetic mine was.  My plan for the weekend was to crank out my application for the  urlLink P.E. exam .  That didn't happen and instead it went down as follows.  I started my weekend by watching the  urlLink Winn-Dixie 250  on Friday night.  It was an excellent race and it actually ended up being one of the highlights of my weekend.  Saturday was spent doing yard work.  I got up and was at it by 9:00.  I mowed the lawn, edged, and swept the driveway and sidewalk.  I was done by 10:30 or so.  Summer showed up about noon so that we could get after the back yard.  Before we started that we took a bunch of old clothes and crap to  urlLink Goodwill .  We also grabbed lunch at  urlLink Subway  while we were out.  After lunch we were feeling lazy and couldn't get motivated to get started outside.  So we were bums and watched a recorded episode of  urlLink Six Feet Under .  When that was over we finally got started on the back yard.  There wasn't really much to be done to tell you the truth.  We trimmed some low hanging tree branches, pulled a few weeds, and put down some mulch in the flowerbed to cover up bare spots.  We made it inside and got cleaned up in time for the start of the  urlLink Pepsi 400 .  The only problem was that the race had a two-hour rain delay.  Summer had planned to stay for the race but decided to leave about 7:30 or so.  As you can probably imagine, that's where the weekend started to go downhill.    I watched the race when it finally started and made it through Saturday evening feeling fairly decent.  Sunday morning was a different story though.  I woke up at about 7:30 and couldn't really go back to sleep.  (That seems to be the case these days.  I've had no problem going to sleep at night but as soon as I wake up, I'm wide awake.  Guess it's because I start thinking about all the B.S. and my brain goes in to overdrive.)  Anyway....the plan was to get to work on the application Sunday morning and really go after until Monday afternoon.  As I said before, that didn't happen.  I don't know what it was but I was really feeling down.  About the only thing I could get motivated to do was a couple of loads of laundry.  I finally called the folks around 1:00 or 2:00 and told my mom I couldn't take it anymore.  I needed to get the hell outta here so off to San Antonio it was.    I got there about 5:30 and met my parents and their friends Bob and Mary for dinner.  We ate at a restaurant at the Quarry called  urlLink Piatti .  It was pretty good food and I had a good time hanging with the old people.  We were back to the 'rents house by 8:00 or so and we got comfortable and popped in a movie (my dad is still really proud of his surround sound system!).  We watched  urlLink Seabiscuit  and I must say I was pretty impressed with it.  You guys may or may not know that I was really in to horse racing when I was a kid so that made this movie particularly enjoyable for me.  After the movie it was off to bed and I slept like a baby.  Monday morning we got up and went to the hospital to visit my grandmother.  She was admitted last Wednesday for an apparent stroke.  Turns out she was just having more problems with her gall bladder and had some kind of infection.  She was supposed to go home from the hospital sometime today (I don't know at this time if they actually released her or not).  After the hospital visit it was time for lunch.  We went back to the house to pick up my dad and headed for  urlLink Charlie's .  If you guys are ever in Helotes, you've got to eat there.  They have the best refried beans I've had in a long, long time.  Needless to say, I was freakin' stuffed when we left.  We headed back to the house after lunch and I tried to help my dad set up his wireless DSL router.  We had no luck so I hit the road for Austin about 5:30 or so.  I was home by 7:00 and spent the rest of the evening being lazy.    Well maybe it wasn't as pathetic a weekend as I originally thought it was, but it sure felt like it at the time....    Word of the day:    urlLink sentient 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Here's a cool little accessory I got for my iPod mini. As you can tell it's called an iTrip. It's an FM transmitter that will let you play music from your iPod on any FM radio. You can get more info. on it  urlLink here .  It came in the mail yesterday and I used it in the truck and at work today. So far I give it a big thumbs up!!  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First Reagan, now Brando!  Will it ever stop?  Ha, ha.  In case you guys hadn't heard....Marlon Brando  urlLink died  yesterday at age 80.  I don't mean to poke fun at his death but I couldn't resist the urge to joke a little bit.  God knows I haven't been able to do much of that lately.  Anyway, the real point of this post was just to chime in with my opinion of the  urlLink Godfather trilogy .  I don't know what you guys are waiting for if you have never seen these movies.  The first two are awesome and I can take or leave the third one.  I'd venture a guess that most people will just pass on the third movie.    If you've got a spare nine hours this weekend, go rent these movies and pay tribute to Academy Award winner Marlon Brando.....     
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All I can do now is pray that she gives me a chance.  It doesn't have to be right this minute or tomorrow or even next week.    Just a chance.    I don't know how the hell I will do it, but I know I can prove to her how different things can be.  If she can find it in her heart to try and forget the bad stuff and focus on the good times, we can make it work.  I've never been this committed to anything in my entire life.  I also know I'll have to work my ass off to convince her that I will never hurt her again.  That won't be easy either.  I'll just have to hope she hears my words and chooses to believe them.    Word of the day:    urlLink fortuitous 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know I'm a little behind the eight ball, but here is something you should all go look at....   urlLink Moore: Bush 'Didn't Tell the Truth'   Don't worry about reading the transcript. That doesn't do the interview any justice. You've got to watch the video. In almost the middle of the page there is a box with two tabs on it. One tab says  Photos  and the other says  Video .  Click on the  Video  tab and then click on the  O'Reilly vs. Moore  link within that box.  Choose your player preferences and then sit back and relax.  After seeing that interview clip, I can't believe anyone on the left is actually embracing this guy. He's such a joke. "Would you send your child to Iraq?" Is that the best comeback he had for O'Reilly? Please. Propaganda at it's finest......     Word of the day:    urlLink cretin  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Summer and I took the day off and went to  urlLink Schlitterbahn  yesterday. It's been several years since I'd been there and I almost didn't recognize the place. It is now divided in to  urlLink two  parts: Schlitterbahn East and Schlitterbahn West. Schlitterbahn West is the original part of the park. The last time the girls and I went, part of Schlitterbahn East had just opened up and I remember that the Boogie Bahn was brand new.  We got there at about 11:00 and stayed till about 5:30. We probably would have been there a little longer if the rain and lightning hadn't started. At that point they closed down all the rides, so we just hit the road. Because of the long lines, we didn't get everything in that we wanted to but we still had a lot of fun.  Even though I was expecting it, I was still shocked at how easily our money disappeared yesterday. We spent $84 in the 6.5 hours ($12.92/hr.) we were there. I can't imagine what it would be like to take a family for day. At least kids have a reduced price for admission and you could always pack some food and drinks in an ice chest. So what will $84 get you at Schlitterbahn? Admission for two adults, three slices of pizza and two drinks for lunch, two bottles of water, one souvenir golf ball, and sunburn for two. These kind of places are such a rip off.  I think Summer would agree that we had a pretty good time overall. Now if I could just figure out a way to not have to stand in line with annoying people.....  Oh, one other thing. As we headed for I-35 on the way out of New Braunfels, we stopped at a  urlLink Taco Bell  right off 46 for a snack. We both got a burrito and a Caramel Apple Empanada. I think the Caramel Apple Empanada is going to be a new must have item when I visit Taco Bell. Mmmmm! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a good  urlLink article  from Mickey Spagnola....... 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What is wrong with these dopes? First  urlLink Ricky , now  urlLink Quincy . What could possibly be going through their heads? Do they not know what a golden opportunity playing in the  urlLink NFL  is?  I guess it's easy for me to sit here and question them. I don't have the athletic ability that they do, and have never had people kissing my ass the way they probably do. I'm sure they live very jaded lives. But did they not ever stop and think how great their lives were/are? I just can't fathom why they would let something as stupid as drugs mess up their near perfect lives.....    Word of the day:   urlLink flummox  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Poor TJ finally went in for his teeth cleaning today.  This picture is from last night.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    And this one is from tonight. The vet tech suggested that if we could commit to brushing his and Bugsy's teeth once a week, we would be doing much better than the "average American with a dog." He goes back in six months for a follow-up visit.  Before today's cleaning, TJ could yawn and fill a room with that puppy breath. But now he smells like a walk through the  urlLink Wildflower Center ! What a difference a day makes! (Special guest posting from Summer tonight.)  urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>