<Blog>


<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Today I am going on vacation. To the big city of Adams, ND. Lately, it seems that Adams is my favorite vacation destination. Who needs fancy museums and pristine beaches? Adams has 1 bar, 1 church, and 1 store... oh yeah, it also has family. That's the best reason to go to Adams.&nbsp; urlLink     The downside of Adams? No internet access. There will be no postings to the blog until Monday. I know. Very sad.   But here is a little something to keep you occupied! Time for another ranking! What are your favorite small towns to visit? Why? What draws you to Grigla? Edinburg? Coon Rapids?
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I am not athletic. I am okay with that. However, I do like bowling. Today I went bowling and got an all-time high score of 106! Very exciting.   Things I learned about bowling: 1. A heavier ball knocks down more pins 2. I bowl better when I only drink diet coke 3. If I were to join a league, I would have a hot pink bowling ball  So, let's hear from you! Athlete or not... What are your top three sports to play? Why?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    draft&nbsp; urlLink     You don't want to admit it... but you have found yourself sucked into the bachelor's big decision or the back-stabbing in the Outback. Rank your top three favorite reality tv shows. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I need to hear from you! What have you observed? What do you think?  Every day the blog will feature the "question of the day." Have a suggestion for a question? Just e-mail me.  Let's start it off easy. We all like to rank things...   What are your top three candy treats? &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For those of you who don't know... my good friend Sara is my inspiration. She always has great ideas and "tasks" for me to do. Sometimes I do them with great speed and energy. Other times I need a bit more pushing and nagging. Her latest idea is for me to have a blog site. She said I don't have to be clever. I can just talk about my opinion. That sounds great. I love to share my opinions.  So, here it is. My blog site.   Talk about people--President Bush or your best friend. Talk about things-- bean burritos from Taco Bell or dogs. Talk about events-- upcoming weddings or the premiere of the latest reality TV wonder- show.   Make judgments. Share opinions. Remember- sarcasm and "tongue in cheek" humor is key. Don't be offended easily.   This blog is a place for all comments-- funny, mean, total lies, whatever. It's okay if you spell things wrong or don't use complete sentences.   Let's get started. 
     
    
</post>


<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have some fond memories of the great (and not-so-great) teachers from our time at RRHS.  Who was your favorite teacher?  Got any funny stories about him/her?  Nicknames?  Stunts you pulled in his/her class?  Share them!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Thank goodness for technology!  We can plan, communicate, and share ideas without even leaving our homes.  This blog will keep classmates up-to-date, share ideas and opinions about the reunion, and catch up with each other.  Check the website and the blog often!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I am not really going to tell you what I think... BUT I did tell the survey what I think!   The RRHS reunion survey takes about 30 seconds to complete... its completely anonymous... and it's a great way to ensure that YOUR opinions are heard for what happens at our class reunion!  Take the survey today! There is a link on the reunion web site!   urlLink http://geocities.com/rrhs95reunion /
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks to Jamie Draxton Fultz for volunteering for the planning committee.  Who knows what will need to be done, but it is nice to know that classmates want to make this a special event!  Thanks, Jamie!  I just realized that there is not a link to the official reunion website...  Go to the website and take the survey, sign and read the guestbook, and check it all out!   urlLink www.geocities.com/rrhs95reunion    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     I am a little nervous. I spoke to a friend of mine who is helping with the Central High School Class of 1994 reunion. She made it sound like they are having problems with RSVPs and getting a good turnout. I would like some suggestions from you regarding how to increase classmate turnout. I would also like to hear about how to make this a reunion that people will want to come to. Please leave your comments!!!   urlLink      
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is great to know that we have talented people in our class.  Robert Benda's company  urlLink Band of Gold  has been scheduled to DJ our reunion.  If you have a talent that you'd like to volunteer, email the planning committee at  urlLink rrhs95reunion@yahoo.com      We encourage all comments to this blog.  Please add recommendations, suggestions, ideas, and thoughts.  However, please try to keep them positive.  We've had to delete a negative comment and that is unfortunate.     
     

    
</post>


</Blog>