<Blog>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay - didn't exercise today because coworkers from London and Sydney were in town, we went to  urlLink Triumph  and I had a semi-late night.  Plus I was so worn out from all the exercise that happened yesterday.  Updates on the girls... Rachael - nothing from her, I'm thinking of closing that one out.  Laura - what the fuck is up with her.  She's about to move in with "her boyfriend" what the hell would she be emailing me for?  Christ - the girls I know really suck.  I'm sitting at home on the couch, watching pbs - blogging, and working at the same time.  I think that I'm going to go to bed early tonight, I'm really starting to get tired.... I'll just read until I fall asleep - right now I'm reading Timeline by MC.  I've read it before and enjoyed it, so I thought I'd read it again.  Ok well - I've got to finish a couple things for work... signing off. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay - did another 30 minutes of running this AM... however, it is a little dangerous to be running on quakerbridge roady - I have to run on the median in the middle of the road, and while it is at least 15 feet wide, its still a little scary.  Tonight I meet with the landlord from my old place to do the final walkthrough.  Devin, who I used to live with, had put a hole in the wall upstairs that was never really fixed right, and wasn't painted.  That's the only major damage that we might have to pay for.  I guess I'll find out tonight!  After that I'll be heading to the  urlLink rock gym  for some more climbing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok - I did 30 minutes of running, and plenty of rock-climbing.  I just need to keep some sort of moderate exercise up every day... alternating to avoid too much stress in one place at a time... and gradually increase the intensity a little each day.  Made pasta with scallops in alfredo sauce for dinner tonight... mmmm and there are leftovers for tomorrow night.... scallops will still be okay tomorrow I hope.  Oh well, time to clean up.  Still nothing from Rachael.  Also still no hint from the girl from  urlLink this post  ... referred to as Laura from here on out.  We're just emailing a little.  Oh well.  Looking forward to my vacation coming up in July...  8 days of diving... sweet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Someting my Mom introduced me to....  Breakfast Smoothie: 5 large cleaned strawberries 1 1/2 cups of non-fat vanilla yogurt 1/4 cup of orange juice 1 bananna  Throw the above into a blender and blend until it's smooth... then drink it!  Quick and healthy... mmmmm and it tastes great.  I'm going to stop now before I start sounding more like a commercial.... and make my self one - maybe I'll throw in some peach too.  Then it's off to the old house to clean it up for the last time so it will be ready for our old landlord to walkthrough. I'm also going to pickup on a physical fitness routine again so I can get back into top shape.... oh, and still nothing from Rachael. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       When I was little I always had those thoughts the the whole world was a stage and everyone around me was putting on a play just for me.  Maybe they were robots, or maybe I was in some MATRIX-like world... but that movie came out after I had grownup so I didn't have the benefit of seeing that movie.  But later on, I began to read books and see movies that at least confirmed that other people had thought the same thoughts and feelings that I had as a kid.... if other people have thought of things as strange as that before, is it even possible that I've had an original thougt ever in my life?  But then when you add my unique experiences then it must be possible.  Like has anyone ever thought about what it would be like to fly a plane while getting a back massage and eating jello?  Doubtful.  :-) That's all I have to say.   urlLink Mr. Roboto     
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm writing this at 8:30 am, the cable/internet guy is supposed to come sometime between 9am and 1pm.  Hopefully I'll finally have internet access sometime after that!  So I met Rachael last night.  I thought she was incredibly cute.  She's 21 and I'm 25, but I think once you pass that age of 21, the difference really doesn't matter that much.  She admitted to being kinda nervous before we met on the phone, and I was nervous too.  So I think that me admitting that to her helped us meet without too much pressure.  The "date" was a little weird, we didn't hit it off as well as we did on the phone, and I think that's because of the circumstances.  Anyway, after the movie she had to run off to a friends party - I'm not sure if the party was really happening, or she was just using it as some excuse to get away.  I gave her my business card, she said she'd email me, but we'll find out.  Oh well - only time will tell! :-)  I think we could get along pretty well - she is just as nuts as I am when I'm comfortable with people.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So Rachael, the girl I talked to the other night, called me last night just as I was putting my phone in the charger.  We only chatted for a couple of minutes, but it was nice... in fact we are actually meeting tonight.. :-)  We are supposed to see  urlLink Fahrenheit 9/11  tonight - I think the movie topic might be kinda harsh for a first date, but she seems excited about it, so I'm sure it will be fine... if we can get a seat! :-)  I can't decide if I should shave my head again or just keep it really short.  I like it really short, but its tough to get it that way without using the bic and letting it grow a day... maybe I'll let it grow a little bit and see how it goes.  Anyway - I've got to clean out my car just in case we decide to meet someplace else and drive to the theater together or we decide to go someplace afterwards - maybe dinner or someplace where we can talk.  I'll clean it out at lunchtime - please don't rain!  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it's been a day, and I still can't get that bestie boys song out of my head.  maybe its because their new album just came out, and i will probably buy it or rip it off the internet someplace.... no, wait, thats only metallica that I would take off the internet.... sue their fans... christ, what the hell is wrong with them.  so I talked on the phone last night with someone from an internet dating site (i know, those things are weird, but it helps me meet people).  Her name is Rachael and wow - we talked for a long time.  I think that we seem to be on the same page when it comes to being crazy - she laughed at some of the dumb jokes I made, and she had me practically die of laughter for something she said... don't remember what exactly it was but it was funny :-)  I'm going to call her back tonight - I know that is supposed to be against the rules or something, but I don't play by the rules anymore!  And the cool thing was - just as I was starting to get tired and wanting to fall asleep, she said she was getting tired.  It was perfect timing... though she seemed to have so much energy, I think she could have talked for hours. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so what do you do when someone that completely broke your heart a year prior suddenly comes out of the blue and says whats up....  I should just ignore her, I know, but there's always that thought in the back of my mind saying why couldn't it have been different.... why is she writing to me now unless she feels that she made a mistake before or something.  So I just wrote an email back - not really giving any real information, just sort of testing the waters - if she has any intention to do anything else, then she'll just have to say it - I don't want to be played with again....   Here's a little picture for the viewing pleasure of my readers - just some random girls :-)     Girls - all I really want is girls And in the morning it's girls Cause in the evening it's girls  I like the way that they walk And it's chill to hear them talk And I can always make them smile From White Castle to the Nile  Back in the day There was this girl around the way She liked by home-piece M.C.A. He said he would not give her play I asked him, "Please?" - he said, "You may." Her pants were tight and that's ok If she would dance - I would D.J. We took a walk down to the bay  I hope she'll say, "Hey me and you should hit the hay!" I asked her out - she said, "No way!" I should have probably guessed her gay So I broke North with no delay I heard she moved real far away That was two years ago this May I seen her just the other day Jockin' Mike D. to my dismay  Girls - to do the dishes Girls - to clean up my room Girls - to do the laundry Girls - and in the bathroom Girls - that's all I really want is girls Two at a time - I want girls With new wave hairdos - I want girls I ought to whip out my - girls, girls, girls, girls, girls! 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've spent alot of money recently fixing up my new apartment.  It's actually starting to look pretty good now.  My room is almost all done - I still need to get the internet setup.  When I get home tonight - probably pretty late - I'm going to make a huge dinner, or a huge  urlLink breakfast casserole  and stick it in the fridge.  I also need to pickup a couch, chair, and rug from my Aunt's house... since its going to be so late, that will have to wait until tomorrow.  My parents are in Alaska on a 2 week trip - so cool, I think I'll go in a year or two.    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok, so i survived the movers.  they were kinda crazy - but at least they were good at moving heavy stuff quickly.  i keep on buying stuff at the stores, and there is constantly more things that i need.  however, priority 1 is getting the internet working. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       not pictured is the laundry room or the garage....  but I've got them.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Halfway moved into my new place.  All the small stuff is moved, I just have the big stuff to go.  I've decided to ask some movers to help me - but it is a little sketchy... they called me and we setup an appointment, however the confirmation email never arrived.  I called them back last night and they said they sent the email already.  I still didn't get it as of this morning, so I have been calling the 800 number they gave me all morning.... still no answer!  I'm wondering if it is some scam that they setup, the truck shows up at your house and steals all your stuff or something.  Well, there will be about 10 other people at my house tomorrow morning for the move, so they will have a hard time killing me or stealing my stuff.  But just in case - The company is supposedly called "Excellent Movers" and I reached them at 866-638-6683.  If there is no more blogs put up on this site, it's because I've beened kidnapped or killed, so please let the police know to start looking for me.  Thanks! :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       whatever i did - it really hurts.  its so incredible i can barely breathe!  must have been when i picked the tv up this morning.... i did it in a weird way so i wouldnt get 2 years worth of dust all over me - i guess that was a mistake.  but i did pickup the keys and garage opener of my new apartment this morning.  i did a quick walkthrough and dropped off a few things - it looks really nice... trying to decide if I should setup a marine aquarium or not... ok - so i've already make up my mind, but I'm trying to decide what type and how big.... :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Van Wilder is probably one of the funniest movies that has been made in the last 10 years.   Also Zoolander....  I shaved my head on Sunday this week instead of Saturday - everyone said that it looked really short - I guess the one day does make a difference.  Gotta finish this last miller lite and then 4 or 5 more, and then off to bed...  I pickup the key to my new apartment tomorrow, so I'll be going into work a little late, but they'll survive without me :-) Tonight its a little steamy - I think I'll blast the fan on me.  Anyway - have a polly wolly crappy day.... and if you don't have seatbelts, just try to go limp.  urlLink Season 4  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hope that we have many more days like yesterday this summer.  Played golf and stayed cool... 75 degrees.  I'm almost all packed up and ready to move - just have to take care of a couple more things. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       cloudy friday.  tonight i have to pack the basement up for my move next week.  ive got so much junk that im thinking about putting a table out on the street with a big sign that says FREE.  im too lazy to do a yard sale, and i really dont want to waste time.  as long as nobody steals the table, and i have nothing left to clean up, ill be happy.  heading to the rock gym now.  since this is the first mention of it, i rockclimb at rockville climbing center.  really cool place with a cool staff.  urlLink Rockville Climbing Center  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay - so here's living situation story.  (yes, I'm sitting in class right now, but again - it's accounting, so who cares)  I've lived in Hamilton for 2 years with the same friends I lived with before.  I was looking for a house to buy for a few months because of the low interest rates.  But in Mercer County, I'd be buying a shack for the same price of (virtually) a mansion in other places.  I really didn't want to live in a craphole, so I decided to rent.  Now I'll be moving into a very nice apartment behind the Quaker Bridge Mall in Lawrenceville.  3 bedrooms and 2 baths.  I'm having my brother and a friend of his live with me, so that will help cut down on my costs.  But at least I still have my own space.  June 15 is the first offical day, but I won't really be moving in until the saturday afterwards - June 19.   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just had lunch with my friend Nancy from work.  mmmm McDonalds.  I was sooo hungry.  Do you think it might have something to do with the strain I put my body through last night at the race?  I say yes.  Anyway - it is slightly cooler today, but alas I do not get to enjoy the weather, I'm stuck going to class again.  I'd really like to play golf, or even just sit at home and do nothing, but instead I'll be driving down to Camden for class.  This is a review class - the first exam is on Monday, so I do really need to go - the prof will probably give out some secrets or tips for the exam.  Well - I'm going to sit back and let my stomach do some digesting - #3 with rootbeer.  grumble grumble grumble. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How do you say exhausted....  It was so hot last night at the race, and my time just wasn't up to par.... Of course the alcohol from the night before didn't help either.  So much for the JPMorgan Chase Corporate Challenge 2004.  I'm still exhausted - of course that we went from the finish line to the pub certainly was not too nutrious, but we really needed the beer!  Today its back to the office, and then back to school for my summer class.  My Dad's birthday is on Saturday, but I can't see him until next week - I'm setting up a tee time so he can see my new apartment and then play golf.... probably Mercer Oaks.  Yes - that's right, I'm moving soon - but more on that later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink JPMorgan Chase Corporate Challenge   Ok - so its going to be 95 degrees today or something outrageous like that.  I'm running in the New York JPMorgan Chase Corporate Challenge this evening, so I better bring plenty of water...  Last year they took my picture and put it up on the website.  I'm in the very left edge of the photograph looking very tired even though there is some little old guy right behind me!!  Ok - so I started the race at the very back end of the crowd, but I managed to finish somewhere near the front:     I'm feeling a little sluggish today, could it be the bottle of wine I chugged last night?  Or maybe it was the huge breakfast I had at the diner on the way to work this AM....  either way, I think I'll just jog in the race, I don't want to get too hot.  Besides, it won't make the trip to the bar come any faster since I'll have to wait for all my co-workers to finish the race too.  I leave work at 2:30, hop on the train and head on up... 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       as this is my first serious blog - i'll just have to watch what i post until i get the hang of it.   urlLink Microsoft fires worker over weblog  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today i'm taking the first accounting class of my life.  the class actually started on June 1, but since this is my first log of this blog... well you know.  coming from a science background, accounting is so strange.  I just want to write mathematical expressions to settle companies accounting issues - but no - we need to follow these conventions set by these "important" people around the world... right... well - oh well, I'll have to press on and deal with it.  the class ends on June 24, so just grin and bear it Jason!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It has begun.  3 fantasy teams - 2 pools.  Here's one.  urlLink 2004 NFL Season One-On-One Pool  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Went over to Sue and Devin's house last night - Christine and Niffers (Jenn) were there too.&nbsp; We hung out and just drank beer, Devin had just replaced the keg, so there was gallons and gallons to drink...&nbsp; needless to say I had to spend the night - so basically, I haven't seen my bed in almost 2 weeks.... It's strange - I don't really like drinking that much or getting drunk too often, but last night the beer flowed like water... nay - like ice cold water on a hot summer day in death valley.... waiting for me when I get home also are my bags which are still packed.&nbsp; I made a stop at petsmart looking for aquarium stuff - didn't find what I was looking for but what did I find instead?&nbsp; Cute kittys just begging to be adopted!&nbsp; It took some serious willpower to walk out of there without getting one.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OK - gotta get up and head to the airport soon.&nbsp; As you can see it's early - definitely too early to be playing with the camera.&nbsp; Just thinking that in 24 hours I'll be doing my morning run near the mall, or maybe I'll run into lawrence square village, or down village road to mercer oaks... I'll just let the wind direct me... I certainly won't be running along a beach in paradise like I'm about to do now.&nbsp; Is Jason naked in this picture - well - I'll leave that to the imagination of the millions of lovely ladies who read this post every day... :-)&nbsp; Hah!   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       7/25/2004 9:30amSo we have a nice quiet Sunday morning on the last full day of the trip.&nbsp; Tomorrow afternoon I'll be back in rainy Princeton.&nbsp; Yay!&nbsp; :-)&nbsp; I've realized that my brother is a big slob.&nbsp; OK - so I knew this already, but still - how can he let all those dishes sit for days!!&nbsp; That would (and is) drive me nuts.&nbsp; Doing some deep dives this afternoon - a little bit later than I'd want considering we won't have a full 24 hours until we fly - but I'm pretty sure we'll survive.&nbsp; 21 hours... 24 hours... not much difference.&nbsp; I also went to the ATM and put together the tips....&nbsp; I'm pretty sure my brother is too poor/cheap to give tips to his 2 instructors or the captain... so I put a little extra in the envelopes.&nbsp; These people work and a good portion of their income depends on tips, so I'm always careful to make sure I give them what they deserve.&nbsp; Oh - and in case you don't think that my brother is sloppy and I'm just making it up, here's proof:     
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Only did one dive trip today (2 dives in the morning) Jeff's ear is bothering him.&nbsp; We did some deeper reefs - on the slope from 60 feet to 100 feet.&nbsp; We hovered in about 70 feet partway down the slope and let the current take us.&nbsp; It was nice to do some drift diving, except for the vis which wasn't the best.&nbsp; But we saw some nice size jewfish and sharks.&nbsp; The guy I was diving with even found a nice Penn reel on the reef - it was all covered in growth, but he should be able to clean it off pretty well.&nbsp; We covered some good distance, so it's a good thing we did the drift, otherwise it would have been tough to fight the current constantly.&nbsp; Said goodbye to Jan and Bob - they are driving back home.&nbsp; I liked those guys - I gave them my address and email address, so hopefully I will hear from them.&nbsp; They also took some video and pictures and promised to send it to me.&nbsp; Here are some pretty spiral worms on coral... these things shoot into holes faster than you can blink if you get close to touching them - so it's fun to watch them hide.   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Met this cute girl who was diving with her brother and Mom.&nbsp; The three of them hadn't been in the water for 3 years.&nbsp; I was sorta turned off from her at first because she didn't seem to want to talk... but who was I to judge without even trying talking to her.&nbsp; Pat - the diveshop owner had me watch the three of them as they got in the water, she didn't want to trust them with their own safety, but once I saw that they had remembered everything important about diving.... don't hold your breathe, ascend slowly, and that stuff, I let them go on their own.&nbsp; Later I was talking to girl, and found out she was a grad student in Tenessee.&nbsp; She seemed to be pretty smart - I told her my story and my job, and she was interested.&nbsp; She was studying theology - and I asked her what she wanted to do - and she said anything that has nothing to do with religion.&nbsp; I'd have married her there on the spot after she said that!&nbsp; :-)&nbsp; But in the end, I gave her my card and said to send me an email - but of course I'm not expecting to hear from her... plus she's in Tenessee, and I have no business in that area except for a quick rockclimbing trip or something.... ugh - can't stand country music.&nbsp; But if she were to contact me, then that would be something different... :-)&nbsp; Attached is a picture of me, the man-whore.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       7/22/2004 11:30PMJeff caught so much fish - we ate between 2 and 4 pounds of fish.... each for two nights in row.&nbsp; I fried some, and, baked some, and I basically steamed some in wine.&nbsp; The fried fish came out the best, but maybe that had something to do with the frying in vast quantities of oil and butter.&nbsp; While eating at the hotels is much cheaper than going out to eat, I do miss the good service and really good food....&nbsp; but my brother is poor, so why not let him save some money.&nbsp;    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow - the wreck dive today was great.&nbsp; Nice white ship hull that could be seen from the surface - the water was just so clear.&nbsp; There was a current that was pretty ripping though.&nbsp; Almost no current on the surface, but from about 10ft to the bottom it was pulling along at about 2.5 knts.... but in the opposite direction of the prevailing current, so that was a little weird.&nbsp; Jeff went out fishing since he couldn't do the dive this AM, but he's said he's caught some yellowtail, so hopefully I'll have some good fish on the way!!&nbsp; I have to go pick him up in a little bit.   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dove alot today with Jan and Bob&nbsp; Also, Jeff finally finished his OW certification.&nbsp; If only he had remembered to take the car keys out of his pocket before he jumped in the water.&nbsp; I guess he'll have to do his advanced certification on another trip.&nbsp; We did some easy shallow dives.&nbsp; Bought stuff at the supermarket for dinner and lunches.&nbsp; That should stop the cash drain somewhat.&nbsp; Oh well, what do I care, it's vacation!&nbsp; Diving the Speigel tomorrow with Jan and Bob.&nbsp; Jeff can't because it's a little tricky dive, so he's going to go fishing.&nbsp; Not sure how I'm going to get home after the dive, but I'll figure it out.&nbsp; Here is a picture of Jan and Bob... very strange guys, but they like to dive as much as I do.   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jeff is in SCUBA class.&nbsp; Went diving today with a really cool guy named Mark from LA.&nbsp; He was diving with this other guy who really sucks down the air... and thus really sucks... turns an hour dive into 30 minutes....&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mark from LA was a little nervous this morning on the Eagle.&nbsp; I could tell it was his first deep dive in a while, or maybe it was just because he was not familiar with the wreck.&nbsp; Either way, I showed him the cool stuff all over the wreck.&nbsp; We did a simple swimthrough - through the wheelhouse of the wreck.&nbsp; I traded cards with him, so maybe we'll keep in touch, and I can send him some pictures.&nbsp; Below is a picture of me... proof that man can live underwater without the need of air or a mask.... ok, so I only took those off for the picture - you caught me!   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ahhhh some nice snorkeling yesterday just to get my feet wet a little to prepare for all the diving to come.&nbsp; This morning I ran along a dirt path the locals use to walk to a natural jetty where they can fish from.&nbsp; It's sorta out in the middle of nowhere.&nbsp; The guys that ran the snorkel trip today offered to take me on a night dive, but since my brother can't go, I'm going to hold off.&nbsp; Besides, there are so many potential night dives coming up, I'd rather go with people I know.&nbsp; Dinner tonight at Lazy Dayz - chef Lupe's stuffed chicken... mmmmmmmm.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nothing like waking up 100 feet from the beach...&nbsp; the air at 6am is still and the sun is just about to rise.&nbsp; 4 mile run along a white sand beach in nothing by the boxer shorts I fell asleep in the night before...&nbsp; then after that a swim in the ocean that is warmer than the air... ahhhhh yep - it's true, I'm on vacation.&nbsp; Now I'm trying to get my brother out of bed so we can eat breakfast and get going.&nbsp; Today we have some shopping - I need a new dive mask, and I would like to replace the battery on my dive computer just to play it safe... there are still 2 out of 4 bars on the battery meter, but that's the type of thing you don't want to lose during a series of dives.&nbsp; Sun is shining brightly into the hotel room now, and I'm really hungry.&nbsp; There was some cafe one block north, I'm going to head over there and get a coffee.      
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Obey my dog!  If there's anything that this horrible tragedy can teach us, it's that a male model's life is a precious, precious commodity. Just because we have chiselled abs and stunning features, it doesn't mean that we, too, can't not die in a freak gasoline fight accident.  A eugugalizer:  one who speaks at funerals, or did you think I'd be too stupid to know what a eugugoly is?  I feel like I'm taking CRAZY PILLS!!!  How can the children learn to read, when they can't even fit inside the building! *smack*  There has got to be more to life than being really, really, really, ridiculously good-looking.  96% of the earth is water. The other half is wheat. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok - so I'm sitting in bed right now, trying to get up, but my head is still so foggy... no real reason for it, I went to bed not too late last night.  I was even reading until I passed out, so I don't even remember what time it was.  I'm going to run about 5 miles today... not sure how it is going to be since I just ran less than 12 hours ago inside on the treadmill.  It was raining so hard, that's why I took the treadmill - normally the rain doesn't bother me, but everything around here was completely flooded, including some of the streets.  Oh well - so this blogging is waking me up - and I think I can roll out of bed now.  Just remembering that in exactly 60 hours, I'll be on a plane to paradise.... and then I'll be swimming alongside this fella...!    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So my old hometown makes the national news once again... 5000 people in it and we have more freaks per capita than anywhere else.  I knew the woman charged with murder - I worked with her on the Ambulance Squad - we saved lives together... kinda weird she's now a killer. urlLink CNN.com - Woman charged in fatal antifreeze poisoning - Jul 12, 2004   Oh well - I don't live there anymore!  Whew!!   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Scorpio! He'll sting you with his dreams of power and wealth. Beware of Scorpio! His twisted twin obsessions are his plot to rule the world And his employees' health. He'll welcome you into his lair, Like the nobleman welcomes his guest. With free dental care and a stock plan that helps you invest! But beware of his generous pensions, Plus three weeks paid vacation each year, And on Fridays the lunchroom serves hot dogs and burgers and beer! He loves German beer!   Check out what I found on East State Street.  Now I know where his secret lair is!!!     
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Went running - did 6.5 miles this morning.  Pottery Barn and Borders for some stuff.  Picked up the soundtrack to Gladiator... wow, pretty decent sound.  Went swimming, now I'm able to swim 2.5 lengths of the pool underwater on one breath.... not too bad considering I could barely do one length just two weeks ago.  Then I went bouldering at the gym...  Just got out of the shower which puts me at the present moment.  I'm going to finish up a load of laundry, read a little, and then head on over to KC Prime for the biggest piece of meat that I can find.  Mmmmmm.  Yesterday was vegetarian, today I guess is the opposite!   
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night was a blast.  It was so cool to be climbing in the dark with my friends.  I didn't buy any lamps, so I'll just have to pick something up in florida city on Friday.  fla city is the last town before the keys begin on route 1.  Today I just got back from running, and I'm heading on over to the pool.  Then its off to best buy to buy a vacuum....  I think they have like 20 different kinds, I'll probably be at a loss.... as long as the vacuum SUCKS then I'll be in good shape.  Tonight I'm headed over to my friend (and she happens to report to me on my team at work) Diane's house.  She got a new dog named Louie, so I'm going to meet him.  Then we'll go have dinner or something. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok - night rock climbing event tonight 10-12 at Rockville.  I'm going swimming directly after work, and then I'll probably take a nap so I can stay awake tonight.  The vendor at the rock gym is Princeton Tec, and they make some good diving lights too, so maybe I'll pick up something for the wreck diving I'll be doing... starting NEXT FRIDAY!!! YAY!!!  So tonight all the lights will be out, and we'll have lights attached to our heads.  We're supposed to top-rope, but I think I'll just be bouldering. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just got back from Borders... I bought... 1. Brave New World  2. Hot Plastic  3. Babbitt  4. The Etruscan Chimeria and some others.  I think that should be enough reading for my trip coming up... not that I'll be able to stay awake enough - I'm usually so tired after diving that I can't stay awake, but we'll see.  I'm freezing a bunch of bunches of bannanas tonight to help them keep for a long time.  Exciting evening, I know. :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Running.... Work... Rockclimbing... swimming... busy day! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Played golf this AM at urlLink Green Tree Golf Course   it was so nasty sweaty humid hot that I didn't think I'd be able to make it through the course... but I did.  My score wasn't that great, but at least I wasn't working.  Oh well - I think I'm going to get an early start on the road and hit a couple of stores on the way home to get some good deals.  Either that or I'll just bomb home really fast and just chill out in bed reading the last of a book.  Or, if I'm not exhausted by that time, I'll hit the rock gym and do some bouldering. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sunday evening, 4th of July.  Did alot of swimming in the ocean today off of the boat.  Did a little bit of fishing just about a mile off of the beach right in front of  urlLink Lucy  but all that we caught were skates, or sea rays.  It wasn't a really good spot for fishing, but we didn't care, just wanted to relax away from the marina for a bit.Then I had crab legs, shrimp, a cheeseburger, and some other stuff for dinner.  Now I'm sitting in my house back in Margate, listening to this horrible... nay... disgusting band on the beach.... most of the time it is REALLY nice having a house on the beach, but right now I wish it was as far away from this band as possible.  Guess I'll go out in about 20 or 30 mintutes to see the fireworks, they should only be about 5 blocks away, and in addition to Margate's, I should also be able to see Atlantic City and Ocean City fireworks too.  Still no sunburn.  Finally - the band has taken a break and is now playing my favorite radio station.  Seriously - I've traveled all over this country, and the best radio station is  urlLink  Digital 102.7.    They play stuff you can't hear anywhere else.  Ok - time to find a nice spot in the sand.   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I'm here in Margate now, ready to begin the relaxing weekend.  I opened all the windows last night because it was getting pretty cool, though still really freakin humid last night.   Think we're going deep sea fishing today with some friends - the ocean is flat, no waves so we could probably go out pretty far without taking too long, I'm not sure how close the gulf stream has come in yet this year.  So here we go, off for an exciting day!  oh - no, wait, I do need to do about 20 minutes of work first... doh! :-(  Oh well, I shouldn't have put it off last night when I wanted to be out of the office by 5pm. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How weird is this - I'm at this liquor store in Lambertville buying beer for Kim's party... I come out of the store, and driving by, staring out at me from the window is Laura's Mom.  Laura, the girl that is trying to screw with my head, moving in with her boyfriend from a couple posts ago....  On top of her truck is a mattress, I guess today was move-in day or something.  I know that her boyfriend that she "cheated" on to see me a couple of times lived in Lambertville, I guess he must be the guy.  Oh well - screw it, I'm not going to dwell on someone who couldn't see the storm through the rain, or whatever. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay - so tired.  Wednesday night .... moving a couch turned out to be just Devin and I getting a big couch into a very small apartment.  It was a tight squeeze - wouldn't really fit in the stairs, so we had to keep it above us.... but evenutally we forced it in.  Then we played drinking trivial pursuit...  so needless to say I had to sleep for a little bit there.... on the couch that we just moved in.  The couch was pretty comfortable, and I had to fight with the cat for a spot practically the whole time.  Then I got myself up and dragged into work.  Thursday night.... party at Kim's house.  Pretty fun time - I never thought that a 100% vegetarian night could be so tasty.  I never did break out the beef franks or steaks, there was no need. :-)  Oh well - somehow I've got to stay awake today, I need to last until 4pm when I can get outta here... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok - so he resigns because he had a gay affair... I still don't see the point.  Wouldn't that be between he and his wife?  Why didn't he resign from all the corruption that he had taken part in or turned a blind eye to over the past couple of years?  Oh well - whatever. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow - I wonder what all this is about!  This came completely out of the blue for me, I guess at 4PM I'll have to find out more... urlLink wnbc.com - Politics - NewsChannel 4: N.J. Governor McGreevey To Resign  Rumors he is gay is what I've heard - but so what!!!  Why should I care if my governor is gay or not?  I mean seriously - what the hell.  And what's this business about California voiding all the gay marriages that happened earlier this year?  Why does it bother so many people!  I certainly don't care.  I think that once some of the more "densely prejudiced older people" start dying off this country will change for the better...   Maybe this weekend I'll tell everybody where I sit for all the important issues, and someone can tell me if I'm a democrat or a republican!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A Toyota Emil saw a slime God saw I was dog Naomi, did I moan Red rum is Pepsi murder Dammit, I'm mad A slut nixes sex in Tulsa Solo gigolos Are we not drawn onward, we few? Drawn onward to new era Straw Warts  urlLink more    
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Big Big man    I have nothing to say but... "holy shit." 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, I'm addicted.  A friend of mine at work brought in these little packets of white pills.  They could have been crack/meth/coke/etc. and I would never have known it until it was too late.  Anyway, they taste like mint, and I can't stop eating them.  If I stop showing up for work, it's probably because I've found another source of these things, and there would be no need for me to go to work anymore.  Ok, so it turns out these things are legal and won't kill me... but I still think it's kinda funny... they look like some type of street drug.   urlLink Complimints   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A spider's web was in the way as I walked through the dark wood. To the right another web exists, though this one is a tight tangle of sticker bushes. To the left, thick deep brown mud. The sunlight glints on the silk, one bright strand in a sea of Verde. I see the spider - staring at me.  Is she going to be mad at me? Does she know I plan on walking through her web?   I mean, really what are my options.   I have new clothes on - I really have no business being in the woods with these clothes. In the end, it is the pitiful look of the spider, whose only method of catching food is her web. I take a sip of my chocolate milk, and a bite from my turkey sandwich. And I walk through the mud.   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       still lying in bed... on my left side... tv on cnn... I didn't wake up with a headache today.  I'm going to go running in about 15 minutes.  Then I'll wash my sheets and clean the kitchen... but by then the mall should be open.  It'll be time to go blow a couple hundred dollars on clothes...  I spent about 150 yesterday, and I like what I bought, so I think its time to continue the trend.  This time I'll buy stuff that I can wear to work.  I also want to find a headboard for my bed... I've never had one before.  Hopefully its going to be sunny and warm today so I can go swimming this afternoon.  I'll bet that I can swim the length of the pool underwater back and forth 3 times.  Changing the subject completely... here is the first fire department I ever joined:  urlLink Indian Mills Fire   urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so I met Misty for a late lunch.  She was actually really cute!  Lunch only lasted a little over an hour, but then we went walking in the Franklin Mills Mall - if you've ever been there, then you know it's a pretty large mall.  I think she and I got along pretty well, she is slightly taller than I am, and while that doesn't bother me, I know some girls like guys to be taller.  Oh well - we'll see how things work out, I'll call her Monday night and see if she wants to go out again.  After our date, I drove through New Hope, then went to visit my Geocache to check on how it's doing:   urlLink GC24B Washington's Crossing 1 by Jason Malatesta   While flipping through the log book, I found an entry that Laura and I had left in Feb 2002.  Oooof.  I had completely forgotten about her until that moment.  Oh well, I'm sure I'll forget her again soon enough.  Isn't it funny how they keep turning up one way or the other?  Anyway, I'm going to make myself a nice pasta dinner, and then I'll head out to the rock gym and do some climbing.  Peace out.   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok - you have to love that you can try to tell the president to do anything you want him to.  If he understands the command, meaning that it is not too many words, and is something a 2nd grader could understand, he still won't do it!  urlLink Subservient President   Anyway, try typing in some instructions and see if GWB will comply! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Woke up early today, but I just couldn't drag myself out of bed in order to go running.  So instead I just picked up my book and read a little.  This latest book is quite boring, and I'm hoping it is going to turn around and be exciting or interesting soon....  I'm going climbing tonight, my first bit of doing something physical since I got back from vacation.  Being sick sure just took the fun out of my life!!  I'm glad that I'm better and I can do some fun things again! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Got an email from a girl named Misty...  We've been emailing back and forth for some time now, but I've finally got her phone number... and what's more... she has agreed to meet me this Saturday!  :-)  I've seen her picture, and she's pretty cute!  Out of respect for her, I won't post her picture or any more details about her here unless she gives me permission.  I'm looking forward to meeting her!  On another note, I think I'm finally past the illness that I've been suffering from.  Today I feel good. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I was sick.  Stayed home and worked on the couch while watching movies.  I didn't get to pay attention to any of the movies because work kept me busy, but oh well - that's how I get paid!  I also kept Max on me, she seems to like to sleep an awful lot, but I guess that's normal, since she is a cat. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sick.  I've been sick since Friday night.  Saturday Sunday Monday.  But it's not some really horrible flu - I have a really stuffy nose, a headache, and I get dizzy.  If there is a fever, it is really slight, or else my body just can't tell it's own temperature any more.  Anyway - my ears are all clogged up too.  I haven't really been sick in, well - I can't remember the last time - must be years ago.  I should probably be glad about that, but I'm not really in the mood to be glad about anything - I just want to feel normal so I can go back to work.  I've also decided to try and pickup the first pretty girl I see someplace no matter what the circumstance (except for someone at work of course!)  But it could just be me thinking in my current state of mind that is all fogged up from being stuck in my apartment all day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       She's such a little baby!  :-)  Named after Max Planck... she's a black cat... and her name is a tribute to Planck's work with thermodynamics and blackbody radiation.... get it?  No?  Ok - well just call her Max and don't worry about the reasons why. :-)   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>