<Blog>




<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    At least, I didn't have to type my own.&nbsp; urlLink     
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wont be able to write much today since I’ll be taking two tests tonight at school and I need to prepare for them.  The subjects in question are:  Business Ethics and Technical Business Writing.    I just want to take a few moments to thank again my friends and family for those great e-mails and messages of encouragement.  It is very reassuring to know that there are people that care and that I ‘m not alone.    
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to my journal.  I decided to start this blog with the therapeutic purpose of documenting this life change.  As of today, I’m another casualty of the downsizing/offshoring of corporate America.  I was downsized today as a result of as what the corporation called “an undergoing reduction in force”.  My position was eliminated so they “can better serve their customers and operate more efficiently”.    As a head of household this has been a great blow to my economic and financial structure.  But I’m determined to make the best of this experience even though I know that anxiety, frustration, and confusion wait for me around the corner.  Hopefully I’ll be back on my feet soon since my values; mental and morale capacities are intact.  I’m very grateful for my wife and my son’s support on this new challenge.  I would like to also thank those family members and friends that are already calling me with words of strength and love.  Thank you to all of you!  I want to say good bye to my ex co-workers and in addition thank them for their uplifting words of farewell and encouragement.  I wish you the best and keep in touch!!  Please keep in mind the following:  •	Since this is my first time keeping a journal, I will ask for your patience and understanding.  This is a work in progress, so expect to see changes often. •	Feel free to e-mail me with ideas and suggestions for improvements.   •	English is my second language so forgive my grammar errors. •	I’ll try to write the same post in Español for my Spanish viewers. •	Since life does not end with this unpleasant incident, I’ll be writing about other events of my daily life.  And of course: •	Feel free to post your comments.   I know that you will be there to help me rise above and win this battle.     Bienvenidos a mi diario.  Decidí comenzar este blog con el propósito terapéutico de documentar este cambio en mi vida.  En la fecha hoy, Soy otra victima del downsizing/ offshoring de las corporaciones americanas.  He quedado desempleado debido  a lo que la compañia llama "una reducción de personal necesaria".  Mi posición fue eliminada para  que ellos "puedan mejorar el servicio  al cliente y funcionar de una manera más eficiente".  Como cabeza de casa y de familia este ha sido un golpe duro a mi bienestar economico y financiero.  Pero estoy determinado ha hacer lo mejor de esta experiencia aunque sé que dias de ansiedad, frustración, y confusión me esperan alrededor de la esquina.  Mi esperanza es que pronto me levantare con empeño a luchar ya que mis valores; y mis capacidades tanto mentales como morales estan intactas.  Me considero muy afortunado de tener el soporte, amor y ayuda de mi querida esposa y mi adorado hijo, se que cuento con ellos para enfrentarme a este desafio.  Quisiera también agradecer a los familiares y amigos que me han llamado para darme animo con palabras de fuerza y cariño.  Muchas Gracias!!!  Tambien me quiero despedir de mis ex compañeros de trabajo y agradecerles por las palabras de animo con las que se despidieron.  Les deseo lo major y espero que no perdamos contacto.  Por favor tenga en cuenta lo siguiente:  •	Como esta es la primera vez que mantengo un diario de este tipo les pido paciencia y entendimiento.   •	Si tienen ideas o sugerencias mandenmelas via e-mail.  •	Como la vida no se acaba hoy, estare escribiendo acerca de otros aconteciminetos de mi vida diaria.  Y por supuesto: •	Escriban sus comentarions.   Se que ustedes estaran conmigo en la lucha y juntos ganaremos la batalla.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Job Hunter&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>