<Blog>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


    

            Venus passed between the Sun and us this morning.   This is one of only two opportunities this century to, for a brief moment, really have some understanding of precisely how tiny we are in this universe.   Venus is about the same size as the Earth, and yet against the face of our star, Sol, it is a tiny dot, a trifling little thing.   One day when representatives of the human species stand upon the surface of Mars on a regular basis, they will, perhaps, be able to experience first hand how incredibly tiny is the planet of their genesis. From the Martian surface, Earth too is just a period at the end of an incomprehensibly long sentence.   If staring at the image of an Earth-sized planet dwarfed by a broiling mass of hydrogen and helium is not enough, consider that this little star, Sol, is relatively small by cosmic standards. There are many stars much larger. Beatlegeuse, the bright red star in the constellation Orion, has roughly the same diameter as does the orbit of the planet Mars.   Of course all the stars are dwarfed to much smaller than dots by the galaxies they inhabit. Light, which takes four minutes to travel from Earth to Mars at their closest approach takes 100,000 YEARS to cross the Milky Way Galaxy. The Milky Way is only one of at least 100 BILLION galaxies and it takes light at least 12 BILLION years to cross the known universe.   There are also those who believe that ours may only be one of an infinite number of universes. If you think something is a "Big Deal", it's probably not.  

    

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

        As I sit here writing this, there are two 20-something, massively&nbsp;tatooed&nbsp;gentlemen in my kitchen hammering away.&nbsp; These gentlemen are from a local carpeting and flooring establishment.     &nbsp;   You see, about three months ago I was fool enough to finally procure my piece of the "American Dream" -- namely an approximately 1100 square foot condominium unit in an out-of-the-way suburb in the Great Lakes region of the United States.     &nbsp;   Many people say that home ownership is the "best investment you can make".&nbsp; I am beginning to wonder.     &nbsp;   This unit is about 10 years old.&nbsp; It was last owned by a chain-smoking Alzheimer's patient.     &nbsp;   In the last three months of owning this little piece of the "American Dream", I have done the following repair or replacement work:     &nbsp;   1.&nbsp;&nbsp; Cleaned dryer, HVAC, and master bathroom exhaust vents.     &nbsp;   2.&nbsp;&nbsp; Moved central air filter closer to "return" vent.     &nbsp;   3.&nbsp;&nbsp; Installed UV A/C coil sterilizer.     &nbsp;   4.&nbsp;&nbsp; Installed new vertical blinds and valence.     &nbsp;   5.&nbsp;&nbsp; Replaced kitchen faucet.     &nbsp;   6.&nbsp;&nbsp; Reseated toilets in both bathrooms.     &nbsp;   7.&nbsp;&nbsp; Resealed lower layer of tiles in master bathroom shower stall.     &nbsp;   8.&nbsp;&nbsp; Replaced suction valve on water softener having accidentally flushed screen down the drink.     &nbsp;   9.&nbsp;&nbsp; Replaced water heater.     10.&nbsp;&nbsp; Replaced the hardwood floors in the entryway and kitchen.     11.&nbsp;&nbsp; Replaced water line for refrigerator ice maker.    12.&nbsp;&nbsp; Replaced ceiling fans in master bedroom and living room.     &nbsp;   This is after the son of the previous owner replaced the carpet, disposal, and diswasher in addition to painting the unit.     &nbsp;   Now, after very careful consideration I am coming to the conclusion that home ownership is the best investment THE HOME REPAIR INDUSTRY can ever make.     &nbsp;   The amount of money I have spent and the amount of time I have missed from work is truly staggering.     &nbsp;   Hopefully this will settle down though.&nbsp; I have high hopes of maybe breaking even on this endeavor in perhaps 12 - 15 years.     &nbsp;   Let me tell you though, I sure miss having a landlord.      

    

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

          What IS it about these   urlLink  young people    constantly talking about killing themselves?  Actually I've reached the conclusion that the human brain becomes so pickled from puberty that basically it doesn't work right  AT ALL  until sometime between about 32 and 40.  I think it goes something like this ... very typically the hormones so interfere with the proper flow of bodily fluids that, for instance, some people get terrible cases of acne. Well, I think a variety of explosions and eruptions go through the typical adolescent and young adult brain and you end up with such people as   urlLink  Ariel   .  Of course what gets me in trouble is that women who suffer from this phenomenon are often  QUITE  interesting ... very intelligent, very creative, and with the sex drive of freshly emerging cicadas.  Sometimes I think it may be the media though. I, too, passed through a period when I believed that some things on TV and movies could be real. I believed there could be a place of employment somewhere in this great country of ours where 430 highly trained people under an articulate, compassionate, and fearless leader could be engaged in exploring the strange new worlds of, say, nanotechnology. No, these jobs are few and far between. In fact, apparently the route to massive amounts of INCOME is being willing to put up with some of the most astonishingly stupid people that are imaginable to an intelligent, creative person.  I wonder often if this is what the young people are suicidal about. It seems they have such an incredible sense of hopelessness -- not just that they can't command a starship, but that they may have no purpose AT ALL.  Well, at least in the case of   urlLink  Ariel   , I certainly hope, if nothing else, that she realizes it certainly lightens up the day of  THIS  old cybernaut, after dealing with abject idiots all day, to get a "giggling smiley" in his Messenger. 
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       Well, I have downloaded the dreaded Windows XP Service Pack 2 from the Top Secret Übergeek site.  The install actually took LONGER than installing XP from a CD.  SO FAR everything is working but I have only tried the "common" applications -- IE and the like.  The new "Windows Security Center" looks suspiciously like McAfee's Security Center.  No doubt I will crash into some horrendous difficulty in a matter of seconds -- particularly because, despite grave warnings, I have both the Windows AND the McAfee firewalls turned on.  My favorite "mine canary" is working quite well thank goodness -- Yahoo Chess.  More reports as situations warrant.  

    

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       According to the  urlLink Palm Beach Post , a 39-year-old, 4-foot-10, 480-pound woman died after sitting on a couch for six years.  Apparently this woman was so disabled she had not even been to the bathroom in six years.  Paramedics were unable to remove her from the couch to seek medical attention and eventually had to try to transport the woman, still attached to the couch, to the hospital on the back of a truck.  Now I've had people tell me I need to get out more, but this takes the cake.  

    

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

        I am coming rather late to this blogging thing.  In fact I hadn't taken much interest in it at all until my good friend  urlLink Ariel  started one.  I had of course read a few months ago that the only way to get a oh-so-sought-after Gmail account was to have an account on Blogger. I have yet to get my invite by the way.  But, after having explored a number of blog sites I came to the conclusion that Blogger did offer some versatility that others didn't, so here I am.  A couple of days ago I found probably the most addictive web page ever encoded by human beings,  urlLink Blogger's Recently Updated Blogs . Oh this was intoxicating. It listed the last 10 minutes or so of all the blogs on Blogger that had just been updated. The screen has been blank for the last couple of days and it has been driving me bats.  First of course there is the fact that I can't see who's posting out there.  Then there is the fact that there may have been thousands upon thousands of people reading  THIS  blog from that page.  Oh, well, I suppose I will have to go back to something more conventional, like surfing  urlLink Ariel's  comments pages.  

    

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

         urlLink CNET  is running an article debating whether or not blogs are "overrated".  It seems a few "high profile" bloggers were given press credentials to the Democratic National Convention.  Yes, some blogs are pure dreck. Some blogs (like this one) are ALMOST pure dreck. However, the blog has returned something to the art and science of communication that I thought had been lost.  You see, I was born into the world one of these "gifted" people. I learned how to read early. I learned math early. Remembering huge amounts of seemingly trivial information was quite easy for me. When I was a teenager I was actually INTERESTED in listening to our main talk radio station in Cincinnati, WCKY.  I wasn't interested in sports or rock bands or any of that trivium -- I wanted to discuss topics of some IMPORT.  Needless to say I didn't have many friends in school.  But, about 20 years ago this week, I picked up something called a "300 baud modem" for a piece of machinery called the Atari 800. I bought it mainly to download what passed for "shareware" from BBS's around the country. I also stumbled into something called CompuServe that was inhabited by a very large number of intelligent, communicative people.  You see, back then, only serious geeks had computers. Only inquizitive people bothered with the cryptic commands it took to run a computer. If you could assemble a computer and a modem and actually get online you had to have SOMETHING going on upstairs.  Well, along came Windows. Along came Netscape, then IE. Along came AOL. Along came Yahoo. Yahoo really brought something neat to the picture -- the very first practical, easy-to-deploy Voice-Over-IP system. Now you could talk voice FOR FREE to anyone in the world on the Internet with a microphone.  Unfortunately it turned into 11 meters (the CB band) almost immediately. With the exception of "Jewish Chat", most of Yahoo Voice Chat degraded into a giggling mass of teenagers playing rotten music to each other.  Then I stumbled across the blogs. They are RELATIVELY easy to create, but it takes someone with at least SOME ability and DESIRE to say something of some substance. Many of them are really stupid, but some are utterly fascinating.  THEN, just a couple of nights ago, I discovered  urlLink Blogger's Recently Updated Blogs . This page is the bomb. It is a list of all the Blogger blogs that have been updated in the last few minutes. This of course let's you know who is "alive out there".  The real trick to blogging of course is to leave comments. Comments don't have to be any greater works of literature than the blogs themselves. Just say what you think. Comments help bloggers improve their blogs and let them know that someone actually is alive and reading out there.  It is hard to say where this art form might go. Hopefully it will, at very least, leave a record of what a small slice of daily life was like in the early 21st century.  

    

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       Just spotted a great Blog on the "live" feed --  urlLink My War -- Fear and Loathing in Iraq .  This is written by a soldier on the ground over there.   Thank God there are people with a gift like his recording for posterity what is going on in Iraq.  

    

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

          urlLink  The Northstar Network      has awarded Illinois Senate candidate and noted Black Conservative Alan Keyes the "Buckwheat Award":   "...for conduct contrary to the interests of people of African descent and allowing himself to be posed like a lawn jockey for the enjoyment of whites who seek to maintain their privileged status in society."   I beg your pardon. Would you please care to explain to me precisely what MY "privileged place in society" is?  Contrary to popularly held opinion, White people are not born in the United states with the title to 40 acres and a mule. One too many of us are born into a world not terribly dissimilar to poor people of all races, colors, and creeds.  Many of us are born to mentally ill, drug addicted parents who, at one time or another were more interested in playing with the dog than taking care of their children.  Many of us, also, were raised by grandparents who were ill equipped, physically or financially, to handle raising children when they should have been enjoying their retirement.  Many of us were shot at, robbed, stabbed, pinched, and shit on. What's worse is that we didn't have anyone to tell us, "Oh, you're in a mess because you were born into this world of an underprivileged caste."  I've interviewed with   Rich White People  . They have looked at  ME  like I have three heads as well -- not because my skin is a different color than theirs, but because, perhaps, I speak a dialect different from them, or I wear clothing different than them, or I don't keep up with the same sports teams as them, or because I am more intelligent than them, or, quite frankly, because I too cannot fathom how human beings who have amassed so much power could be so stunningly indifferent to the plight of so many suffering people around the world.  Somewhere along the lines though I decided it was utterly futile to try to "rub their faces in it". These people are in deep, deep, deep denial and will never, ever, ever,  EVER  take responsibility for having created a society that allows so much suffering.  What you have to realize is that many of these people who run large businesses are astonishingly stupid. They love to "count beans", and almost constantly they count the wrong beans. For instance they will sell you things at a loss for ENORMOUS periods of time because one of the bean counter managers decided that taking a small loss on every item is worth it to capture "market share".  Keep an eye open for these things and any individual, or group of individuals, can amass great wealth and power.  But, always keep in mind -- be careful what you wish for, you may get it. 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       Seems my good friend Nate Livingston has a new detractor, this time from the Black community, who has started the  urlLink Black Cincinnati Blog .  Today's installment  urlLink The Black Discount and Small Town Economy  reminds me of a subject I have been meaning to address for quite some time -- minority economic empowerment.  I grew up in a "disadvantaged" area of Cincinnati called Northside. It was about a third White, about a third Black, and about a third Appalachian. It was almost all poor. Starting from 1st grade I was treated to a barrage of social commentary from my teachers that seemed to imply that the reason that, in particular, so many Black people lived in such bad conditions was because they were the descendants of a group of people who were brought to the United States as slaves. Something seemed a little suspect about this theory as there were some CRASHINGLY impoverished people in Northside, and only about 1/3 of them were Black, so something had to be amiss.  As I have gone on in life, I have had the oppotunity to interact with the "Captains of Industry", or, as my neighbors from Northside would probably say, "Rich White Folk", and I have made some interesting observations.  One, if you are Black and a Rich White Person is looking at you as if he hates you to the core of your being, he does -- but he hates everyone else too. If you are a Poor White Person, he hates you. If you are a Rich Asian Person he hates you too -- unless you are a customer. Basically the Rich White Person hates everyone who is not in a position to make him Richer. Actually I have noticed that quite a few Rich Black People also have this attitude. Yes, I can assure you, I did wander through the "north wing" of the Mickey D's in the Tangeman University Center and came up to the brothers and said, "Hi" and almost came back home with my head in a bucket.  One thing I have reasoned out though -- at one time Rich White People must have thought something of Black people. Even 400 years ago they had enough guns, chains, and dogs to enslave any people on the face of this Earth. Certainly it would have been easier, say, to enslave the North American Indians than go all the way across the Atlantic to capture Africans. No, for whatever reason, the Indians weren't productive. The Africans were. The Africans could produce things of value. Therefore the Africans WERE VALUABLE.  Of course the Rich White People tried to keep this a secret from the Africans. Good heavens, if the Africans came to look at themselves as a valuable, proud race of people who could do things that the Rich White People couldn't do, they just might get "uppity" and decide to start their own weapons factories one day and snarl at all the White people as if they had the mange.  Which brings me to my next point -- it's a nice idea to say that you want to try to keep one's dollars in one's own community. The only problem is that they are not your dollars. They belong to the government. If you want to hire someone you have to give 15% of that person's pay to retired and disabled people, and those retired and disabled people may or may not be interested in frequenting your business. Furthermore, the worker has to pay sometimes up to 40% of his income to President Bush and Governor Taft. I don't know about you, but I can't remember the last time I saw either one of these gentlemen even hosting an informal gathering at Integrity Hall or something of the sort.  No, if you want to be economically successful you have to do it just the way that they do it. If you are Black and want to start a business, you find out every last thing that White people spend their money foolishly on and try to sell them more of it.    

    

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

        My mother has adult-onset muscular dystrophy.      Several years ago she reached a stage where she needed 24/7/365 skilled nursing care. The only way she could obtain this level of care is by going on Medicaid.      I just got another email from her detailing a change in procedure at her nursing home that she is unhappy with.      My mother is VERY intelligent and VERY eccentric. Having her in such a structured setting is a grave disservice to both her and the people taking care of her. Several times she has expressed her desire to exit this planet, as her quality of life will only continue to deteriorate, but our American society has seen fit to hold as a virtue that to be alive and in intractible physical and emotional pain is a virtue.      In many ways, however, my mother is lucky. Her decline in ability and fall into the Medicaid system came just about at the exact moment that she had exhausted her resources. She was not married. She had no dependent children. Others are not so lucky.      In America, being Sick and Poor at the same time is a crime. In some cases, seeking medical treatment and being unable to pay can  urlLink get you thrown in jail .       The scenario goes something like this -- you are thrown out of work due to the declining economy.  You have the choice between feeding your family and paying the rent or picking up COBRA, so you drop your insurance coverage.  You are run over by a bus and ALMOST killed while looking for work.  You are rushed, unconscious, to the local charity hospital where $200,000 worth of work is done on you to save your life.      You are sent home, where, in a few months, you are sued for the $200,000 you owe the hospital.  You are still on crutches but have gotten a part-time job doing telemarketing that you will lose if you miss so much as one shift.  You don't show up for your court date and a warrant is issued for your arrest.      Crime: being poor and getting sick.  Punishment: incarceration.      My mother is in a similar situation -- she is sick and she is too poor to afford the kind of care she really needs, so she is essentially a prisoner of the State.      Other developed nations have decided there is a better way.  They have a National Health System.  Even Canada has such a system.  Every other nation in the world has decided that it is INHUMANE to jail people for being poor and sick.      Sometimes I think the only reason we don't have nationalized medicine is that the US is the LAST country on Earth where the ultra-rich from around the world can come and bid certain medical procedures sky high.      Sometimes I wonder how the medical field has been so manipulated.       Once upon a time only the government and a very few businesses could own computers.  They were as big as a house and used as much power as a small American city.  Now they are as small as a couple of hardback books, run on batteries no bigger than a couple of packs of cigarettes, and, amortized over their useful life, cost less than a subscription to the local paper.      People were griping about medical care being too expensive in the 1930's.  If medical care had advanced at the same rate as electronics and computer science, the doctor would be coming to see YOU every week for $5/visit and common drugs would be cheaper than M&M's.      In any event, something needs to be done, and soon.   

    

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

        I just stumbled across mention that   urlLink  SCLC's Rev. Fred Shuttlesworth Opposes Same Sex Marriage    on the blog of the little brother of an old classmate of mine.  Of course what I find amazing is that the concensus seems to be that the gay marriage issue is SO heated that it will actually drive long-time Democrats to vote for Republicans.  I have an even more radical idea in mind -- separate Marriage and State. In other countries, for instance Malaysia and Israel, family law is an area left up to the individual relgions. If one religion wants to allow gay marriage and another doesn't, there should not be a problem -- just as some religions allow divorces and others don't, and some religions have married clergy and others don't.  In fact, I find myself wondering WHY the gays are in such a hurry to join the straights in this torturous ordeal called marriage. It seems to me that we ought to get some of the problems with STRAIGHT marriage worked out before we attempt to deal with gay marriage as well.  When I was growing up, I saw two basic kinds of marriage --  One type included one or the other party in the marriage being totally subservient to the other. In most cases of course it was the man who utterly dominated the woman. He controlled the finances, madethe decisions about where to live, etc.  The last couple of generations I have seen more and more cases where it is the other way around -- where the woman has to give the man permission on what job to take, how many children they are going to have, where they are going to go on vacation, etc.  The other type of marriage I have seen start out fairly evenly matched -- both the man and woman were "Type A" personalities. Those are the marriages that are the most interesting of course. They last anywhere from 2 to 7 years, usually involve 1 - 3 children, and end in the midst of some of the most bitter, acrimonious and inhuman behavior I have ever witnessed or read about in my life.  I've come to the conclusion that marriage in general is not for everyone. There is almost nobody alive who has the intelligence, emotional maturity, or education to truly make an informed entry into a contract of marriage. For instance, it is abundantly clear that most of my friends had NO comprehension that getting married, and certainly having kids, turns over to the state the right to hunt you down to your dying day. Getting married (and/or having kids) opens you up to a truly BIZARRE situation where the government will confiscate truly crippling amounts of money from your income and hand it over to your ex-wife who will be allowed and encouraged to snort it in front of a good half dozen of your favorite former friends while your impressionable underaged children watch.  Now, mind you, just having the kids can induce all these problems, but I'd like to think in the philosophical analysis of things you could say to yourself, "Okay, I screwed up ... literally ..." in much the same way that one might screw up by driving drunk or buying too many risky stocks.  But marriage takes it to another level. Marriage is essentially the state (or the church) ENCOURAGING people to enter into a contract that almost nobody is qualified to enter into. It is as if the Congress, the President, and the Supreme Court are saying, "Suuuuuuure ... we WANT you to get married ... we WANT you to have more kids than you can afford ... we WANT the bank forclose on you ... we WANT to sieze your children ... we WANT to send you to jail ..."  No ... getting married should be right up there in complexity with converting to Judaism. You should have to approach the rabbi, minister, priest, or judge at least THREE times. The rabbi, minister, priest, or judge (let's just say "official") should sit you down with at least a dozen deadbeat parents, Chapter 7 filers, single parents, and people who have served time on domestic violence charges and listen to their stories over a period of weeks. There should certainly be a test on 1) basic finances, 2) negotiation skills, 3) ethics. You should have to get at least a 90 on this test. You should also have to produce three "sponsors" -- three people (at least one of whom is not related) who promise under pain of fine and beating with a religious publication of their choice to be available 24/7 by cellphone or pager in the event that one or the other of the "happy couple" is contemplating shipping the other to Kuala Lumpur in no less than 52 relatively small FedEx packages.  THEN they should allowed to be married ...  AND ...  The state and/or the church (and/or the media) should send a "Devil's Advocate" to every wedding. When the Official says, "Is there anyone here who has any reason why this couple should not get married?" the Devil's Advocate should have a list as long as Robert Wadlow's arm. The couple should have to defend their choice in open session and need to have the approval of a 2/3 majority of the guests in order to be allowed to go ahead with it.  THEN ...  Within the first 72 hours either member of the marriage should be able to show up at a hospital, fire house or police station with his/her spouse (sort of like one can drop off an unwanted baby anonymously in some states) and/or a note saying, "I was on crack when I did this ..." and arrangements should be able to be easily made to annul the marriage.  Once we have these steps in place for heterosexual marriages for atleast 10 years and see how that goes, THEN we can discuss gay marriage, polygamy, marrying your pet llama, etc.    

    

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       One interesting thing about Cincinnati is our never ending supply of thumpers.  I'm reading the  Enquirer  yesterday and I am assaulted by a review of  urlLink    Finding God in the Questions   by Timothy Johnson.  This is a long-winded diatribe that will certainly sell well here.  Essentially it is the great conservative argument for the veracity of the King James Bible.  The argument goes something like this:    "Upon contemplating the complexity of the human body, I cannot fathom that it could have been created by mere random events.       Therefore, there must be an intelligence at work.       That intelligence must be God.      Therefore the Bible, character for character, word for word, must be true.      Oh, and, by the way, if the King James Version was good enough for our Lord and Savior, it's good enough for me."       There was an argument much like this about a hundred years ago when telescopes were first pointed at Venus:    "I can't see a THING on Venus.    It must be covered with clouds.    If it's covered with clouds it must be wet.    If it's wet it's probably a swamp and if it's a swamp there must be life -- maybe even dinosaurs."    Observation: I can't see a thing. Conclusion: Dinosaurs.    Sometimes I find myself wondering how ANYONE can take literal religion seriously. Now if you go to Papua New Guinea, rural Thailand, Calcutta, or Kansas you will find certain things in common. You will probably find people who have learned how to grow grain and how to fish. You will find people who know up from down. You will find people who know how to do SOME kind of math. However, if you ask all these people how the Earth got here you will be treated to a STAGGERING variety of stories. These stories will range from a whole collection of gods doing all sorts of wild things to one another, to a single God creating something as sublimly complex (and almost impossible to understand) as a human female out of a spare rib. Something can't be right with this picture.     No, religion is not in the same ballpark as science. Religion is in the same ballpark as art and music. Just like the differences between  urlLink  Galactica 1978   and  urlLink  Galactica 2003     being pretty severe and yet telling the same story. If people could just remember that there would be much less suffering in the world.         urlLink    

    

    
</post>


</Blog>