<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well today at work was better then the past few weeks. i talked to neil about being in total freak out mode all the time, and how much it makes my job suck. i guess he didn't realize how irritating he had become. it makes me think that i could never do that job, because i'd totally freak out all the time too! your paycheck basically is based on the performance in the office, and more importantly who is at your desk. the thing that kills me about him is he has nothing to worry about, but he does anyway. i guess i see myself in him a lot. freaking out about money, thinking things are always better somewhere else, everything. i guess i'm a half empty glass kinda person. and i'm trying to change that. so what am i going to do? -eat better (more protein + less carbs=happier meghan) -exercise (trying to find a gym...they're all too expensive...guh!) -focus on the good things that i've got going (no more worrying about what i haven't got) -keep a bitch journal (basically a place where i can vent about things so i'm not complaining to anyone..well, not as much...buying a pretty one at the bookstore tomorrow)  sounds like a plan!!! and i like having a plan for myself. makes me feel like i got one step done!  stopped by mom and dad's house before they ran out. they bought the stuff for that flowerpot smoker, so that's pretty cool.  i guess we're having smoked pork butt...mmm...pulled pork is my FAVORITE bbq...and i think ryan is going to smoke a brisket on monday since we have the day off! good stuff! as for fireworks, i think we're going to lisle's fireworks like we usually do. i don't know who all is going to come with us, but dad seems pretty keen to hang out and check them out.  i took the 9th off of work, and ryan doesn't work on fridays, so i'm going to see if we can have an adventure downtown! maybe we can meet mikey and casey for lunch, and go to some museums, or on a tour of the harp factory!!! that'd be cool! lincoln park zoo is supposed to open their new ape/monkey exhibit...maybe we'll go there!  i also got to talk to my sister in law jenny today. i hadn't talked to her in a couple weeks, and normally i see her 3 times a week! so, i called her to check in. i love talking to her. good times.  so on to my lists: yuckies: -work lately -dirty apartment -having to do laundry -not enough time in the day -not far enough on my project as i need to be  yummers: +getting myself on a life gameplan to better me! +having time to practice my harp tonight +getting to watch that 70s show +kitties! +having a washer/dryer/dishwasher 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, today at work was pretty good during the day. i was so busy i didn't have time to think. all of a sudden it was 3pm, and all sorts of shit started hitting the fan. changes are coming in my office. and they are because of me...   well, we'll see what my horoscope has to say about it...  "The fire burns in your eyes again, and you possess a certain spring to your stride. You are able to laugh about anything that comes your way. Accept life as a joyous jumble and go about living it. Your sense of humor is your best means of transportation, taking you from delight to delight. Don't just ask how, but inquire as to why something is peculiar. This is a great time for brainstorming and innovations."  well that whole fire burns in your eyes thing is right...pink eye and all. i normally do laugh at anything that comes my way...and i think that's good...i have been inquiring why things are piculiar....hmmm....brainstorming...good idea.... thanks yahoo horoscope.... let's see what other sites have to say...  "It's a so-so day for socializing. Work concerns are on your mind and make it difficult for you to unwind or you may find your company a bit boring. Decisions involving your social and romantic interests are right on target."  this one is DEFINATELY on target. work DOES consume my mind right now...like RIGHT now! crazy...  i guess that means its time for me to quit stewing about it all, make some changes in my brain and for now, i'll play my harp...FABULOUS!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so i went to my reports screen and someone linked me from a naked celebrity website. it's got black lines so you can't see their unmentionables, but you get the idea of whats to see. weird ones? melissa joan heart (clarissa?!), katie holmes (too much of a girl next door...creeps me out), and nicole kidman (aka skelator!) funny stuff  work was kinda crappy, but i came home. ryan used his belated birthday giftcard from brendan to buy himself a new zelda game. it's a lot of fun to watch! so we'll probably settle down and do that tonight. i'll probably work on my crochet project some, and maybe read calvin and hobbes too.   funny stuff of today? people at work trying to convince me they felt the earthquake. yeah, i'm not buying that. just seems a little too "something i can talk about by the water cooler" to me...  crappers: -work -pinkeye -apartments that don't clean themselves -not getting to practice my harp as often -being tired  rockers!: +ryan cooking tastey burgers for dinner +being home +kitties welcoming me at the door +talking to old friends +a long weekend coming up +building our own  urlLink smoker  (thank you Good Eats!) +learning how to post a link on my site!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so, yeah. woke up this morning with pinkeye in BOTH fucking eyes. what the fuck? i wore my contacts to the picnic incase i got thrown in the dunk tank and so i wouldn't break my glasses in the moonwalk...fuck you contacts...fuck you... they were new ones the doctor gave me. i wore them maybe 5 times since i got them, and never more then one day at a time. i think the thing that made it happen was i took my nap with them in. but i've never had anything happen because of that...stupid fucking eyes! i CURSE YOU! so i look all stupid...and people at work are going to call me pinky again....at least it happened this morning, so i started my antibiotic ointment crap, and should be contagious free by tomorrow morning. i have some antibiotic pills left over from my bronchitis (i know, i was supposed to take them ALL), so maybe i'll pop one of those and maybe it'll help get rid of it faster. plans for the day? i have no idea. ryan and i  slept in until 12! that NEVER happens. i guess we were really tired...and you know what's sad...i could totally crawl back in bed for a nap this afternoon already...guh!  we're going to the mall so i can buy some capri pants for work and such, going to best buy to spend ryan's giftcard brendan got him, going to his parent's house to print something out for the fork knife spoon cd, and going to my house to say hi.  sounds overly exciting, i know. and all the while, i'll be walking around with big, swollen, puss filled, eyeballs... god i hate this disease. i think it's the worst there is...and to get it 2 months in a row? even worse!  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i just got home from the picnic. it went well.. seems like it was a hit. not everybody came who said they would, and people who said they'd be there to help me didn't show up when they said they would either, but otherwise it was good. a little cool for the dunktank, but people still got in there. the moonwalk was definately a big hit. ryan and pablo grilled all the food together, and i think everything turned out pretty nice! priscilla brought her new puppy Maglio, and he's absolutlely adorable., i left before it was all cleaned up, but fuck it. i'm tired. other people are on the committee too, and they can help get everything cleaned up...at least that's what i think. i set the fucker up, and was there at 8:50 this morning. they can stay another hour and break it all down again.  if we do it next year, i'm going for the MASSIVE moonwalk, and we'll forget the dunk tank...maybe we'll get a cotton candy machine instead!!!   i'm exhausted....it's nap time
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      work was crazy busy! they were suspicious of one of my bigger brokers at work... so they audited my files and they found more fraud, which means bad news, but i think they know that it wasn't me at all...and my manager kinda told me that she'll protect me because she knows i didn't do anything...just stressful all the same. oh well, we'll figure it out. all i know is, if they find it in the older files that have closed already, they'll have to buy $20 million in loans back from our investors...and my name is all over it! blech! enough about crap at work!  plans for this evening?! baking my friend Kyle a birthday cake for his birthday party we're having tomorrow. buying pizza and watching a movie.  tomorrow will be busy too! it's finally june 26th! the day of the company picnic i've been planning for the past couple months. a few people on my committee went and bought all the food and crap. i have it all in my car. the other people are picking up the chicken, burgers and hotdog tomorrow morning. me? well, ryan and i have to be at the park we rented a pavillion at 9am tomorrow morning so i'm there for them to deliver the moonwalk, the dunktank and the grill i rented! AWESOME! and i got a final head count today at work....get ready for this....80+ PEOPLE!!!! wha? that's INSANE!!!!  should be fun though! a long day, but a good time!  i got an email today from my college roommate, Jamie! she's in fucking ireland...i still can't wrap my head around how that happened. i really hope she has AIM so i can chat with her for days about it. i just don't understand how someone who was living in a doublewide in kentucky, trying to be a country star, ends up in ireland, engaged to some guy!!! all i know is i'm happy for her!!! that's so amazing!  nuts!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i got home around 8:30 after a hard day of work, and a nice dinner out with my friend casey from work. ryan was walking from the kitchen to the desk and screamed out "holy shit!" i said "what?!" "chloe is peeing on the fucking wall!" yeah, aparently the litter box was too dirty for her. she had already peed on the matt in the closet, so to get our attention, she peed on the wall under my sewing maching...while staring at ryan...and then she cried afterwards... fabulous! so we cleaned it all up. bleached it all down. ryan cleaned the litter box (which we do once a day anyway) and said it looks like one of the cats wasn't feeling too hot earlier... my first thought? more vet bills  great.  what next? this week has just been great.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      man, on the crappiest of days...all i have to do is come home and watch pirates of the caribbean...johnny in a pirate costume...makes you feel fabulous in 5 seconds.  so i'm now watching pirates with the johnny depp comentary on. i love his laugh. so dorky! hahah. he seems like such an odd character! well, anyway. work kinda really sucked. like a fear-for-my-job-kinda-sucked.  that's great...basically a whole bunch of crap has been going on, and i don't know what's going to happen. i just hope that everyone believes that it's not me...i can't really explain...but it's not good. guess i'll kinda have to see how it plays out. i really don't think i'll be seriously effected. but i worry all the same.  i stopped at jewel, and bought some chicken, cooked it up, and ate it for dinner. it was pretty tastey. and i made enough extra so i have for lunch this week. thats good. chloe is sitting her giving me a bath...i guess i must need it. kitty love!  well, i checked on the total for the company picnic i'm organizing for this weekend. so far? 85 people....that shit is almost as big as my fucking wedding! and i'm supposed to be organizing it all...talk about pressure. i hope that we have enough food, and other people help us get it all cooked up. but a moonwalk? and a dunk tank? that should be good!!!  well, johnny calls!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so, i got to work this morning at 7:15am and didn't get to leave until 6:30pm. man, and not only was it long,  but it was absolutely horrible work to do today.  i can't think...i guess i'll report it later...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey all, i'm just testing this thing to see if i can post from an email like i'm supposed to be able to do... if so, i can post while i'm at work! the big guys at corporate check our computers for what sites we go to...and i'm sure blogger.com has been blocked. but this way i can send a quick note through my email! GENIUS!   		 __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Mail is new and improved - Check it out! http://promotions.yahoo.com/new_mail 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well today was kinda sucky. i think the weather had a lot to do with it. i had a dream last night i was in a plane crash. it wasn't high off the ground, it was during takeoff, and it crashed into a hospital...so i jumped and grabbed some wires. then it turned into a video game kinda thing where i could rewind time...weird. so i checked a dream dictionary and it said:  To dream of being in this event is a feeling of not only a dramatic negative change in your life, but also to everyone around you as well as your enviroment. A very negative symbol and should be meditated upon. To dream of witnessing this event is symbolic of feelings of helplessness in the face of a great tragedy. In prohetic dreams this heralds a great change in the distant future (planes are associated with great distance). This change may not be negative.   another one says: To dream that a plane crashes, signifies that you have set overly high and unrealistic goals for yourself and are in danger of having it come crashing down. Alternatively, your lack of confidence, self-defeating attitude and self-doubt toward the goals you have set for yourself is represented by the crashing airplane; you do not believe in your ability to attain those goals. Loss of power and uncertainty in achieving your goals are also signified.  so basically, not i'm worried about what i'm worrying about! oh well...i guess it's just telling me something i'm thinking about doing is not a good idea...which i kinda knew anyway..or is it that i WON'T succeed because of the poor attitude and me doubting it before i even start....so confusing!   work was okay. came home, we had tacos, i crocheted, ryan played with his recording stuff. i watched the news. depressing. Senator Ryan's sex scandles in his divorce papers, cingular is getting sued, etc.  the worst- they showed a town meeting where people are protesting a mosque being built in their area because they're scared of terrorist attacks happening to them. a quote? "extreme muslims blow people up. conservative muslims fund the extreme muslims" nice...real nice. it amazes me. i made ryan listen.  he just said "What? people don't like brown people anymore?" and i realized it's true!!!  the best- there's a gorilla in a zoo who won't mate. so they've been showing him gorilla porn every night to get him to do it. the perfume didn't work, so they're hoping if he sees how to do it, he'll try. that's awesome!  time for bed
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well today has gone nothing like planned! but who's to say it's a bad thing? we had planned to chill at home this morning, and go to costco, then head out to my parents and ryan's parents for fathers day/birthday festivities. instead, mom called at 9am this morning asking for ryan's expertise cooking ribs. of course we abliged, because ribs always need to be tastey! we packed up our emergency tastey ribs gear, and headed off for mom and dads and were there at 10am. and although they weren't done by 12, those ribs were damn tastey! mikey liked his birthday present of Riddick for xbox and i got some quality family hang out time. i also enjoyed feeling (AND SEEING!!) julie and casey's baby kicking around in her belly after dinner. it was pretty funny when julie pushed a little on one side of her belly, and a second later the baby kicked right back! hahaha! amazing! it's so awesome that they do that! ryan was kinda creeped out, but he's never seen that before, so he didn't know they did it at all. after that, with full bellies and tired eyes, we head over to the croson's for more dad's day food around 4pm. mark and jenny were there already. ryan and mark went to borders. ryan was quite pleased with himself when he came home with 6 calvin and hobbes books that were buy 2 get the 3rd free, and only $5.99/$6.99 a piece to begin with....$105 worth of books for $34? = priceless! we hung out, talked, ate some more, and made it home around 7:30pm. it's now 9:30, and i have found myself sleeping on the couch for the past hour...so much for getting our laundry done! chloe and i decided it's time to change into our pj's and jump into bed! (but not before we update our blog!) been waiting for itsjustmeghan.com to become mine. i bought it last night, but it hasn't unlocked yet. i'm supposed to hang with casey and julie after work tuesday and casey is going to help me out with it...so hopefully it'll be ready by then.  what can you expect? pictures, sound clips, videos, etc of me doing stuff (ie current projects, playing harp, etc)...and things i think are funny (ie fat men rollerskating, old people kissing, whatever i laugh at that day etc).  bed calls...being a daughter is exhausting i guess!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i just bought myself a domain name! i own a piece of cyber space! www.itsjustmeghan.com and it's all mine!  teehee! so exciting! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so ryan and i went to see harry potter today!!! i really enjoyed it! it did bother me that they didn't explain everything that the book did, so i felt the need to fill ryan in. he didn't care. i still can't get him to read them. oh well, his loss. i'm going to start #4 again! i know i loved it. the thing is, i read them so fast, i can't remember everything about them. so, it'll kinda be like reading a new book again! hooray! we have nick, eric, kyle and toddd over right now. celebrating eric's belated birthday.  i made him a cake and everything. his birthday was in march, and at that time we couldn't really afford anything to do for him, so we're making up for it now. he was pretty surprised.  we're watching DJ Shadow, eating birthday cake, i'm poking around on the internet and crocheting. chloe is sitting with ryan looking pretty content. hana is sleeping in the bedroom. nobody is online, but that's okay. i can  poke around for hours. my harp lesson went okay this morning. her harps strings are a little closer together then mine are, so playing for her is kinda akward. she said i'm doing well. but i think she's waiting for me to hit my wall, and be humbled. i feel like i'm already there. it's getting harder to sit down and just have it happen. i'm ready now for some technique drills, scales, arpeggios, etc. to improve my skills. it's time to get serious! no more being casual about it! it's on! i want to be making fat cash next year this time playing weddings! and i was thinking today, at christmas time a year and a half from now, i can go play at borders etc and make money that way too! AMAZING! i've been totally crabby lately...i need to stop that...no fun...no fun at all... we're going to mom and dad's tomorrow for mikey's birthday and for fathers day. and then we go to the croson's for fathers day with them. that means lots of food! i've been chatting with jason a lot lately. he was talking the otherday about flying me out to visit him for a weekend...i'm seriously tempted to! i think it'd be a lot of fun! i always thought he was HILARIOUS to hang around. memories of him running around my apartment immitating the raptor, and doing goofy dances, and i still laugh out loud! i'll talk with ryan about it, and if the offer still stands, i'll see if he'll still have me.  i've been looking back a lot on my past few years. college was a blur of depression, chocolate, and my bedroom. i didn't really do anything but wish i was home, and when i was home i wish i got to stay there. i over-reacted to a lot of things, took a lot of it personally, and i think it was majorly due to the fact that i was VERY insecure down there. after i graduated, i thought i grew up so much. then the teaching situation happened, and i was small and defensless again. then i decided to do stuff that makes me happy and started my job at the small mortgage company in lisle. i thought i grew so much. nope, wrong again. i then went to california for 5 weeks and came back, and i thought i had changed a ton. well, i changed a lot. grew up a little more. made decisions as to what i thought was important to me. and i'm still growing up. i'm at a point where everyone is expecting me to get pregnant and be an adult. and while i want to start having kids because they're so much fun, i still don't feel like i'm mature enough to handle it... oh well. basically, i've grown up a LOT since college, and i'm not done yet.  whew, that was a long tangent. back to crocheting!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so i've set up this account at blogger.com in the hopes of eventually moving it to my very own domain name!!! crazy!  casey said that he's going to see if itsjustmeghan.com is available, and he'd host it on his server at home! amazing! i'm very excited! my very own domain! well we're out the door for now! going to see harry potter, FINALLY! words can't describe how exited i am!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well i'm home now! california was okay. had it's ups and downs. some serious shit is going down and found out that people at work have been talking shit about me, so that was quite discouraging.  but, i did a good job, found a whole bunch of fraud, met an awesome girl from our Herndon branch, went to the beach and got soaked by the surf, ate lots of tastey food, and got a pedicure (and i got flowers on my toes! so cute!).   i also got some knitting done on my hug.  i'm hoping to get some more done tomorrow.     not as far along as i'd hoped i'd be, but i was also playing "the sims" for GBA. awesome!  oh! and i also saw this guy every time i went to eat in the hotel. quite possibly the most amazing mullet i've ever seen!!! i totally jumped up when he came in and went to stand in line for food i wasn't planning on eating to take this picture!!!   and what's better is, when we went to the airport, marilyn and i got in line and she just said "oh....girl..." and there he was. right in line before us, and his mullet was all braided. awesome!  i got in town at 12:30am last night. slept this morning until 11:30. i wasn't sleeping well out there. not at home and just in general, stressed out. we got my oil changed today, stopped by funco land and overheard the new assistant manager telling his employees about the importance of getting game reserves, and heard him sucking up to his regional, bought chicken legs to grill, and stopped by ryan's parent's house to say hi. my parents were off somewhere, so i didn't see them yet. probably tomorrow.  been curious about transferring somewhere. we looked online and we can get a 3-4 bed, 2 bath house with a heated inground pool in a pool room on a lake in Orlando for about $210. that's insane! it was SUPER nice looking too.... hmmm...tempting. but, we'll see how everything plays out i guess. took a nap this afternoon. taking vitamin C. i have the beginnings of a cold (post nasal drip and all), so i'm hoping i don't get sick. now it's 1am, i'm posting here, ryan's playing golf with brendan.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well i made it home.  tired ass. and chloe's ready for me to say "bedtime for bonzos," pick her up, and go to bed. i'll tell you all of my adventures when i wake tomorrow
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      FW: Msg: At hotel. Really nice. Forgot orange county doesn't hbve fast food! Had to eat stuff from grocery store last nigh  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      At hotel. Really nice. Forgot orange county doesn't hbve fast food! Had to eat stuff from grocery store last night. Off to  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Flight delayed! Plane broke. Keep those fingers crossed!  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm leaving for cali in a little bit. hopefully it'll be an enjoyable trip.  i got yarn for my HUG pattern and started on it last night. and ryan bought me the sims game, so that should be fun. i'll try to post from my cell phone since i won't be able to post from the computers at work. should be interesting...hmmm...  i'll keep you posted. next few posts will be short and sweet wish me luck! i hate leaving ryan and my kitties at home :( 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      man, i can't tell you how relieved i am that it's the weekend! even though i only worked wed-fri, that was one of the longest 3 days of my life! my files at work have just been impossible, and i'm telling you, i am getting REALLY fed up with my desk. i think i just need some more time off.  cue the realization i'm leaving for california tomorrow. now i know it's for work, but this kind of work has NOTHING to do with my job...no phones, no brokers, no supervisor telling me to do one thing and then doing another when the broker calls so i look like a dumbass, no irritating questions, no irritating fellow employees. just me, 3 other people, in a room with a pile of files. silence. auditing and silence.  i'm sure i'll get bored with it before the end of the week, but right now? it looks like a beautiful oasis amidst a pile of crap.  i'm going to work all day, get a couple free beers after work at our hotel, chill in the hot tub or the pool, knit a lot, and relax. in the evenings we'll head to the spectrum.  well, i got my jeans (and a couple shirts and a sweater hoodie teehee), my sweet record bag, the kitties their water fountain, and some yarn to make that hug out of. i don't know if this stuff will work the way i hope, but if not, i can make a skinny trendy scarf no problem!  we bought "the office" from bbc america box sets with the first and second season. gonna start it right now! plans for this evening? pizza, laundry, packing, knitting, and watching the office! chow~
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      tonight? went to dinner with the family for mom and dad's 30th wedding anniversary!  happy anniversary mom and dad!    note to self: don't eat so much tarimisu. i feel like i'm going to puke now!  talked to casey about helping me set up some different pages on here. i think i'll have one for photos. but more importantly, this place is going to transform into a knitting blog too! i'm totally going to have a page showing my current projects and current status on them. that way you guys can see what i'm doing! i don't know, maybe someone out there will enjoy it! i can't tell you how many knit and kitty blogs there are out there! and i'm joining the ranks! i can't wait!  tuesday night i hung out with lindsey. it was good times. we went to bakers square. i haven't been to the square in  a while. their chicken fingers were crappier then i remember. but chilling and chatting with lindsey was awesome!  wednesday night i went to dinner with people from work. man, i'm realizing more and more how dumb people are. it's honestly like being in highschool again. people start rumors, talk shit, just in an effort to make themselves look better. all the while they are super trashy! ah well. they aren't as cool as me!   today, work sucked. it was just WAY too busy, and to make matters worse? they had to fix our server, so we were helpless for about 2 hours. you don't realize how much you rely on that shit until it breaks! i'm gonna have to go in early just to catch up the rest of the way. i've stopped taking so much shit from broker's offices lately. got into a battle of wills with one today. guess who won? ME! hahahhaa  list of stuff to do tomorrow: -get chloe and hana a kitty water fountain -go to home goods and see about a stylish bag (thanks lindsey!) -go to walmart and see about chunky yarn for hug project so i can work on it while in cali -try the Sim's Bustin Out for GBA ryan picked up for me with our free best buy giftcard
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today is an anxious day. i origionally took off monday and tuesday this week to relax, but that's not happening. yesterday, although i got to tryout a couple yarn shops with mom, julie and pat, i was anxious all day because my kitty was at the vet.  it really bothered me knowing she was miserable. well, at least she's home  now. today i'm all anxious because i know i have to go back to work tomorrow, and that i'm gonna have to leave for california on sunday. i hate traveling. i just wish ryan and the kitties could come with. it'd make it a lot easier on me.   first round of medicating chloe went alright. we had to do it twice because the first time i shot her liquid antibiotics on her face instead of in her mouth. the stuff smells like oranges, and she didn't seem to mind it.she actually kept it all down. last time she'd foam everything out of her mouth, so half of the drugs didn't make it in. if you haven't seen a cat foam, believe me, it's not a pretty picture. she earned a kitty treat after today's performance! we realized ryan's going to have to give her doses by himself for a week twice a day...i don't know how he's going to do that, but hopefully she'll cooperate.     here's my sick baby.  she's been sleeping a lot. and slept with me all last night on my arm and on my pillow by my head.     jealous hana maru and here's a picture of hana maru. she was jealous that chloe was having her picture posted on the website. she started meowning as soon as she realized what was going on, so i snapped one of her too.   plans for today? lay low i guess. i'm so anxious today it'll be best to keep myself busy at home. i'm going to start working on some hankercheif's for my hair. it's at the point where it's getting big, and if i don't keep it under wraps, i'm going to want to cut it. so i'll have to do this for a couple more weeks until i can get the bottom trimmed and it reshaped a little more. i was hopin to get it done this week, but chloe's dr visit was $120 i didn't expect to spend...so that kinda killed that. i was hoping to get new jeans before california, but i guess that's on hold now too...bummer   hair scarf i'm currently knitting. pattern from  urlLink Stitch 'n Bitch .  i'm hoping i can maybe get some cheap chunky yarn to make a  urlLink Hug , too.  i thought this would be perfect for work! it's kinda like a sweater, but just the arms and the piece across the back.  the office is always either cold or hot. so i thought it'd be nice to bridge that gap!  let me know what you think!!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so after taking chloe to the vet this morning, and her staying all day getting poked with needles, they called us at 5pm, and found out that she's got a bladder infection.  so i guess she has to be on medicine 2 times a day for the next 2 weeks and then get retested...she's not happy with us...not at all...and we have to do the diet thing.. i think we're going to need one of those water fountain cat things. maybe get her drinking more, and it'll help.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so chloe is at the vet. she's been randomly peeing lately, and i don't know if it's her being an ass, or her having a bladder infection... so i brought her in. and for the first time ever, the vet told me she's fat. now, i know she's fat, but until they tell me it's something to worry about, i haven't worried. i've even asked in the past, but they've told me no, she's just a big cat.  not now. i have to put chloe on a diet...that means feeding chloe and hana seperately. and measuring out their food and taking it up when they're done...why does that scare me? chloe likes to bite when she's hungry...she get's so freakin moody...  but, they tried expelling her bladder, but i guess it's not full enough, so chloe is getting injected with saline, and then in a couple hours they're going to try again. they think she might have a bladdar infection. no good. i just hope she's okay, and that it's not too expensive... my poor kitty. :(
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so we think the meat thermometer is broken, because the brisket was overcooked and pretty dry. which totally sucks because ryan worked on it for 10 hours. brownies are okay, just a little dry. timmy went home after dinner. seemed a little disappointed, and i can't blame him. he came over at 1, and we didn't eat until 8...and it kinda sucked.  well, i guess we're ordering pizza tomorrow... blech 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      9 hours 22 minutes.......still no brisket.... i'm freakin STARVING!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      we met our neighbors from across the hall last night. that was pretty cool. ryan was out on the patio cleaning the grill when the one year old girl and her dad came over. she started pointing at ry and screaming "kitty". her dad said to ry that she likes seeing our cats. so, i brought chloe outside so the little girl could say "hi!" she was SO excited. and she kept barking at the cats (because she hasn't learned that all animals don't bark yet). ryan managed to get hana maru outside for a little bit. she was meowing back at the little girl (who we found out is named hannah, too) everytime she barked at her. it was cute. we talked with her parents a while. her mom is due novemeber 4th with another girl. if that baby is half as adorable as their daughter hannah, then they will be very lucky parents! i guess they've been in our apartment complex for 5 years. they moved to this unit from across the parking lot so they could get away from the noisy neighbors and to upgrade into a 2 bedroom.  the guy (i'm horrible, i can't remember the parent's names...we were preoccupied with the cats) was asking me about my harp. i guess they hear me practicing sometimes. and they asked ryan about his guitar. i kinda like that people can hear me playing, and they say you "play" the harp. not you're "learning" the harp. makes me feel like i'm further along. it's comforting knowing your neighbors. i look forward to talking to them again. i think we'll have them over for brisket some weekend soon. and i can't wait to play with their daughter some more. makes me want to start having kids...just not yet. i want a house.   today ryan's smoking brisket.   i'm baking smores brownies. they're SO rich, and SO yummy, and SO bad for you, but SO tastey.    timmy's over playing ninja gaiden. i guess brendan might come over for some eats too, if he gets out of practice soon. it'll be good to have his opinion on how our brisket tastes. that and we have a lot of food, so another mouth to fee would be welcome.  tomorrow i'm hanging out with julie, and maybe jenny if she can meet up with us. we're going to hit some yarn shops right around here. i guess there's one in downtown glenellyn, and one in wheaton, and naperville. i'm hoping to buy a  urlLink yarn baller  so i can organize all of my yarn scraps and condense them. right now they are all getting knotted up in the big tupperware in the closet. hopefully i can fix that.  once i do that, i'm going to finish my purple sweater. and maybe start some new projects. found a whole bunch of  urlLink cool books  on how to make simple chunky sweaters. they knit up fast, and look funky...so, hopefully i can do those, and create myself a stylish winter wardrobe. my only worry? the chunky sweaters make my boobs look HUGE. wish i had tiny boobs....they look cuter in chunky sweaters. oh well. i guess i can deal!  one nostril smells smoking brisket, the other smells sweet chocolatey brownies. i'm in smellin' heaven!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      okay. it's been a while.  nothing else is really going on. last night we went to dinner with the seals at the brookfield zoo. ryan's parents got us tickets to go with them. it's pretty cool. they put you on a tram, take you on a little tour, then bring you to the main exhibit. we had drinks and appetizers by the walruses. they had volunteers around to answer questions about the animals and everything. one was an older lady who didn't know anything about them (we later found out) but she sure did fart while she was talking to us, because all of a sudden it smelled like ass! they had a buffet of austrailian bbq (seafood cabobs with cocoanut sauce, sweet rice, and potatoes), and an amazing dessert table! my kinda party!  after dinner we went back by the seals, and we talked to one of the trainers,  and she gave us the real scoop on the animals! (thus prooving old stinky pants didn't know anything!) she told us about the walruses, and how they like to destroy their exhibit by chewing on the rocks and stuff. i guess that's why their tusks have been removed, and why their exhibit looks so old school. she said they had the nice rocks in there, but the walruses tore it all up within a month or so, so they had to go back to the old school solid cement. crazy walruses!  while we were talking to the keeper, i spied this AMAZING couple getting trashed at the open bar....why people decide to go to the zoo to do this is beyond me! but, they sure did have matching outfits. she had bangs that went from the top of her head to the middle of her eyes. he looks like he just had his minimullet cut off. she was wearing a tiger print dress that looked straight out of the 80s and 4 inch black heels. she also looked like she was one that sunbathed a lot when younger, and by the way she was walking, seemed like she was strung out on something. he just looked sleezy. the picture doesn't do them justice. the guy was watching me because i think he knew what i was up too. and the one i took so you could see them head to toe didn't turn out. it was dark, so i tried lightening it, but meh. you still get to bask in the glory that is white trash getting completely drunk and yelling about racing nascars at the brookfield zoo's dinner with the seals!    today we're going to clean and remove a lot of the clutter and junk we've collected. and just reorganize a few things. i think i might see about gettin a new pair of jeans as well. some of my jeans fit, but i just don't want them that tight. i'm all about comfort! so, i might run to the mall and see whats on sale. ryan's cooking rosemary tritip sandwiches for dinner. should be tastey! mmmm.... i also found some piano sheet music from the movie  urlLink Amelie ! i'm really excited. not sure how it'll sound on my harp, but i'm going to give it a try. thank you , internet, for providing me with free music!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      man today was busy after work...and weird. i had a harp lesson today at 7:30 (she has a luncheon gig on saturday, so we had to move it up). so, instead of going all the way home just to turn around again, i head over to the parent's house.  they had ordered pizza so that was cool. timmy was upset about work, so that sucked. and that made mom and dad worry.  so, i went to my lesson, played a couple songs. i found out i'm about where someone new would be in 2 years...so that was encouraging. i mentioned how my cousin jenny wants me to play at her wedding next year in june, and she said if i want to do it, i'll be ready by then. so i guess that was good to hear. didn't expect to have that seriously happen, but all of a sudden they were talking to me at the babyshower about how they were talking to the church and everything. i don't think they understand that i JUST got this thing a couple months ago...and i'm seriously very new to it still. while i'm learning fast, it still makes me nervous...i guess i'll have to perform somewhere else before i do her's....maybe at some old folks home....or the hospital.... so i'm rocking out to some contemporary harp music, drinking a dr pepper, and chatting with my brother casey.  projects? -hair thing: almost done -sweater: still chuggin along -tank top: not much done -harp: still practicing -cleaning/reorganization: waiting until this weekend to lay the smackdown! (but tomorrow night will be laundry night unless something else comes up)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sorry i haven't posted in a couple days...they kinda flew by... i'm starting some new projects and finishing some old ones. i'm finishing the purple sweater i started knitting last fall. i only have the cuff on one side, full sleve on the other, and the neck. pretty easy. and i'll have officially finished my first full meghan sized sweater! wahoo! other projects i've started? knitting hankercheifs to wear in my hair...my hair is at the point where i want to cut it all off again, and i'm trying to keep that urge at bay...i just have too much hair...and when it gets to a certain point, it get's big! i've also decided to try knitting a tank top from my stich n' bitch book. i have TONS of scrap yarn from blankets and things, so i'm using some of that.  i also decided that we've gathered too much clutter in the apartment again,. so i told ryan we're cleaning house this weekend. i'm going to organize my aformentioned scrap yarn and all knitting accessories. ryan needs to organize records and such. we both need to clear out our dresser drawers of stuff we don't wear/doesn't fit anymore. that'll help get more storage space in the bedroom, and we shouldn't have a problem with that. i have a harp lesson today after work. kinda sucks because it swallows up my evening. i need to call lindsey and let her know about that...i was hoping to hang out with her tonight. and then i'm visiting grandma marita tomorrow. and thursday ryan has a band concert downtown wheaton...maybe she'd like to try to go to that with me....  well, time to go sit in traffic on my way to work! fun times!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so after staying up super late last night, and waking up early, running to 3 different stores this morning for decorations and papergoods, unknotting the balloons, and everything, the baby shower for casey and julie went off without a hitch.  we bought them: -Where the Wild Things Are -a few  urlLink Mr. Men  (the tiny books with people like Mr. Messy) -some Dr.Brown bottles that are supposed to be AMAZING for preventing gas with babies (according to some girls at work.) -an  urlLink Uglydoll  named Tray, Ryan picked him out because i couldn't decide. good choice! -i crocheted a blanket in pink, white and purple that turned out pretty snuggly. -i knitted a purple and white little baby sweater too  i think everything was a hit. looks like they scored some good loot. this is going to be one welldressed baby!  so many cute things! and lots of cool baby stuff...crib CD player, baby bouncer, some crazy high tech gate, everything! pretty crazy how different things are now, then they were even when i was babysitting a couple years ago! the baby was dancing all over the place afterwards. she seemed pretty happy. julies belly was a party! we dined on fried chicken, and mom made a TON of desserts. yummers. pretty cool all around. very chill. not to hoity-toity. just the way  i like it.  got to talk to my cousin jenny a while which was nice. she's taken up the art of crochet! i'm so proud!  well. i guess i'll go play harvest moon. yeah. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so i just got home from work. well. i got out of work, and went to the stadium across the street from our office with a few people afterwards. got my miller light i was craving earlier this week. it was a good time. full of toilet humor and the like.  came home. went for a walk. took a shower. and now i'm posting on my blog! you know what i love? SUSHI! i tried it for the first time in california. and i've found a few people in our office who like it. and there's a decent place right across from our office....and i have been going recently once every other week, at least! and you know what makes it even better? i haven't paid for it ONCE! every time we go, it always ends up that someone invites me and offers to treat, or that  one of the AE's go, and end up treating all of us. today was such the case. i had total intent of paying...because it was my idea. low and behold david decided to go with us...and bought 5 of us lunch...mmmm.... my favorite? unagi! or fresh water eel....    i could eat that shit all day...it's SO good... my favorite place we go is a sushi bar where you sit at this bar, the chefs are in the middle, and they have little boats...and the boats go around in a circle with plates of different pieces of sushi. and they are colored different ways, and they just keep a pile of your plates next to you. when you're done. they count the plates, and hand you a bill... i've decided that things taste better when they were once floating on a little boat... mmmm.... now i want sushi again..... mmmmmm
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well i'm home. i think i found a faster way home...which doesn't make sense but seems to work....basically i need to head south on 53 to get home from work. but the entrances by my office and the mall take around 20 minutes just to get on them and merge on...so, i found a frontage road and i headed north ( i know, crazy but bare with me...) went up one major road, got on there right away, and was cruising past my normal entrance and down the highway while the car that was pulling in there when i left, was still stuck on the ramp, and still had to merge in 3 lanes of traffic. it's AMAZING! it's like a secret weapon! only it doesn't hurt anyone.  bought some food at walmart....wheat bread, yogurt, tuna, milk....so i'll probably get me some grub.... OH and i got a new hoodie.  chloe sacrificed the last one to the not-clean-enough-for-her-litter-box-gods. grumble....i loved that hoodie too...she's such a picky cat....everything has to be buried...she'll even go in there after hana (who buries NOTHING) and bury it for her...hana's just lazy...i thought it was a territory thing, but hana has ALWAYS done that...sheer laziness....or stupidity...she wipes the rim of the box instead of the actual litter...but yea...if chloe goes in there, and hana goes right next to the  entrance of the box, all bets are off...she won't go in there. even when there are two clean litterboxes...we clean them once a day even! but not good enough....so, a few weeks ago, my hoodie had fallen on the kitchen floor....and she got it....enough about the litter talk. thanks chloe....thanks alot...  well, i've got some harp to practice, and i think i'm going to feed my cow and sheep some magic potion so we can have babies! man my life is CRAZY exciting right now! hahahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      man, i must have played harvest moon way too much, because i totally had dreams about playing the game last night...watering crops, getting upset because my cow didn't like me, everything...i was exhausted when i woke up this morning!  so, today was okay. i've decided to not let brokers talk to me like crap anymore. i don't need business from assholes! take that brokers!! neil was drunk by 3:30pm today. kinda nice because i got a break from his whining.  i've been craving beer in the evenings. especially if it's muggy. isn't that odd? i'm not a beer person...sometimes wine...but that's about it...but damn does a miller light sound tempting right now.  i'm home now, and boy have i got a busy schedule planned. -eat dinner -pick up a little bit -practice the harp -play lots of harvest moon until ryan comes home  so that's the plan!  uppers! +playing harvest moon +having lots of junkfood in my apartment +only working 3 days this week +going to the aquarium on friday +kitties!  downers :( -eating lots of junkfood in my apartment -having to pickup around here -driving home SUCKED -feeling kinda "meh" -suspicious people at work
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so today, i did the following: -cleaned the apartment -vacuumed -went to mom and dad's -me and mikey went out -sold my crappy gameboy back at gamespot -bought Harvest Moon for gameboy advance -bought an amazing wrist band by nintendo that says "High Score"   -convinced myself that now because of my super power band, i can punch people and they'll fall down and not hurt me! -went to fryes electronics -showed mikey around -saw timmy working -had a mocha -found a computer case that's shaped like a biplane with floresent lights. and found out they have one like a scorpion and an elephant -realized timmy had his own isle (nintendo) and a photo at the end of it to let everyone know who's the boss of that isle   -went to bestbuy -bought myself a new red gameboy advance sp, with the "executive kit" for free (thank you worksmart $100 bestbuy giftcards) -saw paul b. and invited him to the fireworks/festivities -got harrassed by the girl at the checkout over the product replacement. -i said no -she said "can you tell me why?" to which i replied "because my $100 giftcard doesn't pay for that, i do. and the plan doesn't work the way you think it does."  -had her bring it up AGAIN after i'd already played. -decided that's why fryes is going to put them out of business! -played harvest moon -bought a chicken on harvest moon -went to jewel and got drinks and chips -everybody cancled on the fireworks, so we decided to stay home and have friends over here -i went back to jewel to buy butter and chocolate chips to make cookies -posted on my blog now tonight? -kids coming over to play mario kart -i'm playing harvest moon
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      right now i'm kicking myself, for i have seen glory, and it lives in lisle!  we went out running errands, and when we came back we saw this kid walking in the parking lot of our building.  why was he so amazing? because he was wearing blue/grey/black/white camo cargo pants, with a collared button down blue plaid shirt tucked into it with a black belt! AMAZING! i wish i got my phone out in time to click a picture for all of you! still kicking myself...  got out of work at 4pm today. so that was nice. i came home and we went to fryes electronics grand opening. that place is MASSIVE!!! granite flooring, tons of suits welcome you into the building, they have tons of everything..you name it? they probably have it if it runs on batteries or if you plug it in. the game section was crazy. we saw timmy there all selling stuff to people. they had awesome bundles for xbox, ps2 and gamecube. i don't think i've ever seen people buying so much stuff spontaneously in my life!  ryan found a game he'd been looking for for a while and it was only $20, i got a fiona apple cd for $12. we looked to see if they had the $100 computer, but they were out...cause, hey! who DOESN'T need  a $100 computer!  then we went to fuddruckers for dinner. ryan ate a 1 pound burger in a few minutes, and half a large basket of fries. that's disgusting.  we went to walmart so we could pick up a few things. and now we're home. chillin. gonna check out the new game, listen to my cd,  crochet, practice like hell on my harp and basically relax.  i have a harp lesson tomorrow morning and i'm really nervous about it. i just didn't learn as much this past two weeks as i did last time. the last lesson i had 4 or 5 new songs to play for her. this time? i maybe have 1, and i kinda learned a duet accompniment, but not well enough to play it with her...hopefully she likes playing REALLY slow.  i'm kinda hoping to get a suggestion for another book with good harp music...because, i don't know that i like the ones i bought, and the main book we use all of a sudden gets INSANELY hard.  whoa is me! i think i'll see if ryan can record me this weekend...i can play greensleves/what child is this pretty well now.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      popcorn and a movie! i just got home from work. all of our field guys are in the office today, so they had a appetizer drink thing at prairie rock brewery by our office. i enjoyed chicken fingers, spinich artichoke dip, shrimp, meatballs, pineapple and two miller lite beers.  man, free food is good. i guess i'm glad i went. work has been SO stressful...and very akward. when i first got there i was extremely anxious...waiting for people to ask me questions that don't concern them. i was shaking....but, i eventually settled on a comfy couch and chatted with some new people. i treated myself to a  $.75 ice cream cone from mcdonalds on my way home. mmmm...soft serve.... and now i'm going to munch on some microwave kettle corn, sip on a diet coke, and watch some more lord of the rings dvds. man....strider is HOT!  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so i just got home! today at work sucked, so i'll skip over that and get to the good stuff! found out on my car that she did more damage then we origionally thought. i have to get new spare tire brackets, a new bumper cover, touch up paint, and entire new exhaust system, and a new floor pan in the back because she punched a hole in  mine. the sucky thing? we won't get our car back until monday or tuesday next week! but, fortunately  since this lady has taken full responsibility, i can get a rental car for free. so i might just do that. mom was saying they have to provide you with a "like vehicle". my fear? they'll give me a pickup truck or something! hahahhaa. i've never driven one of those...i guess if that happens, i'll be able to relate with my brokers a little more...  i went to Michelle after work to get my hair done....some quality hair therapy. me time! i love it! i wanted to go darker. and got a little trim. i absolutely ADORE my hair now!  it's a medium red base, with brighter red highlights, darker red lowlights (yes they have those), and some blonde spunks on top! she HAD to have had easily 30-40 foils on my head! i felt like i had earmuffs on because they COMPLETELY covered my head!  and seriously, because she rocks so hard, all of those foils, 4 colors, and a haircut only cost me $70!!!! i gave her a $15 tip because she's so cheap and amazing! if i got this done at my old place? easily $200+ because they charge per foil! if you want an amazing hair cut/color, ask me. i'll tell you where to go.  it's AWESOME!!! see new profile picture above, and although this picture doesn't do it justice, here's a closeup of the new hair.   man, i feel refreshed, stylish, and spunky once again!  i went to jewel, and restocked our food stores too! and i treated myself to some new edy's icecream flavored like smores! with the weather lately being so cool, i keep craving fall things. like smores, apple cider, apple donuts, back to school sales, new clothes, new school supplies, new classrooms, pumpkins, bonfires, and hot cocoa. i'm a total sucker for the fall. the smells. the colors.  the feelings. i love it all! fall also means a return of my favorite thing....christmas music! my harp teacher said she starts playing it in september in our lessons...i'm going to see if i can push it up a couple weeks this saturday at my lesson. oh! and i PROMISE my self that i'm going to get some sound clips of my new pieces recorded so you can all bask in the glory of my new harping skills! awesome! hooray for new hair! it's amazing how much better/cooler/awesome it makes me feel! rock!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, today wasn't as bad as i thought. people like to talk though.  oh well. tomorrow i get my hair done! it's going to be like a therapy session! i'm SO excited about it! i need a change! i think i'm going darker red/brown with bright red highlights on top....should be interesting. i'm sure she'll make it look super funky. just like all the other times...i'm a creature of habit in that sense. then, it's just a matter of keeping her from wanting to cut off too much hair, and keeping myself from letting it happen. it's at that stupid length. too long to be cute....too short to be long... i just finished watching lord of the rings again, so i'm craving Arwen length long wavey hair.... i'm about 3 years away from that.... man, hair takes too long to grow!  well, bedtime for bonzos. chloe calls!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm afraid to go to sleep.  afraid of waking up tomorrow and having to go back there.  afraid of having dreams where bad things happen to me.  there's only so many dreams you can have where people interrogate you at work. there's only so many dreams you can have where someone from work stabs you with a screwdriver.  i'm just very frightened of everything.  just afraid.   i don't want to go back...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, it's the weekend, and that means no work! thank bob! well, last night was pretty cool. me and ryan met casey and julie at BW3 by meijer and had some tastey buffalo wings! they were good, but VERY hot! i think if we go again, i'll get one hot and one regular bbq so i can rotate back and forth (like i do at famous dave's bbq with their wings). had a beer. filled them in on my crazy ass week. and played some trivia.  both ryan and i had a good time.  i came home and crashed on the couch. this week has been exhausting. and EXTREMELY stressful. i haven't been eating for the past few days. lost 6 or 7 pounds, but that's not good either. i got my appitite back a little last night. ate some fried mushrooms and some wings. but i guess my stomach is still anxious and everything because needless to say i woke up in the middle of the night and was pretty sick...damn that hot sauce is even worse later.   today? we might go to the zoo....but maybe not. basically i think we're going to try to relax....a challenging task to say the least. i'm going to try working on my hug today. i haven't touched it since i got back from cali. i might make a run to the craft store to see what kind of yarns they have there....i was supposed to start knitting hankercheifs for someone at work. she's placed an order for one black one. and one khaki one with black edging.   i just don't feel like doing anything.  maybe we should move. i keep toying with the idea. i can move anywhere in the company. houses near orlando are super cheap. we could get a 3 bed, 2 bath house with a screened in pool for like $175000. you can only get a 2 bedroom apartment style condo for that price around here.  i liked the thought of moving out by DC or anywhere on the east coast. i'd still have my winters, but i bet that area is just amazing looking and i'd still have snow at christmas. it's expensive too. i asked a friend who works out there to email me lists of towns that are near her office that aren't expensive. but she hasn't gotten back to me yet.   i wish they had our corporate offices near orlando. then i wouldn't have a second thought about it. california is WAY too expensive. but, then i'd get to do something cool that i like doing.  so confused. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'll i'm going to say is that MAJOR stress is back in my life again... and someone rearended my car on the way to work this morning.... fuck...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well i was back in the office today. it was okay. i did a good job. had to deal with the people who were talking shit about me being icy cold towards me and that was pretty irritating. but whatever, right? kill them with kindness! at least my life it's going to revolve around rumors in the office! rock! came home, talked to mom and dad, ate leftover chicken and velveeta shells and cheese (yum!). ryan was super glad to see me, which always makes you feel warm and fuzzy! we went to gamestop because they got doom 3 in a day early, so he traded some games back for it. ran into the borgione boys and talked for a little while with them and jason.  we're now back home. i'm posting, he's loading, and the kitties are chillin. i think i'll do one of the following: 1. watch pirates of the caribbean 2. watch one of the lord of the rings movies  3. watch ryan play doom 3 4. knit while watching one of the above 5. play the sims on my gba while watching one of the above decisions decisions!  SUCK! -dealing with idiots at work -dealing with ignorant idiots at work -dealing wih icy people at work -having to do laundry -basically, work fucking sucks! ROCK! +being home  +having cute toenails +snuggling kitties +being around ryan +having options +making lists
     
    
</post>


</Blog>