<Blog>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Get your hands off my hot dog that is something . . . . . . can't touch.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hiya. I'm back. Didn't expect me didya? Excellent. . . . . . . :p  Anywho, school is almost over and summer vacation is here for me in 1 more day! :D I can't wait! But the biggest reason I'm so excited about summer is that I will get loads more time to spend with my girlfriend! :D Stephanie ^_^   Maybe I'll go to driving school and learn to drive, and maybe even get my provisional license, and then maybe even get a better (higher paying) job too. But until then, I'm quite content with walking(and running) to see my Stephy ^^ and to go everywhere else.  Incase you haven't noticed. Stephanie is everything to me! :D I love her so much! She makes me feel like the happiest person in the world! Even if I could only see her smile it would brighten up my day! :D There's a piece of her I carry with me! :D it's everywhere I go, everything I see ^_____^ When I sleep, I dream of her and it gets me by :D I can make believe she's here with me ^^ (does it explain why I like to fall asleep alot? lol)  Sure we have our problems, but we work it out and solve them ^^ and I couldn't be happier! :D She's the world to me! My only one ^^ I couldn't picture life without her ^^  "Here I go, scream my lungs out trying to get to you You are my only one I let go, there's just no one, no one like you You are my only, my only one" --Only One-- Yellowcard  Songs like that remind me of her! :D They make me appreciate how fortunate I am to have her ^_^ how lucky I am to be with her :]  I love you Stephy!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I knight ye post: SIR UPDATE THE FIRST!  >Pick up ye flask.    Ye can't pick up ye flask. >Dam ye.    Dam ye too.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A blog! @,@ so simple yet so very, very effective.   I think I might like this. I was first introduced to this by my girlfriend! Who also happens to have a blog! :D (lol, whaddaya know? hehe, she actually made it first, so I'm giving her due credit)  I might update this blog sooner or later. I think it has a lot of potential.
     
    
</post>


<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... I was awakened by an awful stench. To my greatest horror, the giant branch that fell on me, was actually the cow itself. And the incredibly terrifying stench was its crap, on my face. This is turning out to be the worst day of my life, I should run home and clean up now but...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and then it happened a giant branch came down on me.  I was knocked out.  I then dreamed of a beautiful world where everyone was biped versions of animals.  It was totally amazing there were many people there some wonderous with wings while others were dragons.  In this great dream world there were other dream worlds and each one was just as unique as the last i couldn't believe the site.  This world was totally amazing and i wish i could never leave....................
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I nearly crapped my pants when all that happened. Not only was I beaten to within an inch of my life, but she threatened to castrate me too. I ran for my life, and my genitals.  I tried to run as fast as I could, as far as I could. But apparently I couldn't, seeing as how I ran into the tree, very fast, although not very far.  It happened to be that same tree that had the cow in it . . .
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...Until some odd woman came up and started beating the crap out of me.  I felt very amused and ashamed at the same time, laughing because she was rather short, but she was managing to hurt me.  "Ever mention those cows again and I'll castrate you!" She shrieked.   Geez, what does she have against cows?  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... there was a UFO in the sky. It swung around and curved, apparently searching for an open space to land, but it didn't find one, so instead, it exploded.  ::><> <> ::><> <> ::><> <>  It went up into a thousand pieces. The strangest part of it though, was that about 200 or so little calves scattered into the sky from the explosion. How they could possibly land safely with 4 little hooves is beyond me, but one slammed into a tree right next to me. I stared at it for a while . . . .
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       at the request of the moderator i am startng a story with a different aproach maybe ppl will actaully add to this one!!       I have always loved walking around at night.  It has become a rather interesting hobby of mine cause as i walk i see the most weird people.  Where else do you see a man in a cow costum being pulled on a leash by a lady dressed as a milker.  Anyway on one of my usual nighty walks soemthing happened........................
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (Yeah, whomever is the 100th visitor, please send me an email. Dunno what I'll do for you yet, but it'll be nice, eh?)  "Fodder, dear?" My wife asked, pointing to far corner of the room.  Unable to stop myself, I ran over on my little stubby cow legs, and started chewing.  "You'll start to enjoy being a cow. Just imagine how wonderful the children will be. You'll see." She said.  I have to admit, being a cow isn't so bad. Even being married to an alien cow hybrid isn't bad.   At least the kids are cute. Didn't I tell you about the kids? Well I can't mention all of them. There are over 200 of them. Let's just say the wife and I were rather busy.  So now, I must leave you all, and continue to enjoy my cow filled days aboard this star ship.  Didn't tell you about that one either? I must be slipping in my old age. I'm about 3000 years young. Of course, I'm immortal.  So, without me ending this, it would go on forever. I'm sorry, but I'm quite tired of looking at you people. Goodbye.  (And so ends Bob the Builder that went awry!  Hal will be along with another story shortly. After that, Katie gets a turn to start one. I have no idea what we'll do after  that , so stay tuned!)  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... and then it came to me! What are these weird alien squirrel people doing intruding on our mad cow love?  Apparently I was thinking out loud, they heard me and responded.  "We are the muscle behind your wife's great plan, and you happen to be on our ship."   "Oh ... crap" I said.  They gave me a hostile look and continued poker. I had a sudden craving for fodder....
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        It didn't take me long to figure out what exactly she meant.  You never made out to you made out like a cow i mean MOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO it was down right bodatious.  AFter the mad cow love we layed there.  I think she passed out because she began to snore didn't matter much i could have time to think.  I looked over to the alien squirrel looking critters they were all aplauding me and shaking their heads up and down.  One did a thumbs up which was weird.  Anyway as i lay there i started to think that being a cow might have advantages cause i mean i could always go to work at a chick-fi-lay. Still i had a very unsettled thought just now what did my darling wife mean but great plan.  Just when i think i am at ease something else always has to come up.  Besides didn't we just make out in front of like 10 alien squirrel people man what is going on...................   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Well of course we're going to have children, dear. Who else would carry on my, well our, legacy?" My wife replied to my thoughts.  " Can read your mind, by the way. Just thought you'd like to know from now on." She added.  I was starting to regret marrying a cow right about...now.   "You see, Bob, I'm the brains behind this whole operation. I'm like the queen bee of the hive." She grinned, although a cow's grin isn't rather comforting.  "Well at least you're important." I smiled, but inside my brain was screaming. I knew she could read my thoughts, so I tried to quiet them.  Like that worked.   "Enough of this banter. Open your child receptacle." My wife commanded.  I had no idea what she meant... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i decided to just go with the flow at first. hell, i was still in shock cause im not even human anymore.   i asked my lovely wife "what's next? what are you gonna do with me now?  she answered saying "well now we can head back home and start on my great plan"   by now she had freed me from the table and i was adjusting to having 4 legs. "great plan? and whats the great plan?"  she looked at me like i was nuts. "you didnt actually expect me to become a human and have human children did you? those things are so dirty"    only one thing registered in my head...CHILDREN?!?!?!?........
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .... verbally and genetically radioactive walnut eaters from Mars!!! @_@  I panicked! Struggling to be released from my imprisonment as the victim of large glowing utters, I nearly broke a hoof.  My wife explained to me that it was for the better of our relationship... but was this really true? Was my transformation really intended to strengthen our love? or perhaps was I in for a much bigger scheme devised by a greater power?  Why is it that I had to turn into a cow? Why is it that she didn't turn into a human? Could I trust her and live in peace and harmony with this alien race and live happily ever after? or would I have to go Duke Nukem Gone Bovine on these aliens?  . . .
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i couldn't beleive what had just happened.  One minute i see a purple light and my beautiful "MOOOOOOOO" wife and the next i am in a bed surounded by a very odd white like and now i am a "MOOOOOOOOOO" cow.  Well not a cow more like a bull i mean i am still a guy.  This is so weird.  "I see you have transformed quite nicely my love" it was my wife she was wearing a lab coat  "what have you done to me" i ordered an answer i wasn't happy about this i liked behing a byped  "What any loving half alien cow wife would do with her sadistic beastaility lover of a human i turned you into my kind"  "oh ok that works i thought you were just insane i mean looks at your company" i made a notion to the gaint squirrels in the other room.  they were eating walnuts and laughing about something.  "THey aren't squirrels my love they are........."
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up in a plain white room. Gleaming metallic instruments lay everywhere. I went to rub my eyes with my hands, but I soon found out that I no longer had hands.  Sharp hooves scraped across my face instead, making me scream in pain. However, my screams sounded nothing like the sort.  "MOOOO!"   The animal sound echoed in the small, sterile room.  *Did that sound come from me?!* I asked myself inwardly, afraid of the answer.  I glanced down at the rest of my body. Flabby, pale white stomach with dark black spots. Small stubby legs with hooves for "feet".   I think that was when I actually started to freak...  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And so... I wondered over toward the strange light coming from that strange group of trees and I could barely make out a very strange figure ...  It was my wife!  She immediately spotted me and charged my way! I soon found myself lieing on the ground, ignorant of what was about to happen!  Within a fraction of a second I was knocked unconscious by a large set of glowing utters . . . . . . . .
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      everything is starting to look rather barren. the grass is fewer and farther between. out there in the center there is a weird gathering of odd trees. there is no grass anywhere around it, heck, the ground looks like rock with cracks, not even soil. i look back to the trees and notice a weird purple light comming from inside of the gathering. as i move closer.......
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        i never asked my beloved wife why she takled to those green me or why they have given her the ray guns in the first place.  I always thought to myself that some things are better gone unchecked and all.  Besides that thing that bothered me the most was how could she shoot the guns when she doesn't have any hands.  I mean i love my wife dearly more than my last wife who oddly enough was a dear.  But she doesn't have any hands which makes some aspects of life hard but then again what is love without hardship and all.  Wow i must really be in deep thought cause as i look here i am actaully not on my farm anymore where am i must have wondered off somewhere................  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I once heard a story about cows and chickens. It was even made into a cartoon, but that has nothing to do with ray guns.  I once saw her mooing to short, little, green people with big eyes. They gave her the ray guns and then she shot them in the head.  I love it when she does stuff like that! :D . . .
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh the cows. How I love them so. With their creamy white skin and dark black spots, they must be the most beautiful animals in the world.  Of course I say this, because my wife is one. No, I'm not insulting her, she really is a cow. Udders and all. That's why I love my job. Always makes me think about my lovely wife.  Although I have no idea why she has such a large collection of ray guns...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        then it hit me.  I finally saw why everyone had loved this strange food.  WHy people enjoyed ingesting the flesh of such an odd creature.  The image came so simple to me.  The details of why people loved this strange food.  It is so clear it is like looking into a piece of glass.  BUt i don't have time to rant on i must finish my lunch and continue my job milking the COWS or my boss will ring my neck.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (The first story was finished so I started another one at the request of another)  Once, long ago, I, Bob, the Builder, period and comma user extraordanaire, ate chicken.  It was a rare occasion and I was looking forward to it. I've been led to believe that chicken is more nutritious than most meats, and tastes better too. Now this seems to good to be true, so I had to pack a lunch with chicken sooner or later.  And so the day came, where I sat down and had my lunch. There it was, the beloved chicken, but why do so many seem to love this strange food? ...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Something in my mind stapped i just couldn't stand that smell anymore.  Earlier that morning i had just finished off the three bean chilli we had last night for dinner and i was feeling it now.  I just let it all out unfortunatly it was silent but totally deadly.  Teressa started to look around the room.  Before she could say anything i took action.   I yelled out loud "hey guys smell that looks like teresa's ass just exploded in her skirt".    The Entire class start to laugh and even the teacher couldn't hold it back.  Teressa let out a loud cry and stormed out of the room crying.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (I've decided to start a random story. I'll start writing, and leave off at a certain point. Someone else will pick up the story from there.)  Teresa was the most popular girl in school. All the boys loved her, and the girls loved to hate her. She was like a living Barbie doll, her blonde hair immaculate, her eyelids smothered in blue eye shadow.   I remember shaving the hair off of those disgusting dolls, and then decapitating them. Right now, it didn't seem like a bad idea.  She seemed to haunt me no matter what class I was in. Always there, with the stench of expensive perfume and her voice full of money.   That is, until something happened.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      See title. (^_~)  That's a science term by the way. It just sounds kool. My biology teacher taught me it. Anywho, Steph invited me to add posts! :D so I shall ^_^ I love Steph!! wooooo!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude I joined!!!! Woo hoo!!!!!!!!! *happy dance disco*
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm planning on writing whatever comes to mind in here. However, that doesn't mean my daily life. It will be alot of random things, like song lyrics, poems, and unfinished stories or rants on a random subject.  I'm planning to invite other people to join this, so there is a variety of opinion and content.  That's all for now, I may write an actual post tonight, but probably not.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ....  "hey! hey! wake up!"  ....  "HEY! wake up! ... Dumb drunks these days ... well at least he's not out driving."  .... I wake up and see the bartender yelling at me.  "You idiot! Finish your job and get the heck outta here!"  Apparently I had passed out and didn't finish cleaning the place up. Yup, this is where I work. It's all that I've got. It's all that I've come to remember, nothing else gives me hope...  Hope for something... someone... not anyone... just her. It's where we first met, maybe we'll meet again?  Bah, what am I saying... this alcohol must be getting to me... I should finish cleaning up ... 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i stared into my mirror watching my past slowly become smaller.&nbsp; i knew i could never return to my town not after what i had done.&nbsp; i must now drive forward not looking back.&nbsp; THe past is just that the past i needed to make a future now.&nbsp;   i must have been driving for hours soon i even forgot what road i was on.&nbsp; It was getting really late and i needed somewhere to stay.&nbsp; I thought to just park my car off the road a little and rest there but i saw what looked like a motel aproach on my righthand side.&nbsp;   It was a rather small motel in comparasin to the ones back home but it should suffice.&nbsp; The large neon sign read "Darkside Inn" under that was a vacacy sign.&nbsp; I noticed serveral cars park and some of the rooms had lights on.&nbsp; It was late at night and i needed a place to stay, looks like this will have to do.&nbsp;   After checking in i took a look around the office a small tv on top of a ragidy stand was placed in the corner and the room smelled of blood oddly.&nbsp; Walking out the place had a very ominus feel to it.&nbsp; Before i enter my room i took notice of a small tavern like bar at the far end of the building.........   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       He always used to say that. Oh, how I loathed that phrase. So optimistic all the time.    &nbsp;  I wonder what happened to him...    &nbsp;  Well, it's none of my business. Neither was his drinking problem. I don't know why I drove him away with my nagging. He was all that I had.    &nbsp;  Now I'm stuck in this run down motel, trying not to get felt up by the regulars at the "juice" bar.     &nbsp;  I wonder what he would do now..    &nbsp;  Maybe he'd be mad at me for giving up. Or maybe, he's still wishing I would come back.    &nbsp;  Boy, you sure are romanctic when you're tired. He doesn't want you, Cheryl. You know that.    &nbsp;  Half of Manhattan knows that. Especially after that night...  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I'll be...fine...   I repeat that to myself on a daily basis. I've got nothing else on my mind, and no worries on my chest. It's a nice, honest sentence, I've grown to like it.  It's getting late into the day. I don't feel like I've accomplished anything. But I seem to be&nbsp;getting by, paying my dues. Making my way with just&nbsp;enough money to drink at this bar. My&nbsp;life isn't too colorful... but that's ok, because&nbsp;whiskey makes up for it... right?  A remember her voice... she always told me to be strong... but I'm doing alright... aren't I?  I'm... getting by... just me... and my whiskey... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Make sure there is a sharp crease in the sheet when folding.    Polish till it shines. Shines so much you can see yourself in it.    Greet every guest warmly, regardless of their behavior, or their manners.     &nbsp;   That's what she said, right before she packed up and left.     &nbsp;   For the life of me, I cannot remember what brought me to this place. In fact, I can't remember anything before I got here.     &nbsp;   There's a man at the bar that thinks this place does things to people. Who would believe someone who seems to have no life besides heckling the work force here. Not me, that's for sure.     &nbsp;   I've got a good head on my shoulders. I bet my inability to remember things is due to using too many cleaning products in an unventilated room. It'll come back soon.     &nbsp;   He sure babbles alot. Talks even more when he's really drunk. No one knows where he came from, or where he's been.     &nbsp;   Some say he came with the place. They love trying to trick the naive and the gullible. I just smile and keep working.     &nbsp;   I'm no ones friend here. I got a job to do. As long as I get by, I'll be fine.     &nbsp;   Yeah, I'll be...fine...      
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok, this was an experiment. Meaning, I sat back and watched what happened, not really controlling anything. Now, I have decided to lay down some ground rules for the survival of this blog...thing. Cause right now it's looking pretty dead.    &nbsp;  And why should the other members listen to me? Well, I made it, and I said so. So nyah.    RULES FOR WRITERS  1.) No more random cow insertions. I'm serious.  2.) No more huge fart scenes either. It just ruins things. 3.) Try not to repeat the same thing over and over again. It makes things more enjoyable. 4.) Try to have some sort of a compelling story. Please? 5.) Stories should really not run on for thousands of posts  unless  they are really good. And I mean  really  good.   RULES FOR READERS ( LOL J/K)  Ok, hopefully this should prevent&nbsp;long periods of time without new writing.   Whatever story was going on before this message is now terminated. I should have a new one up soon.  Hopefully no one is too miffed. ^_^()  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It inspired me! It made me want to make an army myself and yell at weird people. And so I did.  I gathered an army of green, striped rabbits, with two butts, and called it "The Army of Green Striped Rabbits With Two Butts".  With my army at my side, we went over to the cow that crapped on me.... and CHARGED!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      but then as i was walking home an army of midgets wielding T-shirt cannons poped in out of nowwhere.  Their leader ordered them to hold their march.  He spoke to me in a deep and dark tone for a midget.  "DEAR GOD what is that smell son, smells like you spent 24 hours in a horses ass or something!!"  he was close actaully it was more like 5 minutes and a cows ass i explained that to him.  He then told me to carry on and his army continued their march into the night...............
     

    
</post>


</Blog>