<Blog>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dont be too harsh on me I may seem strong but I am as frail as a vine in a storm I may say I'm OK but I'm about to break into pieces  Don't believe me when I say I'm happy And you can see my smile is a lie And my eyes are betraying me  Don't leave me When I say I can handle it, I can do it by myself That only means I'll try, that I can but I don't really want to  Don't be fooled by my seemingly quiet confidence when inside I'm a child, confused and terrified
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Polka dots appearing on these pages.  I don’t remember the last time I cried like this.  It’s  so hard to say goodbye to something so beautiful.  How can something so brief, so distant be so painfully sad.  I only have tomorrow’s time to relish  and I wish tomorrow would last forever. Because after tomorrow, things will not be the same.  Why does it hurt so bad?  Where did all this pain come from,  how did it get here? Pain finding its way through my eyes.  It’s like dying a bit. There’s this weird connection that we have that feels so damn right, so damn perfect and so utterly rare. .  To hopeless romantics like us, all things happen for a reason. You almost wonder if it was a cosmic trick of fate that brought us together.  If the end is staring us at our faces right now. I just don’t get the point fate is making.  If moving on means moving away from you then I don’t know if I want to move on at all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing fancy.  The irony of it is that I had to go to a country with almost the same culture and environment to make me aware of the state of the Philippines as it is right now.  Jakarta, Indonesia – I have been here since Sunday April 17 for an SAP training.  What immediately struck me coming out of the plane was that their airport was very similar to ours.  The bare tiled uncarpeted cement, the tropical decorations pathetically attempting to  disguise the deterioration and shabbiness of the place.  The long confusing lines at the immigration.  The lack of modern facilities and persistency of the 70’s (or is it 80’s) outdated  look of the counters.  What was different – on the road on the way to the hotel, trees everywhere serving as diaphanous covers to the poor housing conditions at the road side. Still it was prettier than looking at the rusty roofs of the squatters areas that  you will find on the way to NAIA.  NAIA has nothing but honesty (I scoff at that!!).  So what else is the same?  Aside from the absence of jeepneys,  visibility of mosques and Islamic worship houses, the long lunch breaks on Friday for prayers – everything else is.  The traffic, the pollution, even the colonial mentality. The drivers will stalk you to pay more than what’s in the meter, they’ll refuse to let you ride if they don’t like you.  Rain results to flooding and yes, heavy traffic.  And I mean everywhere.  Oh yes, let’s go to colonial mentality – that’s always a fun topic.  Indonesia was colonized by the Dutch for 350 years and for a very short period by the Japanese.  The Dutch tried to regain supremacy but eventually Indonesia got its freedom in 1949.  Really makes you see a lot of parallelisms between PH and ID.  But unlike the Spaniards though, the Dutch barely left any legacy it seems.  The religion stays predominantly Islam and the language essentially Bahasa with probably a few hints of bastardized Dutch.  But the people have been left with the scar of colonial mentality – and probably value the same things as the Filipinos. The color of the skin, the locals being second class citizens in their own country . Foreigners particularly Caucasians are favored.  And I understand very well, after all I am a Filipino.   The buildings in Jakarta are all modern ones – made of steel and concrete. It is in sharp contrast to what I saw a week ago in Warsaw.  The Poles rebuilt their city after the war and until now are trying to preserve the old architecture.  Their patriotism is unwavering and their sense of nationalistic pride is noble and admirable.  I wish I could say the same for Indonesia. For me, it was a good experience  in a way– providing me with an objective , third party view of what is probably my country  with a different name and a slightly different environment. What a foreigner may feel when visiting the Philippines for the first time.  Made me feel the flickering flame of patriotism that I didn’t know was still in me.  It made me aware of my identity and the sad fact that most of us Filipinos are trying so hard to be foreigners in our own land.  That instead of striving for a unique identity and making that thrive, we are contented and happier with embracing the culture of other people and calling it as our own.  That is our pathetic claim to raise our status.  BUT that claim and all our effort will always be in vain.  Because no matter how hard we try, all we’ll ever amount to are  copy cats without our own identity.    I am a Filipino.  But what is, who is the Filipino? I can’t think of anything to describe us that is unborrowed, that is truthfully ours without foreign tarnish.  I don’t know who I am. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am looking for a person who can see beyond my lips to picture a smile, who can read beyond my words to see poetry, who can look beyond my eyes to see my soul.  Excerpt from a journal of mine long forgotten. Just thought I'd post it here.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Time wrapped  In the vastness of the skies Phosphoresence slowly flooding  the arid nothingness  Eyes closed Feet cold, thoughts asailing a kaleidoscope of mirages unfolding slowly  Libra,  Casiopeia,Orion,  Stars amiss on the canvass of pitch black  Thirty nights of looking up in the sky A cycle, a life Unseen renewal   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was my first time. To take a bath. ..(wait, im not done yet).. in public(i see some eyebrows raised)!  I spent a night in a depressed area. My friend's "house" had no bathroom.  I never imagined a simple thing such as peeing could give rise to so much complexity.  How to take a bath in public? Put on a big shirt, a jersey preferably, and tabo your way to cleanliness.   I couldn't sleep.  Something was moving in the dark, making noises.  I opened my eyes and saw a rat, almost the size of your average cat.  I screamed and almost cried.  It was one night in my life. My friend has lived like that for 5 years now, so i've learned. Things like this keep me grounded.  We always remember the first time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im riding an ordinary bus . Here airconditioning is unheard of. The air is dingy. Second hand smoke fills my lungs and german roaches roam freely. I am riding an ordinary bus, they say it's ordinary because it's hot and humid. The moisture mainly comes from the sweat on the other passengers foreheads. It's always a humbling experience. It's always a moment. The wind blows on your face and you cant wait until you get to your destination. Everystop seems to be taking forever. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>