<Blog>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday was a day of poker, bar-b-q-ing, and blackjack playing at Vince's house, while his fiance is in Hong Kong.  We had lots of food, friends, and fun, as 12 hours just seemed to flash by.  While playing Texas Hold'em, she walks in with her best friend, who happens to be my best friend's younger sister.  No eye contact, no glance over here, but we both know and feel each other's presence.  Ignoring each other has been our method (although, not a very amicable one) for the last 4 years.  I tried to call her once a few weeks prior to Ray's wedding, in my attempt to smooth things out so that there would be no awkwardness.  As I call her, she was on her way, with boyfriend in hand, up to Yosemite to go camping and would call me back.  Obviously, I never received a call back, as I never expected one.  It's so odd now, whenever we have group events with my friends, we know the drill.  I put all of the blame on myself, as I honestly can say, I SUCK at ending relationships and treat people so poorly.  But Karma has it's way of making things balance out.  At the same time, I'm learning and trying my best to right my wrongs, and not make the same mistakes.  I've had this burning urge to wave at her and greet her, but I can't seem to do it.  I'm sure if I bumped into her on the street, I'd say hello, but something about doing it in front of all my friends causes me to hesitate, which in my opinion, is so showing of my character, and I HATE that about myself.  It shouldn't be this hard!!!   

						
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Woke up at 8PM today after a 4hr nap when I got home at 4.  Just closed my eyes for a few seconds and bam, gone for the next four hours.  Now I'm wide awake and looking to workout or read.    What am I going to do tomorrow?  I wonder how I'm going to be when I'm retired and don't have work.  We all work hard so that we don't have to in the future, and now I can't think of what to do on my day off - probably just going to waste the day away and wait for Ray to get off work, and play poker at someone's house.  That seems to be my Friday night drill now.  It's either that or go to the clubs with Patrick and Tony.  But the latter doesn't seem like a viable option anymore.  Whenever I'm at the club, I think of all the money to be made, and just lounge around, never really thinking about having fun.  Maybe I need a Friday night book club or some sort of competitive league sport.  Realization that I'm bored, and boring...  I've got to be the Nap'n Lounge King.  That should be my new screenname.   

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A new beginning (my first post)...  So I just finished showering after a 9:30 squat workout, and I can't seem to fall asleep.  I'm usually in bed by 9:30 the latest, but I've had so much on my mind.  I can't seem to stop thinking about Emily, who I don't even know that well and is 3000 miles away.  Yet, it's that infatuation or what I perceive her to be that's making me think so much.  I've tried to distract myself, but I can't seem to get her out of my mind.  It's pretty hard when I think about her most of all at work when I get an email, hoping that it's her.  I keep looking at the pic we took on my camera phone.  What a great personality I saw that night, even though I had just hurled with a measly 5 Heinee's (what a lightweight I am).  In other news, I finally spoke with Jessica today after almost a month of not talking to her.  She came to meet her online friend from the UK, and now she says they're an item.  Seems to work for her in meeting people; I mean - that's how we met and we get along so well.    Why are we never satisfied with ourselves?  Men, today, have the same pressures of looking perfect as women do (i.e. comparing ourselves to the ripped guy in magazines).  That's why everyone is on a diet and watching their carb intake.  I am.     

						
</post>


</Blog>