<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got to the guest house - where I am staying - it was a long day at work and I was looking forward to a night of rest...  that, not counting on the fact that my Swedish friend - who also lives at the guest house - was waiting for me, all dressed up in her Swedish colors ready to go out to watch the Sweden - Denmark Euro 2004 soccer game... Big game for Sweden as they would qualify to the Quarter finals if they draw or win.  I stated that I will stay home and watch it here... but she said I should join her as they are going to the American Colony (A hotel/bar in Jerusalem) to watch the game - big group she said... and that her good friend Vanunu will be there! Vanunu is the renowned Israeli nuclear scientist that was in prison in Israel for 18 years 10 in total solitude confinement!   Naturally I changed my mind and I decided to go - looking forward to meeting the man... and shaking his hand.  In the American colony the Atmosphere was jolly, Danish in Red, Swedish in Yellow and blue... both cheering loudly for their team... all drinking heavily ($6 Us dollars for a tap beer!) their is so much money in this town.  Any the game ended 2-2 which meant both Denmark and Sweden made it to the quarter finals on the account of Italy missing out. So both the Danish & Swedish gangs were happy... I was too....but I was slightly disappointed for missing out on meeting Vanunu... he didn't show up... too much noise I guess - can't blame the man... the closest I got was meeting his brother. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today on my way to Ramallah I was reading a beautiful poem from Rubaiyat that goes like this:  Awake! For morning in the bowl of night Has flung the stone that puts the stars to flight: And lo! The hunter of the East has caught The Sultan’s Turret in a Noose of Light  As I was reading this to my friend while she’s driving us through a check point … I left my head up and saw Soldiers and the wall… so far from what I was reading that I decided to write a lil poem:  'Once upon a wall'  Once there was a wall Once I danced in the rain Once I loved              … under a full moon Call me crazy – if you want              … a ‘majnoon’ Who dances when love is not              …When walls are put Who dances when passion is not              … When soldiers rule Call me romantic – if you wish              … call me a fool Once I danced              … to gypsy music              … to waves… and a river              … to love… passion              … once I danced forever Today another wall is built              … made of blood              … mesh              … and cement Once we will dance              … with no wall              … hate              … just a the moon              … and a jasmine’s scent  Now I am in the office contemplating... why... am i here... we are here...?  I sip my turkish coffee ... and write one more line on this blog... life goes on.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Sunday i went to Taybeh... taybeh is a small village 20 minutes from Ramallah and Jerusalem... situated high on the mountains so you can see Jerico and Jerusalem in the distant... very beautiful village... and unique in being inhibited only by christians... and have the only beer brewery in Palestine... Taybeh beer... go to any Israelui bar and you can buy it.  So my family comes from there... and we still have a house that my father grew up in as a child before immigrating to Sweden... currently one of my uncles lives there - my only relative living in Taybeh...  So i arrived their for lunch... but before lunch i went to the church which happens to be next door to our house in Taybeh... it is said that my grandfather was there every sigle sunday... his entire life! His seat left unused till today...  After a huge huge lunch... i felt that the heat, the food and the breez... and my uncle's boring stories... required me to retire for a siesta and some reading... so i asked my uncle if he had any books i can read... he said he doesn't read much but pointed me to an attich with a book shelve... and to my delight and total surprise i find... lots of old yellowish books from the 30s and 40s... some in elglisg ... some in arabic... i even found a magazine from the 40s with coloured ads in arabic! but what attracted my attention was a poetry book half torn... with the first page a poem for Gibran Khalil... so i picked up and went to the guest room...  Are you ready for this? well, i found among it's pages... writings.. not just any writings.... but my dad's ... in fact his signature... in many styles... looks like it was my dad's whn he was 10- 12 years old... wanting to create a signature... there was also comments on the poetry... wow... how amazing is it when a book finds you...  So all the way to Jerusalem i was holding tight to my bag... worried about my torn yellowish poetry book... espicially going throu check points... if i had common sense i would have known that soldures are not really interested in books... not while they on duty anyways. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No time to write much... on my way to inspect a flat in Ramallah... Furnished... and on a roof... so should be good for parties :)  Last night i spent it drinking Carlsberg and watching the Euro2004 Sweden vs Italy game. In the guest house we have to swedish girls... they provided the beer and the entertainment... I mean them screeming every time sweden gets the balls... "Stollllla"... that was their fav player... fun night... still feel the effects..  Today i worked in Ramallah on the Children's application form for Hakawati... a 13 Y.O girl called Sodos... took over the computer and reformatted the whole thing for me... wow she was so good with Word and Photoshop... so sharp in Arabic & English even though she never left Ramallah... !!!!  Very impressed... and amazed... how grown up these kids are... and so up-to-date with what's happening outside the walls of their city... and the walls are getting higher... 8 meters high... ok i finish on that note.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I went to Jenin the other day... but i have been soooo busy to write about it... so here it goes:  I have to describe the trip to Jenin... in fact i have to say that road trip has been the strangest and most informative of my stay here (more than a week so far)  So I get to the UNDP office in Jerusalem... I am to be driven to Jenin in a UN car which is the only way i could get there as Jenin is restricted area and the check point there is one of the worst in the west bank - Al Hamrah check point.  First thing i find out that there are a group of UN Vets that will share the ride with me to Jenin as it is hard to send cars there so they try to car pool- We are to go to Ramallah to pick them up (they would never be allowed to leave Ramallah otherwise)... so me and Said (the driver Palestinian Expat from the US) take the road to Ramallah... on the way and as we pass some Israeli settelments - to my surprise - Said proclaims how beautiful these settelments are! and how he thinks that Palestine is history and we should move forward! Mental note... why ius he saying that?!  So we get to Ramallah after two check points in which Said tells the soldures in an exasurated NY accent that we are diplomates... which we are as we are carrying UN IDs... but the way he says it makes me laugh...    Now the 4 Vets, all very polite 50 something Palestinian Experts, get in the car... they are on their way to Jenin to inspect the sheep in the surrounding villages...  Listen to this conversation:  Dr Samir: Laugh man... nothing else to have but laughter (he laughs loudly) Dr Ajar: Don't want... get fuck... jockenly Dr Majid: Shou (what) Samir did you have sex last night Dr Samir: No.... she had the red flags up (as in that time of the month)... then he tells a joke about Yasser Araft and red Flags...   [All Laugh - me included]  [Silience for few minutes]  Dr Majid (the elder) every now and then points out to a beduin tent and tells us the name of that clan... he knew it all... every sigle clan we passed... and every sigle village... histroy and all... for the two hours to get to Jenin .. ilearned so much about the beduins of Palestine...  [Silience, laughter... jokes]  Dr Samir [points to a house in the distant on top of a hill]: this is were we domonstrated against the settelment post... Dr Omar [ Laughing]: Yes we did until they arested Ghaleb [their leader]... Dr Ajar: did the Israeli's hit you Dr Samir: I was lucky on got hit once on the leg Dr Majid: I copped it three time... my arm still hurts [six months after]  [Silience for two minutes]  Dr Samir: anyways... what happened? Dr Ajar: well, the settlers won... they got it  [Silience for two minutes]  Dr Samir: ahhh what do we expect.. yallah... Dr Omar: Did you bring the Vaccine? Dr Samir: No, we'll have to come to Jenin next week again... its still in the freezer in Jerusalem...  [Silience, laughter... jokes, Dr Majid pointing places...]   So we get to Hamra Check point... the Israeli greeting was ... so rude pointing the guns at us as they talked to us... totally abusive.. and rude... Even Said was angry - I wanted to ask him then if he still likes the settlements.  Once you get to Jenin area, the poeple are so nice... the mountains are so geen... the air so fresh...  Hard to see how life changes every meter you travel in this land... from hate to love... from west to east... from mean occupier to spirited kind people...  and again maybe i am baised... go ask Said.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I havn't written for days...  I have been a bit disheartened... every day i pass the Qalindia check point... they have built another huge section of the wall... there is abuslutley no excuse of why you would build a wall separating Palestinian houses  from thier land.... in east jerusalem the Street is been totally dug out and house on each side of the street will be separated by an 8 meters high cement wall, even one woman on the bus today was looking out from the windows at the scene of destruction... and she said to her friend - casually - this is where my grandba lives .. on the other side his son... now they have to travel the 5 Km of to the next check point so they can see each other.... yesterday they were across the street from each other... so how can we allow this... how can the world allow for walls to be built! in the year 2004... in the name of secuirty... whos secuirty... and on whom land is it being built... and whose lively hood is being destroyed?    I have no more to say today.... except that i ran out of my Australia wine... and i am conteblating buy Israeli wine!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I am here in Palestine working on  urlLink 'Hakawati'  and I need to sell the idea to the head of UNDP (I mean the big guy... the one that talks to New York) ... so I am taken to this huge office... so much formality you think you are meeting a Sultan...  As i entered i noticed that the office was beautifully furnished and the man was beautifully modest... he sat there listened and then said "i like your project... make sure you don't make any compromises... any thing you need just come to me... even more money"... wow even more money great :) ... oh and the furniture in his room it is original Syrian and Palestinian from 150 years old restored sofas and chairs.... how cool.  Anyway i liked the guy... and he liked me... which helps.. good start huh...  Well, I am a bit hung over from last night ... I went to this cool bar in easter Jerusalem (called borderline... interesting name) ... very cool bar... only the music was 80s and took me back to my teenage years... well as i said i am a bit hung over so going to have a siesta... tonight i am invited to dinner - one of the girls here at the UN... shrimp Palestinian style... I will take my Australian wine and it will make of a interesting mix :)  Two thing before I go:  #1 Yesterday i went to ramallah to look for an apartment... the apartment we saw were too fancy for me... Gym, Spa, daily cleaning/lenin... and a view... not to mention a resturant and cafe in the apartment... I was driven there buy a canadian girl that wanted to share with me... well, me no like.. (the apartment i mean)  ... on the way back we saw the new wall around rammallah :( really sad... I took some photos and will post here once i figure out how to do that...   #2 I promised to tell you about the Guest house...well, i now live in Jerusalem in a guest house inside the Agusta Victoria hospital... the guest house has an amazing view of the old city... and the guests are so pleasant... mainly expates from around the world... coming to help the Palestinians and working for NGOs ... so it is a fun enviroment... and very comunal... which i like... I wish there was something like it in Ramallah... next week i will have to move to rammalla... hope i find an apartment there... NOTE: Ramallah is only 20 minutes from Jerusalem... but with the check points and the wall the trip back and forth will take 3 hours!... so me have to live in Ramallah...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that I got to a computer... and managed to register for this blogging thingy... I can tell you that my flight was a nightmare... BIG mistake to fly EL Al (the Israeli airline) ... now here I am a Palestinian born in Libya, with an Australian passport full of stamps from all around the world including Lebanon!   I felt sorry for the Israeli girl on the security desk at Bangkok  airport... yes they have their own security team there! Well, she looked amazed/confused, and called her supervisor and they both talked for ages then he decided to get my bag of the plan and do a thorough check and yes they also checked every bit of  my body... three funny things to mention:   1- I had just bought wine from duty free while leaving Sydney airport... and her supervisor insisted that they had to open the wine bottles for security reasons (X-ray is not enough in this case - the wine could be a security risk), naturally I offered them some wine tasting   2- The security girl was not happy with her boss wanting to open the wine... and she actually had an argument about it with him ON MY BEHALF! Well, she did have nice eyes...   3- When I got to Jerusalem I found out that they had taken my shampoo... must have been another security risk!   Ok... I am getting tired... jet lagged and in need of some Australian wine  to sample... and so I am leaving the my office in the UNDP headquarters in Jerusalem and going to the guest house where I am staying which is on top of mount of olives - actually as part of the Augusta Victoria Hospital - but that is another story, next post.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I met um Ahmed, I don’t feel like saying much, just what she told me:  &nbsp;  [She was smiling, and referring to me as her son while she was saying the following]  “I was a freedom fighter 40 years ago. when I was 20, I was put in Jail, my sun had been on 7 months, when I got out of jail he was 17, at the age of 18, he too, became a freedom fighter. How cloud he not [she giggles], I only new him for 1 year for he was shot soon after, until today the Israeli’s have not returned his body to me”  &nbsp;  -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; where is his body I asked?  -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; At the cemetery of numbers  -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The cemetery of numbers?  -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Yes, that’s were they keep bodies of some of the Palestinian killed fighting them, near Jericho, they give them a headstone with a secret number only so the families don’t know where they are and not to grieve  -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Um Ahmed, you suffered a lot…  -&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Others did too my son… what can I say [she smiles or more like have smiles, and puts her hand on hair waste, and leaves me]  &nbsp;  I have never heard of this cemetery, so I ask some people about, I am told hundreds of Palestinians are kept there, some for as long as twenty years, only a number, their family not allowed the basic right to grieve for them.&nbsp; &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I travel between Ramallah and Jerusalem regularly as I am staying in Jerusalem, the UNDP office is in Jerusalem as well, but most of my meetings happens to be in Ramallah.  Today was another day at the office, I took the bus from Jerusalem to the check point, crossed the check point and another bus from the other side of the check point to center of Ramallah, a trip that would last 20 minutes with no check points and lasts about an hour and a half now… a trip many Palestinians take on daily bases.  Today, was slightly deferent… on my way home I took the bus to the check point to notice the that it was unusually busy. Later I noticed that in fact it was closed and all these people were just waiting on the hope of the Israeli’s opening it.  I bushed my way to near were the soldiers were to get a better look at what’s happening, I asked one of the soldiers what was happening, I was told the check point is closed for today! “why?” I asked, “orders, we can’t tell you”, the cordial reply.   -Butttt… I live in Jerusalem what am I to do?  -I don’t know, find friend… find hotel -I am Australia, look my passport -Sorry, orders, no one can leave -But I was only here from the morning, why didn’t you tell me you are going to close the check point, my house is on the other side -Sorry -Just tell me why? -We have orders to close check point  It was 6pm, by 9pm the check point was still closed, I saw so many sad situation, families wanting to go back home, an old lady begging that her house is just meters on the other side of the check point, a 9 years old boy crying that he wants to go home and he has no one he knows in Ramallah to stay the night, I even saw a man faint after waiting for four hours to cross the check point to go to hospital for his daily kidney dialysis.  The soldiers were strict no one pass, one of them felt sorry for every body, and kept saying he was sorry, the others didn’t care, but one guy seemed to be enjoying it, laughing, even pointing his gun at angry, tired Palestinians waiting to pass.  That night I really felt the brunt of a brutal occupation, an occupation that has it it’s core a mission to humiliate Palestinians and create a culture of hatred, cultural cleansing and a systematic plan to create ghettos of cheap labor Palestinians living solely for the benefit of a modern Israeli supreme Jewish state. Sounds familiar? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>