<Blog>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha. Just kidding. I'm not really THAT depressed. Anyway, why would I improve society? So, as you know, today was graduation. And Khaki stood up and gave a speech and all that jazz. Later, I talked to him and had a one-sided conversation. You know, the ones that go like this: Me: I picked up your violin. What would you do without me? Khaki: Thanks. Me: Have fun "certain-college"ing. Khaki: Yup. I won't be leaving for a couple of weeks, though. xx/xx is moving day. Me: Oh, is it just you or is your whole family going? Khaki: Just me. Me: Alright, well, enjoy summer! Khaki: Sure, you, too. I can almost feel the fires of Mordor nipping at me. The flames mock me and my Khaki-less-ness! "Khaki is leaving on xx/xx!!! And he's never coming back! Muah-hahhahaha!"... crappy cheap cinematic flames... I'll get you   :P . By the way, I probably just gave away Khaki's identity.. However, he is leaving so what the hey. I've got Matchbox 20 to take care of me. *sniff sniff*  I got a disease Deep inside me Makes me feel uneasy baby I can't live without you Tell me what I am supposed to do about it Keep your distance from it Don't pay no attention to me I got a disease Tell me what I am supposed to do about it Keep your distance from it Don't pay no attention to me I got a disease  I think that I'm sick But leave me be while my world is coming down on me You taste like honey, honey Tell me can I be your honey Be, be strong Keep telling myself it that won't take long till I'm free of my disease Yeah well free of my disease Free of my disease...  Argh.   Can't wait for Monday's movie. Later days~ 
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Graduation
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's still summer, apparently. The sun's usually out, the little children flock to my house to play with my little bro's gamecube, they're knock on my door to try and get me to wake up so I can then kill them one by one. Parents: don't send your kids over to my house. They might not come back in one piece. I've set up my little Jayne-fort in the computer room, in a desperate attempt to get away from them. And of course, the computer chooses now of all times to be retarded. I should be able to listen to Linkin Park and type this blog without being interrupted by popups that ask me, "Who is this pop diva?" I don't CARE who it is! But if I close this popup, then the computer will go on a full-scale alert, kinda like the CIA whenever Bush comes around to visit (j/k military intelligence fans!) and decide to freeze up. And every time it does this, I have to RESTART on this stupid blog that complains about it. The horrible cycle. I've realized that I could probably alleviate this problem by NOT listening to LaunchRadio, but Jet is just too addicting.   Once upon a time, there were no popups and everyone lived in a state of bliss. Then, some evil entreprenuer decided, "hey, let's make life miserable by freezing all the computers and interrupting whatever makes these people happy! That way, they'll buy our products. Products like, 'the alternative to plastic surgery!'" And so it came to pass that the land of high speed internet was plagued by evil unclosable, unstopable, titanium-coated popups. And the popup stopper could do nothing! And the people despaired. (someone, think up a happy ending!)
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a big fan of comedy. If it's classy and funny, I'm in love with it. Madtv, however, is not classy. It's like a cheap watered down, sexed up version of Saturday Night Live. Can't stand that show. There's a second season of Last Comic Standing starting.. this Saturday, I think. I really enjoyed last season because of that one Vietnamese dude.. Dat Fan! Although his routines were more energetic than the other performers', I really don't think that he was as naturally funny as the other comics. I felt kinda bad for him because he was the underdog and was teased by all the other comedians. But he won in the end, so it was okay. Last Comic Standing is the only reality show that I can stand. There are just WAY TOO MANY. Back when it was just Survivor, I'd take time out to watch them walk around eating whatever they could find. Now that they have shows like, "Extreme Makeover" and "The Swan", I think television's gone a little overboard. "The Swan"??? It's a show where "less than spectacular" women go and get plastic surgery. Then they line the prettiest ones up and have a beauty pageant. WTF? It's an insult to the idea that true beauty rests within. But, I guess the ratings are good or something. 
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's summer! That wonderful time for movies and stressless fun! And summer readings, but that comes later. So there's this guy. And according to different sources, who know me at different levels, he's either a senior, a smartass freshman, a nice freshman, or a random movie star. I'm just going to refer to him as "Khaki". If you have any guesses as to who this "Khaki" person is, feel free to leave a comment. I might respond with something like, "heck no". But then again, you might be right. In which case, you get some prize or another... I'll think of something. Maybe a large candy bar. Nah, too expensive. How about a plastic party cup? It's red... and you can fill it with coke. You'll have to provide the coke, but I'll have the cup ready to go. I'm going to miss Khaki this summer... *sniff sniff* Summer! I usually don't have plans for this time of year, they just kind of pop up, like dandelions. And between events, I go into this wonderful stage called "hibernation". Or if the hibernation plan doesn't work out, there's always Terry Pratchett or Dave Barry to read.  I got a digital camera for Christmas. I'm going to have a good time at graduation. *wink wink* There's a kid giving away free kittens down the street. They're orange and brown and adorable and I want one and my allergies will reject it so I can't have the adorable, lovable kitty. *achoo!*  Leave me a message! I want to go to Cedar Point but I have no money... (This is only a minor setback. When I take over the world, Cedar Point will be mine! and Chinese people will be the most athletic people in the world! *insert evil laugh here*)
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it's summer. One word describes the arrival of this break: FINALLY! After a week of lost sleep because of final exams and another week of insomnia due to music theory crap, I'm so glad to have a break. I don't have to put up with annoying people obsessing over their GPA's anymore! YES.  I'm going to see Harry Potter with some friends, namely Saumitra and Joanna, tomorrow. Harry Potter! Dude, that kid is too hot for his glasses. I'm sitting here.. sneezing because it's allergy season. My brother, Lance, has a couple of his friends sleeping over and they are LOUD. I was never that loud when I was 8 years old. Oh yes. That comment section is meant for comments and questions. I can't guarantee that I'll actually read all of them, but I'll try to check it every few months and answer your crazy questions if they don't pertain to gpa's and that jazz. I find those people that take FOREVER to say goodbye soo annoying. If you're going to go, just go! I don't care if you love me a lot or want to thank me fifty million times! Just go! This is a clippet of an actual conversation. The names are changed because I'm nice like that. Person: "I g2g" Person: "ttyl!" me: "k" Person: "lylas!" me: "alright. bye" Person: "I'll cya tomorrow" me: "you bet." Person: "I'm going to go sleep now." me: "k" Person: "oh yea, I almost forgot..." me: "oh?" Person: "I have to go watch a movie today." Person: "crap, that means I can't go sleep now" Person: "so I'll cya." me: "k" Person: "ttyl" etc.  I miss the class of '04! They're off to do all those big things that college kids do and leaving me behind so I can stay in high school for another 3 years! I have to play for graduation, so I get to see them one last time and say goodbye to all of them. The best of luck to them. There's at least one that's going to go on to become world-famous. But it's very late, or very early, which ever way you want to think about it. So, I'm going to go sleep in. Because that's what Jaynes do when summer hits. Later days~
    
</post>


</Blog>