<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This post is a quick deviation from the main purpose of this blog, but here geos. I've started another blog called "Movie Drivel", whose purpose is to convey movie reviews posted by anybody who wants to post, on movies that they've watched. Now these can be Movie reviews, discussions, analysis', whatever. The movies that are reviewed are also rated out of a possible five gold bars (yes, you heard it here first, we are using gold bars to rate movies), and include plot overviews and actual content (review, discussion, etc).   So Check out  urlLink Movie Drivel  Note: there are currently three people including myself who post movie reviews, and we are looking for more people (anybody who wants to post). So email me if you are interested:  urlLink kayvzb@gmail.com   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone who has their license can remember the tedious process of actually acquiring it. First you'd have to go through countless hours of Drivers Education, followed by Drivers training, and then whole year of having a Learners Permit, until finally you can get your Provisional license (which still doesn't give you complete freedom for another whole year). As a teenager currently going through the process, I've noticed a few things and realized that  the process of licensing teenagers is a method of control instituted by the government to control young drivers, and to allow private buisiness' to profit.   Until about a decade ago, Driver education services were run by the government. There were a few problems that the government noticed with this method of instructing future drivers. Firstly, as time progressed, more and more drivers would be on the roads, which in turn increases the amount of unsafe driving, thus raising the accident level. Since these classes were issued by the government, they had to be free to the public so that any teenager enrolled in a public/private school could attend them. In turn, the government ceased public drivers education/training classes of their own, and issued licenses to private buisiness' that would allow students to enroll for a price. This in turn decreases the amount of teenagers that could get their licenses, because of course not all families can afford to pay the hefty bill that the process of getting a license incurs. As you can imagine, the eagerness of teenagers to drive allows these private buisiness to rack up quite a lot of money, and in turn, the government has more control over the legality of teenage drivers.   On top of all of this, insurance Policies serve as a stronger method of control. Many families don't bother paying for their children's drivers education services because Insurance prices for teenagers with vehicles continue to skyrocket. It's no wonder insurance Policies for teenagers are so high anyway. It allows the teenage driving pool to be much smaller, and makes teenagers that ARE licensed to be relatively good drivers (because of the expensive driving lessons). And also, when parents can afford to send their kids to drivers education, and do so, the result is often that the teenager goes through with the process and actually gets a license, which brings us to the fact that: any licensed driver has to be insured; and then as result of that Insure Companies make loads of money.  Teenagers and their families are basically caught by the throat, not that the teenagers care or anything, it's mostly the parents who end up paying literally.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Gross; that pretty much sums up this topic. He was a respectable president and all (not that i lived through his time, but i know a little about him), but the amount of media attention his death recieved was so over-dramatized and over-publicised that it bothers me, and im sure many others. It's as if all the national television broadcasting stations turned into FOX News: "We give you the news that DOESN'T matter, 24 hours a day!". For three days straight (throughout the days following his death and the memorial service) you couldn't watch TV without watching something about Ronald Reagean, whether it was the shit he did through his service, how he'll be missed, or all the pretty crap they were putting around his coffin at that moment.   Sure somebody like him should recieve a decent public memorial service (check), and people should pay their respects (check), but to discuss such an event to the scale at which it was stretched is just over-kill. Obviously the media is pretty fucked up as it is, and this isn't the first retarded thing associated with the media, but it just comes to show more evidence of how useless and hypocritical it's purpose can be. How are people around the nation supposed to be informed about events that are important; things that are going on that could change our lives every day when Ronald Reagan analyst's are blabbering away on whether the decisions he made throughout his service were justifiable; for three days straight.  Anyway unless FOX News becomes the only News channel on TV i think we're quite a safe ways away from the apocalypse.  P.S. Obligatory  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You ever notice how when you're listening to somebody speak for a long period of time, especially younger persons who haven't yet become adept at communicating with a large audience, that it is extremely easy to be annoyed by all the otherwise "minute" things that they do while communicating. Two things, probably the most popular, is the use of Like and Um in sentences. Daily conversations are filled with Likes and Ums, but they are not as noticeable as listening to a single person speak in front of a large audience. If that person uses Likes and Ums, you notice it; after every word you're just waiting for another "Like", or an "Um", as if you're trying to predict when it will come next. Anyway, as I sat in an audience, listening to some guy use Likes and Ums while trying to give a serious speech, I began wondering why people, especially young teenagers, use these "filler" words while communicating. After thinking about my own use of these filler words, and by examining other peoples, it's obvious that most uses of the words occur when trying to describe a certain person/place/thing. "Oh yeah .. He's basically like ... The other guy we met yesterday.." It is interesting however, that people use these things in daily speech, but refrain from using it in writing because it is deemed as informal, or generally a bad form of writing. If you can write a speech without using likes or ums, why can't you speak a speech the same? This brings up the second reason why "filler" words such as Like and Um populate conversations. People use filler words because they are unsure of what they are talking about. The most obvious example is, our own use of Like and Um (assuming of course, that most people have used Likes and Ums before). Whenever we talk about an unfamiliar subject, or perhaps try to explain to someone something they themselves don't understand, or even try to give directions to someone who probably knows the area better than you do, Likes and Ums are always used. These filler words are just substituted into sentences, allowing the speaker to formulate his/her thoughts. "Yeah, I think the road is ummm... That way... It's like two blocks down the street from here." This is probably strikingly normal for daily conversations, but quite different for speaking. Who wants to listen to somebody give a speech about a topic (let say), that they are supposed to expertise in, when all that's coming out of their mouth is more incentive for you to think that they don't know what the fuck they're talking about. Here's the real killer though; If people can censor the use of filler words such as Like and Um in writing, why can't they do the same for speaking. Nobody wants to read a supposedly informative essay, written by an author who obviously isn't sure of himself. But for the most part writing is rid of these caveats, while speaking remains un-filtered.  The third reason is similar to the second, and was explained by a STANFORD speech analyst a couple years ago. He proposed that the use of Likes and Ums (and filler words in general), are used either intentionally or unintentionally as a means for the perpetrator (if you will) to detach him/herself from the topic at hand. Basically the speaker is uncomfortable with what he is saying, whether he is not informed enough about the topic at which he's describing, or his confidence allows him to place filler words into his sentences to drag out conversation, and slowly detach himself from it. It's clear with this reasoning that people in general are not as comfortable speakers, as they are writers. Maybe it is because of the spontaneous and live thinking required by speaking, whereas in writing there is time to formulate thoughts and write them down. Anyway, this is something that got to me, after listening to a guy (who shouldn't have been there in the first place) speak in front of a whole bunch of people, and suck at it.    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blogger was discovered. Wih a firm grasp of interweb as well as Nil's mom's firm handles I grappled the obstances Blogger and established my first ever blog, wow. Anywho, last day of school tomorrow, blogs commencing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay so today was the day before teh day before school ends. Math test of course. me and aaron got Foster (math teacher) PERT shampoo, whic his quite ironic cause he's bald. Anywho math test was fairly easy (logarithms and such), and i proceeded to going to to orcestra, where there was a shitload of food and people watched edward scissor hands (the girl who brought the movies was a johny depp fanatic and had a shitload of his movies, and we'd allready watched pirates of the carribeans like 4 times that year so yeah). GG 
    
    
</post>


<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:  The movie follows two undercover narcotic officers and their investigation of the murder of a police officer. Nick Tellis (Jason Patric) promised his wife, and himself to give up field work as an undercover narcotic officer, but the recent investigation in a police murder has drawn in his participation. Tellis is partnered  with a nearly psychotic narcotic detective, who's partner was the victim of the murder; the two intent to find his killer.    Review:  Narc was great movie in many respects.  It followed the usual police-detective-movie genre style, showing the nature of police investigations, and the nature of police work in general, especially when dealing with narcotics. What Narc really shines on though, is it's portrayal of the outside-life of these specific kinds of police officers. The movie plays a great deal of attention to the characters' lives outside of the job, and how it is affected by their work. Regardless of this aspect, Narc is still a very entertaining movie to watch, as it proposes a fairly decent storyline with great acting. Ray Liotta (the character Henry Oak) plays his part superbly, adding to the overall quality of the movie. Even if you are not a big fan of detective (if you will) movies, this movie is still very entertaining to say the least. If however, you mind the portrayal of brutal violence in films, this movie probably isn't for you.       Overall Rating (3.5):   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:  A group of disaffected Scottish boys relinquish life's pain and loneliness through their heroin addiction. The story follows Mark Renton, who catches up with the distraughtly after effects of such addictions, the effects that his addiction has on his friends, as well as their [his friends] effect on him (in their whole state of fucked-upped-ness of course).    Review:  This movie, in it's own sick and disgusting way, is hilarious. Their are moments that are absolutely disgusting beyond belief, but you'll find yourself laughing without knowing why. Trainspotting has quite a few interesting themes, such as a parody regarding heroin addictions, and a portrayal of the dullness of modern-day existence (especially if your Scottish eh?), all wrapped up in an intriguingly dark story that will surely entertain (non-witty personnel be advised).  Excerpt:   Choose life. Choose a job. Choose a career. Choose a family. Choose a fucking big television, Choose washing machines, cars, compact disc players, and electrical tin openers. Choose good health, low cholesterol and dental insurance. Choose fixed- interest mortgage repayments. Choose a starter home. Choose your friends. Choose leisure wear and matching luggage. Choose a three piece suite on hire purchase in a range of fucking fabrics. Choose DIY and wondering who you are on a Sunday morning. Choose sitting on that couch watching mind-numbing sprit- crushing game shows, stuffing fucking junk food into your mouth. Choose rotting away at the end of it all, pishing you last in a miserable home, nothing more than an embarrassment to the selfish, fucked-up brats you have spawned to replace yourself. Choose your future. Choose life... But why would I want to do a thing like that?          Here's a little quote to keep you busy while you wait for your [mom, dad, yourself, servant, bitch, maid] to get the movie, or if you're just that fucking lazy and use Netflix.   I hate being Scottish. We're the lowest of the fucking low, the scum of the earth, the most wretched, servile, miserable, pathetic trash that was ever shat into civilization. Some people hate the English, but I don't. They're just wankers. We, on the other hand, are colonized by wankers. We can't even pick a decent culture to be colonized by. We are ruled by effete arseholes. It's a shite state of affairs and all the fresh air in the world will not make any fucking difference.    Random quote, but it's interesting anyway cause it not only deprives the Scottish (who cares about them anyway, they obviously don't want to be understood by anybody else for speaking a fucking language that shouldn't be considered a dialect, but rather meaningless blabble), but it's Scottish guys depriving themselves, which actually has a lot to do with the theme of the movie. They slightly sound like Canadians too, which is cheerful cause they are funny ol' chaps as well (bloops, I just lost my entire audience).   So if you're in for some witty humor and  got some time on your hands, and wouldn't mind relying on the subtitles once in awhile, pick up Trainspotting at your local heroin deale-- err sorry; at your local video store today.    Overall Rating (4):   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:    Underworld is a movie that follows the daily life of a vampire, starting with shower and breakfast, to work, cigar at night, a drink in a local bar, you know. Just kidding. Anyways, Underworld is actually about a vampire(es?) Kate Beckinsale (:0) who is part of centuries long war between the vampires and the lichen (werewolves). She happens to meet a human during a good old battle only to realizes that he has become a lichen and is being chased by the lichen for his ability to become both lichen and vampire (a hybrid).                                                                        Review:     I'm no vampire saga nerd and my limited knowlage of vampires and such comes from Dungeons and Dragons, however I'm guessing that this was a fairly good vampire movie in comparision to other vampire movies. It didn't focus to much on the horror portion of the movie, probably because the main charcter (our hero) was a vampire. The movies main falling point was that it didn't give you a side to support, It wasn't like vampires are the good guys or vice verca. Kate Beckinsale did a fairly good job of portraying a vampire without so many of the vampirish qualities that they are usually associated with. It was fun to watch, but nothing amazing. The plot left something to be desired, I was hoping for something a bit more astounding. Rent to watch, don't buy.       Overal Rating (3):   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:   Bob (Matt Damon) and Walt (Greg Kinnear) are conjoined twins who live happily in Martha's Vineyard. Their relationship however is tested when Walt desides to follow his dreams of becomming an actor by moving to Hollywood. The two quickly rise in fame as Walt lands a spot on Cher's TV Show, while at the same time Bob furthers his relationship with May, who was Bob's e-pal buddy before he moved to her hometown. These new experiences force Bob and Walt to re-evaluate the values of their bond, and eventually cause them to realize the negative aspects they hadn't seen before.     Review:   Stuck on You, like most mediocre comedy movies, had it's good moments, and it's bad ones. There were certain points in the film that were amusingly funny, while others were plain stupid. The story was fairly interesting because of the Bob and Walt's unique bond (literally), which is basically the aspect that made the film. Acting was fairly decent by Damon and Kinnear, while the supporting actress Wen Yann Shih (who played as May) will keep you wondering whether or not she's acting badly on purpose. Even if she was, you'll be dissapointed because she does a horrible job at acting bad, if that was her intention in the first place. The movie was fairly entertaining, and the comedy mediocre, but certainly not the best we've seen of the Farrelly brothers.        Overal Rating (2.5):   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:   Mystic River tells the story about three childhood friends who re-unite after one of their daughter's is murdered. The story follows all three characters (Sean Penn, Kevin Bacon, Tim Robbins) in an intriguing style to find out who was responsible for her death. Jimmy's (Sean Penn) daughter is the victim, and Sean Devine (Kevin Bacon) is the detective on the case. As the story progress', Bacon gathers disturbing information suggesting Dave Boyle's (Tim Robbins) involvement in the murder.    Review:  One thing can be said straight out: the acting in this movie is superb. Sean Penn, Kevin Bacon, and Tim Robbins make an incredible leading cast, supported by a great directing style (Clint Eastwood), and a very gripping storyline. Although the movie is fairly depressing, It's very well done and worth the watch if you don't mind risking the emotional-well-being factor. Even if you don't like depressing movies, see it for the acting! I can easily through 4.5 gold bars at this piece of work.        Overall Rating (4.5):   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I think i've marked this down as the worst movie of 2003, with the potential of being the worst science fiction movie of all time.  The story follows of a group of archeologists in France who find out that their boss (who is the father of the main actor, the dude from Fast and the Furious) was taken back through time, to 1357, at Castleguard, France. The archeologists, accompanied by a few ex-marines, are introduced to the secret time-travel machine that was accidentally discovered in an expiriment, and are sent back through time to find their boss (Fast and the Furious man's father, which is too bad cause the movie would have been significantly less annoying without him and his gang). Anyway a whole lotta shit happens while they are there, because that day happens to be when the French attack Castleguard to take it back from the English, so there is DANGer and FIRE and other sHIt.   The story is mildly entertaining, but viewers are highly likely to be totally distracted from any story implications because of the horrible acting. The supporting actress Frances O'Conner has set a new high for supporting actresses who ruin movies.   Subject in Question:      urlLink   
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I recently watched 50 First Dates, actually I watched it a couple times because I really had nothing better to do. Allow me to break it down for you: Essentially it is a film about a marine (water not military) vet living in Hawaii. He manages to get a lot of shall we say attention from lady tourists by lying about his job and showing em a good time. Anyways, he meets his girl, blah blah blah, typical love story, only to find out that she had an accident and her memory refreshes ever 24 hours. So Mr. Sandler spends the entire movie trying to get her to remember him.   Generally the movie is pretty good, it rate 3 and 1/2 gold bars our of 5 gold bars. Why gold bars? I don't know, make up a good story. Anyways, it is pretty funny certainly 294% better then Sandlers last film, the terrible Anger Managment. The story is funny, and the plot works with it pretty well, but hell there is always room for more of teh funny. If you want a new comedy that is actually worth the watch, give it a try. Don't buy though, don't buy unless I tell you to.   BTW: there is a hobbit in the film, you get a cookie if you spot him.   Overal Rating (3.5):   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:     Hah! Blast from the past. Yes folks, this is Speed a movie that is old enough to make people go "Why the hell are you renting this old movie", without it being old enough to be classic. But enough of my mindless blabbering, the movie is a about a young policeman who with his partner foils a brilliant concocted plot of a deranged person to collect some money through some terroist plans. Foiled, the man becomes angry and takes a personal vendetta against the main character (Keanu Reeves). Reeves ends up on a bus trying to save the lives of a dozen innocent civilians. I'll leave it at that.    Review:      Well, since everybody around here is freaking LAZY; Kayvz hasn't written a review since Narc and the other loser on here hasn't done a single review, I am forced to make up for the slack. I was surprised! Yes, surprised. I had never seen Speed, and though I heard it was good i thought I would find it kinda lame compared to the current day high tech cgi action thrillers. I found Speed quite like Speed, fast and a high. It was rather enjoyable and had some twists that actually surprised me. The acting wasn't anything amazing, but the actual substance and constant action made up for it. I'd recommened that if you are looking for an action flick and havn't seen Speed, to check it out. BTW: I AM NOT TALKING ABOUT THE DRUG SPEED, IF YOU TAKE SPEED, DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK!. Btw (2), if you want to donate to this site you can bake me cookies and fedex em to me. Thanks in advance.         Overall Rating (4):   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Plot:     NOTE: Before you read this, you may want to copy the entire review into word and run spell check because I am too lazy to do it.  Now, before you read this, I am going to apoligize. This apologe for the following not being funny. I'm sorry. Anyways, to the topic. Slackers is a movie about a trio. Yes a trio, as in three, like 2+1, or 1+1+1, or just 3. In this case I'm not sure. Anyways the three fellows are slackers. Yes, slackers, as in they don't do work at their college. However, this is not the case, they do plenty of work; just not the kind of work that the college wants. These young men spend their free time (when they arn't smoking large amounts of Mary Jane and wasting time) planning extravagent schemes to cheat their way out of taking tests. They happen to pull a little job to gain the answers for a midterm, however one the guys involved (Dave) writes down his number for a woman, however the number of left and a curious invdividual who has an obsession (I put this lightly) for the same woman takes the number which happens to be a copy of the mid term and uses it to black mail the trio into helping him get the girl.       Review:   Well, writing a review takes a lot of effort. Most people don't realize that I actually have to type this out. Most of you think I some sort of program where I just select "Good" or "Crap" from a menu and click "Go" and it automatically writes a long detailed review for the movie. This is not the case. I would have to say, this was a "Good" movie. I did not expect much, and however I found myself laughing almost as often as I was not laughing. It used a good selection of characters to bring teh funny. The plot left a little to be desired however it didn't get in the way like most comedys so, my hat is off on that detail. I believe that it would have been made better if they had expanded the movie a little, made it more detailed and used a full 2 hours rather then an hour and a half. It had potential to become a Van Wilder, but didn't quite make it. I recommened renting it and checking it out, and if you feel like it, laughing.          Overall Rating (3.5):   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>