<Blog>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mind..crippled, flummoxed, embittered.
These flashes of thoughts devour my humble soul 
or perhaps my bleeding heart is what I speak of.
Dripping with the poison this existence has wounded my flesh with.
I've blind folded my energy from itself.
Why make it grieve for something so treacherous such as love.
That two faced monster...Oh how I yearn for a taste of it.
I crave and thirst for you..you wicked fuck.
Should I give into you and let you hypnotize me with your voodoo?
I rather slice my veins and drink myself to death.
I hold the beating heart of a tortured mortal.
You think you can catch me?
I dare you to try and find me
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't look at me,
I see myself in your face.

Don't touch me,
Im full of poisonous thorns.

Don't speak to me,
Your words are worthless syllables.

Don't understand me,
You never knew me.

Don't pity me,
I pity you.

You left me,
I wither without you.

You taught me,
My reality now a nightmare.

You loved me,
Enough to torture me.

My father,
Is only my mother.




     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You poor soul,
You swallowed the witch's poison.


You foolish mortal,
You're stuck in the cage of sorrow.


You blind boy,
Open your stitched closed eyes.


You used puppet,
You handed her your strings.


You fucking coward,
I laugh at your torment.


No longer a little girl,
Looking up at your nightmare.


No longer crying,
Watching your heart dragged to its grave.


I pity your life,
Your undesired path.


I am your sister,
The truth I shall reveal.


Oh my brother,
You fell into hell's palm.


You poor soul,
Death is your only escape now.


You poor soul...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why speak out when, no one really listens.
Why try to explain, when no one really cares.
Why put effort, when no one understands.
Why not keep silent, no one is really there.


What is that smell?
My thoughts rotting inside.
Why not set them free, 
For I do not know how.




Empty, are its contents
Long, are its meanings
Sad, are its feelings
Weeping, all it knows.


To leave, is all I want.
To love, is all I care.
To feel, I have no choice.
To let go, what else is there?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lying in despair as bitter thoughts consume me
Drowing in a pool of tears
Reaching out to taste your agony.
A reflection of dust as I look in the mirror
Confusion swims through my veins 
Ending with blisters at my fingers tips.
Your face I remember,
Engraved in my heart
A hope that is lost, farewell you had said.
Our love always remembered
My friend I will miss
As a Hypnotic Blur it started
In a Tragic Style it ended......
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting here twiddling my thumbs.
My mind goes numb, or in hopes it will.
Bleeding from the thoughts that stab it.
These corroded knives, I knew they'd come.
Time didn't call them, I prefer intuition.
Useless memories, why remember.
My peak.. never touched, but footsteps did climb.
Back down the mountain, the ground I did miss.
My heart I never packed in the backpack of fear.
Feelings did suffocate, I had to give them air.
My intelligence insulted, but my dignity grown.
Babble, jabber, bullshit....spare me the garbage.
Those were the words he chose to say goodbye.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do those eyes look at me with coyness...
that look, yet so deceiving.
Why do I want to plunge into them, 
yet hinder myself from stumbling into the unknown.
Why do those hands clutch this putrid craving,
yet still this tenacious palisade won't sever.
Why does that wistful kiss tantalize me to abandon my phobia,
yet still daunts me to my grave.
Why does that peerless smile bend me....
so proficient at cloaking its demon.
Why does the scrimmage between my angels and devils
prevail in molding my daydream into grime.
Why do I meditate over this absurdity
when sublimity is vanished from my reality.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I envision myself there next to you,
letting the voices of my inner being sing to you.
This time..no misery, no tears escaping my eyes.
I frisk the outlines of your perfectly built silhouette,
falling into this rapture of eternal bliss.
My fingers explore your lips....immersed by its prevalent beauty.
As the warmth of your breath eludes from your mouth,
it embraces the chills my heart trembles with.
You brush your hesitant hands on the curves of my naked body.
With every inch.. my desire screams for ceaseless felicity.
The sweat your body seeps onto mine makes my skin twitter.
I can hear your petrified voice hiss the words " I love you" into the ears of my soul.
You confine me into your possession as if fretful I would evade.
I unlax your spirit with my alluring kiss... 
as I dive into the sea of your addicting amour.
Whirlwinds of aphrodesia obscure my mind.
I suppress this explosion my body wants to spit out.
So I turn over and say goodnight...
and later awake you to realize...it was all just a dream.
Are those tears that leak from your eyes?
Wipe them out of my presence, for they provoke me
to make your agony linger.
How does it feel?
     
    
</post>


</Blog>