<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A big hello to Wardy, whose new blog  urlLink Mustard Cats  is far, far more originally named than mine. The bastard.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Causing my heart to swell to Queen Mum gawd-blessing size is  urlLink this news  of the hate campaign waged against the Swiss referee from England's last Euro 2004 game. And the main rabble-rousers? Guessed it in one - the fucking Sun.  The day after the game they were openly calling him a cheat, then printed his e-mail address and encouraged readers to "tell him what you think". After that - having seemingly decided that simply abusing him wasn't enough - they printed articles about his marriage, home and workplace. The next step was to slap a huge England flag outside his home. Ha! Ha! Ha! Twats.  And the upshot - never saw this coming! - is that he's been receiving death threats and hate mail, and has had to go under police protection.  Even more heart-warmingly, a Swiss girl got the shit kicked out of her by three English thugs for the crime of wearing her country's football shirt. And I guarantee you those three also told Meier "what they think" in their finest scumbag English.  It's always the bloody same - they stoke the fires with crap jokes, snide comments and outright abuse, then tut-tut-tut when it turns into something from Lord of the Flies and lager-fuelled morons unite under the Sun's xenophobic banner and someone gets hurt. You know that if they even bother to report the story of three of Our Boys giving one Swiss girl a shoeing - and I'm pretty sure they'll ignore it - they'll be back into Simpleton Moralising mode before you can say "Rebekah Wade is a chump".  Oh, and Asda? In the same article it mentions that they've jumped on the We-Can-Be-Boorish-Football-Muppets-Too bandwagon, and have offered all Swiss nationals free eye tests.  I prefer Tescos anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Via  urlLink Rory Parle  comes the joyful news that the last three books in the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy trilogy have been produced for radio. All the original cast have returned, aside from the late Peter Jones as the voice of the book (which is really not good enough if you ask me, as Douglas himself puts in an appearance as Agrajag, and he's been dead since 2001).  Find out all the details  urlLink here , and then celebrate by getting hit in the small of the back by a large and extremely disreputable cocktail party.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pointless lists are what makes the internet great, kids. (With a hat tip to  urlLink PZ Myers ). If it's in bold, I liked it, if it's in italics, I ain't seen it. And if it's got a comment next to it, it's because I love slagging things off more than anything else in the world.   1. Titanic (1997) $600,779,824   2. Star Wars (1977) $460,935,665   3. E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial (1982) $434,949,459   4. Star Wars: Episode I - The Phantom Menace (1999) $431,065,444 - damn you, Lucas.  5. Spider-Man (2002) $403,706,375   6. The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King (2003) $377,019,252    7. The Passion of the Christ (2004) $370,025,697  8. Jurassic Park (1993) $356,784,000  9. Shrek 2 (2004) $356,211,000    10. The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers (2002) $340,478,898   11. Finding Nemo (2003) $339,714,367   12. Forrest Gump (1994) $329,691,196    13. The Lion King (1994) $328,423,001   14. Harry Potter and the Sorcerer’s Stone (2001)   15. The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring (2001) $313,837,577  16. Star Wars: Episode II - Attack of the Clones (2002) $310,675,588 - for the love of God, Lucas, stop! Stop, it's already dead (breaks down into pitiful sobbing)...  17. Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi (1983) $309,125,409  18. Independence Day (1996) $306,124,059  19. Pirates of the Caribbean (2003) $305,411,224   20. The Sixth Sense (1999) $293,501,675   21. Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back (1980) $290,158,751  22. Home Alone (1990) $285,761,243 - the little fucker was born to hang, you know. 23. The Matrix Reloaded (2003) $281,492,479 - at least George Lucas waited til his fourth film before he fucked everything up.  24. Shrek (2001) $267,652,016   25. Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (2002) $261,970,615   26. How the Grinch Stole Christmas (2000) $260,031,035   27. Jaws (1975) $260,000,000   28. Monsters, Inc. (2001) $255,870,172  29. Batman (1989) $251,188,924   30. Men in Black (1997) $250,147,615   31. Toy Story 2 (1999) $245,823,397   32. Bruce Almighty (2003) $242,589,580   33. Raiders of the Lost Ark (1981) $242,374,454  34. Twister (1996) $241,700,000 - in which Helen Hunt goes on a revenge mission against a spot of inclement weather. As you do.  35. My Big Fat Greek Wedding (2002) $241,437,427   36. Ghost Busters (1984) $238,600,000  37. Beverly Hills Cop (1984) $234,760,500 38. Cast Away (2000) $233,630,478 - in which Tom Hanks might as well have painted "Can I have another Oscar?" on his forehead. 39. The Lost World: Jurassic Park (1997) $229,074,524 - answer me this: How the holy fuck did the T-rex get out of the ship's hold, slaughter all the crew (including the chap steering the ship, who was in a tiny cabin, and managing to leave his hand still gripping the wheel) and GET BACK IN THE HOLD ready to leap out on Jeff Goldblum?  40. Signs (2002) $227,965,690   41. Rush Hour 2 (2001) $226,138,454  42. Mrs. Doubtfire (1993) $219,200,000 43. Ghost (1990) $217,631,306 - I remember liking this when I was young. The shame of it.  44. Aladdin (1992) $217,350,219   45. Saving Private Ryan (1998) $216,119,491  46. Mission: Impossible II (2000) $215,397,307 - how many times can someone pull off a fake plastic face before that particular plot twist becomes boring? Answer: this many.  47. X2 (2003) $214,948,780  48. Austin Powers in Goldmember (2002) $213,079,163 - they should've stopped at the first one.  49. Back to the Future (1985) $210,609,762  50. Austin Powers: The Spy Who Shagged Me (1999) $205,399,422 - no really, they should've stopped at the first one.  51. Terminator 2: Judgment Day (1991) $204,843,350   52. The Exorcist (1973) $204,565,000   53. The Mummy Returns (2001) $202,007,640  54. Armageddon (1998) $201,573,391 - hnnngh..grnnnnph...wrrggg..(vein in forehead pops).  55. Gone with the Wind (1939) $198,655,278   56. Pearl Harbor (2001) $198,539,855 - thank fuck.   57. Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade (1989) $197,171,806   58. Toy Story (1995) $191,800,000   59. Men in Black II (2002) $190,418,803   60. Gladiator (2000) $187,670,866  61. Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs (1937) $184,925,485  62. Dances with Wolves (1990) $184,208,848  63. Batman Forever (1995) $184,031,112 - "It's burning acid!" squealed the bank teller in the opening scene. "Aah, knackers, there goes the franchise," moaned I into my popcorn.  64. The Fugitive (1993) $183,875,760   65. Ocean's Eleven (2001) $183,405,771   66. What Women Want (2000) $182,805,123  67. The Perfect Storm (2000) $182,618,434 - people saying the title of the film in a dramatic tone as part of the dialogue: for this I would bring back hanging. The Lord of the Rings films get a let-off for this, cos they're great.  68. Liar Liar (1997) $181,395,380   69. Grease (1978) $181,360,000  70. Jurassic Park III (2001) $181,166,115  71. Mission: Impossible (1996) $180,965,237  72. Planet of the Apes (2001) $180,011,740 - insert your own "damn you all to hell!" joke here.  73. Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom (1984) $179,870,271  74. Pretty Woman (1990) $178,406,268 - Julia Roberts: another reason to bring back hanging.  75. Tootsie (1982) $177,200,000  76. Top Gun (1986) $176,781,728  77. There’s Something About Mary (1998) $176,483,808    78. Ice Age (2002) $176,387,405  79. Crocodile Dundee (1986) $174,635,000 80. Home Alone 2: Lost in New York (1992) $173,585,516 - sigh.  81. Elf (2003) $173,381,405   82. Air Force One (1997) $172,888,050 - the very worst in Yankee Doodle patriotic chest-pounding cheese.  83. Rain Man (1988) $172,825,435   84. Apollo 13 (1995) $172,071,312   85. The Matrix (1999) $171,383,253    86. Beauty and the Beast (1991) $171,301,428   87. Tarzan (1999) $171,085,177    88. A Beautiful Mind (2001) $170,708,996   89. Chicago (2002) $170,684,505  90. Three Men and a Baby (1987) $167,780,960  91. Meet the Parents (2000) $166,225,040  92. Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves (1991)$165,500,000 93. Hannibal (2001) $165,091,464 - didn't Hannibal Lecter use to be scary?  94. Catch Me If You Can (2002) $164,435,221   95. Big Daddy (1999) $163,479,795  96. The Sound of Music (1965) $163,214,286  97. Batman Returns (1992) $162,831,698   98. A Bug’s Life (1998) $162,792,677   99. Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (2004) $161,963,000   100. The Waterboy (1998) $161,487,252 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For a sample of the afore-mentioned madness, take a look at  urlLink this place . Yes, it's like shooting particularly devout fish in a sanctified barrel, but screw it, it's good for a larf.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm.  Looking back over the pathetically small number of posts so far on this blog, I can't help getting the impression that I'm not really fulfilling the role I assigned myself when I started up - namely posts on the utter crapness of religion and the Right, and the splendiferousness of science and skepticism (which has a nice alliterative ring to it, might copyright that). Ah well, I'm sure I'll get up to speed eventually.  The thing is, very few people in England care if you're an atheist. At least in America if you say you don't believe in God, you're denounced from the pulpit, thrown out of the car pool and banned from the local sewing circle (probably). That's something a guy can rage against, can blog about in tones of great vengeance and furrrrious anger. Over here, a raised eyebrow and an "oh, really?" is about the best you can hope for when you point out some religious idiocy. If you're an argumentative bugger like me, it gets right on your wick. I mean, where's the fun if they're not going to start quoting Bible verses at you?  So until I get my act together and start uncovering dark plots by the Church of England to contaminate our precious bodily fluids, the only other option is pointing out the madness overseas - both East and West.  And finally, don't get me wrong - I'm glad to live in a secular society where you can tell God to stick it up his nose without being the focus of a hate campaign by the local newspaper. Fighting the religious majority in the US seems like fun from the outside, but I'll bet it gets bloody tiring and frustrating after a while. I'm just having a moan, as per usual.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Tim Ireland's  taking a break, done in by Tony Blair's tendency to stick his fingers in his ears and go "lalalalala" whenever someone disagrees with him. His  urlLink farewell flash song  is another blinder.  Here's hoping for a swift return.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't like football much.  The players are dense, the supporters are morons and the pundits are dense, moronic  urlLink racists . I'm generalising madly here, of course, but I've got enough empirical evidence from the pubs in the city centre to back up the theory.  Even in the case of major international tournaments like the one currently underway in Portugal, I really can't get too worked up about whether England get to the semi-finals (as far as we ever seem to get in anything, but which I believe is generally considered to be enough to warrant knighthoods, going on past Sun campaigns). Cricket's the only game that ever gets the old blood pumping; there's nothing like a one-dayer with 10 runs needed off the last over to get you on the edge of your seat (unless it's England against Australia, in which case the result is in no doubt, no matter who needs the runs). A good run in Euro 2004 would be nice, but...y'know.  So how is it that I could be found last Sunday night screaming  "You fucking French bastards!"  at the TV, after only 9 cans of Stella?  Oh, right.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Righty-o, all being well this blog's comments should now be Haloscan powered
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't like talking to myself, generally because after five minutes of it I realise what shite I'm spouting and then it's three days before I speak again. So over the past couple of days I've been trying to think of the best way to increase the traffic to this site, so that (hopefully) people will leave lots of lovely comments. And yes, I know, "write lots of interesting posts that people will enjoy reading" is the most obvious way to achieve this. That's a lot of work, though, and requires talent. So any suggestions from any poor schmuck that stumbles across this site by accident would be most welcome.  Mind you,  urlLink this thread  on Pharyngula is enough to put anyone off running a popular blog. Surely no right-thinking person, given the opportunity, would fail to shove  urlLink Susan's  keyboard down her throat. Sideways.  Update: hmmm...seems the Susan link isnae working right. She starts at comment no.4, and no.6 is a doozy.  "WHEN YOU MESS WITH THE BESS, YOU DIE LIKE THE RESS . . . LESS!!! :>)"  Oh, how we laughed.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right then everybody. In the (admittedly unlikely, though less so since  urlLink Ben's  kind link) event that anyone from the UK reads this, please go and sign  urlLink here.   (found the petition via  urlLink The Panda's Thumb , by the way. Been reading up on blogging etiquette, you see.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tony Blair, eh?  Bounced us into war with a load of WMD guff; backs the teaching of Creationism in schools on the basis of diversity and exam results; uses the bloody Sun as his propaganda mouthpiece; claimed he was a "pretty straight kind of guy" in the wake of the Ecclestone affair; rolled tanks into Heathrow days before the anti-war march in February 2003; set his attack dogs on the BBC in the wake of the Kelly affair. And so on, over the last seven years...  Blair's had his time, and he's now a liability to the Labour party.  And so here's the  urlLink Big Intervention .
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A brief note on each piece of linkage and why:  The Guardian: daily newspaper of choice, even if it does sometimes seem like it's been written by Kitten off Big Brother (and if I ever mention that show ever again, you have permission to hit me. A lot.)  Crooked Timber: a bunch of extremely clever lefties and liberals, who provide the sort of well-thought out arguments that this blog will so sorely lack.  Butterflies and Wheels: a site dedicated to opposing pseudoscience and politically motivated truth claims. Also very smart people (I'm hoping that by linking to all these brainy types I'll get some reflected glory), and the Fashionable Dictionary is amusing.  Bloggerheads: Tim Ireland's weblog - he posts about 10 times a day, is always funny, I agree with his politics and he links to some cracking flash games. Oh, and his "Labour Needs Leadership Change" flash song is utterly fantastic.  Pharyngula: the blog of PZ Myers, scientist and atheist.  The Panda's Thumb: a group of scientists opposing the growing Intelligent Design movement (aka Creationists in ill-fitting lab coats).  Muckraking: a chap whose blog I found by following a link from Pharyngula. In the first post I read he made a joke about "Bovine University" with a picture of Ralph Wiggum attached. This is enough to get linked, people - take note.  There will be more links as they occur to me...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is sort of a warning...  Four years ago I voted Conservative, believed in God and bought the Sun everyday. Hell, I even thought that Richard Littlejohn often talked a lot of sense  (hangs head in shame) .  Today I read the Guardian (only buy it on a Saturday, mind - I like the TV guide - otherwise I stick to the website), vote Labour with Blair-related misgivings and am as atheist as they come.  And in the same way born again Christians tend to be a bit swivel-eyed about their conversions - clutching their bibles, trying to convert non-believers, invading Middle Eastern countries - I think political converts tend to get a bit worked up about the things that used to (in their eyes) hoodwink them. So let's have it upfront - I don't like the Murdoch empire, don't like religion, don't like the Right and think Richard Littlejohn is the world's biggest arse (at which point he would no doubt insert some lame joke about homosexuals).  So I'm biased, and you won't find much in the way of serious-minded, thoughtful critiques of these gits - it's ad hominem, unfair digs all the way. But at least you're forewarned.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, this blog is called Insert Joke Here because I couldn't think of anything clever to call it. That's the sort of inspired creativity that's going to make this blog a daily must-read for all and sundry, by crikey.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bet no-one's ever used that for their first title before...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lawks, go read Scaryduck's Friday  urlLink tale of woe , and prepare to giggle foolishly.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey,  urlLink Daily Mail Watch  has launched! I could've sworn I signed up to be notified when that happened, but my inbox remains devoid of tabloid-trashing emails.   urlLink Today's  post sticks the&nbsp;boot into the Mail's oh-so-predictable "Ban This Evil Game"  urlLink article .  I remember the article they once did about Goldeneye on the N64 (Best Game Ever?) The reporter claimed that a baby&nbsp;was addicted to&nbsp;the game, and played it&nbsp;8 hours a day, shouting "Die!" each time he notched up another kill (and what a lovely touch that was, I'm surprised they didn't claim it was his first word). Accompanying this was a photo of a slightly puzzled-looking kid holding the control pad in entirely the wrong way (you have to be a Nintendo geek to notice these telling details) and seemingly staring out the window rather than at the screen.   All of this, I believe, was designed to get your standard Mail reader muttering something about banning all these dangerous Sony Nintendos, or at least making that Spikey the Hedgehog a cert 18.  It fair brings a nostalgic tear to my eye, it really does. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I weren't being a lazy, unemployed doss-monkey at the moment,  urlLink this  would have cost my employer an awful lot in wasted time.  (via  urlLink Bloggerheads ) 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Jonathan Derbyshire's post  about Richard Dawkins' approach to politics (rather less reasoned than his scientific work, putting it mildly) is an interesting one, and his point is one that's occurred to me before. Dawkins' letters to the Guardian and Independent are not exactly rigorously argued -&nbsp;they have&nbsp;more than a touch of the Michael Moores about them, to be honest.   Thing is, though, they're only letters. A typical one sent to the Independent in response to an article by Johann Hari prompted&nbsp;Hari to reply to him by email. The  urlLink resulting exchange  can be found on&nbsp;Hari's website, and makes for far more interesting reading than the original sniping about blowing up McDonalds. Arguments are made, points acknowledged - it's much better.   Admittedly, Dawkins is a well-known public intellectual and his views have greater influence than your average anti-war protester, in which case perhaps he should take more care to back up his arguments. But I'm not sure short letters venting steam about something you believe to be wrong should be taken as the full extent of your political opinions.   UPDATE: Jonathan  urlLink also points  to a petition signed by Dawkins regarding academic sanctions against Israel. I remembered reading about that a while back, and&nbsp;pointed out to Jonathan that Dawkins didn't sign the Rose petition, but a different one (Jonathan has now corrected the post). Further to this, I've also found a  urlLink letter  from Blakemore and Dawkins that explains their reasons, and also&nbsp;notes that Dawkins has since publicly stated that he regrets signing the petition.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hooray, Richard Dawkins has been voted  urlLink Britain's favourite intellectual  by readers of Prospect magazine (link from  urlLink Butterflies and Wheels ).&nbsp;Even better, he's got a new book out next month,  urlLink The Ancestor's Tale: A Pilgrimage to the Dawn of Life . There's also an article about him in today's  urlLink Observer .   I'll be writing something a bit more in-depth about Dawkins in the next day or so. In the meantime, go read the article, order the book and ...um... look at the Prospect list. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Get used to that title, it'll probably be a weekend regular. You're not missing much, just yet more crap jokes. Just thought I'd acknowledge the deleted post so as not to get all 1984 on you.  Oh, the advice about Super Bock beer is worth salvaging though - give that stuff a wide berth, it tears your innards up like a  urlLink jagged metal Krusty-O . 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last over before lunch in the first test against the West Indies. Flintoff is facing, the legendary Geoff Boycott is commentating (the quotes are from memory).   Boycott:  ...there's no need for a conference, you've got to put three men round the bat, he won't attack, Flintoff will be playing for lunch, he-    CRACK. Six, straight down the ground. Lara scatters his fielders to the boundaries.   Boycott:  Oh, now look at this, he's gone on the defensive. You've got to keep those men around the bat, keep the pressure on, they-    CRACK. Flintoff goes for another big hit, plays it straight onto his stumps.   Boycott:  Well there you go, you see, in going on the attack he's got himself out. He should've done what I said and played for lunch. &nbsp;   &nbsp;  You tell him, Geoff. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Christ, I've been  urlLink linked  by the mighty Norm. Look at the state of this place, whatever must people think?   Still, this is as good a time as any to update some links - the following are blogs I read every day (yes, every single day. I have nothing better to do. Happy?)    urlLink Norman Geras : I've mentioned my opposition to the Iraq war before, and also the fact that I came to politics fairly late in the game. Even though I was playing catch-up, the sheer certainty of the anti-war movement bothered me (so did the certainty of the pro-war movement, but I digress). Reading Norm's blog was a breath of fresh air - a pro-war site that didn't start with a Bush/Cheney 04 banner and go from there.   urlLink Harry's Place : Again, a Lefty site that deals mainly in sticking it to idiotic Lefties. It sometimes gets a bit snarky, but it's always interesting.   urlLink Kevin Drum : of Washington Monthly, a must-read US Left blog.   urlLink UK Politics on the Left : I said I read these blogs daily, right? Well, I  check  this one daily, but John only posts about 2 or 3 times a month. Still, the "has he posted?" suspense is... well, pretty weak actually, but when he does, it's  urlLink worth it .   urlLink Scaryduck : pant-wettingly funny.   urlLink Mustard Cats : me old mate, Stef.    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blimey, it's  urlLink all kicking off  at Butterflies and Wheels.   Leaving aside the&nbsp;fun, if somewhat undignified,&nbsp;sight of philosophers calling names and telling each other to grow up, this is an interesting topic, and it touches (slightly) on the  urlLink argument  I had at the weekend.   The guy I was arguing with was a classic bigot, prejudiced against anyone a different colour from him, and each time I agreed with him on some characteristic of Islamic fundamentalism - death by stoning, suicide bombings, attitude towards women - I was uncomfortably aware that we were approaching the topic from entirely different directions: he'd already made his mind up about all Muslims, and wanted any evidence he could get that would back up his stance - I tried only to criticise those facets of a culture that I felt needed to be questioned. Whenever we agreed, I think it merely confirmed in his mind that&nbsp;Muslims were irredeemably evil - surely, if even this wishy-washy liberal he was talking to was unwilling to defend them!&nbsp;Never mind that I'd already argued any number of points with him, whenever we agreed on something, I could almost see "well, there you go then," running through his brain.   Each time I attack some part of Islamic culture, am I helping to demonise it?  urlLink Norman Geras  makes a good point in his two cents on this topic:   "...in the tense political climate we all now inhabit, it is important to avoid doing anything to feed ethnic or religious prejudices and hatreds. In so far as Muslims are on the receiving end of these, they must be defended - as would go for any other group."   Obviously, agreeing on certain points in a slightly boozy discussion with someone who's about as likely to change his mind about Muslims as he is about beer isn't on the scale of feeding ethnic hatreds. But I've posted about Islam before, and I will again, and although I'm unlikely to have much influence given my single-figure readership and somewhat shaky arguments, does this amount to what  urlLink Marc Mulholland  was originally talking about?   Personally, I think it's one of those times when the answer lies somewhere in the middle*. We must never stop criticising those aspects of any culture that are unacceptable - we must always highlight them and&nbsp;present arguments against them, never keep silent on the grounds of being understanding liberals. But, at the same time, we should be careful not to give ammo to the bigots - we should always highlight that we are only attacking a certain idea held by a certain number of people, and that using these points as a defense for prejudice is equally unacceptable.   Bloody hell, it must be so much easier being a racist wanker.   *Annoyingly - I'm a great believer in  urlLink Dawkins's Law of Adversarial Debate &nbsp;(scroll down to Richard Dawkins)  UPDATE: there are more posts on this topic at Butterflies and Wheels  urlLink here  and  urlLink here ,&nbsp;and an excellent post by  urlLink David T  at Harry's Place.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right, let me try and get my head round this.  urlLink Empire  is the UK's biggest selling film magazine, a position that&nbsp;no doubt&nbsp;rests on a reputation for reliable reviews. Why then, in the name of all that is nerdy, did  urlLink Spider-man 2  get the same rating as  urlLink The Day After Tomorrow ?  &nbsp;  Anyone who's seen Spider-man 2 doesn't need telling that it's a fantastic film, and if you've not seen it then go this instant. Four stars from Empire is stingy as hell, especially when you consider that they gave  urlLink Attack of the Clones  five (and don't even get me started on that, it manages something I thought wasn't possible - it makes The Phantom Menace look good).  &nbsp;  The Day After Tomorrow, somehow, is also deemed a four-star effort. This is a film where people  outrun  cold weather. Where a tsunami hangs unmoving in the street long enough for the hero to&nbsp;jump over two cars, grab his girlfriend,  point&nbsp;the wave&nbsp;out to her , and then get back to the safety of the library. Where said library safeness is apparently assured by shutting the door on the devastating tsunami. Where Ian Holm manages to look like a bad actor. Where the teenage hero's dad crosses a frozen state, causing the death of one of his team in the process, in order to find his son and, erm, well, that's it. Where a bunch of CGI wolves .... oh screw it, I can't go on.&nbsp;This and Batman and Robin are the only films I've ever wanted to walk out on (only my legendary tightness kept me in the seat to get whatever money's worth was possible).  &nbsp;  Looking in the  urlLink trailers section  of Empire's website offers a clue as to how this waste of film got such a generous rating. There's a whole bunch of interviews, clips, theme discussions etc; far more detail than any other film in the trailers list. Exclusive access, anyone?  &nbsp;  Next week:I uncover the conspiracy that led to Futurama being cancelled, and once again no one in their right mind gives a damn.   UPDATE:  urlLink Rory's  made me realise how ambiguous that last sentence was, so allow me to rephrase... &nbsp; Next week: I uncover the conspiracy that led to Futurama being cancelled, and once again it turns out that it's Fox fucking about with scheduling in order to show six episodes of  urlLink "World's Blankiest Blank"  back to back.  &nbsp; Um.&nbsp;And that's that. Guess I'll have to uncover something else next week instead. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tim's  urlLink back , and brings us&nbsp;a  urlLink video clip  that's well worth a look. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Coming soon, a blog "dedicated to watching the antics of The Daily Mail, a right-wing UK newspaper".  urlLink Apparently  they'll also be taking swipes at The Sun when required (daily, then). Looks like it'll be required reading. &nbsp; There'll be another link when the  urlLink Daily Mail Watch  launches for real. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of the problems with having a blog is the temptation to write a post whilst under the influence. Since starting this up I've been waiting for the Sunday morning when I wake up thinking "I think I might've...did I? Oh god, I did," and then logging on to read an illiterate, incoherent rant in place of the usual literate, incoherent rant.   And yesterday it happened. The post below about Richard Littlejohn was written at 2am, after a marvelously drunken barbecue. I think it came about after a depressing argument with a relative regarding Muslims and what should be done with them (his opinion was of the "boat and sink 'em" variety), and the relative merits of Christianity vs. Islam - and never mind that I can't stand either faith, apparently rejecting Christianity makes you a supporter of Islam.   Anyway. If the Littlejohn tribute is the worst drunken drivel that appears on this blog, I'll be happy - it ain't  that  bad. Too much snarky rhetoric, some appalling attempts at being funny, but nowhere near the level of crap I've posted on some other blogs whilst sailing on the Stella seas (I'll see if I can find them and post some links, they're truly cringeworthy). Phew.    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To quote a  urlLink splendid, splendid film :  &nbsp;  "Even a stopped clock gives the right time twice a day."  &nbsp;  Richard Littlejohn is the clock. Occasionally he's right. Most of the time he gets it so wrong that Tara Palmer Tomkinson would say "Sorry, Rich, you've committed a classic ad hominem fallacy there", and no-one would be surprised by Tara Palmer Tomkinson's sudden philosophical sharpness because even Barney the fucking Dinosaur would be onto him.  &nbsp;  Thanks to the Sun's "no archive material without payment" policy (god forbid that we should all start linking to the "Brits 45 Minutes From Dooooooom" headline) I'm afraid I can't bring you a direct list of Rich's greatest hits. However, I can link to an  urlLink article  from Johann Hari that details his appearance on the Littlejohn show. Note that this is the bloke (Rich, not Johann)&nbsp;who  urlLink doth protest  (you may need to register with Guardian Media):  &nbsp;   "People project their own prejudices on me - what they'd like me to be. I'm a convenient whipping boy. So I'm the 'homophobe' who had a whole column in favour of gay weddings, I'm the 'racist' who supported Trevor Phillips for London mayor."    and then:  &nbsp;   "Does anyone really give a monkey's about what happens in Rwanda? If the Mbongo tribe wants to wipe out the Mbingo tribe then as far as I am concerned that is entirely a matter for them."   &nbsp;  Cheers Rich. And his article about the Scottish bloke who refused to allow&nbsp;a gay couple&nbsp;to have a double bed summed the situation up as follows ("hilarious" Scottish accent removed so as to stop my reader splitting his sides): "Some do dogs. Some don't. We don't do dogs." Simple as that, apparently, auld Scottish fella just exercising his right to choose.&nbsp;Change the word "dogs"&nbsp;to "blacks", however, &nbsp;and Littlejohn's cheerful justification of it doesn't seem quite so acceptable.  &nbsp;  When Tim from Bloggerheads was still posting regularly, he (typically)  urlLink nailed it.  Richard Littlejohn, Queen of Denial, seemingly argued that even if the people held in Guantanamo were innocent, they should be kept there, because:  &nbsp;   "What if they decide to take out their frustration at being held in a prison camp for two years by driving a truck bomb into the Bullring shopping centre or detonating a Semtex waistcoat in Selfridges?"   &nbsp;  As Tim said, a real  urlLink "blood on the knob"  moment.  &nbsp;  This is the bloke who&nbsp;says that the liberal elite (whoever&nbsp;they are - do I count?) have no arguments, just slogans.&nbsp;Oh yes. So lets take a sample of Dicky's columns over the last year or so.  &nbsp;  "Hell in a handcart" (where we're going should that awful Toynbee woman get her way)  "Grinning Jackanapes" (crap name for Blair that didn't catch on, bless him for trying)  "Damien" (nasty nickname for a  baby )  "Wicked Witch" (nickname for Blair's wife)  "Guardianista" (nickname for people who don't term&nbsp;minorities as the "Mbingo tribe")  "You couldn't make it up"&nbsp;(except he does)  "They've only got slogans, not arguments" (possibly an exceedingly clever in-joke)  "Buggeryarsebanditfudgepackershirtliftermygodtheperversionofitallwhat!" (I may not have quite accurately quoted that one, but it's pretty much the conclusion of every single column the man writes.)&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Did I say Richard Littlejohn was a clock?&nbsp;That's with a silent&nbsp;L, of course.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   *  ok, a hatchet job.    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phew, haven't had access to the internet since Wednesday, the withdrawal symptoms having been agonising. &nbsp; Bloody NTL and their bloody broadband connections, don't they know I'm trying to change the world one post at a time? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's that  urlLink speech by Douglas Adams  that I mentioned the other day. It's worth reading the whole thing - naturally; it's Douglas Adams - but here's the relevant part:   "In the case of an idea, if we think ‘Here is an idea that is protected by holiness or sanctity’, what does it mean? Why should it be that it’s perfectly legitimate to support the Labour party or the Conservative party, Republicans or Democrats, this model of economics versus that, Macintosh instead of Windows, but to have an opinion about how the Universe began, about who created the Universe, no, that’s holy? What does that mean? Why do we ring-fence that for any other reason other than that we’ve just got used to doing so? There’s no other reason at all, it’s just one of those things that crept into being and once that loop gets going it’s very, very powerful." 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anthony Cox makes an excellent point over at  urlLink Black Triangle :   "The fact that  urlLink Polly Toynbee  was voted "Most Islamophobic media personality" should be warning enough about the way any incitement to religious hatred laws will be used by vocal lobby groups. It will be used to close down debate and silence criticism."   Polly Toynbee? Come again? She's a secular, atheist liberal, hostile to all religions, and with good reason. Presumably at some point she's made some kind of (no doubt well-judged, unarguable) criticism of Islam, thus earning her a place alongside Nick "BNP" Griffin.  Fair enough, I look forward to my 2005 nomination as Most Islamophobic Blogger (10 Readers or Less category). 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One more to scratch off the card...  Visiting a relative in hospital today, got talking to an old cockney couple.  Her: "The Krays might've been cruel, but they loved their mum!" Him: "And I'll tell you what, there weren't no mugging of old ladies when Ronnie and Reggie ran the place. You never locked your front door, neither..."  All I need now is coal-encrusted Yorkshireman with a whippet and talk of t'pit, and I've got a full house.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's a blinder in the opinion pages of today's Grauniad, about that charming fellow Yusuf al-Qaradawi. Step forward  urlLink Sohaib Saeed :   "For a person who does not believe in God, the concept of martyrdom may remain incomprehensible. A question such as that over the rights and wrongs of suicide-bombing in Palestine can legitimately be approached from different angles. A jurist like Mr Qaradawi is required to draw conclusions about its status within Islamic law - his comments are made in the context of a debate about the interpretation of Islamic texts...  ...Islam's negative view on homosexual relations is not unique, it is common to western religions. Muslims have not abandoned the truth to please liberal fundamentalists...  ...Again, when Mr Qaradawi has discussed homosexuality it has been about weighing up different interpretations of Muslim tradition."   We don't understand suicide-bombing, it seems, because we're atheists. We can't even debate the point, because it's being argued within the context of a bloody work of fiction. We'd have to go all the way back to debating belief in God before we could even begin to talk about anything else. As for homosexuals, the argument seems to run "ahahaha! You do it too!" And pointing out that we disagree with Western religions as well would most likely just bring us back to "For a person who does not believe in God, the concept..." etc etc. And note that he talks about taking things in context, then pulls out the idea that to accept homosexuality is to abandon the  truth . It's probably God's truth, or something.  Still, he does say one thing I can agree with, towards the end of the article:   "The freedom of expression enjoyed in the UK is a source of pride, and should encourage debate between cultures. If people have criticisms of Islam, they should feel free to raise them in appropriate times and places."   Damn right - yes, Blunkett, I'm looking at you.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I first read about David Blunkett's latest  urlLink lurch into fascism  (hope nobody here's allergic to hyperbole) my initial reaction was a shrug and a "meh". But the more I hear about it, the more alarming it sounds.  Read these:   urlLink Butterflies and Wheels   urlLink The Independent   urlLink Johann Hari   urlLink Anthony Cox   And  urlLink this  by Polly Toynbee, from the last time Blunkett tried to get this through.  It was the piece by Butterflies and Wheels that first made me sit up and take notice - regarding Blunkett's appearance on the Today programme (I haven't listened to it myself because it's a Real Player file, and I won't have that thing on my computer. Won't have it, I tell you!). To quote Ophelia Benson:   "He wants unity and community and tolerance, and he doesn't want us expressing strong opinions about religion if they might get in the way of unity. Of course, we're allowed to express opinions about religion - as long as they're sensible."   We can express opinions about religion as long as they're sensible, can we, Dave? No danger of misunderstanding or dodgy interpretation there! To hell with freedom of speech, now everyone's got to be sensible. Fine by me - how sensible is the opinion that a virgin, impregnated by a ghost who was also the creator, gave birth to the son of God? Or the opinion that the earth is around 6,000 years old? How fucking sensible is the opinion that 72 virgins await a martyr in paradise? That women are subordinate to men? That homosexuals should be put to death? That September 11th happened because  urlLink God had removed his protection  from the US thanks to those eeeevil queers, secularists and baby-killers?  But religion must be protected, because it's special, it's spiritual, it's  precioussss . Why do we draw a ring around religion to prevent it being questioned? Because it wouldn't last five minutes in a straight fight with logic and reason.  Maybe my first reaction will be the right one. Perhaps all this is worth is a shrug and a "meh". I hope so. But just in case my point has been lost in this otherwise subtle and balanced post, let me state again - religion is utter tripe, and David Blunkett can go sanctify himself.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A current hot topic is Michael Moore and his latest effort,  urlLink Fahrenheit 9/11 . It's being discussed at  urlLink Crooked Timber ,  urlLink Butterflies and Wheels ,  urlLink Harry's Place  and  urlLink Washington Monthly , to name but the tiniest fraction.  Personally, I moved pretty quickly from being an real fan of Moore (here's a guy stickin' to the man!), to being vaguely wary (the more I learned about him, the less trustworthy he seemed to be), to feeling downright betrayed (his constant fudging of facts was making the Left look foolish). Now he's kind of growing on me again, although a large part of that might be because this is the US election year, and anyone who helps to get Dubya out of the White House gets a free pass from me.  Plus if it wasn't for him, I most likely wouldn't be interested in politics in the first place.  urlLink Stef  and his missus got me  urlLink Stupid White Men  for Christmas a couple of years ago, and I lapped it up. Looking back on it, sure, it's a real My First Politics polemic, not the sort of place you go for nuanced argument. But it got me interested, got me active, and it's (probably) done the same for millions of others. And that's A Good Thing.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had to change the look of this place. Couldn't see a damn thing, the links were practically unreadable. As is much of the content, but I can't blame Blogger for that.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Guardian's  urlLink leader  has a piece today about Dr. Jeffrey John, the gay priest who was supposed to become a bishop last year, but was forced to step down because his cheerfully unrepentant attitude wasn't good enough for the more conservative god-botherers (presumably they were after some sort of "truly I do regret that I partook in the sinful perversion of buggery, O foul and unnatural act of degradation!" with full accompaniment of hand-wringing and self-loathing). He's been made Dean of St. Albans Cathedral instead. Good for him.  Still - and bear with me on this one - I sometimes think I'd prefer it if homosexuals weren't accepted by the Church at all. Either it's the word of God, or it's not,  urlLink right ? And they could ban their members from eating shellfish, and sell their daughters into slavery, and grow their hair around the temples, and put to death anyone who works on the Sabbath. And then they'd swiftly be shown up as out-of-date fools and everyone would be atheist and we'd all be happy. Well, I would, anyway.  But instead they shift and change and modernise, clipping away the bits that don't fly in modern society, talking up the touchy-feely Jesus parts, claiming it's a metaphor if something is really whacko and so on - adapt and survive tactics.  Deluded though they may be, at least the wingnuts are consistent.  P.S. Some of my favourite articles about religion were written by Richard Dawkins. Anyone who's never read his articles "Time to Stand Up" and "Dolly and the Cloth-heads" should  urlLink check them out . 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With a hat tip to  urlLink Norman Geras , I bring you  urlLink Colin's Movie Monologue Page . Some favourites:   urlLink General Ripper's fears about children's ice cream.   urlLink Sergeant Hartman welcoming the recruits to boot camp.   urlLink The Holy Hand Grenade!   urlLink Jules tryin' real hard to be the shepherd.   urlLink Brown M&Ms  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Bloody hell , I bet I stopped reading before you did. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been a bit light on bloggage recently - I rejoined the ranks of the gainfully employed last week and I've spent some time settling in before continuing my mission to abuse the company internet on an almost legendary scale.  Anyway. It's my 26th birthday today, and in less than two hours I'll be off to get blisteringly drunk. Hurray! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's a great article in this month's  urlLink Total Film  about the "Video Nasties" hysteria of the 80s. You know, the likes of  urlLink Cannibal Holocaust ,  urlLink Zombie Flesh-Eaters  and  urlLink I Spit on Your Grave  that had the Defenders of Our Nation's Morals running round in circles and flapping their hands, and that meant true classics like  urlLink The Evil Dead  and  urlLink The Texas Chainsaw Massacre  got swept up in the net and banned for years.  The article contained a choice selection of quotes from  urlLink our favourite scaremonger :   "Are we insane?"   "Turn back this tide of degenerate filth!"   "Are we bent on rotting our society from within?"   "How many more women will savaged and defiled by youths weaned on a diet of rape videos?"   "Ban These Sadist Videos!"   and the crowning glory:   "Rape Of Our Children's Minds!"     Glorious, absolutely top notch. I reckon the headline writers must get bonuses based on hysteria levels - Princess Di-related stuff is taken as part of the standard wage, although anything to do with a conspiracy to murder her might warrant an extra 100 notes. Health scares and single mothers get 500 quid. Asylum seekers and the latest New Labour attempt to destroy society as we know it earns the mouth-foamer a cool grand. And computers, the internet, video games and movies? The sky's the limit, I'll bet the creator of  "Rape of Our Children's Minds!"  was able to quit the next day, to spend a happy retirement knocking off ten letters a week to his old employer lamenting the day capital punishment was abolished. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>