<Blog>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Big event scheduled.  For Friday.  I will be shopping for groceries.  Its not an ending of the world event, but its a very important thing for me.  For the first time in a long while I will be shopping for someone else besides myself.  I think a list is in order.  Kinda a list, I don't want to be too organized... half the fun of shopping for food is the suprise.  Maybe I should just do minimal shopping.  I mean rachel is coming in a little over two weeks; I should go with her to the store for the food she wants.  Sometimes... I get sooooo excited I want everything to be perfect.  As Domino would say.... Purrrrrrr-fect 
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Marlow and Humu fish met for the first time June 4th.  The meeting went well I think, after all Marlow is a cat and humu is a... fish.  They had talked over the internet for a long time before that, and Marlow was pretty sure that he wouldn't eat humu fish.  The humu fish jumped out of her tank and gave marlow a hug, a wet sloppy fishy hug but marlow loved it.  He had never been hugged by a fish before.  He knew that coming to Kansas was one of the best things that he has done.  It's been almost a week since Marlow has seen the humu fish, and he was missing her terribly.  He went back home and meowed... and meowed... and said meow many more times till Domino (his cat roomate that hates him) jumped off the couch and tried to hit Marlow with his cat claws.  Marlow didn't care tho, he just wanted to see the humu fish again.  In his kitty mind he had planned out the things they could do if she was here.. they would go to the ocean and walk/swim in the surf.  Sand would get inbetween Marlow's claws and in his fur but it would be so great.  Humu fish could swim till she was tired then Marlow would gently take her to the Motel room and place her in her tank.  Later that night they would go out to eat at a resturant that serves no seafood... Humu fish likes to catch her own fish to eat, she doesn't like the idea that a fisherman threw nets down and grabbed her prey like kelp.  Marlow remembers his trips to the beach, all 27 of them.  He thinks of his favorite places to go, then he imagines the Humu fish next to him.  He is allowed to do this since he has met her in real life.  It doesn't mean she is really next to him, or that he is even at the beach.  He is sitting alone in his house, looking out the window, Meowing at the grass covered in water mist and gently whispered to by the wind.
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I decided to play a little "Counter Strike", an old First Person Shooter that has been around for a while and sucked up more of my time then anything else over the past 4 years.  While on I got a message from a friend I know in oregon, he will be in town this weekend.  The thing is, I haven't been too social the past year... Im afraid I will get all excited and want to play with my new friend and jump up and down and...  Oh.  I crushed him.  *sniff*  Sorry friend.  Well, I hope it doesn't go that bad, I will be cooking the best steak ever tonight, since Friday night is officially "Steak Night."  I'm thinking of something I know for the wine, like BV Coastal.   
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink My old blog , but I'm unsure if I will be moving in or not.  Must have time to think.  And apply for a new job.  Yes, think and job.  Job and think.  In the meantime, here are a few pictures of my cats:       
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Quitting smoking       Alot of good discussion,  which I like.  Living with a smoker  when your a non smoker is uncomfortable.  I want to help them  quit, but I don't want to drive them away.  Its not that big of an  issue yet, but I feel that in the future it will be a fine line I will  have to work at.      In other news, waffles and domino have met.  More details will be  forthcoming  urlLink on my Live Log City Blog .  
      
</post>


</Blog>