<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey, I've been kind of busy since Sunday. On Sunday I went to my grandpa's for a cookout, then I went to get my haircut, afterthat I went to my great grandma's. THEN I went to my grandma's. WOW, a lot in one day. And today I really didn't get a chance to go online. I went to the park and stuff.  Right now I'm just tired. Hopefully I'll post again tomorrow. BYe.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello, Well really haven't done nothing today. Been waking up around ten each morning :). I might go to the movies tonight, time permitting. But just been watching TV and going online. I think I'm just being lazy bacause I'm recovering from all the hard work from the school year. Hmmm, I don't know what I will be doing this weekend. I'll post again tomorrow. BYe.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I woke up at 10:20 and as usual went downstairs to watch a little TV. Then I came upstairs to go on the Internet. I've currently been online for 49 minutues. I don't know what I will be doing today. I think I might go pay my phone bill, other than that, watch TV  , go online. You can't even go outside because its raining and dark out. Oh well.  Later.  P.S. Oh yea! I'm going to watch the finals basketball game tonight. GO PISTONS!!!!  GAME UPDATE: The Pistons beat the Lakers by 20 points! And the Lakers got the lowest score ever in game three!!!! (Updated 10:54 p.m.)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On the last day of school a very close friend of mine that I've known since preschool and another friend went to Wendy's. Here are their pics:   urlLink    Here's the friend since preschool.&nbsp; urlLink      urlLink    Here's another friend in my Bio class.&nbsp; urlLink     We walked downtown to Wendy's and came back to school to hang out. Then all of a sudden this psycho crazy person comes and is yelling about seeing a roach's son!!!!   urlLink    Here's a crazy person that ran up to us telling us about a roach's son!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    ME at School.&nbsp; urlLink     This is me at school on the last day. On my next post I'll show the pics when some friends of mine go to Wendy's. Mmmmm Good.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>