<Blog>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           I used to have this argument with this girl from Bermuda, my friend in writing school.  It was the most simplistic argument - there were many other brilliant things being vetted and interpreted around us - but it was also fundamental.  And we were fundamental girls: both raised in paradisical climes with fathers who owned small, honest businesses, the kind which will soon be obsolete.  We grew up not wearing many clothes and not paying attention to the time, and we were good girls who needed to answer basic, persistent questions first, before we could accept luxurious debates on Cubist fiction.  This argument I think is our necessary division, we stand at each other from either side, and that's where our happy friction comes from, our bite.  What she says is that to be a writer, a real writer, one must publish.        We never decided on how to frame what we meant by "real", did that mean on the cover of Poets & Writer's?  Three year contracts with excellent foreign rights? Visiting positions at good schools?  Or was it a more discreet situation, a home in Bangor and another on the Key, low-profiledom, a following, a stylish Underwood?  Did "real" mean established? Easily referenced by all, or known only by the inner sanctum, the small coterie of agents and publishers and pressers and scholars and professors in Manhattan?  These were all literal attributes, and could not be more "real".  But real to whom?  The individual reader, the population, the bookstore, the audience, the agent, the planet?  Or real to the writer herself?  The writer's parents?  "Real" for us relied too much on proof, or was the same thing entirely.      My view was and is the opposite.  A writer is really a writer if she writes, publication be damned.  To this my friend said that her third cousin wrote sweet, banal, rhyming poems, pages and pages, nearly every day.  All told, the cousin wrote more than my friend did.  Did that make her a real writer?  This is the trouble with my position.  It's too democratic, benign, idealized.  It's also strident and unforgiving: if I didn't write for a week, and my friends did, I was less a writer than they were.  This was severe, but it did feel true.  If I believe that writing is a practice, that it's an effort and that most of the work I love only comes out with a lot of piss, then what I believ is something fairly earthy and evidential.  If you write, eventually something good will happen, but the good part is not what makes you a writer.  The writing part, the action, qualifies.  That's it.        This does not sit with my friend, and sometimes it does not sit with me.  But I think it can be true, or that it's true enough.  Publication is too arbitrary a crown.  They must have their own maxims: if there's a new voice, an original something that deserves to be published, we will eventually find it.        I am a terrible writer by my friend's standards.  I have been published a few times, it's true, but nothing has really come of it except a lingering vanity to see my words in print.  I have been rejected many, many times, and I have left New York.  I don't pay enough attention to the writing season, do not mark the contest deadlines on my calendar, do not write full time, or travel for inspiration, or live rent to rent anymore.  When I don't look like a writer to myself, I wonder who I am.  In the suburban world, as expected, writers have gone the way of poets, into marketing.  Yet I am back in a state of grace, where and how I wrote before New York, the famous writing school, the literati parties, the readings, the pressure, the competition, which were all right and good, but did not make me a writer, either.    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>