<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a packrat to the extreme. Until recently I had every single paper from every single class from the time I started learning how to write the letter A until my last college class. I always had one excuse or another to hang on to box after box of paperwork and books. Last year, no excuse was great enough ... I was getting married and moving into a new house and all of that stuff just wouldn't fit. So I threw 98% of it away. The 2% of the things that I kept were from classes and teachers that I adored with the thought in the back of my mind that one day I might have to teach a class and I knew I wouldn't be able to do it quite as well without the guidance of a few of my favorite teachers. Now, I was a business major with hopes of starting my own business or working at some large advertising firm or owning my own art gallery... why would I ever dream of teaching?  It’s for every lousy teacher that I have ever had in my life... If I had just one fabulous English teacher maybe I would know how to spell or catch grammar mistakes or if I had one creative history teacher maybe I would be a history buff like my husband. Knowing that I would have the ability to be a big influence in today’s youth ... yea, I know it's cheesy but I'm worried about the next generation and this is the most active way I know to try and give them something to be inspired by.  Currently, I’m trying to find a job in this small provincial backwards town of hell that I must call home (we tried the moving thing and failed). There are no big advertising firms or corporations that need a creative eye, no nonprofit organizations with enough organization to hire a manager or an assistant. This city bites.    Finally, I got a lead by a very close friend of the family who used to be a teacher. She came up with a brilliant idea … teaching. Yes, I don’t have a teaching certificate but the district is so desperate for teachers  (300 to be exact) that they are willing to accept anyone with drive and a degree. The wheels in my head start turning … I would finally need those papers that I saved for so long … I will finally get to make some sort of a difference.  I’m determined to be the best Fine Arts, Computer Science, or Algebra teacher …..    I’m turning in my application this week … wish me luck!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello all .... Like my husband brian I had to join the blog world. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>