<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We Gotta make this movie it will be awesome i'll bet the people around here would love to say bush is a good president aye' god it will be sooooo cool you gotta get this camera Ursula ohh mow im all excited yay. and Moore is my hero BTW we could wear offenseve t-shrits and stuff like that and bring uo racy subjects i cannot wait
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You gotta check this out www.bushcalendar.com bush can't even speak engalish (misspelling is a joke) oh and by the way and I qoute "Hydroelectric power will greatly reduce Greenhouse Gas Emmisions" 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have an idea. (Yes, be afraid.) My idea is this: we should make a documentary, a la Michael Moore. We could do it over the summer! All we'd need would be a digital video camera; there's people all over we could interview, and we could focus on ignorance. You know—the reason these people are so biased is because they're uninformed.  We could map out an interview, figure out what questions to ask, and go talk to neighbors and friends and random people at the D&B. Eh?  We could edit and cut and stick it all together on my primitive vid editing program. And then we could...! Well, I don't know what we'd do then. We could mail a copy to Michael Moore, I guess. And have copies to show to our kids and brag about.  What do you think? It would be fun, and we could make a lot of people mad!  Also I get the feeling that I'm going to be really bored this summer.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wanna read a delightfully twisted web comic? It mocks conservatives without mercy, and I think we can all relate to the pink-haired heroine who steps back, looks at the world, and says "This is f*cked up." It's how I imagine South Park might be, only I hardly ever watch TV, so anyway...   urlLink Clicky. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The time thank you is purposely wrong it is Kuala Lumper's time zone I had to do sorry for any inconveince nothing else to say goodbye (gonna test this link thing)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The date is wrong. If you did not notice. I actually posted at 3:26 pm. After school. Fix it someone.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's something messed-up: the schools that score lowest on tests are given the least money. That means lower salaries for the teachers and less books for us. Whose idea was that? Three guesses. He has effectively found a way to take money away from the schools who need it most. No Child Left Behind... unless they can't afford it.  So do well on the EOGs, guys. Our teachers need us.  (A little aside: they're starting a Charter school in Watauga for "gifted" children. That means all the rich white kids. Which means the other schools' averages will go down. Which means even less money for them! Also a form of segregation: upper class kids away from lower class kids. This way they will be totally unprepared for the real world. Of course! It's brilliant!)  I tend to be sarcastic when I'm angry.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pisses me off. Plus, nobody  cares  about the Iraqis. The mindset is like "Well, what did they expect?" GYAH! But then they hear about the waaaay smaller amount of Americans and then they're all "How horrible!" Pissedpissedpissed.  Ah... did you really post that at 3 in the morning, or has Garrett not figured out how to put us in Eastern yet?  Check  urlLink this  out. It's Susumu Hirasawa, a Japanese musician. This is his site against the Iraqi war. You can download a couple of really beautiful/sad songs. (Also check out his main site, there is more mp3 goodness to be found there.) Of course, it is in Japanese, but they have translations. Very pretty.  Maybe I should change my username to perpetually_pissed.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      5500 Iraqis and over 800 Americans have died and nobody gives a damn. I hate that. And you all heard about the wedding bombing in Iraq. 45 people died of all ages. But no. The U.S. government has to go further on than that and lie that, quote,"no children have died." Now this is getting even worse than I thought it would be. Our economy is down. WAY down. Gas is almost $2. Big company scandals are popping up everywhere. When is the this going to end? Lets hope that Bush does not get reelected.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't be hasty Ursula. Bush can still pull something out of his sleeve. What if he catches bin Laden? Then, I am moving to Germany. Maybe I should do that anyway. I hope to God that Bush does not get re-elected. I wish we could take over the U.S. Government. Then maybe we will not be a trillion dollars in debt.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good news, lads! Bush's approval rating is at an all-time low (42%). Any candidate with approval this low in May has ultimately lost. So, unless he can think of something clever —not likely, considering his  urlLink IQ —he's sunk.  Hahaha.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My newly installed bush buck spender counter thingy magiger is making people who love bush gasp and say "we don't have that much money" and people of low intelligence say "well that thingy goes up awful fast 'aye god" well both are true yet these same people support the war in Iraq i've said it before America is based upon hypocrisy oh well. (thought provoking end)
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Massacre? Being a bit melodramatic there, G. But I agree, that is scary.  Wanna see something  urlLink scarier?   I think this is what caused my severe case of depression this afternoon. (I took off—I was about a mile away from home before I cooled down. And then I had to walk back in the rain. Ugh.)  Yuk, yuk, yuk. I am royally pissed. The fact that I haven't even  started  my math homework doesn't help, either.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      since bush took office in 2000: NC state of state facts  ~ 34418 are unemployed  ~ 37600 lost unemployment benefits  ~ 159400 manufacturing jobs have been lost  ~ 50% of NC taxpayers will recieve less than 100 dollars because of new bush tax-cut plan  ~ 1368000 have no healh insurance up 16.7% under bush ~ 222800 are worse off with new bush medicare plan    Stop this massacre vote Kerry in 2004 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys, if you hate bush you gotta go see this movie! Michael Moore is coming out with a new socical critic film it will be awesome, it's called fahrenheight 9/11 but Disney will produce it never fear it will not be long , regards
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      According to some reliable sources Mr. Bush has now ordered 783 Americans to die for what??? for oil and only oil seems odd that you would kill all those Americans instead of just well coming up with an alternate energy source we have these really smart people called SCIENTIST they think about these things unlike you(bush) who just likes to see explosions on CNN. Death for your entertainment isn't it? 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, now for a real post. This doesn't have much to do with politics, but I couldn't resist linking to   urlLink this   Must.... rub...... bald man's...... head!  Tee hee. What an idiot.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So let me get this straight.... the sole purpose of this blog is Bush-bashing?  YES!  Sorry it took me so  long to join. The invitation had a link in it, so it was filtered with the junk mail.  About the title? Less is more. I think Beat Around The Bush is sufficient. (Dude. I just used the word 'sufficient' in an everyday activity. Cool.)  Dunno where Jonathan is. He hasn't updated the other blogs recently, sooooo yeah.  Oh, Garrett? Try to use those lovely spelling and grammar skills they teach you in school. It makes you look smarter. And if you throw in the word 'sufficient',  well .  Oh, and... Bush sucks.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've repeatedly ask Ursula and Jonathan to join in my bush bashing blog but noooo they've got better things to do don't they curses arghh and grrr an them 115 days till elections GO KERRY  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once upon a time in a land far away; a land called "America" a land that was in dismay. Now this land boys and girls was powerful, very powerful but it's new ruler called a President was, well... an idiot we handed this very powerful country to a complete idiot. why? called most Americans why they ask, why boys and girls would you hand such a country to a fool. Well I plan to eventually find out..... (Cliff-hanger)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, first thing's first:  squeeeeeeeeeeee!   I went all the way to Johnson City just to see F911 and  it was worth it!  Michael Moore managed to combine fact, satire, and emotion into an explosive bundle of socio-political commentary. Now I am horrified, saddened, and having random fits of hysterical giggles. But predominantly? I'm pissed off.  Without giving away the movie, let me tell you the gist: Moore will focus on the emotions of soldiers and civilians in Iraq, then the horror of actual battles, and then Bush and his minions coldly and calmly saying that all this is justified. And what Moore movie would be complete without one of Mike's stunts? In this case, he borrows an ice cream truck and rides around Capital Hill, reading the Patriot Act over a megaphone (seeing as nobody bothered to read it before they passed it).  I laughed. I cried. I 'grrr'-ed. And you will too, when you see it.  PS: Sorry we couldn't give you guys rides, but they were doing ID checks, so we might not have gotten in anyway. FIND A WAY TO SEE IT.  PPS: Michael Moore is my hero.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No,  urlLink this'n . Idn't it great?
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Which movie poster?  Or is there only one?  Is it the one with the envelope (that you're talking about)? It's R because of Violent and Disturbing Images and for Language.  I don't get with the language...I mean, really.  Y'know?  But some things are disturbing...oh well, have fun.  I didn't warn you. Nice to see you're alive and well, Shine dearest.  So glad you haven't died on me...I would be so very sad, and lonely, and depressed...*sniffsobsniff* Of course you're a genius, G.  Who isn't?
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, here's what's up. We say that we are exchange students from Canada. Nobody will care if 4 Canadians get in to see a movie, we can slip by all unnoticed likeish. Im a genius by the way 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need your email to join my blog. But don't post it. If anybody knows what it is send it to my email. Thank you for your cooperation.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THIER NOT SHOWING MOORE INSTANT CLASSIC IN BOONE U, WE NEED THAT RIDE HELPS US AND WE ARE FOREVER IN YOUR DEBT!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should have told you this, but I was in D.C. for 10 days for aleadership conference, wich, by the way, was great. Ursula knows what it is. Welcome Jessica. It is a pleasure to have you on this blog, and I definitely know you. And your mom. She helps the Education Foundation, right? My parents are there too. Garrett. Your blog is catchinging up to mine, but as time speeds on to elections, it is probably more important. Love you to G. Meg, I owe I you a special apology, for I haven't been here and I am not ignoring you. It has taken me a whole night to get up to date with the blogs. Were still going to Germany, but I'm running out of ideas of where and what to do there. Well, now I have to go to soccer camp. So, see you all later.  P.S. U, why did you gie me the reins? Thank you anyway. And apoligies to all.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yayness! There're ads for Fahrenheit 9-11 on TV! We must go see it on the opening day!  ...If they don't show it here, we can always go to Charlotte or something. My parents would totally take us, they wanna see it too. *grin* My parents are too cool.  If you guys haven't seen the trailer yet, you can find it on Michael Moore's website. At one point he tries to get Congress blokes to send their children to Iraq to fight. I don't know what the answers are going to be, but they will be funny. Or at least make us angry. Or both.  Bowling for Columbine is like that too. Mike and two survivors of the Columbine shootings went to K-mart and single-handedly stopped them selling ammunition. It was great. I'm not sure I've seen the whole thing, and I'm not sure I could handle it. Not anymore.  Blerg. Now I'm depressed. Just promise you'll see F 9-11, okay guys?  It will rock.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you all are like me, you won't read all of the article thing, but this is really...kind of sad, in a infuriating sort of way.  "As unbelievable as it may sound, the combined wealth of the world's seven richest people could end world poverty. According to United Nations Human Development Report, $80 billion could pay for access to basic social services and eradicate poverty. The net wealth of ten billionaires is worth 1.5 times the combined national income of the 48 least developed countries."  That was on page six (how many pages  are  there?), so if you want to read everything else...yeah, go ahead.  It's very interesting,  I  think.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't actually read all of it, I kind of skimmed, so it might not all be exactly relevant.  It's not specifically about Bush, more about why America is very...pointless, maybe?  Bad, anyway.  But there was a bit on page...um, 5 maybe about 1% of the population controlling like 19% of the nation's wealth or something...yeah, I hardly read any of it.  It's too early to learn...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel all left out.  How come all the communication happens when I'm gone, and then I come back, and it's all...y'know.  I feel all unloved.  You'd think I'd be used to it, going to Parkway and all that...people tell me I have no life all the time, and that I'm ugly and have no friends and should go live in a hole.  After a while it stops hurting--and then it does again.  I hate...them.  The It people.  You were wrong, G, I'm not loved.  By these people here.  You probably know nothing about the It people, it's no secret that they hate me.  But these people just keep avoiding me.  Except I am admin to the TABASCO one now, and all...okay, Ursula doesn't hate me.  And G, you don't, do you?  And I don't know--Jessica, do you hate me?  But Shine does, don't you Shine?  You never talk to me anymore...don't you care?  All the good times we had...they were just a joke for you, weren't they?  All that talk of Germany, all lies, every bit.  I knew it.  You were wrong, G, and I don't appreciate it at all.  Not a bit.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Garrett told me you were the "owner" of the "Weird World" blogspot thing, and I was wondering if you might be so kind as to invite me to that page to be able to blog and comment...Thanks sooo much if you can...  Muchas Gracius, (sp?) ~*!*Jessica*!*~
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me as in the owner of this blog&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have any of you ever heard of a newspaper-type thing called the "Funny Times"?  I think it might actually be called "We're Living In FUNNY TIMES".  It's very very very hilarious, my Dad gets it and it's always hilarious.  Wicked funny, it bashes Bush, makes fun of things people do, it's chunked full of comics.  Check it out sometime...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Garrett says to introduce myself to his "home dogs".  So I am introducing myself (I think :-/) Yea my name's Jessica, uhh I can't wait until high school, middle school sucks is my final conclusion about things.  It's really late, it's almost 1 AM and I almost spelled late as latte...what I need right now (haha).  I need sleep is my other conclusion about life...so maybe I'll tell all of you more when I'm actually awake...I'm out...later!  o btw jonathon i know u...space camp, beach trip, algebra contest...um ursula were u in any of those? um i know u from speak outs and soccer a loooong time ago but idk if u remember me or not...sry for the IM lango...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone this is Jessica she is a liberal democrat who hates bush. Enough said right 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following is an essay by Michael Moore:    Patriot Act: What it is   On October 26, 2001, just six weeks after the devastation on September 11, Congress passed the USA Patriot Act. Ashcroft and his cronies wasted no time in attempting to further their agenda at the expense of a traumatized nation. USA Patriot is an acronym for "Uniting and Strengthening America by Providing Appropriate Tools Required to Intercept and Obstruct Terrorism", but all that elaborate language does not succeed in hiding the dangerous nature of the document.   So just what does the Patriot Act give the Bush administration the right to do? Well, for starters, it allows the FBI to monitor everything from e-mail to medical records to library accounts, providing frightening access to once private information. They can now legally wiretap phones, break into homes and offices, and access financial records without probable cause.   The Patriot Act broadens terrorism to include "domestic terrorism" which could potentially be used to target activist groups within the country speaking out against Bush's treacherous deeds.   The Patriot Act also disregards attorney-client privilege and authorizes government surveillance of previously confidential discussions.   Immigrants can be detained indefinitely based on suspicion alone, and the Patriot Act aids the excessive amounts of deportations that are taking place.   Calling this the Patriot Act is quite a dangerous action within itself, because the implication follows: if you speak against the Patriot Act, well, you sure aren't being a good citizen in our country's time of need. When Bush labels his actions as the model of patriotism, he then classifies all dissent as un-American. While this may be comforting to him, it is actually an insult to patriotism. Protecting the Constitution and the Bill of Rights demonstrates a great respect for the government of this country and the rights of its citizens, and that sounds downright patriotic.   Read the text of the Patriot Act here.    Patriot II: What it is   It's not over yet. Currently, the Justice Department is working on the Domestic Security Enhancement Act, an extension of the Patriot Act that has been dubbed "Patriot II". Perhaps one of the most dangerous aspects of this bill would grant the government the right to detain someone indefinitely without ever disclosing their identity, allowing the person to ultimately disappear. It would also broaden local police's ability to spy on "terrorist" groups, including domestic religious and political organizations. The government could take sweeping "anti-terrorist" action, like obtaining an individual's financial and library records without a warrant and allowing wiretaps without a court order. How else could this affect you? Well, if you engage in civil disobedience, the government would have the right to strip you of your citizenship! Had enough? Stop this act before it starts!   You can read more about Patriot Act II, and the text of the proposed act at the Center for Public Integrity or through the ACLU.   Take Action!   Representative Bernie Sanders, a Vermont Independent, has proposed a bill that would revoke the sections of the Patriot Act that allow the government to invade your privacy at bookstores and libraries. The bill is currently stuck in committee, despite having 141 co-sponsors. For an explanation of the bill, visit the ACLU. E-mail the Judiciary Committee's Subcommittee on Crime, Terrorism, and Homeland Security and put pressure on them to push this bill forward. Also, contact your Representatives and tell them to sign on as co-sponsors to the bill if they have not already. For a list and description of all pending anti-Patriot Act legislation, check here.   Check here for information on how to stop the NEW Patriot Act before it gets off the ground. Demand an end to the elimination of civil liberties masked as anti-terror legislation!     Please excuse the unworking links it is very late and i don't want to worry about them to outradged to type goodbye 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You found it in your hearts to blog, on my blog of all places. If I might quote Ursula: Joy Rapture Ect. I would also like to give my regards to Former President Reagen and his family, I don't know how he ran the country but death is bad period.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reagan died. It was not a surprise at all. He was 93 and had alzheimerx disease for 10 years. Don't get me wrong. He might have been a good guy but I wouldn't know since I wasn't  alive then.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone sent me something about how being Republican is hereditary and now I can't find it.  If anyone knows what I'm talking about, say aye.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      at joining this blog.  See, who says I don't have friends who care? *cough*Lison*cough*  Just because people from Mabel (can't say "at" Mabel anymore, can I?) are cooler than people from Parkway... So anyway.  How is our "friend" the Prime Idiot today?
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lo, and behold. shine's meaningless nasty blog is larger than mine arghness
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Ok we  gotta  do this.&nbsp; we must go protest the war next to wendys in boone. im serious whadda you think  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, it's kind of weird at first, but once you get to the end you'll see what I'm talking about.  It's hilarious, and I really think G would like it, as it's his hero.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Conservatives are absolutley howling about F 9/11, go to any of the big news sites and you can read 100 inteveiws with Republicans claiming that all of Moore's movie is lies. So sometime last week Moore issued a challenge: If any one person can find a single factual error he will award them with 10,000 dollars. Sweet beyond all reason 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just the victim of some mad phone survey telling me that if I haven't picked someone to vote for for senator to please consider some mad Republican Conservative--'the smart choice', I think the recorded message said.  Well, he was quite polite about it, but I kind of can't vote.  Hmm, I wonder if I totally screwed up the survey by pressing 6 for Undecided.  I am a minor, you know.  This could completely upset the democratic process.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If somthing ever possess you to sign-up for John Kerry's mailing list DON'T and i repeat DON'T not that his cause is bad but getting 10 emails a day from him is 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kerry picked Edwards. Kerry picked Edwards. This is so awesome. Most of us were expecting it though. Still, it is cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jessica has disappeared.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad said that he thinks they're supposed to be showing F 9/11 tonight somewhere in Boone, and I looked through the Wed Democrat, but of course didn't find anything, anyone have any info they'd like to share about this?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've not posted here since June 17, I therefore do apologize for any inconvenience. Oh do you like my techlike new links and banners and colors. The banners largely due to the very fast speaking of Abe at 3rd lunch. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had Jenna get me some buttons, so I have one for Shine and one for G.  I didn't get Ursula or Jessica any because I only had three dollars with me at the time, and the ones she got I think Shine and G might like better than Ursula or Jessica might, especially as I don't know Jessica and she's not exactly super-communicative is she?  Sorry though.  Maybe some other time.  So next time I see either of you I'll have to give them to you.  I really think you'll like them, and if you don't, um, give it to Ursula or Jessica or something. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>