<Blog>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After browsing through TODAY, i made a very important decision. Never trust movie critics! Conclusion: Well, simply because that particular audience who watched the movie and find it boring and gave a low rating, it doesn't mean that I will find it boring too! and there is simply more to watch and observe other than whether or not hallie berry is not that kind of sexy or how their outfit crings out the "shape"!  It's only when i watched the movie, before the critics can actually be published, that i truely enjoy the movie. If not, i will be bring a very reluctant mood into the cinema and come out saying, "it's not bad after all" or a very anticipating urge coming out with "it's not as facinating as expected!"  Maybe, that's got to do with my expectations for the movie. Nevertheless, don't ever read critics! Just buy yourself a ticket and a cup of pop corn (and of course the movie ticket! -_-) and sit yourself in a very comfortable position and ENJOY YOUR MOVIE! YEAH~!   theory behind this: when u read critics, there is already an image created in your brain, telling you what you are going to expect. And normally what you expect and what you experience are totally different! 
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Singapore Idol   Well, I watched first two episodes and something literally caught my attention, which raged me. What I have to say is this, if you know about Singapore Idol, you must have heard and watched America Idol; you must have know what exactly are judges anticipating; and what will make you qualify as a Singapore Idol.  Somehow, some went for the audition and became Singapore Idiots! Real Idiots!  If these idiots actually make a quick or brief glance through the nowadays idols, and get the definition of what an idol meant, then scram!!! We don’t need idols that can hula-hoop and sing at the same time! We don’t need singers that strip and sing at the same time! I have had enough of that irritating William Hung for the noise pollution he caused when my radio suddenly blasted his “she bangs” while studying…  Worst still, a lemon tree guy actually wanted to be Singapore’s version of William Hung?! Oh Please!!! Why are you so useless?? Why not have a bigger ambition rather than being a nuisance?! I’m just sick and tired of all these “potential wannabe William Hung”!!! See that wall in front of you? Well, don’t bang it! Bang all the walls you can find in your house except the one in front of you. Hopefully, it makes you wake up and face the reality!  Oh, by the way, this other TV program I watched yesterday… “ The Singapore Brainiest Kid ”! Oh my! I think the producers should have titled that “Brainiest Kid” the “Most arrogant cum haughty cum O.P. kid”!!! Fancy looking at her competitor with that you-will-lose-to-me-one-lah look, giving that who-cares snare, and that last word “I’m so sorry” when the host announced her as Singapore’s Brainiest Kid. Wow! It’s like, I’m so sorry, I’m cleverer than you. You know, I don’t mean to be cleverer than you… I just happen to be more intelligent! Oh I’m so sorry! I won the title… I meant to let you have it you know… but I’m force to be entitled the title, because it just happen that I am more brainy than you…. I’m so SORRY!!!  Eat shit la!  And one look at her attire, a black long plaited shirt, which looks like one in some granny’s closet, and a pink blouse, like those kind of working adult type! Yucks! What an insult to the colour “pink”, having you destroy the beauty of pink! Yeeks!!!!  Not to forget, she actually snatched that trophy from the winner last year. Yeah, snatched! No kidding! Oh no… is that the kind of what Singaporeans we are producing… I’m fainting!!!  Just don’t ever let me see her again… 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It’s Singapore 39th birthday!! HAPPY BIRTHDAY SINGAPORE!!! Belated of course, looking at the time and date now!  Well, just simply have this sudden urge to rattle about how much I love you Singapore, and how much I hate those Singaporeans how hate Singapore… Singapore has provided us with a very conducive environment. No to mention, we are living in a very peaceful place, where there is no war, riots, nor any prejudice or discrimination that is as serious as countries such as Afghanistan, where women have no rights. Yet, these hateful Singaporeans take them for granted.  I do admit, sometimes, the raise in taxes, the increase in transport fares are inconsiderate acts of the government, but sometimes I wonder, are these really the government’s fault to be blame? Or should we be pointing our finger at the transport companies which are monopolizing the transport market?  Well, nevertheless, I still love you Singapore!! Nothing, and nobody can stop me from loving you!!! Yeah~!!!  
      
</post>


</Blog>