<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      a note from Skotia...   Dere Mom, who can evre have a mom like you.  You are the best mom in the world!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This blog, for me, is incredibly difficult.  In the same sense I feel it is good for me as well.  I am always hesitant to let people know how I feel.  Obviously not many people read this and I should still feel safe.  I don't.  It makes me feel exposed.  One of my goals however is to let more people in.    Still...scary shit.  Yikes!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "Gotta kick at the darkness till it bleeds daylight."  Lovers in a Dangerous Time - Bruce Cockburn   "We cannot do great things, only small things with great love"   Mother Teresa
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mom, me and my Grandma at my graduation.&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    just me&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today when I showed up for my placement I knew my preceptor was not going to be there and I was to be paired with another nurse.  Well, that nurse called in sick and they could not find anyone to replace her.  So, it was all about me.  I had to be a real nurse today.   2 suppositories and a million pills later everyone is still alive.  Whew!  I can't pretend I didn't send up little prayers every now and then that nothing would go wrong.  But, I have to admit, it was a good ego boost.  Knowing I can do this job.  Maybe I will even make a bit of money at it eventually.   I feel so adult-like...weird.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is the kind of day that makes me want to stay outside all day.  I want to go kayaking, hiking, horseback riding....instead I am inside making banana muffins and trying to create order out of the chaos my house is in.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I graduate tomorrow.  Yay!!  I have been waiting for this day for an awfully long time.  I have a month left of consolidation and the provincials in september but this still feels great.  :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think if everyday every one of you who read my blog (keltie, pete listen up)say a prayer to the Great Car God for my car to work till July 19th it might happen.  I am counting on you!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A perfectly shitty day.  25 minutes to suck it up and put on 'happy mommy' face.  Can it be done?  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      28 more shifts to go before I am finished my placement.  I can hardly wait.  What I need is a hot tub a bottle of wine (well, more than one bottle) and a few days away from this insane existence I call life.  Some other stuff would be good too but we won't go into that here.    The end is near!!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Put on 'Sweet Home Alabama' by Lynyrd Skynyrd.  Loud.  Dance around.  There, doesn't that feel good?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay Pete...This is my blog.  I do hold you responsible for e-mailing me once in awhile and telling me what a difference this has made in your life and how extremely interesting it is.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Really that about sums up this entry.&nbsp; All I need to do for school is write my registration exam in september.&nbsp; Till then I am enjoying being with my kids and working.&nbsp; They are wonderful people and&nbsp;I love them.&nbsp; I know every mother probably feels like that but they are so unique and funny.&nbsp; I have missed being the kind of mom&nbsp;I always wanted to be.&nbsp; Now I am not so sure that is what would have made me happy.&nbsp; Now I just look forward to living my life as an example to them.&nbsp; Showing them how to be independent, have fun and help others less fortunate.&nbsp;  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes I get stuck on a certain song.&nbsp; Awhile ago it was John Mayer's "Your Body is a Wonderland".&nbsp; There have been a bunch more inbetween but right now it is Queen's "Radio Ga-Ga".&nbsp; This song rocks!!&nbsp; I will play the snot out of this song and dance around to it for probably about 2-3 weeks then hardly ever listen to it.&nbsp;   So... to get the true alannah experience play this song as loud as you can and sing along.&nbsp; Here are the lyrics&nbsp; urlLink http://www.kronawithleitner.at/lyrics/showtext.php/id/316 .&nbsp;  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Keltie has been bugging me to update my blog.&nbsp; Sadly, I don't have a heck of a lot to say.&nbsp; Hope you're happy Keltie.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I expect some amazing comments on this thought provoking entry. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes, in your life, you have to make decisions which can never be unmade.  There is always a lot of uncertainty which goes with that.  You wonder, 'Did I make the right decision?  Will I always regret this?'.  And then a day comes along which reaffirms that indeed you did make the right decision and your life is better for it.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a great day.  Woke up, took the kids to Tae Kwon Do.  Then we went to a pool party at their Oma and Opa's.  Then we went downtown and took in the Busker's Fire Show.  We are all exhausted and happy.    The best thing however happened on the way to the pool party.  I had to go to Loblaw's to pick up some fruit.  While I was there I decided to pick up some wine to take as well.  In Loblaw's little wine store I found what I needed and was chatting with the guy who worked there while my interac went through.  When it was done and I was walking away The guy called me back..."I don't want to seem weird or anything," he said, "but I had to tell you that you look very pretty."    Thank you Loblaws guy.  You made my day and put a smile on my face all day.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The Boyds love summer!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, at the facility where I am doing my placement, an amazing thing happened.  There is a lady who lives there who only ever says 'yes' and 'no', and those pretty rarely.  Every now and then a volunteer will come and play piano for the residents.  While she was playing the piano I was in the med room pouring some pills.  I could hear someone belting out "you are my sunshine".  I came out to see who it was and it was this woman.  We all stood amazed and had the pianist play it over and over.  I can't say she was a good singer but it was the most beautiful sound I had ever heard.  It brought tears to my eyes.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On saturday a bunch of us from work are going out for a 'Girl's Night'.  I am really looking forward to it.  These girls are some of the most fun people I have ever met.  I am going to take the camera so maybe I will post some pics of us having our fun. 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>