<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Life is all about ass. You're either covering it, kicking it, kissing it, or trying to get a piece of it.  (props to ScottKnapper from the Runner's World forum—dunno if he wrote it or lifted it, but it's fine) 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Everybody Loves Raymond" is our dinnertime indulgence.  We don't watch much television here.  (My husband, who complains about it most, watches the most television; he stays up later than the rest of us and eats his pints of ice cream while watching bad reality porn, like "Extreme Dating."  My daughter loves the show.  She asks how much I did at the store, and when I tell her, she says, "Holy crap, Marie!"  She says that for just about everything.  In one episode, Debra asks Ray for some time. She wants him to take the kids and leave, let her have the day to herself. But he can't stand it. He has to know what she's doing, so he spies on her, peeking in the living room window, where she's sitting on the sofa sobbing, the stereo blasting.  She explains to him later that she listens to sad songs on purpose so she can have a good cry.  I think of this episode as I press the back button on my CD player half a dozen times while waiting in the drive-through line at the bank.  I've never been a fan of the Dave Matthews Band (though I admit to liking his last CD a lot more than I liked any of the others, and "Crush" actually made me dance around). But his solo LP is another beast entirely. I bought it for my husband because of the song, "Gravedigger." This is one of the songs that "does it to me."   Because it is my husband's CD, and he keeps it in his truck, I don't hear it much. I borrowed it yesterday. This morning, I catch one of the lines and cry my eyes out.  "Little Mikey Carson '67 to '75 He rode his Bike like the devil until the day he died"  I think of my six-year-old daughter flying along on her bike, fast as the devil, going, as she likes to call it, "speed limit," which means really really really fast.   I can't fight the tears. This is the second saddest song I've ever heard. It's haunting. It's genius.  It's very easy to make me cry, especially when it's my time of the month for all things emotional.  But there's something about good poetry.  And this is a particularly good poem.   ----- Gravedigger Dave Matthews  Cyrus Jones 1810 to 1913 Made his great granchildren believe You could live to a hundred and three A hundred and three is forever when you're just a little kid So Cyrus Jones lived forever  Gravedigger When you dig my grave Could you make it shallow So that I can feel the rain Gravedigger  Muriel Stonewall 1903 to 1954 She lost both of her babies in the second great war Now you should never have to watch As your only children are lowered in the ground I mean you should never have to bury your own babies  Gravedigger When you dig my grave Could you make it shallow So that I can feel the rain Gravedigger  Ring around the rosey Pocket full of posey Ashes to ashes We all fall down  Gravedigger When you dig my grave Could you make it shallow So that I can feel the rain Gravedigger  Little Mikey Carson '67 to '75 He rode his Bike like the devil until the day he died When he grows up he wants to be Mr. Vertigo on the flying trapeze Ohhh, 1940 to 1992  Gravedigger When you dig my grave Could you make it shallow So that I can feel the rain  Gravedigger When you dig my grave Could you make it shallow So that I can feel the rain Feel the rain I can feel the rain Gravedigger  ------  Coming Soon:  The Saddest Song   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In my last on-line journal, I whined about my inability to lose weight.  I went on Atkins Induction for five straight days (twelve times), then decided my running was suffering and ate cereal and grapes.  Then my legs swelled, and I tried South Beach for awhile.  Lots of non-conviction. The journal was on a low-carb web site, so my ramblings were about food.    In this journal, there's a little more pressure.  People are commenting that my writing's better here, that these are little essays.  And every day, when I want to post my menu and nothing else, I think better of it.  Nothing poetic about an avocado smoothie (though I did write an avocado haiku once).  Nothing rhapsodic about Fitday totals.  OK.  I can rise to the challenge of an essay.  I know how to start and finish.  I know little tricks that make readers want more while they're reading yet feel completely satisfied when they're finished.  I'll be teaching those techniques to the students of my essay-writing course at Towson.  They'll all leave better writers; I'm confident of that.  (Even if I were the example of what not to do, they'd improve.)  I write a little like a teach.  My students are sometimes surprised to hear my opening monologue—a story about my daughter's star falling, say, because she wouldn't stop whistling.  Three times she whistled; twice she had to move her star.  Why didn't she just stop?  Because she had just begun.  She said, "I was afraid I'd lose my whistle."  So when she puckered her mouth to remind herself of the shape of a whistle, and when she exhaled to remind herself of the feeling of a whistle, the tiny whisp of a whistle came out, and she was caught.  My students look around the room at each other after they chuckle, all of them thinking, "What the hell does this have to do with writing?"  And then I pass out a drill, a clever little word game assignment that forces them to translate hoity-toity billion-dollar lines like "Scintillate, scintillate, asteroid munific" to the more mundane but familiar "Twinkle, twinkle, little star."  (Neophyte's serendipity, I tell them if they get a correct answer.)  Once again, they look around the room at each other, wondering what the hell it has to do with writing.  And then I tell them that thinking has to do with writing, that sharpening their brains with word games and inticing them with the meat of a cute real-life story will do more for their paragraphs than a textbook.  And then we move on to the textbook, which I correct along the way.  And then, end of class, I finish the story I told at the beginning.  I tell them that I am worried about my daughter's falling star—not because she is going to be in constant trouble for disrupting the class, but because I'm going to be known as Whistler's Mother.  Not a pretty picture.  I don't look good with doilies on my head.  But frankly, I don't plan that sort of thing.  It just happens.  They just wrap up nicely, as if my brain has got it all worked out but hasn't let me in on it.  I even make the connection that, like with whistling, if you don't practice writing, you'll lose it.    This entry wraps up the same way.  I came here to say  that I'm sick and tired of the pressure to write something engaging and interesting, when I really want to write that I spent yesterday dropping things and cutting myself (an 8-oz. Father's Day crabcake for $17 hit the floor, along with a tub of coleslaw).  That I ran 5.5 miles this morning with my new Rio and learned that it only holds 55 minutes worth of music (grrrrr) and that I couldn't even keep up a 10-minute mile pace.  That I went to Target and Rite Aid and spent more money than I had on a shirt, running shorts, earplugs, a toothbrush, toothpaste, hair dye, headbands, barettes, and cheap (but groovy) sunglasses.  That I spent $40 on writing and running magazines (these go hand in hand, since I do most of my writing in my head while I'm running).  That I bought nitrate-free salmon and bacon from TJ's so I can be on Atkins again.  And that I came home and fell asleep in the sun while reading Runner's World, and woke up with a roaring headache and my period (which explains yesterday's clumsiness).  I really just wanted to say that.  And this: Breakfast:  1/2 crabcake, chocolate banana smoothie with Genisoy powder Lunch:  1 oz. fontina; 2 cups salad with grape tomatoes, 1/2 oz. feta, and 2 T Litehouse dressing; and 1 mushroom-asiago sausage (blech), with 1/2 slice of cheesecake for dessert Dinner: same salad as above, 2 Boca burgers with Swiss cheese, and the other 1/2 slice of cheesecake for dessert.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In this, the summer of cicadas, the sultry mood of the season of brood x, some things we've believed and some things we've doubted have switched places.  I've become enamored with the red-eyed bugs that squeal like banshees.  I've not jumped when they've landed on me, I've handled them, and, quite frankly, I'd have eaten one if they were being offered—cooked, of course. The very thought of them freaked me out, but, if there's one advantage to having a six-year-old daughter who behaves (and dresses) like a boy, it's becoming familiar with these noisy creatures.  She took the fear out of the experience.  I doubt that I would hang upside-down over a vat of them and move them to a dish with my mouth, but I can honestly say I will miss them when they are gone in a week or two.  Second, who'd have thought I'd be leading a rah-rah cheer over the death of a human being?  But reading Lucky, by Alice Sebold (author of The Lovely Bones), really pounded the humiliation and fear and pain of rape into me.  It has made me tenuous running at the park, and it's haunted my dreams.  (I don't recommend the book, by the way—not for the subject matter, the writing, or the outcome.)    Our governor, Oken's last resort, has decided not to intervene.  (Duh.  He's a Republican.)  Steven Oken will die sometime in the next few hours.    Third, I'm going off next week to commune with Internet stalkers.  Well, not exactly.  I've made some friends on the low-carb forum, Brownie being one of them (she blogs—correction, weltanschauungs—here).  She came to my home for a visit and caused my daughter to fall madly in love with her.  The moment Brownie walked in my home, the girl said, "OK, Mom, Brownie and I need to talk," and she took Brownie's hand and walked her out of the kitchen.  So Brownie and I will share a room.  Cerise, the Tiki Goddess, Soy Sistah, and Science Girl will be rooming down the hall, so as not to disturb us when she gets up at o'dark thirty to exercise.  We will be visiting Dr. James, forum member, and his wife, known only as SWMBO (She Who Must Be Obeyed).  And our dear friend Max (who also blogs here) will be along, too.  I always thought only lunatics trolled the Internet looking to make friends.  (Look at me, after all.)  I was surely wrong.  I've made some good friends I hope will last my lifetime.  (Mudpup, you will be missed this trip.)  Yes, be jealous, gentle readers.  If I were not going, I'd be jealous myself.  It sounds like a good time will be had by all.  The question is how I will be able to squeeze in a 10-mile run on Saturday or Sunday morning, when Philly heat and humidity are nearly as bad as Baltimore's.  We shall see.  There's always a treadmill in the hotel, though I can't imagine a more boring, albeit air-conditioned, ten miles!  Again, who'd have thought I'd become a runner?  Just another switcharoo.  I have flip-flopped on my diet more in the past six weeks than in my entire life, choosing carbs, then binging, then choosing Atkins, then fighting dead-legs syndrome, then choosing Atkins again after two migraines, then finally settling on a lower-fat, higher-veggie version (also known as South Beach, for the uninitiated).  I might be happy here, even though I will be cheating on Father's Day with an Atkins-approved cookie dough cheesecake.  I have not run in two days.  Yesterday, I did The Firm's Maximum Body Shaping with heavier weights than usual (and after a month-long hiatus).  Today, it hurts to walk up stairs, sit on the toilet, walk, and sit.  I'm hoping to feel better enough to run tomorrow, though they say it will reach 100 in the afternoon.  I am supposed to do my first ten-miler this weekend.  Countdown:  2 weeks to the end of the cicadas, 8 days to Philly, 3 days to crabcakes and cheesecake (oh, yeah, and Father's Day), 2 days to 10 miles, and just hours to the executon of a rapist.  Countdown to ecstasy. http://www.oldielyrics.com/lyrics/rickie_lee_jones/a_second_chance.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There's an old joke (and I use the term loosely; it's not particularly funny) about some natives on a tropical island who take a pair of American male marauders (tourists) prisoner.  The natives give their prisoners a choice:  death or ru-ru.  The first one, unsuspecting, chooses ru-ru, for it must be better than death.  Of course, when the second one sees the brutal, violent, fatal attack that is ru-ru, he chooses death.  I'll leave the punch line until the end.  ----  I'm a registered Democrat who has never voted Republican (though I couldn't vote for anyone in the year Dukakis ran).  I am pro-choice.  While some might call me liberal, I don't fit neatly into a category.  For one thing, I'm pro-death.  I can't find a single compelling reason to keep the likes of Jeffrey Daumer alive.  I can't fathom mere incarceration for someone who causes intentional physical harm to a child or to someone who rapes, tortures, and/or murders innocents.  Lots of variables with the term innocents, but that's okay; the death penalty should not be used liberally.  But the punishment should fit the crime.  So when Steven Howard Oken forced his unwanted penis (and a bottle and who knows what else) into Dawn Marie Garvin's vagina and then again into Patricia Hirt's (his sister-in-law), that was an injection.  And when he murdered them both and also murdered a hotel clerk in Maine, where he fled, that was a lethal injection.  Punishment should be lethal injection.  Three of them, if you're counting.  I suppose I would leave it up to the victim's family, rather than to the State to decide whether to invoke the death penalty.  In this case, Dawn Garvin's family has been outspoken:  Steven Oken must die.  My husband is against the death penalty because he sees it as State-sanctioned murder.  He admits, however, he'd have no problem should the victims want to push the button, pull the plug, inject the drugs.  He'd have no problem should they want to hire someone (after all, it's got to be tough for most people to kill, even in self-defense).    I think about it occasionally, like when I hear someone's child was abused or raped or kidnapped.  I think about what I would do.  I would kill.  Oh, yes.  I would kill for my daughter.  It would not be about revenge, either.  It would be about justice—a mother's justice, not the State's.  A lot of people believe that it's just too expensive to kill someone.  But the execution is not what's expensive; it's the legal process.  The drug's cheap, and my tax dollars do not have to pay for a pedophile's television time, meals, and cot.  I didn't know Steven Oken, but I went to high school with him.  I knew him from the hallway.  I knew his friends.  Had I seen his picture without his name, I might have been able to remember it.  I recognized his name without his picture.  Steven Oken lethally injected three women.  He raped two and tortured one.  Steven Oken must die.  But first:  ru-ru.  http://mc4se.org/oken.htm
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Our moms never told us the importance of male shopping habits while shopping for a mate.  While it may seem great to find a man who likes to shop, remember that you will find it hard to get away from him.  Your shopping trip with just the girls might make him jealous.  His spending may rival yours, and that just won't do!  No!  If you find a man who abhors shopping and leaves it all to you, there's a certain amount of freedom you can enjoy—picking out the tea towels, for example, to make sure they match the kitchen, or choosing the sheets; do men speak the language of thread count?  My man loathed shopping, and that was good.  But after 20 years, his amateur ways have begun to irk me.  I indulged him his Christmas sprees, the days he'd head to the mall and, quite literally, meander, picking stuff up and looking at it, putting it back, buying nothing, spending most of the five hours on a bench looking at the scads of people who are actually accomplishing something and getting the hell back home (probably to watch TV).  A few months ago, his boom box was stolen from work (a Catholic school classroom).  He decided to "shop" for another.  One day, he went to Target, Circuit City, Best Buy.  Another day, he went to K-Mart and a few other stores.  Each day, he came home with nothing.  I told him, "Honey, every store sells the same crap for just about the same price."  He figured that out.  I also told him that he needn't have looked much further than Target.  (His biggest concern is money, rather than quality.)  Everybody sells the same brands, the same styles, the same colors.  It's just about where you choose to patronize.  You'd think he'd have learned his lesson.  (He never bought the stereo, by the way.  I had a nice lime green Memorex boomer from Target, which I'd bought for $50 and gave him after I upgraded to a $65 Sony with detachable speakers.)  Our washing machine broke.  It's an 11-year-old Amana, and it started oozing grease because the transmission is dead.  My husband, who is rereading Gerry Mander's In the Absence of the Sacred, is doing some lamenting of his own.  He is weeping over our disposable society.  He is grieving our washer.  He told me today, "Look at it!  It's still a perfectly good machine!"  BUT IT'S NOT!  IT NEEDS A $350 TRANSMISSION!  HELLO!  ANYBODY IN THERE?  Just because we didn't bang the shit out of it with a hammer and break off all the buttons and buzzers with a pair of pliers doesn't mean the thing is worth more than a buck in parts.  The thing not only doesn't work but also has destroyed (by leaving huge black grease spots) three white cotton blankets (2 queens and a twin), a few luxurious towels, my REM tank top (I'm sad about that!), my daughter's white school uniform polo shirt, his gorgeous linen pants (the ones I request when we're going out), and about four sets of sheets.  (My daughter is six and cannot hold her water through the night.)  So after the Lander's guy came to tell us the bad news and charge us $70 for the message, my husband went on a tirade about conspiracies, about how the Lander's guy (who fixed our dishwasher twice and replaced our garbage disposal) works for "the man" and how he's only saying that to sell us a new machine.  Why, I wondered, would he not want to do the work and get paid for it?  Why work, asks my husband, when you can get the customer to just  buy a new machine?  Well, I suppose you'd have a point, m'dear, if the Lander's guy WORKED FOR MAYTAG!  HELLO?  ANY BRAIN CELLS IN THERE?  We're not going to be buying a new machine from this guy!  He's the repairman!  Oy.  So our out-of-town guests left yesterday, and I fell asleep on the sofa while my daughter watched Men in Black II (are those Ballchinians the best?).  When my husband got back from walking the dog, we went to get our machine.  Or so I thought.  First, we went to Best Buy, where they have plenty to choose from at reasonable prices.  I had decided on a Maytag, since ours was an Amana (now owned by Maytag), but was also looking at the Whirlpools, which have the best reputation.  I found two machines, about $350.  I was ready to go.  But no.  My husband wanted to look some more.  In the same shopping center was a Lowe's, so we drove the quarter mile to it and found a perfect machine, a $347 Whirlpool with the same functions as the one we already have.  They had three in stock, it would be delivered the next day for $39.95, and they'd take our old one away and hook up the new one.  Yes!  No.  My husband didn't want to spend $50 extra dollars for the two features I liked, one of which was an infinitely variable water level (I am a Libra; I need infinite variables!), which our old machine had.  The other was a white-painted porcelain barrel, rather than a polka-dotted, granite-looking, dull barrel.  OK, that may not be a big deal.  So we left Lowe's, my husband deciding he will continue the search tomorrow.  What?  This is a man who can't find time to pee during the day.  And he's going to spend his second day of summer vacation the same way he spent the first?  Looking for the same crap at the same price?  I practically MADE him stop at Sears (right across the street!) then, rather than do it the next day (can you believe someone concerned about the environment is going to drive his big gas-guzzling truck back another 6 miles to the same place for the same thing?).  Same crap (except lots of Whirlpool/Roper/GE-made Kenmore applicances), same price.  We left.  What's left for him today?  BGE Home, which marks up their prices so folks can pay them off as addenda to their gas and electric bills; Lander's Appliance (OK, the repair guy works for a store that sells the stuff, but he didn't even tell us that, so surely he didn't expect us to drive all the way to Essex), Cummins (an expensive place in Pikesville—about 30 minutes away), and a scratch-and-dent place (so when something breaks, the machine will at least look like it's ready to throw in the towel!).  This morning, when he realized this was the state of things, when he lamented and grieved the loss of our washer and our $400, we discussed getting the one I wanted.  He still doesn't want to compromise on the $50.  He also doesn't want the 5-year warranty.  I told him to see if we could extened it after a year, and we'd wait to spend that $100 next year, if we felt we'd need it.  I told him to check with Best Buy, who had free shipping, to see if they'd haul for free, and to open up a credit card at Lowe's or Best Buy, if we'd save 10%.  I guess he feels the need to control the price he pays.  Or control me.  Or control the shopping experience.  My husband has, admittedly, done a little more laundry than I because he does a lot of it; he gets up at 5 and often beats me to it.  But I do plenty of laundry, too.  Plenty.  Unlike my husband, I have never shrunk my clothing by leaving the heat on high and the clothes in too long.  I have never put red clothing in with whites, making all our tighty whities pinky winky.  I have never overloaded the washer and/or the dryer, resulting in unrinsed, wrinkled clothing that needs to dry much longer.  My husband admits these things.  Yesterday he said to me, "Let's not wait to do loads of laundry until we have a full load.  Small loads won't put a strain on the machine."  First of all, I never wait.  When I need laundry done, I do it.  Second, I never mix whites and colors just to have a full load.  And third, strain?  Our washer was eleven years old!  That's good!  That's a nice long life for a washer!  I'm sorry about planned obsolescence; really, I am.  But I am not the one who planned it.  I'm just the one who has to abide by it.  My husband just called to see if he should write a check for the machine or if he should charge it.  Well, we have the funds.  No sense in paying interest.  But, I told him, apply for the store card if it'll save 10%, right?  And buy an air conditioner for the attic, too, while you're there and saving 10%.    He will.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wah.  Not that I particularly care for bread (though a hot loaf and soft butter are almost erotic) and pretzels, but I was hoping to be a little more normal, to have a little more leeway (leeway, slack, give—all noble causes) with food in my life.    And the running.  It will suffer.  But on Thursday (my dad's birthday, which, preoccupied oaf that I am, I forgot), I got a migraine following an aspartame-sweetened piece of French chocolate from AmyLee (from France but not a conehead by any means).  I got another yesterday in the truck on the way to Red Brick Station with the extended fambly (in-laws--my husband's sister-in-law, nephew, niece, and niece's husband).  What had I eaten?  Crap, crap, I say.  Could it have been, oh, I don't know (Satan?):  the sour cream and onion Pringles?  the Pretzels?  the two Michelob Ultras (no, not them)?  the four nonpareils (non-perry ellises)?  the sourdough bread with tomatoes and cheese?  Could it have been the stress of the knowledge of my lard ass growing?  ----  My husband and I had a big blowout fight the other night.  I didn't get to bed until 11:30 and couldn't fall asleep very easily (but I slept for 7 hours once I did).  It was about many things—our lives, our child, my failed low-carb store, my obsession with my diet, my running.  He laments my poor body image (though I imagine, if he told the truth, he would also lament my poor body!) and criticizes me constantly for what I eat or don't eat.  He watches me binge, and really, he knows he can't stop me, though he tries.  ("Stop eating that," he says.  Oh, all right then!  "You're going to bitch about it later!"  You're right.  But you'll have to kill me to get me to put down the cashews, hon.)  ----  So I'm obviously going to have to quit carbing up.  I had my first bagel in well over a year on the day of my first migraine.  It followed my first plate of pasta (plate—ha!—half cup).  No, it's back to bananas, strawberries, cottage cheese, and LC wraps.  We'll see if I can handle the running.  Maybe I'll be able to force myself to run more efficiently.  ----  My friend, Lucia, is in the same boat.  She and I e-mail each other daily with our psychotic diets:  No more low-carbing for me; I'm eating sensibly!  Me too!  I only had six bites of pizza and a pound of chocolate.  Great!  My bottle of wine was just what I needed after that sheet cake.   And then we discover our IBS or migraines or reflux or whatever-it-is-today is back with a vengeance.  And so are we—back to low-carbing with a vengeance.  ----  In other non-food news, Kathy has offered to design a web site for me, and I am absolutely thrilled!  Her work is terrific, and I'm sure it will be well worth the price of the crabcake and Michelob Ultra!  I just e-mailed a guy to see if I could use his cicada photo for my next mosaic.  Superman is not finished, but he's boring me to death.  I still have a thigh and a half left, in addition to the underwear and the silver bullet penis.  Zzzzzzzzzz.  I haven't written any more of my novel, Brood X.    I started to write a brilliant poem this morning on my run.  Now I can't think of what it was about.  Our washing machine began spilling spits of grease on our clothes.  It cost us $70 to find out the ten-year-old Amana is dead.  It would cost as much to repair it as it would to buy a new one.  So it's off to Best Buy today, since we have laundry to do tomorrow!  And my daughter wets the bed almost every night!  I got to use a Nikon Coolpix yesterday.  It's really easy to operate and very light.  I will be allowed to get a camera with some of our tax return money, as long as I have read Gerry Mander's In the Absense of the Sacred first.  OK.  That's doable.  I really wanted to have that camera for my trip to Philly, though.  Two weeks to Philly.  I'm eager to see my friend Joy and meet Max and Cerise for the first time.  I'm also glad to be hooking up with my friend and former UB professor and dean, Neil Kleinman.  We're going to meet at the hotel and go for a drink.  And I'm out of things to say, so I'll say this:  Ciao. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not a one.  (Yet.)  I slept through the night (after a particularly horrid night before) thanks to an evening binge.  I was abed by 9:30 and awake by 5:00 for a little nookie, though I did worry it would steal my pre-long-run mojo.  I had coffee and 1/2 cup yogurt with a little cottage cheese, three strawberries, and a sprinkle of LC granola at about 6:30, and I got out the door for my 8-miler by 7:30.  The weather was gorgeous.  Gorgeous!—about 60° and sunny, no humidity despite rain all night.  I did two laps around (3.6 miles), stopped to put on my 24-ounce Camelbak, and did another three laps.  Not 8 but 9—count 'em, NINE—miles!  (OK, so it took me more than 1:35:41, but I did it.)  I didn't bonk.  Didn't hit any walls.  Didn't puke up the food.  My arms are tired, though, so I get that now.  I'll have to get back on the strength-training tip.  The only thing that bugged me (no cicadas when it's this cool) was my left knee and two index-toe blisters.  (Does that toe have a name?  Surely it's not an index toe.)  I don't know why I think I now have license to eat, but here's what today's looking like so far.  Pre-Run:  1/2 c  yogurt, 1/4 c cottage cheese, 3 strawberries, 1 T Mini Carb granola Run:  9 miles (5 1.8-mile laps around the park) Breakfast:  1 cup Kashi Go Lean, 3 strawberries, 1/2 banana, 1/2 box raisins, 3/4 cup Soy Slender Snack:  1/2 banana with 1 t natural peanut butter Snack again:  3 Smarter Carb biscotti Lunch:  vidalia onion bagel  with low-fat cream cheese and 2 oz. salmon Snack?  I dunno.  Don't really deserve one. Dinner:  I dunno.  I'm going to see a friend's band at the Hon Fest, so I'm sure I'll eat sumpin' dair, hon.  I am on death watch at my low-carb store, where no one shops, even though it's practically free.  I am hoping to stay off the Internet long enough to work on Superman's right thigh.  I'd like to get that close to finished today.  Nine miles.  I can't get over it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I lament the lack of Spectrum red, a flat, smooth, bright, and perfect glass for Superman's bikini bottoms and cape.  I've already begun the bottoms and have just enough glass to finish everything except Superman's "member," which was originally going to be a silver bullet.  I started thinking about whether the Supe (we're on friendly terms) would really have his wanger hanging out of his blue tights and red drawers and thought it unlikely.    Had we but red enough and time.    Superman will be supersized and mirror-ized.  As for the flowing cape in the background, I've found another red that will suffice (though it's about $30/sheet).  I also lament my lack of sleep, as I needed two, not one, sleeping pills to get back to sleep when my husband's snoring, loud as a train, woke me at 1:10.  I moved my blanket to the floor and tossed around for an hour, took a pill, then went in my daughter's room and tried to sleep on her floor.  I took my second pill at 2:50 and fell promptly to sleep until 6:30.    It's good quality sleep with Sonata, even though it had been broken, but after my five-year struggle with insomnia, I hate to see it return, even for a night.  I've been sleeping well for over a year.    I've added carbs to my diet and am wondering if reduced protein from yesterday had anything to do with my lack of sleep, or if it was just LC forum crap bugging me.  I think it was mostly the latter.  After reading a few posts by people who find that staying out of controversy makes them so much happier, I realized that they do more to stir the pot at the forum than those who simply speak their minds.  It's a double standard, and it's ugly.    Hence this blog.  I write because I have to write, because it helps me work things out, because I can, because I have a lot to say, even if there's nothing important to say that hasn't been said better.  But it's time to move out of mom and dad's house and get my own place:  A Doggy's Life.  (And DRAT!  Why won't they let me have an apostrophe?)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      #1 I went to see my therapist yesterday.  I saw him last more than a year ago.  Now, he noticed, none of my problems are physical.  I'm sleeping, and I've only seen one doctor for a checkup all year.    We talked about the fact that my husband didn't want me to travel to Utah with him and our daughter because I always have trouble sleeping or get sick and because I'm afraid of flying, which would probably make me think of nothing else but the flight home while we were away.  I don't blame him.  Well, yes I do, actually; I blame him for saying it out loud, not for thinking it.  Had he not called attention to the last two trips to Utah, during which I had serious insomnia and was anxious about flying home alone (yes, alone; I usually got there with him or someone and had to go solo home), I might have been the new me who sleeps and goes with the flow.  I might have put on a good show in front of my daughter.  Truth is, I don't wanna sleep on the ground.  I have a bad back, and I'm almost 42.  There's some kind of law that you shouldn't sleep on the ground after forty.  But I really went there to discuss my brother-in-law and his wife.  I am having a difficult time being friendly and kind to them.  I am resentful.  My husband and I have had fights about them.  On Father's Day, I told him to invite them to dinner with the caveat that I was buying everyone a crabcake and that everyone was paying me back—$17/crabcake.  Maybe laying out $34 for your inlaws wouldn't be such a big deal.  But it was this time.  So when his brother announced that he was going to take his food home (he was joking about something), I told him that was fine, but he needed to leave me $34 for the crabcakes.  He was shocked.  He knew nothing about it.  My husband quickly said, "Don't worry.  You don't owe anything."  Later, we argued about this.  We also argued about the fact that my husband wanted to leave a day early (the day I had a long-awaited therapy appointment a couple weeks ago) to go canoeing on the Pokomoke so he could come home a day early and babysit for his brother's kid all weekend for free, while his sister-in-law was at Artscape making thousands of dollars.  Now I understand they're strapped for cash, that she doesn't work a regular job (though she waits the occasional table) because she takes care of their son and is a jewelry maker.  But before he was born, his parents had no problem shopping at WholeFoods, eating dinner out every night, and buying $200 shoes.    I don't know what kind of sob story my husband has been told, but it was enough of one to give them $5,000 toward a down payment on a dinky little rowhouse that was far more than they told us they could afford (I spent a long time looking for houses in this neighborhood, unaware that they were determined to stay in their own at whatever cost).  And I think my husband is considering giving them more money.  I, who worked hard for a $60,000 investment in my store, get lectured all the time about getting money from Mommy and Daddy.  But I didn't just buy shoes and clothes with that money.  I worked my ass off!  I was determined not to go into debt.  But it happened.  (My therapist says that only 10% of startup companies make it.)  Fortunately for my inlaws, my husband doesn't live with them; he can't see how they spend their money.  He offered to babysit for them while they went to see a movie, then they would babysit for us while we went.  So I suggested we share a babysitter and go together.  Little did I know it meant we would be paying the babysitter, who charges us $5/hour, $10/hour to watch both of them.  While we were in line at the movies, my husband told me just to get four tickets (probably to avoid anyone else having to stand in line).  I said I was getting two tickets, since his sis-in-law was right behind me with money ready.  She also had money for two drinks before the show.  How was I to know she couldn't contribute to the babysitter?  When family comes from out of town, they stay here.  I can't think of a time that we've ever not invited them for dinner.  In fact, he's been here dozens and dozens of times over the last 11 years we've lived here, and he has not once, not a single time invited us to dinner.  (We ate at his place twice: once, his mother bought the Chinese, and we picked it up on the way;  the other time was for lunch, and we stopped at a sub shop and bought our food.)  In fact, not only has he, have they, never invited us to dinner at their house, never cooked for us, never set the table for us, but they have never once brought anything, offered to bring anything, helped us clean up, offered to help us clean up, offered to pitch in, or ever seemed gracious (other than saying thank you when the evening was over).  They have never been to one of my poetry readings, art openings, parties, or anything that involved other people.  She was going to come to my reading two weeks ago, which was two blocks from her house, but she never showed up.  I mentioned in an e-mail (her husband asked me to send a link to her) that she'd missed a good reading.  She didn't respond to that e-mail, not even a thanks for the link.    I was not invited to her wedding shower (her friends didn't know me, and I guess he declined to remember me).  When they had a relative stay at their house for the first time, they went out to dinner, and we were not invited.  Or called.  The relative lives in Alaska and is not someone we see very often.  And when she threw a birthday party for him, we were invited at the very last minute; she had forgotten us.  My husband and his brother have been, in the past, very close; they are two years apart, my husband being older.  My therapist told me I needed to say all these things to my husband, that I was not to write them a letter or discuss it with them or in any way come between them.  And so, when we were alone yesterday evening, he asked if I could share why I needed to see a therapist again and what we talked about.  I shared these items, and, to my huge surpise, he agreed with them!  He agreed!    Now, will he talk to them?  Will he mention these things?    At one point, I was crying and told him that I can't even be civil or pleasant to them when they call on the phone because I'm so angry about all this buildup of bad manners.  So I'm hoping that he does, sometime soon, express these feelings.  He told me once, when I complained about the babysitting offers (there have been several; they have never offered to watch our daughter so that we could have some time alone!), he said you don't do things for people in hopes of reciprocation.  Well, that's somewhat true.  But with most people to whom you bestow these favors, you know in your heart they would do the same for you.  It's not true with these people.    I told my husband last night:  I am not looking for reciprocation!  I'm looking for CATION!  Just once, I'd like them to do something for us!  Offer to babysit, invite us to dinner, ANYTHING!  My therapist said they are obviously not Jewish.  No kidding.  Jewish families may fight and argue and cuss at each other, but we always give to each other.  We are not just about taking.  doggy  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A favorite Ani Difranco song, "Not a Pretty Girl," goes like this: "I am not an angry girl but it seems like i've got everyone fooled Every time i say something they find hard to hear, they chalk it up to my anger, but never to their own fear."  Well, I AM an angry girl.  I don't know why, but I am.  And when I get my period (like right now), I'm also a sad one.  Last year, during a particularly angry mood and sad period, I watched the news.  I heard a story about a woman in Pikesville, a mostly Jewish area, a nice neighborhood in the 'burbs, who walked across the street to a store.  It was only about 10:00, I think.  I imagine she went out to get some ice cream.  And maybe some pickles.    She was raped.  She was pregnant.  I cried for days.  And then I wrote this.  --------------- no wonder  like the pocket of an old coat,  worn from use, from fingers  feeling their way around loose change  for six cents, too many crumpled tissues,  children’s toys kept safe, cough drops, and keys that poke the threads,  my head can’t hold all it should, all you say—that i look pretty today, that dinner was good.  the nice slips through, too fine for the mesh of mind unraveled by frets and worry and world.  and you slip through—the hello kiss,  the weekend plans, i love you,  the frog you held for me to touch.  all is gone, lost amid the taffy of criticism and complaint,  the lead weight of slammed doors,   the smothering clouds of flowerless  holidays and goodnight kissless nights, gummed up works of fear,  chunks of doubt, thick loathing, want. Surely—certainly—with all that glutinous mess of matter, a smile could take hold,  a laugh could catch, a pat on the back reverberate a moment then stick there, glued to grief and insomnia,  wedged like a shim between an airplane flight  and another sleeping pill, tangled up in a child  stolen from her bed, a pregnant woman raped,  the disappeared, yet another priest fucker, the arabs, the israelis, enron's murderers  and thieves, the god-damned president.  well is it any wonder i don’t remember the last time you laughed?  is it any wonder i have misplaced my keys?  © Leslie F. Miller 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      coffin  this milestone gets a modest box, wood but unfancy, small but roomy enough to fit a few others (though after awhile these burials  will become sloppy).  the first to go: mandibular central incisor, letter P, the right bottom tooth. its placeholder, #25, was already in behind, leaving us no gap to make fun of, no unimaginative nickname like toothless.  P didn't earn her much. the tooth fairy fumbled in the dark with his father's coin collection, grasping a 50-cent piece. daddy called it a silver dollar when she awoke and ran through the house in her underpants, waving the prize, squealing with delight.  a few weeks later, when letter O departed, the grownup version in place, the tooth fairy overslept and had to slip the coin beneath her pillow when she got up to pee, disappointed, til dad urged her to look again.  now two teeth are buried here in this modest box, two tiny hollow bones buried by a mother  grieving the loss of a baby, celebrating the birth of a girl.   Leslie F. Miller   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      When I first got insomnia, I saw a few doctors and therapists.  None of them helped me much.  The first therapist was intent on teaching me relaxation techniques.  She made me bring a tape on our second visit, and she turned down the lights and recorded progressive relaxation as she said it to me.  That was our session—her recording of the tape.  She had a cold.  That night, when I lay down to make a stab at sleep (my stabs only seemed to poke holes in the night, letting in too much light), I listened to the tape.  Right as I'd started to doze off, there was a cough.  She coughed on my progressive relaxation tape!  I told her the following week, and she said to bring another tape in, and we do it again.  I told her I'd already paid for that session, and she should record it on her own time.  That was the end of our relationship.  I realized that her constant focus on trying to relax me wasn't going anywhere.  I had another therapist who claimed to be a hypnotist.  I kept asking him to do his magic, but he, too, wanted to record a tape.  His voice was more relaxing, but he was so slow and boring that I was more annoyed than anything.  It wasn't until a year later (by now, four years had passed) that I met Joel Knispel.  I'd say he's my current therapist, but I haven't needed him in over a year.  He is that good.  In fact, he is so good and so honest that he actually tells you when he thinks you're done.  I went an extra time or two, just for the hell of it.  And there was nothing to talk about, which, in therapy, is excellent.  What made him different?  He listened to me.  He didn't give me what he thought I wanted (hypnotism, a magic pill); he gave me what he knew I needed.  I told him my whole story, how I had a baby and got insomnia.  He asked what my life was like before, and I talked of poetry readings and rock concerts and drinking binges and LSD and all the things that made life fun, B.S. (Before Serena), not as if there was no fun A.S., of course, but it was different fun.  He looked me in the eye and said, "Here's the answer.  Write poetry or join a punk band."  I said, "What?"  He told me that when I'd walked in, I was weepy and sobby and depressed and heavy, but when I spoke of what I used to do, I had a light in my eyes.  He asked when I wrote poetry last.  It was four years earlier, sometime during my daughter's infancy.    He told me that blocked artists develop mental problems (in nicer words, of course), and that I was the extreme case of the blocked artist because I wasn't even TRYING to write, I didn't even KNOW I was a blocked artist.  Write, he said.  Sleep will come.  I took his advice and became a better sleeper.  I told my husband, my family, my best friend.  They all said, "Well, duh!  We've known you all these years.  Why didn't WE think of that?"  No one paid them to think, perhaps.  (And perhaps that's the best use of that putdown I've ever heard!)  I wasn't perfect, mind you, but I was better.  And each mosaic project made me even better.  We both realized that I needed projects—any kind, whether it was work, art, or writing—in order to keep my brain healthy.  The problem with my sleep was not that I worried about anything.  It was more that I WASN'T worrying about anything!  My brain was unstimulated.  Eventually, we moved on to dealing with the sleep issues themselves, the so-whats, the plans.  Whatever it was worked, though I still believe it worked in concert with calcium/magnesium supplements and Atkins dieting.  Chalk it up to synchronicity, the planets being aligned in exactly the right way for me then, everything in the proper order, at the proper time.  But how is it that a total stranger can tell you what you need?  That strangers on an Internet forum can see more clearly than you can?  Perhaps you are too close to the subject.  It's not that you need an objective eye; those strangers and that therapist certainly have their biases and seem to want the best for you, so they are not without partiality.  But they are without fear.   So thanks to all with insight.  Thanks to all the fearless (a Weir film recommend by Joel Knispel).  And thanks to the Jewish Buddhists for their righteous zen selves. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Goat. Goat. You could be a child's first word, easy as dog, daddy. Goat. Poor man's lawn boy, frisky pet, reason to claim the buns we pay for but never eat.  On the way home from lunch with daddy I pick you for your looks, black and white, feed you bread through the chicken wire, whisper secrets  over the steady hum of traffic:  Goat, I can't afford my shoes. Squishing my toes in the mud didn't feel as good as it should have. Being filthy rich would be nice. I have lost my way.  I once loved a goat like you. Took him home. Named him Goat.   Leslie F. Miller
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm reading a book now called Fire in a Canebreak.  Where I am in the book, the FBI is finding it impossible to find evidence against a single white man in a town where a mob of 20 was responsible for the last mass lynching in the US.    Someone writes a letter to his senator that says something like this:  If this had been a crime against four white people, the town would have no trouble finding 200 of the 20 negroes who did it.  It's a terrible thing, I'm sure, to live in fear.  I'm sure because I was robbed at gunpoint in Herring Run Park.  Yes, at gunpoint.  It was pretty scary, but it doesn't keep me away from the park.  A year later, the DC snipers murdered their first victim.  I was afraid to pump my gas until they were caught; I even suffered a bit of post-traumatic stress relating to the robbery.  I know who robbed me.  And I admit that I will walk the other way if two teens with a similar look head in my direction. It's only natural.  So my heart goes out to New Yorkers, who must deal with the terrorist alerts daily, who may easily suffer PTS when seeing machine-gun militia and large alerts.  And I can certainly understand wanting to steer clear of terrorists.  Who, though, are they?   If we're speaking of the 9/11 murderers, it's pretty obvious:  they were mostly Saudis (with some Egyptians and UAEs).  So who are the so-called terrorist huggers hugging?  The Iraqis?   Seems like the only ones doing any terrorist hugging are members of our own government, like the ones who quietly ushered the binLadens out of the country and the ones who are still kissing Saudi Arabian ass—instead of kicking it.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If a hell band is bagpipes and an accordion, surely there’s a place in heaven’s band for maracas.  The incessant hiss begins every day at around 9.  By noon, it’s a noise so white it almost cleans the day.  But at night, when the kids are in bed, while she sweeps the heaps of dead, dying, and emerging cicadas and their exoskeletons from the front porch and into the storm drain, the music is done.  The bug music, the wardrobe debates, the telephone calls—all are done.  It’s so quiet that Caroline swears something must be wrong.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On a chair in my living room, atop a pillow, a parasaurolophus (par-uh-sor-OL-o-fus) lay beneath a tissue.  He looks comfortable there, his six-inch plastic body snuggled softly.  Though I am used to seeing these things—four years of dolls draped with dish towels, stuffed animals tucked into tables with crocheted blankets, plastic dinosaurs paper-toweled gently to sleep—it still has me in its charming spell.  But I always wonder:  Did the weedy sea dragon wrapped in a shred of paper towel have a bad day, a cough?  Maybe the plastic army men were sleepy from holding their poses for so many years.  And if the stuffed polar bear were really cold, would an entire box of tissues warm him?  How does my daughter, now six and a half, choose which creature to cuddle?  What determines the time they retire?  What are they telling her that I am too old to hear?  For a fleeting moment, I worry that this is some manifestation of a mother’s lack of attention, that "covering things with blankets" is some textbook childhood disorder.  (Seeing faces in the abstract patterns of trees, upholstery, and water, for example, is a sign of mental illness.)  If a psychiatrist came to my house tomorrow, he would probably think nothing of Baby Tender Love in her cradle, a pink blanket pulled up to her chin.  But what might he say about the rubber frog wrapped in underpants?  What would he think of the parasaurolophus?  In dreams, blankets carry different meanings.  Clean ones mean success and good health; dirty ones mean treachery.  Covering something with a blanket in a dream means you are covering up something or covering for someone. In waking life, the blanket is a symbol of safety and security.  Charles Schultz gave Linus a blanket, and good insurance companies give us blanket protection.  I could drive myself nuts wondering if she is feeling unsafe or simply wants to make everyone feel as safe as she.  And though it might be akin to learning how your favorite magic trick is done, I suppose I could come right out and ask my daughter why she has covered this toy or that, why she has swaddled one in a sock, settled another down in her shoe.    When my daughter comes downstairs in the morning, I ask her why the cretaceous-period creature has been put so gently to bed on an overstuffed pillow on the living room chair.  "Well, the parasaurolophus has a broken leg.  He was getting eaten up by three weedy sea dragons because they thought he was lunch.  The blanket makes him not cold, since this house is freezing cold right now."  I am not sorry I asked.  It is still charming.  She is still magic.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>