<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So yahoo  urlLink strikes   back with a vengeance and we are all wondering how good this strike is. Well we will keep wondering and will never know, until Google releases Gmail to the general public. For now, however Yahoo is the only mail that provides 100Mb of free storage space and that is a fact. This happened in the wee hours of last night when to my surprise, I was not on the 100% mark of my yahoo mail. Now it is at a measely 5%, and that makes me very happy.   Search Engine Technologies have come a  urlLink long way   since the advent of the Internet. We now enjoy many search engines with thousands of algorithms at work everyday. But somehow critics always find the time to complain about competitors. Have we forgotten what competition can do to current technologies. Upgrades take place often and allow us to see what can happen with improved mechanisms. Search Appliances have upgraded itself since the advent of  urlLink Google  , mostly because of competition. It is similar to the professors who sit around and educate students in Universities. The professors get old, rusty, forget to update themselves, and before you know it, your program is backdated and the world has passed you by. If the search engine technologies are not constantly updated, all you are really missing are, pages, web pages, hidden in the dungeons of the  urlLink deep web . 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Design Analysis   In your thoughts about design, it is a good idea to reduce gaps. Gaps are spaces in design that may cause inaccurate synchronization of design elements. For example, a hole in an iron sculpture will allow liquid to pour out. This analogy may fit best for a content website where the design is important in the maintenance process. The hole refers to a problem with the template, that may eventually cause the pages to update without uniformity.   Synthesis Gap   is the term that exists in many disciplines, ranging from web development, library science, physical sciences, architecture to industrial manufacturing areas.  For this and many other reasons, it is always best to plan the website using some sort of design guideline.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Postal Service - Such Great Heights - 4:26 The Future Sound Of London - It's Not My Problem - 4:02   Radiohead - Scatterbrain (Four Tet Remix) - 4:26 Modest Mouse - A Different City  - 3:10 Llorca - Wordless - 6:38   Peace Orchestra - Shining - 5:00   Morphine - Whisper - 3:28  Shirley Bassey - If You Go Away (Moloko Club Mix) - 7:05   Chicane - Locking Down - 4:45   Deep Purple - Lazy - 7:22 Bob Marley (prod. Bill Laswell) - Is This Love - 4:31 Groove Armada (Al Green) - Light My Fire - 4:32  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      15:35:49  Sia - Moon   15:31:12  Mogwai - Killing All the Flies   15:27:30  Trip Hop&Acid Jazz&Trance - Pedestal   15:24:04  Trip Hop&Acid Jazz&Trance - Dummy (Remix)   15:18:22  Orbital (Moby Remix) - Speed Freak   15:18:22  zero 7 - 07.the space between   15:14:14  Da Lata - Rain Song   15:09:32  BT - Superfabulous   15:04:40  Mogwai - Helps both ways   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes called a sacred pipe or a calumet. The peace pipe is a ceremonial object of American Indian culture. The peace pipe was smoked at various American Indian ceremonies - from declaring war to making peace, and from practicing medicine to preparing for a good hunt. Since white people were exposed to it the most during the signing of peace treaties, they started calling it the "peace pipe."  -- from Native Encyclopedia   Above all else, remember that this is a peace pipe that I have given you… It will bring peaceful thoughts into your minds. If you will use it when you pray to the Strong One above and to Mother Earth you will be sure to receive the blessings that you ask.  -- from Lakota Indian's Origin of the Peace Pipe  Then the Chief holds the Pipe high, level in two hands, and proclaims: "Wakan-tanka Wakan neekay-chin, chandee eeya pay-ya-wo." (That is, Great Spirit, by this Pipe, the symbol of Peace, Brotherhood, we ask thee to be with us, and take part in our Council.  - from the Zuni Sunrise Call 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am a passive user.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Life is a sea of bubbles that we tread on everyday, to reach the top; stay where we are; or sink as if we carried the weight of the world. Hattiesburg Gravity started on a desperate therapeutic attempt to save the soul from drowning. Music being a passion, food for thought and fuel for the mind, gravity played all genres of music combining sounds from the east and west, and therefore creating a list of neurotic tracks. The playlist made no sense, there are no shows, we play music and with that we survive.  The following are some of our frequently played groups & labels:  DJ: Chicane, Kevin Yost, Karsh Kale, Tabla Beat Science, Nitin Sawhney, Kruder & Dormeister ... Label: Buddha Bar, Cafe del Mar, Naked Music, Chillout, Hotel Costes, Global Underground ...  Alternative: Coldplay, Pearl Jam, Queens of the Stone Age, The Doors, Morphine, Mogwai, Sigur Ros... Bangla: James, Miles, Artcell, Warfaze, Maya, In Dhaka, Faith, Winnings, Bangla  http://orca.st.usm.edu/~nsayed/Gravity/
     

    
</post>


</Blog>