<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Today was an okay day, I guess.                                        Two good things happened.                                         1) I went to Chris house and he put a waxing on that ass! I swear that was the best sex we had. We started on the bathroom sink then just stand up (my legs wrapped around his waist) And then in the bed. That was good!! And 2) My best friend called me. She told me she moved with her father because her and her mother got into it. But I'm happy my real best friend called me because these fucking so called best friends in my school were really getting to me. But anyway I gotta breeze!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am so freaking mad right now! My face is swollen from fighting that stupid ass girl yesterday! I want this shit to go down!  So besides that...Chris got a attitude for lord know what reason, I just came home from taking my U.S History regents in which I probably failed! And lastly my whole body aches!  Since I was meaning to see that damn girl, I came to school looking like a bum and it was so funny because when I just got home my father was like "Where you coming from?" And I was like, "Schhool" So than he was like "Like that?" It's crazy!  LOL, Chinell  and  Tauri were and my house yesterday and they were taking some strong stabs at each other. I was hoping a fight didn't break out. Luckily it didn't!
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    insn't this picture nice? I don't know where the hell it came  from but whatever.                                                                             So anyway, let me tell ya'll about my crazy day.                                                                         Well first of all it was the last day of school, so of course I just had to fight right?                               LOL, I fought some cornball girl and I had my 3 1/2 inch heels on from Steve Madden, so I fell but it's all good because when I got up I hit that bitch with my shoe.
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    So here is how I looked last night...   Anyway, so here I am. It's 6:30 and I not accomplished a damn thing! I got through some of the book I was reading but it's real slow.  Me and Chris has been talking on the phone for most of the day. We started out arguing but now we're the best of friends *winks*  One good thing about tonight is the dinner I just had! *UMMM!* My mother wound up cooking on the grilled. She cooked chicken, steak and corn, then made macoroni salad. It was really good.  She's been on my back about cleaning my room but I can't! I always start to but I always get distracted! All the time! I am going to try tomorrow then.  Now let me go and call my boyfriend!  *Lattaz!*
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   Wow! Another picture or me! *Cheese!) Anyway, I am about to go to the city with my mother and one of her best friends. *yay* I want my sister to come butsince her and my mother not talking, she don't want to go.  Oh yeah! Good news! I got my "Friend"! Okay, well that's bad news... but good because now I don't have to go to the GYN on Monday. *Cheers*   Well, I'll tell you how my day goes. *Kisses*
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I just finished my book.  Inside a Thug's Heart . Tht means it was really good considering I just got it on Thusday. So anyway, it's basically a whole bunch of letter's that Tupac excanged with this beautiful model while he was incarcerated.  It's exciting and sad at the same time because as she as she finally fulfilled her fantasy of having sex with him, he died! I was so sad!  But that's all about the book. I'm about to start reading   Use me or Lose me  next.  Wow. Today is a Saturdy and all I can think of doing right now is cleaning up (Which I really need to start doing) So after that I have no idea what the hell I am going to do!
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       > urlLink  I adopted a cute lil' fairy fetus from Fetusmart! Hooray fetus!   
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! This is my first entry on this blg so I wanted everyone to see me. Hehehe.  Well right now there really ain't anything to talk about but there will be soon. I can start my life back again since it's only 2 more days left of school! Ok, so I'm exxagerating my life never stopped but I am really excited about the end of school!  No that it's the end of school I need to see who is more real...Chinell or Tauri. Who will stand the test of times this summer? LOL, don't this sound like some reality show? It kind of is. These girls hate each other! I don't know why but I think Chinell will win. Basically because she is always at my house already and Tauri hardly ever comes!  Damn! It is friday and I am all alone in the house. I really miss Chris but once again he is away on a basketball trip. Actually he is at Hofstra University, which is type close to me but only by car and since I don't have one......I will just have to wait 'til tomorrow night to see my hubby. *tears*  He was being so sweet today, which only makes me want to see him even more.  Oh my God! Speaking of Chris, My mother set me up an appointment with the GYN! She still doesn't know that I am not a virgin. This kind of makes me want to tell her but I don't know. I still think that I shouldn't. I'm confused! Chris wants me to tell but I don't know. I'm scared! I know I won't get in trouble but still!   urlLink     
      
</post>


</Blog>