<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay. this is the maddest i've ever been in my entire life. okay. mike d'neil and his stupid daughter umped our game. just to give you a little idea of how one-sided it was... i was playing third and there was a girl running to third... after she's called save the ump goes over to her and says, "next time knock the third baseman over". and i'm not just saying this stuff because we lost, if we would've had fair umpires we wouldn't have... we were down by one after coming back for like the 5th time. whenever there was a play at home the catcher would come three feet off the plate blocking the runner and kneel down and they wouldn't call it interference... and when we did actually reach the plate and were safe... oh don't worry we were out. in the last inning we were down by one and in the field... we still got to bat since we were home team. the crowd got fed up with the bad calls and flipped out when we clearly got someone out at home and he called it safe. so the crowd started yelling because obviously that's what people do when the umpires are idiotic and bias. so he says, okay the games over white wins. "(that's the other team) that put the crowd into such a rage someone actually called the police... actually i don't know if it was on account of my grandpa and andrea's dad yelling and about ready to strangle him or if it was me yelling "you idiot! somebody punch him in the face!"... even the other team came up to us and said it wasn't fair and that we should have taken first. and i seriously think i would have attacked him if he and his daughter wouldn't have ran to their car and left right away. at least if they were gonna make us lose they could have done it fairly. i seriously want to KILL HIM! why would someone stoop that low? i know i shouldn't care because everyone knows that we should have one but i mean it was for the championship. i better not see that man ever again otherwise he's gonna get it. grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr! okay... i have to stop typing otherwise i'll lose my sanity. 
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      that comment above was first stated by the one and only lawrence (aka even haha cristey) from the school of rock... just thought i'd point that out. anyways, i was referring to bill clements softball team. grrr. we play them tonight for the last time... and if we win we get first and if we lose we take second... pressure pressure pressure. i know we can win though... it's all a matter of TEAMWORK! (everybody everywhere teamwork! everybody do their share! ~barney) okay... anyways... come cheer us on! i'll most likely be playing first base again... bwahahaha. anyways, the game's at 6:00 at john muir upper diamond (home team! yay!) kim will go and maybe courtney and tricia so you can hang with them... okay that's basically it for now... i took my corn rows out... a very stressful and painful proceedure. but it is done. yay. my aunt is coming up today... and i'm going to kim's shortly... or she's coming here. whichever. i am distraught though because i missed yesterdays episode of "all my children"... actually at the moment it started i was getting of "viper" and getting onto "raging bull". oh well. it was worth it. oo yes i met someone new last night... cam's (my FAVORITE cousins) friend... he seems cool. and i saw someone i know at 6 flags! but only one person who reads this knows who she is so that's okay (kim). okay. goodbye. have a nice day... i know i will!
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      TODAY WAS SOOOOO MUCH FUN! me and criddy went to great america! we had the absolute best time ever! the two favorites had to be raging bull and superman...which we both had FRONT SEATS on! yes!!! we also went on iron wolf, batman, the one that goes up really high and then drops, the teacups, the carasel (2nd story of coarse), the rapids ride where you're in a circle thingy (i got soaked... and yes... i attempted to keep myself dry because of my white shirt) and another water ride where we didn't get a drop on us and my dad got soaked which was HILARIOUS. anyways, we only got a couple pictures... one of us by the bus and the old guy that's in their commercial and one of us going up and down on the thing that drops... i'm hoping to get some pictures so i can start a photo album online and put pictures of bowling and stuff... anyways, if you go to great america this summer i have a few words of wisdom... 1. buy a "fast track" pass, with that you get to cut in line and it saves you like 2 hours for each ride you use it on. 2. raging bull has the greatest drop you will ever experience in your life and to make it even better be in the front row... and be sure to "eva, put your hands in the air!" ~emporers new groove 3. superman is the most satifying roller you will ever ride... it is the scariest, funnest thing ever!!! but you have to be in the first row because then you really feel like you're flying. the loops are the greatest thing ever... you're right side up at the top but then you flip over at the bottom. it's seriously the greatest thing i've done in my whole life. anyways i'm really zonked out since i got up at five so i'm goin to bed. goodbye all.
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HOOT! the past two days have been great. yesterday was a nice do-nothing-relaxation day and then at night i went to kim's and we played sims and fell asleep to the one and only bill cosby. this morning it was back to the wonderful sims, anastasia (great movie), and patricia dear did my hair which took her approximately 4 hours (of pain and suffering... but don't worry the final product was worth it) i had a softball game today. it was definitely the best game i've ever played AND the funnest! it was sooooo fun! i played first again and basically layed down sacrifice bunts the whole game. anyways, one player on my team (amber, she'll be in 8th grade at lombardi) stole third and the third basemen shoved her in the face and she got hurt. and of coarse, nobody, i mean NOBODY messes with my teamates, especially red-heads that think they're all that. so i made it my point to take her out. and that i did. as i ran full speed at third i could see the look of terror in her eyes and as we connected and she went flying, i couldn't help the smirk that came to my face. and then there was not just a great cry from the dugout, but the parents too. yes, it was wonderful. i did get nailed in the shin with a ball though, luckily it doesn't hurt, but it did leave the ugliest bruise i've ever seen though. oh well. no worries mate! great america tomorrow! (i actually have to get up at 6 a.m.... that's earlier than i get up on school days! ahhh!) oh well! it's gonna be a blast! until next time my chums... i salute you! ***SALUTE***... and i have left the building.
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Good day, good day... the morning was pretty boring... just sat around. kim picked me up at like 1 and we went swimming at the howard Y with her two sisters... that was really fun... and we saw, da da da dun... STEVE ARCHICET! ("steve archicet you never saw... hahaha kim!)after that we went to mcdonalds and then we went home and played SIMS! that is officially the greatest game ever... especially when you set your neighbors houses on fire... bwahaha. and you can send your kids to military school if you wanna get rid of them! now that's a good system. anyways... that's pretty much it... and oh yes! on the ride to the Y we saw the billboard that says POOCHIE on it!!! it was great! kim's camera that she had with her didn't have any film left in it though! oh well. next time. we also devised up a plan to right down in a notebook everything this other person says about each of us in it and then gang up on him/her. but that's a secret. don't tell. anyways, that's basically it for now. i'm watching the olympic gymnastic trials! yay diana! haha. okay. PEACE!
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow. okay. let's start with yesterday. i umped with my sister and kim and cristey came to watch but cristey watched the other game. anyways, surprisingly, the only rude comment i got was not from ben, but his older sister. actually it wasn't rude at first, because she just said "hi anna" but then came the snickers... but of coarse being my nice self i said hi politely and turned back around to talk to my sister. ben's little sister was cool though, i talked to her for a second. other than that the game was boring, my coaches other team lost and took 4th... but me and kim did sneak into the picnic to steal a bit of food... actually i didn't steal kim did. (i was invited to eat any food i chose :) ) anyways, today for kid's day me and kim went to "Wild Air" in the downtown mall but since there was a 3 hour wait we just walked around, ate, and shopped, and i managed to fall on the escalator 3 times. it was actually surprising how much fun the downtown mall is even if it only has like 5 stores... big sales though! :) the ride home was pitiful with my mom driving... she actually was tried to make a u-turn on a busy road and ended up like running into the curb and having to back up with all of these cars around her... then on that same road she saw a pelican on someone's yard and made a dead stop in the middle of the road until everyone said they saw it... keep in mind all of the cars behind us had to stop too. yes... that's my mom for ya... anyways, okay ben... this is for you... i'm sick and tired of us being mean to eachother and talking behind eachothers backs... i'm not apologizing... because i have ALWAYS been the mature one who stepped up and apologized to end our fights even if they weren't my fault at all, but this time you went a bit to far... so i know we're probably not ever gonna be friends again... but we can at least be considerate of eachother and stop being mean. okay. my speech is over. goodbye all.
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i'm at cristey leigh johnson's house! she rocks my world! i call her priddy criddy. she hates ben. kim smells like a cows butt and eats like a horse with her mouth open. CHOMP CHOMP. 
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay. this is basically directed at ben so if you're not ben then you don't have to read this. okay. number one. you were lying about me saying that i lied because when you talked to diana she did tell you that everything i said was true. so. there's a shut down. too bad your plan didn't work about you getting her against me. and about tonight, the there's strength in numbers thing. very cute. too bad ryan's on my side. and yes, i will be with other people and not because you will be there because we planned this a while ago. and i would be happy to take you down any day of the week. and now that you know that i know that everything you just put in your blog is a lie and i know that you know that everything i said was the truth you must feel like a complete idiot. amen.
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ahhhh! i just played like the best game in my softball career! i batted four times... i had a single, two doubles, and a triple and i scored all four times... but bad news... if i can't get mr. johnson to help my dad coach allstars there's not gonna be an allstar team because stupid clement is taking 5 girls to play for the purple aces! gosh! anyways... i'm really hating this storm... actually, i love thunderstorms it's just that the stupid weatherman interrupts my t.v. program approximately every minute and a half. there is a tornado though... that's pretty scary. oh well, it's not coming by us. i'm going to great america on tuesday! yay! i'm so happy! anyways i ump again tomorrow! it's the championship game! i'm umping with my sister and andreas coming to watch after her b-ball game so that's gonna be fun... and then afterwards they have their little picnic/party thing and i get to go so me and andrea are gonna go and eat all of the food... oooh yes and on friday it's green bay day and like everything is free everywhere so me, kim, and andrea are gonna go to this place in the downtown mall with all of this blow up stuff (like the slide we had at the 8th grade fairwell) so you can meet us there if ya want! it's gonna be a blast! alright... well... that is all of my thoughts at this point in my life. amen.
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      GOLLY! you ask someone something that you think  you can talk to in a quiet calm matter and you end with the person never speaking to you again. now that's what i call immature. what's worse he knew that everything i said was true but he refused to believe it! grrr that makes me sooo mad! and then he gets mad at somebody else too for no reason and that makes me even more mad! he had no reasoning and he still doesn't! okay... question people.... mostly toward the girls i guess... if someone (from the opposite sex) asked you to SLEEP OVER (even if it was not intended like that) and the person liked you but you didn't like them... would you be a little concerned? okay well, what's done is done, i guess i have lost a friend but you know what? if he's just gonna be a stupid immature idiot like how he was acting yesterday... well then "cheryl,cheryl, CHERYL... I DO NOT CARE!" ~remember the titans. if you didn't get that it means that i don't care. haha. okay. PLEASE comment on this one... tell me what you think either way. okay. i'm out... softball game today, 6:00 john muir lower diamond... another gauranteed win. 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wooo... great times... let's see... sunday night i slept at kim's (big party) and then monday afternoon we met cristey at hansen's for lunch... which was great fun standing on the side of the highway doing "hi, my name is joe, i have a wife and three kids and i work in a button factory (etc.)"... me and kim received many weird looks... i guess i would look at someone weird too though if they were standing on the side of the highway turning both of their hands, their left foot, and head. oh well. we were amused. monday night i had a softball game... with only ONE error... unfortunately it cost us the game (but don't worry, it was not caused by my AWESOME ability of playing first base.) the score was 4-5... i had two RBI's and i ran one in myself. now we're in second but we still have one more chance to take first. but, more bad news, four of the best players in the league are playing for the Purple Aces so now our Allstar team is officially gonna SUCK. oh well, it's still fun. Last night i slept at kim's again (cristey ditched us) and we watched Win A Date With Tad Hamilton (which i would recommend) and Chasing Liberty (which was the 4th worst movie i've ever seen, don't waste your money on it) anyways... we woke up and took kim's little sister out to eat at subway (aren't we so nice!?) and then i UMPIRED my first game! ... yes... $24 for doing nothing... now that's what i call a dream job... i didn't realize that the junior league got this bad... i wanted to cry. to make it worse these girls were only 3 feet tall. it was PATHETIC but very entertaining yelling things and feeling important. i did see one cool thing while i was there... as i was not paying attention to the game i looked over and this girl was doing cartwheels down this big hill... it was amazing to see her body being thrown by gravity but yet she did not fall over... and i can't even do one on a flat serface... it was possibly one of the coolest things i've ever seen... anyways... tomorrow i have a game at john muir at 6 on the lower diamond... come watch us kick some booty... i gaurantee you a win. and then i have to ump again on thursday at 4:30 same park. so yes. goodbye all. smooches.
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey! great news! (even though i'm sure like only 3 of you out there care) My sister FINALLY broke up with her do-what-i-say-or-i'll-kill-myself boyfriend last night! i'm so happy for her! hopefully now she'll be nice again! my whole family is rejoicing (behind her back of coarse) he keeps calling here though and i know that if she talks to him they'll probably get back together so i have made it my point to answer the phone whenever it rings and with great pride hang up on him. ALELUIAH! i wouldn't be surprised if he did commit suicide now... but it's his life! oh well! i know that sounds mean but he really is messed up... actually he's the reason why my sister dropped out of steven's point last year... oh well. it's all over. ALELUIAH ONCE AGAIN! amen. 
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes. Another day in the life form known as Anna Klarner. Me and Jecolia stayed at the Hilton last night (with the closest supervisor approximately 7 minutes away!) anyways, we were awoken at like 8 this morning by the stupid maids singing and yelling at eachother! grrr. Anyways, they left in the afternoon after wooping jeremy and jecolia 5 times in egyptian rats grew (clever name ain't it?) okay... after a game of pool against the one and only eric perez i went on a little bike ride to kimberly's house, the start of our adventure to come. after watching patricia's "character" dance in a gogo cage on sims we rode to mcdonalds (and the one and only kara (noel) pollatz mad our food). on the ride back to kim's (kim made me lose my momentum 6 times and ran me off the sidewalk once) we felt the pain's of old-ladiness as we rode up the final two hills... actually we literally thought we were dying... but not once did we get off our bicycles... what strong women we are kim! haha. anyways, i think i have made up my mind to go to colorado, so yeah. i will be flying by myself and i am scared to death. but oh well. oh yes! next tuesday and thursday at 4:30 me (and probably brittany) will be umping the little children at john muir! it's gonna be a blast making the coaches mad! and i'm gonna have a clicker! wahhhhh! yes life is good. anyways i am off. word of wisdom for your comments and everyday lifestyle... if you have nothing positive to say don't say anything at all... well unless you want to comment something bad... because you know i'll just beat you down... i happen to be well-known as the queen of comebacks. keep that in mind. adios amigo/as
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay! please tell me what you think on this subject... i would REALLY appreciate it! i have been invited to go to COLORADO with jecolia for a whole month! BUT, then i would miss camping, allstars (ooo that hurts) and maybe even an american idol concert... and if i went to colorado i would have to work out with this trainer every day... i do know him though... but still it's colorado! i really don't know what to do! please help me decide!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey everyone! this week has been soooo GREAT! okay... yesterday... the morning started out as usual... my mom throwing the cats on top of us to get us up... a game of cranium... and then a couple games of speed, grump, and double/triple solitare here and there. then, we went SWIMMING! yay! at the hilton mind you, i was a little disappointed on the pool size of such a nice hotel but it didn't matter because we had the whole place to ourselves! wahhh! and of coarse we brought out Target beach ball along and had mighty fun with that... did you know if you hold on tight enough you can actually do flips on those things? wow. after that we caught a ride with jecolia's mom back to my house for dinner, played a game of cranium... brought three plates of food back to mr. reggie... (yes, he eats a lot! haha) then off we went to the movies... (i rode with ms. sara so we could get in our "bonding time")... anyways... me and jecolia ended up seeing Raising Helen... which was good... it was funny, but i think other people would appreciate it more since i'm not really in to those kind of movies... in a way it was kind of like Uptown Girls... except funnier. anyways... KIM'S BACK FROM NEW YORK! woo! oh yeah... i have a game today too... (i haven't played softball in a week so i am overexcited) come watch! jecolia's coming so you can meet her! (kim too?) anyways it's at 6:00 (as usual) at john muir, and i play on the lower diamond (with andrea and brittany) COME WATCH!... but as for now... i'm out!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! the last couple of days have been unbelievably fun! and amy and adam have been NICE to me!!! it's sooo great! yesterday we just played cranium and grump and then went to this party at night... it was great fun. today was cranium and then we went bowling... which was GREAT! jecolia tried talking to like 5 different kids and nobody would talk to her because they were all scared of her! then tonight we had this banquet at lambeau... we just ate and then me, adam, and jeremy snuck out to the arcade which was AWESOME! their game room is great! you get this card which is like the coolest thing ever! and jeremy played that game where you have to dance, wow i cannot tell you how much my body hurt from laughing... goodness... you know how much i would pay if to have someone like jeremy my age? he is like seriously perfect... he's the nicest, generous, gracious, funniest, and most polite guy i have ever known! jeez he's awesome... too bad he's WAY too old for me! haha... anyways... oooo yeah! after the arcade we snuck out and were driving around while jeremy was making up his own words to adam's rock music (which i seriously thought i was going to die from laughter... since you probably know i can't breath when i laugh) we past this huge billboard and you'll never guess what it said... POOCHIE! YES! it said POOCHIE!!! i thought i was gonna have a heart attack! ahhh! that's pretty much it for now! P.S. eric perez rocks my face off     P.P.S i wore my shaniqua shirt today! :)      PEACE OUT! 
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hello again chums. it's kim's birthday! everybody say "HAPPY BIRTHDAY KIMMY!" anyways... she's in New York. that's dumb. but, anyways, news from the underground (that's from the lion king if you didn't know) eric perez (jeremiah's best friend... at least last time i checked) is going out with megan weis (lilmego25)!!! that's craziness. anyways... white's are coming in tonight! i'm so excited! and they're actually staying for a whole week! better yet jecolia's staying at our house! oh my gosh... just to give you a little hint of what i have to put up with... my family (my dad, mom, amy, and her boyfriend) are all sitting in the family room right now watching "the wiggles" together and enjoying it. not cool. that's pretty much it... and ben i don't know if you're mad at me again or not but this time it wasn't my fault and you know that. so... so long everyone. 
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yay! My first blog! I am very excited. Okay. As long as I am on this subject with somewhere else let me first state that there are only two, I repeat, TWO poochies in the 7th going on 8th grade. This so called "poochie" that Ben claims to have claimed as his own shall be known as a "woochie" for reasons that are obvious to some, but shall stay in the shadows for reasons I shall not state. Anyways... It's summer. I just got back from Door County! It was a blast! I went with Kim and Courtney and... the terminator (my mom) anyways... i'm sure you don't want to hear the juicy details and if you do... well then just say so, but i shall not bore you any longer. Tomorrow White's are coming for a whole week and Jecolia is staying at my house... everyone else is staying at the Hilton... so we can take advantage of their pool! yes! and, i am glad, i guess, to say that me and ben are once again friends, though i don't think it will quite be the same. but, i shall make every attempt to be positive. yay me. i am done. goodbye.
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      it's happening again... and i HATE it! i really want it to stop but i just can't help it and it's driving me crazy!... i guess i'm sort of like greenly in a way... even though that might be a bad thing... i'm refering to all my children of coarse. anyways, my grandparents are here... i just finished a great game of croquet... and of coarse i beat everyone vigorusly. it's really fun playing with my family because my grandpa thinks that he's the greatest and then makes up excuses, my grandma doesn't know what the heck she's doing... my mom is terrible and cheats almost unbearably but then claims that everyone else cheated. my dad thinks he's cool but he's not. and my sister is just weird. so yes. i beat everyone easily :). i'm puttin' the badmitton net up tomorrow... and i think we'll have a bonfire at night... that is after my uncle's girlfriend and children leave. :) my family's so mean. oh well. that's the geyer's for ya. i shall be runnin' now. i don't know what i'm gonna do but i'm gonna do somethin. get everything out of my mind... actually i'll just probably think of it more but oh well. greenly always gets over everything! haha. see ya.
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      that has nothing to do with what i'm writing that song is just in my head so yeah. go beatles. wow... today so far has been sooooo boring! it's my sister's birthday so i can't do anything... well now i can because she and my mom went to a movie and wouldn't let me come... oh how my family loves me! anyways, if kim doesn't get home soon i might just take a dip in my pool... or in jenna's pool... both work. tomorrow all of my family from my mom's side is coming over (except cam!!! grrr that sucks)...that shall be quite interesting... except my uncle's girlfriends kids are coming too and they are soooo annoying!!! me and courtney shall have to escape somewhere... that is if she doesn't bring her weird mung boyfriend (they're both going into college and i'm taller than both of them... bwahaha)... he does do an extremely good impression of william hung though i must admit... and he rocks at ping pong and badmitton... hmmm. maybe i shall set the badmitton net up... that always causes controversy... anyways... GOOD NEWS! a camping date has been set! wooooo! there is bad news though... cam can't come with us because he has baseball on the day we're leaving because he's their star pitcher and catcher. boo. anyways, we're leaving on thursday (july 8th) and coming back either sunday or monday (the 12th)... i think monday though. it shall be fun. and i hope both of my uncles go because they make it even more fun. and kim don't forget to bring the axe! haha... knockin' joe hear we come!.. and hopefully nobody will walk in on you when you're going to the bathroom this time... hahahaha. i'm hoping courtney will be able to come though but we are very tight on room since we used my dad's work truck before but now he quit so yeah... hopefully we'll be able to use my uncles... wahhh. oh well. camping is camping. my sister started singing "the water is wide" today... it was really scarey. and i wanna see spiderman 2 really badly so if anybody wants to go with me let me know. anyways... i believe i have run out of things to say... oh well. it's probably for the best. until next time young grasshoppers... let the force be with you.
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      although i am still VERY upset about yesterday's happenings... today was a bit better. this morning kim's phone call woke me up around 10:30, i pet my dear poochie for approximately 10 minutes while talking to my dear father about what happened last night. then i showered, got dressed and rode to kim's where we then took off to eat lunch at subway. there we met up with courtney and jenna (jenna got stood up) and caused a huge scene... well courtney did. first we tell her, courtney the man's talking to you tell him what you want... so she turns around and yells "OH!" then she told the man she wanted a little mayo and he loads it on and the expression on her face was the greatest thing i've ever seen. then she's getting a drink and steps in a big puddle of red stuff and screams "OH MY GOD! EWWWWWWWW! WHAT THE HECK IS THAT!" every single person in the place (and there was A LOT of people) turned and stared at her... it was the funniest thing ever... then we went to mcdonalds to get ice cream and french fries then we all went back to kim's. after we started to catch up on all my children we made cookies. kim had to go to the dentist so we proceeded on to courtney's house where we had a great refreshing water fight where each one of us were ganged up on at one point and got drenched. i mean there was not a dry spot on us. it was great! then we took a long bike ride to try and dry off but that didn't help at all. the we had more ice cream and i came home to my wonderful family. yes it was a great day... besides dealing with yesterdays business. oh well. life goes on... hopefully not mike deneils. grr. okay. i shall be going now. i must chat with my dear diana. 
      
</post>


</Blog>