<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Dirty Harriet&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Good morning!  I hope this Monday finds you bright-eyed and bushy tailed!  I just ended my strenuous training session with my personal trainer.  I'm even too exhausted to hose off in the shower before I start my day of errands, chores and what-knots.    Just one more week until I am officially sworn in at the local PD.  What better opportunity than now to just look like sh*t, I say.    Truth is, I really don't care what I look like today.  I care more about how much I can get done before I pick the twin tornados up at 3:00.  So, my secret today:  No shower.  Hey did anyone hear about the hate crime in Lee's Summit?  There were two white boys (15 and 16 years old) that took a stuffed monkey, severed its limbs and tied a noose around it's neck and put it on a black family's porch.  They admitted to the police that they did it.  Apparently the family had just moved in about a month prior with their 4 children.  What do you think should happen to the boys that did it?   
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok.... I've joined the bandwagon of bloggers.  It's true.  I guess you can say I'm a follower.  And I'd probably jump off a bridge too, (that is, if all my friends were doing it).  So here it is, my first official blog.  I'm not much of a writer, so I guess you can say this might come as a shock to most of you.  Let's just say that I won't be doing this thing every day.  I'll blog when I've got a funny story to tell.    Be forewarned that most of the things I write about will be nothing more than just a bunch of bulls**t.  But hey, when you're bored with nothing better to do with your time, sit back and relax while you waste time reading my blog!  And just for stopping by today, here's a joke for you to enjoy!   Uses of Vaseline   Joe wanted to buy a motorbike. He doesn't have much luck until, one day, he comes across a Harley with a 'for sale' sign on it. The bike seems even better than a new one, although it is 10 years old. It is shiny and in absolute mint condition.  He immediately buys it, and asks the seller how he kept it in such great condition for 10 years.  "Well, it's quite simple, really," says the seller, "whenever the bike is outside and it's going to rain, rub Vaseline on the chrome. It protects it from the rain."  And he hands Joe a jar of Vaseline. That night, his girlfriend, Sandra, invites him over to meet her parents. Naturally, they take the bike there. But just before they enter the house, Sandra stops him and says, "I have to tell you something about my family before we go in." "When we eat dinner, we don't talk. It's a rule.  In fact, the first person who says anything during dinner has to do the dishes."  "No problem," he says. And in they go. Joe is shocked. Right smack in the middle of the living room is a huge stack of dirty dishes. In the kitchen is another huge stack of dishes. Piled up on the stairs, in the corridor, everywhere he looks, dirty dishes. They sit down to dinner and, sure enough, no one says a word. As dinner progresses, Joe decides to take advantage of the situation.  So he leans over and kisses Sandra.  No one says a word.  So he reaches over and fondles her breasts. Still, nobody says a word.  So he stands up, grabs her, rips her clothes off, throws her on the table, and screws her right there, in front of her parents.  His girlfriend is a little flustered, her dad is obviously livid, and her mom horrified when he sits back down, but no one says a word. He looks at her mom. "She's got a great body," he thinks. So he grabs the mom, bends her over the dinner table, and has his way with her every which way right there on the dinner table.  Now his girlfriend is furious and her dad is boiling, but still, total silence. All of a sudden there is a loud clap of thunder, and it starts to rain. Joe remembers his bike, so he pulls the jar of Vaseline from his pocket. Suddenly the father backs away from the table and shouts, "All right, thats enough, I'll do the f**king dishes!" 
      
</post>


</Blog>