<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yea... Today studies 3 chaps of Geography. Quite a good achievement liao.. haha... I guess my revision plan will intensify in the days to come. One step at a time ma... Met JY for dinner. Had a really good time listening to his story and getting to know him better... and into a deeper level. IN LOVE! Hee... Tmr Ms Sandran's wedding... Wonder how will it be. Keke!
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yup.. Time to study and "chiong" for the o'levels. Haha. Yupz... Gonna study real hard. Have lotsa support and encouragement from JY and all the ppl around me. Not gonna let them down. I am getting better from my flu. In a more appropriate state to study. Haha. But of course, i wun miss my sleep, my tv progs and my play too. Keke! After all, I am still the Shiling who loves to have fun and slack all yr round. Keke.  ~Jace~
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yoz.. Am still sick. But dunno why... feel so different from Sunday. Yea! Haha.. Gosh... Am i in a chalet? My grandma house? Or what? haha. Well... I am so loved by all the ppl around me. Hee...  Am so far from home. Now at the east.. Miss my stuff toys, my room and my radio. Well... nothing much today. Just enjoyed so much. Going "gai gai" later. My joy is to the utmost fullest. Nah... This joy is suppose to be kept within. So not planning to shout it out on this blog. Haa... So whoever is reading, so sorry. Keke! Bleh...  Oh ya! today's Joel's birthday. Hee.. But none of my business. I wun spend that much effort on him though he had spend much on me during my birthday. But hey... Staying till 12 am for me isn't that bad la.. Haha. But i ain't gonna do that. I need my sleep. Cus i am sick! Bleh...
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Haiz... Today is such a blue sunday. Have fallen ill. Throat not feeling well... Kind of flu. Yawn... so tired. Wanna study but "li bu chong xin" keke. But things are not that bad. Atleast, i got ppl who care for me. Winnie sent me home... And JY can't help worrying. Hee.. Feel so fortunate. Keke.  Receive quite a number of birthday presents today... I love the Eeyore... But i am extremely disgusted by the one who gave me that present. Haha.  Yea that's all... Tmr still got lesson... Ultimate sian...  ~Jace~
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's exactly what i am feeling today. Well... The elders always think that their views and opinions are correct. But that's not 100percent. Everyone makes mistakes ain't it? no doubt they haveexperience and have seen more stuffs than us, but we are not totally a fool. I wanna make my own decisions, wanna fight for my own rights. But somehow, this will seem rebellious in thier eyes. This is so absurd. I wanna live my own life. Why must i live up to their unreachable expectations? i know what i want... I'm not going to live under their pressure and opinions... i wanna break through. To live the life i want, to be the girl i wanna be. To love and to be love by someone who respects my decision.   ~Jace~ 
      
</post>


</Blog>