<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've never liked the idea of putting up an online journal. It kind of makes me feel exposed and vulnerable. But, I figured that this is the best way for me to keep everyone updated on my life. I think it would also be nice for people to see the Peace Corps experience through my eyes and for me to share it whole heartedly. I enjoy writing. Since I'm not as open up close and personal, writing is a good expressive release. I don't know how much I'm able to tell, but I do want to be able to share the good as well as the bad. Don't take anything too much at heart because one day I may be crying my eyes out, but the next day I could be having the time of my life.  Note to all family members: Whatever I write here can never get back to my parents. I don't want them to worry anymore than they need to. I will e-mail them personally to keep them updated my own way. Another thing so that you won't be blindsided, I've signed an agreement with the Peace Corps so that if anything were to happen to me, the family will not be notified unless I'm pretty much dead. I hope you can understand why I made that decision.  This is not private, so I don't really care if anyone should want to share this site with anyone else. Anyways, I hope to keep this updated as often as possible. Wish me luck! 
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I wake up every morning at 10 a.m. and lie there for an hour, knowing that I have half an hour left to get ready and eat breakfast before I go to work at the ice-cream shop.....scooping ice-cream, blending drinks, asking endless questions on how customers want it: ice-cream or frozen yogurt? cup? cone? size? etc. An hour goes by. A day goes by. A month goes by. Then one day I realize that I'm approaching a year and I'm still stuck in my ice-cream twlight zone. What happened to my life? A year goes by and I have nothing to show for it. It's all very sad really.      I don't know when, but one day I just stopped smiling. Some customers have even made comments about it and all I can manage to do is force one out politely. I'm not rude. I'm just not so nice anymore. I've felt like a walking dead person.....emotionless. I honestly feel sorry for these customers. That I had to be the one helping them.     I came back last summer so full of life. I was genuinely happy. I don't want to say that that person doesn't exist anymore, but she feels so far away. Don't get me wrong. I've had many days of great laughter and good times, but they're just small in comparasion to the whole picture. Luckily my best friend has kept me sane. Everyone needs a rock in their life.    But now it's time for me to go my own way. I don't like who I am right now. It's no one's fault but my own. I know that it's selfish, especially to the family, but I need to get away. I need my space and time to figure things out on my own. I'm not searching for some kind of meaning in my life or some kind of ephiphany. I just don't want to feel empty anymore.    I don't know how the next two years will turn out. The ice-cream shop was my curse, but strangely enough it may also be my savior. In my twenty-four years (though still very young), there's one thing I've learned, that no matter how hard life gets......there's still some hope, for a better tomorrow and happier days. There just has to be. I may be a naive dreamer, but that's all I know how to be. I think that's something worth holding onto to get me through another day.  
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      An apple in one hand My tooth in the other I stood by the door Waiting  My mom out on the town As well as my dad But separated they stood Another night  My brother ruled with his fist We had no other choice So many nights full of tears Helpless  A night I still remember A punching bag I was When will they be home? Praying  Waiting by the door I took a bite from an apple A baby tooth broke Scared  Watching car lights pass The next one will be dad's But all hope was lost Never again  An apple in one hand My tooth in the other I stood by the door Crying 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Is there a difference? Can you really be alone and not feel lonely?  Somehow being lonely has an air of sadness about it. A longing that stays with you. Lonliness seeks companionship. Being alone seeks solitude. But, is it the kind of solitude you choose to have or learned to live with?  If I had the choice, I'd rather be alone than lonely. It makes life easier to live. Less thinking and emotions involved. But I know that in the end it's all the same. Love never gives up on you no matter how hard you try to give up on it. It's up to you whether you want to accept it or not.  
      
</post>


</Blog>