<Blog>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for not posting much. Been busy. Cough.  Let's see....what's new...hrm. NCAA 2004's coming out pretty soon, and that's got Live play, so it should be fun. Spider-Man 2 comes out tomorrow, and I can't wait to see it. Hopefully it lives up to the first.  Ever notice how when you first wake up in the morning, you can't really make a fist? It just feels weird. Why is that, exactly? Seems to me it would be the best time for a fist, because you're pissed off you have to wake up. "Fuck, it's morning? Goddamn! Fuck, it's early. Gotta make some fucking coffee. Fuck!"   Oh, and just because it's my blog and I can write whatever I want: you suck, Kristin. :p
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FINALLY! All my exams are over, and it's time to kick back and relax for a month or so, and then get some stuff done. Have to put up a fence and build a deck. Fun!  Only crappy part about school ending is you don't get to see people you're friends with, but not close enough friends to be hanging out with all the time. That always sucks. =/ 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please, get in your anti-stupid suit and browse some of the crap they've posted here:  http://www.mavav.org/  Alright, here's where my opinion lays reguarding violent games, from a person who's headcapped (more then) his fair share of freedom-hating terrorists and those goddamned Nazis.  Children under the age of 12ish shouldn't be allowed to play games more then maybe an hour a day. Parents must teach their children proper "rationing" values. Remember, everything in morderation. Go outside, get some fresh air, then come in, have dinner, and play some games for an hour or two. After they've reached a certain level of responsibility, let them decide how to spend their time. However, continue rationing time if grades drop or they're missing out on a social life.  Let's check out some of the stuff posted there, so I can break it down and tear it apart piece by piece:   "Fact: Videogames aren't just for "fun" anymore, the videogame industry made a net income of $6.3 billion in 2002, surpassing even the movie industry. Developers profit and continue to take advantage of today's youth with cute, loveable, addictive, and recognizable franchise characters. A practice and strategy similar to those used by the tobacco industry."   Ok, here's a fact for you: Games don't require the user to inhale addictive substances or wreck their respitory systems. Good tactic, comparing games to one of the leading causes of death in the United States, but it just doesn't hold up.   "Fact: Videogames have been proven to prevent the development of the proper social skills and interaction needed for a long happy and enjoyable life. Young gamers are prone to being burdened with depression and sadness all throughout their life."   They've got somewhat of a point here, I'll admit. But nowadays, games are part of a normal social life. It's perfectly normal to go over a friends house and kick his ass in some  Halo  deathmatch. Other games promote teamwork. I played  Call of Duty  and  Return to Castle Wolfenstein , WW2 team-based shooters, for a few years competitively, and my tactical thinking skills were increased, plus I made some very good friends. Yes, you heard me. Friends. One or two of them I completely trust. And I've never met these people face to face. It's just not the "standard" social interaction, and people fear what they don't understand. Sort of like aliens, or Martha Stewart.   "Fact: Hardcore gaming not only leads to videogame addiction and abrupt lifestyle changes, but to crime and felony as well. Hardcore gamers never buy computer videogames. Instead, downloading illegally copied videogames or “warez” is the only method acceptable by the underground. Buying a legit copy is grounds for abandonment by community groups. You may not be buying your child videogames, but they can illegally obtain them off the internet."   Wow. Just. Freaking. Wow. This has to be one of the most misinformed, poorly researched statements I've EVER heard in my entire life. (Edit: Aside from anything said by a radical group and/or hippies) While some "hardcore" gamers do get addicted, and that is a problem they need to deal with, I would say most gamers buy their games. Ever notice how the people that are most into music buy their music, instead of downloading it? Because they want to support the artists and the people related to the music. Same deal here. Hardcore gamers want to support the developers and programmers related to the creation of the game, because it's a *lot* of hard work. So we shell out our $40 for a new game, because we want to make sure the developers have what they deserve, some Ramen noodles and maybe a new keyboard.  Enough quotes for now, I don't know how much stupidity this server can handle without collapsing, or something. All in all, MAVAV wants to do a good thing, but it's way too militant and radical in it's approach. I don't want to see "Violent Bloody Man Kills People 4" in the hands of an eight-year-old either, but I'm not going to try and brainwash everyone into thinking that violent videogames make people become criminals, because they don't. I'm one of the least violent people in my school, yet I play the most violent games out there.  You know why? Because my parents and grandparents brought me up RIGHT. They tought me responsibility and consequence, and that just because Sam Fisher just broke a terrorist's neck in half, doesn't mean I should go around town with an AK-47 and kill people.   THAT's the approach groups like MAVAV need to take to be sucessful. I blame horrible parents and poor supervision for kids being violent, not video games themselves. Just like anything else that it's possible to get addicted to (work, drugs, gambling, idleness) you need to ration yourself.  I'd love for someone from MAVAV to read this, and e-mail me, or better yet, post a comment by clicking the small, blue, "x comments" link after the post. It would prove...interesting.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was hanging around outside my apartment yesterday, listening to my iPod, and just relaxing. Some neighborhood 8-year-old comes up and asks what I'm listening to. "Metallica." "Metallica sucks!."  Must. Resist. Urge. To hurt kid. In face. With hammer.  Now, I'll agree that some bands can, and do, infact, suck. They can suck for various reasons, but they suck. But can millions of Metallica fans be wrong? Doubtful. Most people don't realize there's a difference between a band sucking and you simply not liking their music. Stuff like Metallica is definitely an acquired taste, but once you get the feel for it, it's awesome. Just like Sushi and Wasabi.  Unless, of course, you get the Wasabi in your eye. Then it sucks.   But then, your friend gets it in his eye. Then it's awesome again.   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever watch a fly try to get through a window?  They'll keep flying into the window, back and forth, trying to get past it. But they can't, because of the window. Pretty funny, isn't it? Yeah, well, I'd like to see how you'd deal with it. You're just walkin' down the hallway, minding your own buisness, and then SMACK, face-first, into a wall. You might even fall down. Then you know what you'd do? You'd try again, like the wall magically disappeared. Finally, you'd turn around and go the other way. Well, the fly has no idea about the window, or why they can't get outside, just like you've got no idea about the wall. So don't laugh, it's not nice.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Game 7 of the '94 Finals took place 10 years and 2 days ago. I may not be a Ranger fan, but it was still very cool to see them get what they've been after for 40 years. Of course, they had to screw it all up the next season, but they still got the cup.   There's a senator in California who's trying to pass a bill that will allow 14 year olds to vote. The system works like this: 14-16 gets 1/4th a vote, 16-18 gets 1/2 a vote. Now, I don't know how many of you are in school or other close contact with 14-16 year olds, but this is about just as good as an idea as going up to a Marine and slapping him right in the face. You just don't do it, it's not smart. If this passes, then well, between that and the Californian recall, I say we just all group together and push California off the country. It can go hang out with Japan, or something.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently, scientists in St.Louis have sucessfully conducted an experiment where patients played a simple video game with thought alone. Using electrodes that pick up signals from the brain, the "players" were able to issue simple commands without moving a single muscle.   Outside of gaming, this technology can be used for a multitude of services, such as helping the paralyzed control a wheelchair. Inside of gaming, well, it's just one step closer to a HoloDeck. Sweet!
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The regular school year's finally over. Time to kick back, relax, and wish I had enough money to buy one of these:     It's called Aquada, a British-designed amphibious car. The vehicle hits 100MPH on land, and with the flick of a switch, the wheels retract and a jet-engine kicks in to propel the Aquada to up to 30MPH in water.    It's not completely new, so why am I bothering to mention it here? A Brit by the name of Richard Branson sailed his Aquada across the English Channel last weekend. He set a new record for amphibious crossings of the channel, completing the journey in only 1 hour and 40 minutes.   The car seats 3, and is priced at around $271,300 USD. For another $350,000, you can have an evil scientist shoot torpedos at you from another boat-car:       
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Coke's finally jumped onto the low-carb scene, a move that's suprising to...erm...only one person. And he's been stuck in a cave, on Mars, with his eyes shut and his hands over his ears.  They're introducing "Coke C2" Tuesday, in an ad being shown during American Idol. Supposedly, it's got half the calories, carbs, and sugar of Coke Classic, but retains the taste, for people who want to cut back but don't like Diet Coke.   Personally, I think all this "low-carb" and "look at me, I'm skinnier then an anorexic penguin" attitude that the country has is bullshit. As long as you're not inhaling sugar like you need it to live and you're getting in a good 20-30 minutes of running every 1-2 days, you should be fine. Nobody cares what you look like except for yourself.  Too many people worry too much about their health. And guess what?  That means they're not fucking healthy!    But, what're you going to do? As long as companies are going to make globs of money off diet this and low-carb that, they'll keep tricking people into buying it. Hell, I'll support them, it's a brilliant marketing strategy. DRINK THIS BECAUSE YOU'RE FAT:   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend of mine has just recently graduated High School, and will be moving off to college shortly. He's excited, but he keeps mentioning how much he'll miss his friends. It really tought me something, and that's to cherish the friends you have, because sooner then you'd like, they'll be gone.   (Shoutout to Mike, Steve, Phil, Ken, Ashley, Matt, David, John, TJ, Joe, Megan, Arrigo, John, Pat, Kristin, and the rest of you! Ya'll kick ass.)
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know what would be really funny? If the internet caused people to go into some kind of spastic relapse 30 years or so after the first time they used it. Then you'd just have a bunch of Amish people going "What the fuck?"
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone, finally back online. School's almost over, just have one more day and finals to worry about, then I'm in the clear for a little while. Unless, of course, some guy with a flamethrower decided to chase me down. Then I'd be screwed.  Since I stopped writing, I picked up an Xbox. Most of the games are lots of fun, and online play over Live is a LOT better then with PCs, thanks to the voice capabilities, which allow for easily coordinated teamwork. I'm mostly playing Rainbow Six, so if you want to play me (and probably kick my ass), my GamerTag is RecklessSoldier. I've also been playing  Full Spectrum Warrior,  and it's actually pretty cool. I wrote up a review that can be found  urlLink here.   Anyone ever notice how goddamn hard it is to open one of those plastic "blister packs?" If you haven't, well, it's goddamn hard! They should use that material to make nuclear fallout shelters or protect soldiers or something. You need a freakin blowtorch to get through these things.   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Opened up my blog again. Good news for the two of you who actually read the thing. :p  I'll start posting again soon.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I can just type anything here and it'll sho...
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think so.  I think peanut butter would be better if it came with a free monkey. You know, a peanut-butter monkey. It would make the sandwhich for you and shit, then run away and live in a box on 5th avenue. 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to be broke before the end of the summer. For starters, I'm picking up some new Paintball equipment, and I need a new goalie mask.&nbsp;Other then that, check out this list of releases- &nbsp; -Doom 3 (PC, August 3rd) -RB: Black Arrow (X-Box, August 3rd) -Madden 2005 (X-box, August 9th) -ShellShock, Nam '67 (X-Box, August 24th) -Half-Life 2 (PC, September 1st) -CoD: United Offensive (PC, September 14th) &nbsp; And probably a lot more stuff I can't remember.  &nbsp; &nbsp; Anybody in the market for a new spleen*? How about a kidney? Anyone? &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;  *Spleen only available in the contiguous 48 states and Canada  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh. Fevers really do suck. I'm rediciously tired, but I can't fall asleep. I'm hot, but can't turn on the AC. I'm hungry, but I can't manage to eat. It's really a bad situation, so I'm just trying to soldier on and not let it get in my way, but it's rough. If anyone has any advice or "home remedies," by all means, share them. :p
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I heard some rumors going around there may not be a next season for the NHL, due to lock-outs and salary issues.   All I have to say is: WTF?  Hockey  has  to be making enough money for it to stay alive and the organization to try and save itself. If the NHL goes down the tubes, thousands, if not millions, of people will lose their jobs. Not just players, either. Coaches, technicians, doctors, everyone down to the zamboni drivers. I don't know the specifics, but I really hope the problems are fixable, for the game, the players, and all involved.  Long Live Hockey.    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMGOMGOMGOMGOMGOMGOMGOMG   urlLink Red Vs. Blue  have just released the finale for season 2. It's about 13 minutes long, and really, REALLY funny. If you don't go check it out, you deserve to be slapped. Hard.  With a hammer.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I picked up a new book the other day, mostly because a friend of mine recommended it to me.  urlLink Last Citadel  is a historical action novel about the Battle of Kursk, the last German offensive on the Eastern front during World War 2. It's pretty good so far, and if you know what a T-34 or Tiger Mark IV is, you should check it out.  Aside from that, Burger King's Angus Burger is pretty good, if you like your food to taste like crap. At first it was ok, but then I realized I was expecting something more along the lines of food, not crap.   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not going to get into Politics here, aside from the oppertunity to make a quick joke at either party. But, when I saw this picture at  urlLink Rock, Paper, Saddam  I had to caption it.    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just once, I'd like to see Bond screw it up, and have the world explode. Just once. Think about it. No one would see it coming, and it would shock audiences worldwide. There might even be a parade.  So Bill Cosby recently spoke out on the black community. Sort of like a State of the Blackness address, if you will, and for the most part, I agreed with him. I'm a huge believer in education, and without it, you  will  go down the tubes, and have no chance at success in life, unless you get incredibly lucky somehow. Like if you have a lucky hat, or something. It's not just black people, either, and it's certainly not all black people, or perhaps even many. Way too many people of all ethnicities are putting education aside, and it's going to really damage the future.   I just felt the need to point out that in newer BMW models, an iPod can be connected to the car itself and controlled via the steering wheel audio controls. If that's not awesome, nothing is. Now, all that's left is getting that BMW. Might be hard, eh?
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sick and tired of hearing what people think about politics. You see people arguing over the 'net about it all the time, but why the fuck bother? You're not going to change anybodies minds, and they're not going to change yours, you're just going to aggravate yourself. What's the point? It's sort of like trying to convince a toaster it's a lamp shade. It just...doesn't work.  24-hour news channels piss me off for the same reason. It's not the news anymore, it's people's opinions, and I don't give a crap what these people think. Just give me the news, and let me decide for myself. 
    
</post>


</Blog>