<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    this is jeremy sumpter&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    gir&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey ppl  today i hav my lil cousin joey over for a while. while hiz mom duz some stuff. i cooked more food today. homemade mac an cheese kame out the bomb. i had to wait to take a shower cuz i dodn't no wut exact time he was actualli coming  wel there is nuttin to talk bout. so peec luv an chikn greec
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    ain't he beautiful&nbsp; urlLink    i meen look at his face its almost in the right position but he's very kute {ppl if u don;t know who this is he plays legolas in lotr}
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        i'm so freekin happy right now. cuz yesterday skool finished. an then other stuff to. i brang my xbox to skool to play wit my friendz an other ppl.   then the most beat thing happened. my crush EDDIE STACK{if your reedin this} came in the room to play. i brang this game called dead or alive3. an i played against him a few times. i felt so happy wen he walked in. i had to stopp playin for couple ov minutes because my hands were reeli shaki. i thought i was gonna die or hava sezour or sumthing thats how how bad i was shakin.   softer a while i calmed down an then i went bak to playinthe game an i versed EDDIE  a fews times an he kiked my ass reeli bad{i guess he doesnt hava lot ov time on his hands} get it.      this summer i'm goin on a diet to loose alot of wieght. i'm gonna pik up inline or agrressive skating this summer. an i hope learn more tricks on my board that i need to fixe reeli badli cuz a car ran over my old one. so basicalli i need a new one.    i'm goin to my moms house this summer. an she told me that there r sum skater boys around my age that i kan hopefulli meet an chil for the rest of the summer.                 peec luv an chikn greec  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        right now i'm so bored at my house wit my like 4 friends. i reeli don't know wut to say.there reli isn't nuttingoin on in my lil old life but more EDDIE STACK{the kid i like in skool} sorry there is reeli nuttinelse to say buy ppl to whom is ever readn this
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      this is my first post   high ppl my name is natty i'm 15 an that's all your getting 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          i'm finalli in florida wit my mom. an i'm sik as a dog i'm coughin like crazi an sniffin an syff like that/ i've been here since the 4th of july an i wana go home. but i'm gonna be here for the hole summer.  i areedi made my mom sik an i hope to get better by yhte moment but i don't cee it happening.   no offense but i luv my mom an all but i alreed i wanna go home to my kat my room my bed an my friends. i mis my kat so much its not even funni i hav no klue how i'm deelin wit him right now, i'm always hime alone an he's always the onw there for me. now that i'm away hes not there to comfort me me an lay there wit me bye my side.  nobodi to kuddle wit or to wake me up in the we hours of the mornig to feed him.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>