<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uhh...today is my last day to rest,cos tomorrow i start working lor... Some how today get rabbit' sis call me for lunch n go JJ lepak. Today i feel so lucky day, cos buy everything cheap cheap one. Another thing make me happy is the phone call from Clara Beautician!! She call me for contract employment for abt 2 mth,so sorry i cant get the offer. I oso dont like the interviewee attitude,remember last time i go for the interview. She is so 'LCLY', she say to me if u r beautician i can offer u RM1500++. Then she said nowadays office work is no used n no value at all. Office work is so cheap, n ask me better go back home town if not i cant survive at kl. Today wen she call me, she ask me whether being emplot o not, she have great offer to me. Heh~~I tell her i have advance course to take at full time n not decide to work lor... She sound like not happy,cos she say i cant survive if i didnt get a job. Wen u find job,never let those 'hidung tinggi' ppl mark u as the stupid fresher n 'eat' ur price. During interview,she suddenly recommend their product n say how gd is it. U know by the time she giv tat beauty intro to me,i m looking her face. My heart think tat:"Wat a wrinkle n not elastic face,how u persuade ppl to buy~~~" Anywhere hope tat tomorrow is the lucky day lor...Kambateh!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If u had been there b4 u wil find out that this mamak stall is very success. The famous food likes Naan, bbq burung kecil, tosai and others. The seat is circle around the shop, and many leng lui n liang chai go there. Excluded us like the animal run out from the cage. I personally like the ‘Cheese Naan’ n the the ais there oso tasty. Every time we went there must sit n have a long talk, we r so talkative. The boss knows speak mandarin n Cantonese, he act like the magician wen bill. He has his own skill by used of his hand to check whether the cash is real o not…… Cool…u knows!! Steady n like magician…   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      接到家里的来电，就知道家里有人又闯祸啦！ 那就是我的小弟，课业问题和不听话咯。 此时就当上了辅导师，劝劝我的小老弟，要乖不要顶嘴和打电动。 讲了一番后，希望往后的日子会有点改变吧！ 电话盖了后，我发觉这一路走来还真不容易。  在独中念书不是件容易的事，还好我能顺利毕业，间中路还走的蛮坎坷的。 但也因此觉得中学生涯还真是多姿多彩和充实写意。 现在轮到我的弟弟要面临独中的生活，希望他也熬得过来和学习独立。 然后呢…就不要进拉曼，丢出国去留学，等他中学毕业时学历要求更高了！  以前我的理想是到牛津大学，泰莱大学念酒店管理。 后来没有把心完全放在课业，而每天忙碌着篮球练习。 曾经想当职业篮球手，在十五岁就参加全国赛，应该是好的开始！ 谁知竟然意外扭伤了腰间中骨螺丝，半年内都不能用力，甚至走路都会痛。 从此以后我开始过着没有人生理想和梦想的过日子…… 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do u all know tat at Ampang Park there have a great food stalk start biz at the early morning until noon only. At the Ampang area there have a very famous food Of “Yong Tao Fu”!! The location is near the Ampang Point there, the most famous and cook tasty food is located at the area. They have 2 shops commence biz beside each other, but they have their own secret recipe to cook the food.  The 1st shop has variety of choices and not only “Yong Tao Fu”.  U can have the meal like Asam Laksa Fish, “Yong Tao Fu”, “beggar chicken”, sizzling and fried food. They provide many choices depend on the food u like. The 2nd shop is the very traditional Yong Tao Fu n has many years of experience n cook in traditional recipe. The choices of the Yong Tao Fu really have many choices from the fried, soup cooking, braise, brew and others. And one thing u find out special in this shop is …If u have went ‘Redbox’ before u find out the servant there used the mic to pass order o even the Burger king. Here also….hahaha…once the kitchen is ready the food for serve up table,the chief wil use the mic to call theirs servant to pick up the food for customers. Sound like:”Table 12 have order 10 pieces of Yong Tao Fu, Please served now!!” I know this place once we skip the class n go there to eat the tasty food there. I like the place but I think must have car is better n convenience to go there. The price is fair dealing n not so expansive, if have the time I wish to go there one more time lor…  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      “真爱是无法天长地久，只能曾经拥有！” 人生短短几十年，既然都不能长久，为何不能努力等待心中的Mr. Right. 很多人在还没恋爱前，都会想像心中的“他”是拥有那几项的条件的。 每一个人的心中都会有她自个儿认为完美的情人。 但往往会成为恋人或老公的…都不是之前心中的Mr. Right.  是因为失去耐性，因为等待的他还在遥远的地方。一旦失去了耐性和坚持，放弃了等待而选择了眼前人。是因为寂寞难耐，还是害怕“等无此人”。时间久了心中的恐慌悠然而升，一旦有人对你好一点点，感动万分而选择了眼前为你守候了很久的痴情汉。这是爱情？还是同情？  Mr. Right一定就像童话故事里头的白雪公主与白马王子。听起来还蛮幼稚的，但最完美的爱情是来自那最纯真的心而互相珍惜彼此。而不是时下的“快熟面”，煮得快（一见钟情），吃得快（亲密接触），吃腻了丢得也快（分手快乐）！Mr. Right相等于初恋般的滋味，就是酸酸甜甜地；就像红酒般那么香醇迷人。  “先苦后甜”，相信‘好事’永远都在苦日子挨过了后，才能尝到最珍贵的甜蜜‘结果’。在这科技急速发展的社会，人们脚步加快；然而在爱情世界也同样的，来得快去的也快，正符合轻快铁的速度。但请相信在你心中的Mr. Right 其实就在下一个车站等着你的到来，只是你还没遇到那辆“幸福小巴士”而已。  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      人與人的相遇就像是一個隨機抽樣  在不同的時間空間之中.....彼此相遇....  有些時候...你會發現..你一開始最看不順眼的人   竟然是你的好友.......  因為你發現了他的好....  有時候...你根本不想去認識一個人....你覺得無趣    後來你卻發現...... 他是你想要認識的那種人...  有時候.....你非常喜歡一個人....但是你知道...你們根本不能在一起....  愛你的人....你不愛..你不愛的人...卻是那樣的愛你.....  這複雜的習題卻又如此的跟著我們...解不開也算不清  人家說在對的時間愛一個人...你是幸福的...  在錯的空間遇到一個人....你是痛苦的.....  有些人你就是有一種一見如故的感受  有些人你怎樣就是說不上幾句話  像是一部公車　大家在這一站上車　又在另一站下車  事事總是充滿變數與未知  曾經感情很好的朋友　即使感覺還在　可是大家都有自己的事情而疏離  所以大家要珍惜每次都偶然邂逅  因為你根本不知道　錯過了這次　你跟他會在哪個空間在相遇  也許是你們唯一一次的相遇    緣是個很奇怪的東西  它可以讓在相距數千公里外的人在同一處相遇  這是你我無法想像的到的  但　它就是這樣  可是若是沒在適當時機好好把握  也許就再也沒機會了....... 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i wake up at 7:30am,y??play badminton wit my fren lor... But actually i m not so good in playing badminton. We play until 10am,then wen i back after shower n...sleep 4 another 30 min. Afterward,wake up n study my secretary practice,as to prepare for 1st of July. I plan i have to finish this revision in 5 days more. One day for shopping n the other day for watch my life last movie before i go to work.. Actually i m a bit,i think not a bit...is very tension n panic to start my first job. So start fm now everyday i have to practice my typing skills and revise my study. Yeah!!is being prepared to start my career there. By the time i start jobless after graduate,i have make to wish to my "wishing Star Bottle"!! One wish is come true now...so i can say wat the wish i make...My wish is to get the job at the KLCC area there n is co. sec firm n provide great opportunity for me to learn n build my career... The other wish still no sign at all... Hi fren!!If u have some wish tat u think u cant tell other n hope to say out ur wish...u can follow my steps!! -"Wishing Star Bottle"   During to make a wish,take one paper tat can make a star.   Before tat write ur wish at the paper,the close ur eyes n make the wish.   After tat make the star n drop into the bottle.(size like Sub-zero is ok!!) I not say every wish wil be come true,but unless u can put ur hope n secret thing in somewhere tat ppl dont know it!! "Dont worry be happy!!"  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      有次，老许对著两个吵闹不休的女儿训话说道：“你们别再吵了行不行？难怪有人说，两个女人加起来等于一百只麻雀……” 就在这个时侯，老许的老婆打电话回家，大女儿接完之后，转头向老许问道：“电话中有‘五十只麻雀’问你晚上要吃什么？”  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is so happy,cos i get the job!! Actually today i really dont wan to go for the interview...cos i am a bit blur tat ...i dont noe wat the co name call for me actually...hehehe... So i juz have the address n contact no. only. Although i get lost at the middle road...finally i have reach there. I didnt expected i have to take an hour to fill in the employment form and ans Q that have few pages... 1st i have write the article approximately to 150 words,n the 2 pages of co. sec Q. After the whole interview,i feel so nice to talk wit my interviewee...she is so nice person. Every Q she ask me i juz try my best to be honest ans her...cos this is my real habit n my own way of thinking...I think i m too honest...But luckyly she accepted my positive attitude...i m so appreciate the golden opportunity tat she given for me. I wil try my best n not to let her disappointed. Afterward,go to meet my nice icq fren. Finally we meet,i m a bit shy...n dont noe how to start talking. I guess he might think i am a quiet girl...hahaha... If we become very fren to each other,he wil be regret to noe me...Y?? Cos i m so naughty n 3 8 lor...n talk so much... Ha~~'Mr.Tiang' once u read this blog as to tell u tat...'Nice To Meet U!!' Have a nice day n be enjoy...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      有次，阿信到非洲自助旅行，由于天气炎热，因此，当他经过一条河流时，就想到河中游游泳，消消暑气，但又怕河里有食人鱼，于是他就向岸边的土著问道：“河里没有食人鱼？” 土著答道：“没有！” 阿信听了之后，随即放心大胆地跳入水中游泳，游了一阵之后，他觉得不放心， 又探起头向岸上的土著问道：“你为何那么肯定河中没有食人鱼呢？” 土著答道：“因为，食人鱼虽然凶猛，但是，它们还是不敢在鳄鱼的地盘上撒野……” 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of the great food stalk in KL...i think is Jalan Alor. No matter in the morning until the evening. At the morning...i think only the early bird can make it... Cos i find out one shop sell claypot seafood food. The shop is very unique...y??Once u reach the shop u wil c the words "Only one shop dont have any branches" Another unique sign is they introduce their meal by writing in the poem. The price per bowl is not expansive,everyone is affordable. I like the meatball n the 'shui jiao'. Very big n tasty,RM0.70 each...especially the meatball is handmake. N the nite market at there oso...... I like there very much... Remember last time i went there is wen i m so sick...my fren bring me there eat n go to c doctor. Before i m so sick,after eat the food there i feel better...Then i tell them no need to c doctor lor...Cos i afraid to c doctor!! Who know the next day i m serious sick...my face white like paper n my lips become green. My housemate is frightened...n quickly bring me c doctor... Lastly,no matter i m sick o not i oso go there to have the great taste food!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      一步一步踏出大门口     我仿佛看见明天呼唤我 我以为我会       不停疑问      我是否属于我 大早起来     我梳洗好头发    身穿好衣裳 表面冷酷酷    内心热腾腾    兴奋来不及 啦~~~   别老是想自己是个“量地官” 挺起胸膛往外面世界闯一闯    摇身变成大老板   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      世界上最遥远的距离           不是生与死 而是我站在你面前             你却不知道我爱你  世界上最遥远的距离           不是我站在你面前       你却不知道我爱你 而是明明知道彼此相爱         却不能在一起  世界上最遥远的距离           不是明明知道彼此相爱   却不能在一起 而是明明无法抵挡这种思念     却还得故意装作丝毫没有把你放在心里  世界上最遥远的距离           不是明明无法抵挡这种思念      却还得故意装作丝毫没有把你放在心里 而是用自己冷漠的心           对你爱的人             掘了一条无法跨越的沟渠  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today my interview location is at Menara Uni Asia,a huge building. I think today i have a great day,cos... Once i reach the office main door,when i came out from the lift i meet a handsome guy. Woh~~~He is very tall n very gorgeous!! And he look like very gentleman,wat a lucky day let me meet the guy. During the interview,the intervwee also very nice,and he tell me in detail of the company secretary duties and responsibilities... And today interview i am so energetic and i hope tat i being choosen among all the participants. Y??Once i get the job i can meet the handsome guy always lor... I think the working place oso convenience to me. That all for my interview...n i have another interview held at Wed...Good luck again lah!!Hahaha...To meet another tall n handsome guy...i wish...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      某日下午，小雯向刚结婚半年的小爱问道：“男人，在订婚前像什么？” 小爱答道：“像个孙子！” 小雯不解地问道：“为什么？” 小爱补充答道：“因为在订婚之前，男人绝对会像‘孙子’般地对你百依百顺。” 小雯继续问道：“那么，在订婚之后，男人又像什么？” 小爱答道：“像儿子！” 小雯问道：“这又是为什么？” 小爱答道：“因为，男人在订婚之后，就会像'儿子’一样，开始学会顶嘴。” 小雯接着又问道：“那么结婚之后，男人又像什么呢？” 小爱答道：“结婚之后，就像个老子，开始向你发号施令。” 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why i am sick for today?? Cos yesterday accompany my fren n her mom go for eat. They wish to eat the delicious food at KL,n ask to bring along them Shopping n "eat"! Firstly we go to 'Kimcary' eat Hong Kong traditional food. Afterward go to Timessquares,also eat...eat...n eat... The last move to 'Chi Qiong Gai',we walk around n they choose the small stalk they wan to eat for. We have our dinner beside Hong Leong Bank there,the food is very special. They cook by using Alluminuim Paper pack the food...have many choice like... Sotong,fish,chicken wing,vegetables and others... We pick 3 meal of sotong,fish n chicken wing. Something we r unexpected is all the food is very hot n spicy. Yeah...is all served with hot chili n samba. Tat y today i really sick cos eat too much of hot n spicy food. Now have a bit of fever...it cant be...cos tommorrow i have to go for interview leh... 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i wake up earlier for prepare for the important interview! When i reach there,wah~~~So marvelous the place. And i c the signboard state "Pusat Perdagangan". The very unique place for working n the environment is so nice! Then i have an interview on time,the interviewee called Mr.Lee. We have a long talk for the interview,somehow Mr. Lee is quite nice. He briefly explain everything for to noe wat i have to do now. Afterward i have bring for the test on typing skills...... How nervous i am cos 2 people look me type from the back. So tension and panic that i feel so uncomfortable. Hmmm.....Wen the interview is finish i go back home n terus pengsan... Dont noe y tat i am so sick for this few days n so pressure.... Hope tat tomorrow i wil be fine......n no more any headache.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      紫：代表浪漫，在这无限的空间里，尽情发挥心中地喜怒哀乐！！  梦：代表幻想，在这奇幻的空间里，将梦化为美妙地奇幻旅程！！  坊：代表自我，在这私人的空间里，让知己们真正地一起分享！！ 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dont know why i am so careless that let my leg injured all the time. I am in office work but who know this few week i make my leg seriously injured. 1stly is my leg hit by the thick n heavy minutes book,then paint. Then i am so careless n hit by the heavy chair n my leg now is 'o che'. Now 2 leg also 'o che',then...hmmm this timw more serious is my foot is hurt by my new shoes. Some shoe make the lady look sexy but seksa,i am so stupid n let the new shoes hurt again my leg...... Now my foot is serious hurt n very paintful,i cant even walk properly now. I am so sorry to my leg that always not take care of it n let it hurts n paint always... Yes,is always not juz one time only...oh~~~So bad i am to treat my leg like that. Now dont know when my leg well fine!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The dreamlanf of the I-Robot!! I think this movie wil giv u an unexpected ending story, So i only can grade it as C only...Stil can watch it lah i think...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      People laugh people cry, people live&nbsp;in Emotional; People live people die, people live&nbsp;in&nbsp;Reality; People&nbsp;win people loss, people live&nbsp;in Competition; People love people hate, people live&nbsp;in&nbsp;Everyone; People stand people sit, people live&nbsp;in Command; People talk people scold, people live&nbsp;in Political; People fight people attack, people live&nbsp;with&nbsp;Enemy.  "Face the reality,face the truth,never make youeself being lefy behind of other." "We are not born to&nbsp;left behind other people,we can walk infront of&nbsp;those people."&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I sick but not fever is citir-birit,once i eat must rush to go in toilet. Now i afraid to eat but i am hungry now...so how?! They all go to practice dancing,cos next friday note have the annual dinner party. So they want to make some dancing performance,n i not decide to go. Dont know wil make them angry of me or not,cos i really not feeling well for the moment...hope tomorrow i wil become more better! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my I-Robot,but he only know dancing only...Wen i feel bored and unhappy...its will dance n i still remember i bought this robot wit my fren...we buy it at Sri Rampai pasar malam...although its juz little but its work oso!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I so afraid that i m&nbsp; easily get headache n south throat. Today i really not feeling, dont know whether is my job o my brain is oredi stuck now n can even have the answer that i want it now!! I really have to attend sth like the English class to upgrade myself n&nbsp;dont the chance for other to say i m so poor in English. But i really dont have the time n the problem i face in my job is...i didnt get the motivation n inspire spirit to perform my job well. Start fm 2nd week i always ask myself...am i suit for this job? Then 3 rd week i start to face the office political. How can?!I havent pass by the one month in this job n i already meet all those problem! B4 that i have other diff field of part time work,n i&nbsp;meet many ppl... But in this place i juz can say those ppl also act like 'small ppl' but the diff is they used their high educated knowledge to step on the head&nbsp;on the 'young bird'. As a conclusion,Malay ppl is really very nice n always ready to giv u a hand to help n take care of u...Until now i always help by the&nbsp;Malay ppl,although they didnt have high education...but they have their gentle n kindly attitudes to treat u like their fren n not enemy. Unless they know the freshes have the problem in new environment n always motivate u how to face it...That why i being confuse whether to leave or not...Hmmm&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Pringles really is my favourite junk food...Now its was cheap sale at Guardian cost RM3.89!!If u oso like it can go there n pick either in original or sour flovour...yumi :P&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    See how close to each other...this pic wil never appear for now loh! Anywhere the 'Tai Lou' change his hair style to freaky n short hair oredi...n his's fox gf wil be married in next month n have invite our only fren Joan to go...y is Joan cos she sms her then the fox ask her to participate her wedding lor!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dont know why,tis July i felt so hard to pass the time. N i always repeat to ask myself wat the ppl i wish to be n now... i make the big decision for now...i want to quit! In my plan i hope i can get the job wch allow me to further other field of study. Cos as generally office working time is 9am-5pm. I oredi plan to take course at 6pm-9pm at systematic. But now i cant,cos always start work at 8.15am-9pm. And make me dont have the time to do other thing n the task is not innovative n inspire. I m so felt up the perception of those ppl i meet,n my 1st sense tell me tat i not even have the motivation to work in this kind of environment. So i try my best to survive in kl n get the other job b4 i really have to giv notice to tis co. Hope i have make the rite decision n not b'cos of my childish emotion.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday nite i have great enjoy to watch the Channel [V] 2003 concert. That why today i feel so sleepy,n no energy to perform in work. And onother reason is others element thatt make me few unhappy. But nevermind i like music very much,so i cant lease all the unhappy by singing loudly in my room,no one can disturb or stop me for doing that!! Music is always in my life,without music without fun! The energy make me survive......
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Faye juz 23 years old n have the great voice like Ah-mei n Alanis Morrisette...she have a great future in the music industries...i like her very much!Kambateh yo \(^O^)/&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I always easily get headache,but today is b'coz of thinkin wat kind of digital cam is worth to buy. I think i cant b tat rush without survey of the px n buy it immediately. So i decide wait for next week end go Sg, wany there to cont my survey process. The worst thing is&nbsp;i m so out of knowledge in the selection of those hi-tech equipment. Like my notebook,i survey n asking others n take 2 years time to decide wch brand is worth to buy,luckily now stil perform very well. But my printer is too bad,juz used for 3 months only then problem occured n i force to buy another one...... I really fell headache wen have to decide for buy those thing!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tis is some pic i get fm my YG magazine fren,u guess where they visit the place in KL??&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Announcement tat SHE confirm open a big concert in KL at 11st November 2004 at Bukit Jalil Stadium outdoor!!Huh leh!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Long long time ago the nite we go to Sg. wang  Redbox VIP room have own toilet one n sing-k until morning......&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Finally i get the corrs new album,yeah!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm,i m so glad tat can go to the mini concert of FIR. I like to hear for live of those great singer o band performance. From the nite i start to admire how cool of Ah Qing performance n he is so attractive wen he play electronic guitar...... I reach there at 9p.m.,tis is the 1st time i attend in late,wah!!!many ppl juz more than last time i go to c Energy n Machi. I think tat Malaysia ppl is nothin to do,once the artist is come they wil always appear many ppl n so frightened,more ppl is not a bad news...but sometimes there wil b so crazy until someone is hurt n force the singer afraid to come out n cancel the show then...is not good lor!!! Altho i come late,but luckily still have the great place to view n take photo,i think mine one is not tat nice,but my other fren have,so i wait for them to pass Ah Qing pic for me...Hehehe...   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is a great show i m being watchin them in Warp.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the F.I.R. on live in KL,n there r so many ppl to watch their show......&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    F.I.R. in Warp dance club,Faye is very pretty,Ryan is very smart n Ian is very cool~~~&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Until today i still confuse wat i wish to be n wat i hope can get it n where i can get it...... I can imagine tat i m so alone n stay at the middle of the ocean,depends on the direction of my boat n dont noe where is the actual place i want to go. I m become more confuse n confuse now...but never mind one thing i can so sure is today i can go to enjoy the mini concert of F.I.R at warp dance club!! Life must be full of fun n not juz working only...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cutie  SHE now become more pretty n sexy in the 'Golden Award 2004' in Taiwan!! They will open a big concert in KL soon at November 2004,i wil be there to watch their great show!!                   &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We must fight for our future like tis cutie baby who support u always...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My new favourate band FIR is now in KL...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Wat do u think tat who is the target this cat wish to shoot??&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    There are my frenx who study at Liverpool JohnMore University...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yesterday i am so glad tat all my best fren make a phone call to me fm far away.  Firstly is Rabbit who make call fm Kluang n talk so much n we wil meet in next week.  Secondly,this really bring&nbsp;me a surprise tat calling fm overseas tat is fm Liverpool leh...  All my best fren at Tarc call for me yesterday,we talk approximately half an hour.  Finally they giv me a call,sigh...they not forget me ...hmm...a bit touching lor!?  By the time they call me they all stay at the Shefield' Strawberry Farm,n let me hear the sound eating the strawberry,they all really bad err...  Nevermind,i can show off to them how enjoy i am at here to watch many varieties i can.  Because tat is too expansive to watch at Liverpool,RM 21 sth...so there all not afford to watch the blockbuster movie!!  Mr Ronan wish to watch Spidey 2,hahaha...i watch liao lor...hope can let them drool tat can not watch the movie wch they waiting so long oredi...hehehe...     
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my idol called Wallace Huo Jian Hua&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my first pic upload to my blog...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Nice people i meet today    &nbsp; Firstly is the TARC college staff,they provide a gentle n nice svc to me wen i request for my transcript,n giv a confirmation tat will ready for next week in sharp. &nbsp; Second person is my icq fren,happy tat he still borrow me the vcd drama,then i can have a nice weekend. &nbsp; Thrid is the Nicole gal stuff sales gal,the indian gal is nice n good svc oso. &nbsp;  Bad people i meet today    &nbsp; Firstly is the carrefour promoter,i only buy table fan then he dont svc me n quickly go to other customer who buy microwave n rice cooker. But one thing is funny,if u wan to be the promoter of the electonic dept. U must have 'misai' n fat body n oso cury hair then u can be employ. Cos all of them is look like tat one...really standard like the 'SIRIM' mark for their eletrik. &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1st is the morning "cha guo's stalk",the aunt is very polite n gentle. She greet me morning n have a nice day...i m so surprise n juz smile to her only.  2nd is the lrt's security,once i reach the 'mountain ppl moutain sea'to take lrt. He walk around n warning those passenger be queue n care of ur own safety.  3rd thing i assume mayb happen in office,who noe today i bored at office n wan die.  Actually 3rd thing happen in lrt oso,a malay gal stand in front of me. She is crying n her fren try to calm down her n giv some advice to her. She cry n look like very sad...  Happiness is not always surround us,i think only the bad n sad thing will always accompany to grow up. Once u meet ur happiness never let it go tat easy,cos is too hard to get it. N for me i treat 'Happiness' as my treasure...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whole day do failing job,half way wan to die cos too many failing to do for. And i am so thankful to my heas tat she teach me so many thing n giv me the opportunity to learn from them... My head is the very very nice person,i think i m so lucky can meet her for my 1st job. But...today i half way die in the data storing room,ppl dont noe i m inside then they close the row...a bit like the Sandwich...luckily not be the 100% fat sandwich!! One day tat over n past so fast.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I believe tat everyone have their own goal n mission to reach n achive. No matter who u r,u shd make ur life more means to urself n ppl around u. We born to bright up our life not to sit there n nothing to do n thinkin tat y my life is tat bored...... We make our life more means then waiting someone put u into the 'Happy Basket'! So i re-new the look of my room,hope can have a new inspiration n thinkin. Thing shd change,ppl can not always stand at the same point: change wen needed; change wen u stuck; change wen u bored; change wen u halfway wan to die; change wen u sad; change wen u lonely...... change watever u wish but never change the truth heart inside of u......  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      这几天不时都会不停的在问自己，一生中活着是为什么而活?希望得到什么？在追求什么？走出门时是有目的地的吗？还是像个苍蝇般地盲目冲撞？！  这一生所订下的目标、理想和抱负都离我好远，也渐渐地一个跟着一个删除掉…… 只留下一句歇后语，那就是“过一天算一天，多一天玩一天。”  人人都说我幼稚，不管是长辈、同辈还是晚辈。 但必要时，还会吓人一跳；那就是……还是那么幼稚！！  这几天的生活就是，早起上班、午休用膳、晚归休息。 好平凡啊~~~有约太晚又不敢去，怕明早起来变成一只熊猫去上班。 不行啊！这样会被抓去动物园……  我的生活就像白饭那样，粒粒皆幸苦；然而生活也尤如白饭般，平凡且清淡。  最近和白色很有缘，上衣是白的、鞋子是白的、文件是白的、天空是白的、空气是白的，就连我的脑袋都一片空白的……  对啊！我好想去旅行，去环游世界，感受大自然的清新与幽美。 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      y i say like tat...wan sth u wish to know,to meet,to ger,to have,to join n etc. U wil never make ur wish,but wen u give up all the wish... Then all the thing wil be appear n appear... Long long time ago,i wish to meet a guy in my living area,cos he live very near to my living area...but we never meet,n meet at college. Everyday wen i walk back to home i always wish i can meet him. Now i dont wan to c he face anymore,then tis few day we meet twice. Previous wen i saw his face fm far far away...i wil very heart attack one... But now wen i saw him i wil say "wat a bad day to meet him again"! I m a bad gal,so i m so alone now...n waiting for someone tat he never come back. i know he never come back,cos he imigrant to American...then i stil waiting him...mayb one day he may come back...we know each other for a long long time ago... So can i not to say tat the god juz kidding to u?! Wen i wish so its not dreams come true,wen i giv up then all the dreams is come true...but i dont have the heart to welcome its anymore...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A week i start work...i learn many thing like Blar blar n blar #$@?! But beside tat my fren they all r very busy n i m so 'eng eng cheng cheng' I think i can go to die la...i bring junk food n eat wen really bored n nothing to do. At ampang park have one new pub open n today is 'Lady Nite'!! My fren ask me to go but i still thinkin...coss tomorow have tooo work leh... I really 'fan jian' wish to get more jobs to do. Cos my environment hare is everyone is very rush up for sth but i m too free liao. Hei...wat can i do,i always finish on time wen each job assign by my head. But a learn many thing juz a bit here n a bit there,so hope tat the a bit wil be an 'Success Mountain' for build up my future career...Hope so! But...actually i m so confuse to my future...look like no future n so bored of my life!!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i m so busy n non-stop for doing my job. Until i left the office still left 7 more co. waiting for me to prepare the AGM doc. I m so sad tat i cant help my fren n resolve her upset n unhappy. She think she is buuly by the senior,but for me i dont think so. For her mayb a bit of hurt by those 'orang tua',wen she dont noe how to start a new job n those old ppl not teach her wat the whole procedure to do so...then die lor...she scold by the other dept. For me y i dont even think tat is hurt,cos mayb my skin is very thick n dont noe hurt gua...Or mayb i face many of tis kind of ppl. I hate ppl never think for the side of the shy n fresh workers po trainee. But sometime bully other act is needed once those ppl is very annoyed u n wit bad motive to treat u!Ha~~tis kind of ppl i half way wan to kill them. But juz kidding...i always bully by other,so i think i have the experience to handle it...n the same thing happen i wil take the chance to bully others.Hahaha........ Now i have the good idea,if once u wan to bully by ur bad ppl,u must at the same time bully by two bad ppl. WHY?Let say mr.A n mr.C at same time bully u,then u can used the act of Mr.A to stand wit Mr.C.(vice versus) So lonely tat no one chat wit me online,not even my icq fren n my fren study overseas. I m so alone,n dont noe how to entertain myself to happy n bright it up.......  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally,i go to klcc watch spidey 2. As a conclusion,quite nice i think. So long hour for the movie,b4 i go into the show i meet some fren at the cinema. I meet my johor's fren n my ICSA coursemate. Hoh~~i c the guy finally n his fren. Quite some time not c him at wangsa maju,then we meet at klcc...haha!so funny. Back to the movie,i think i m so impressed for the part tat the spidey 1st time show his face at public to safe the train passengers. But until the end still sense like next episode is waiting for u. I have another movie tat i wil go to watch,tat is--Anaconda!! Anywhere be enjoy,life is full of fun once u made colour to it.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Play Badminton   Today awake by mis cal,then is time for play badminton lor... Today is very stable n can play very well then b4. We r so enjoy for today event,afterwarg go to take breakfast. So happy can eat the 'chu qiong fen' at red traffic light corner. Another great thing happen is on the way we back,we decide to 'buang' See Kham into the swimming pool. But we felt to do so,cos she is too heavy, i m so scare tat i wil incident fall into the pool...so very careful.   Introduce u all the cutie junior in tarc--See Kham @ See Ham(seafood)   She is so unique n fun,wen u saw her face u wil be very happy!! She chi name is 诗琴 but i call her  晴丝(sunsilk),n the another name is see ham. She is unique,y?? Cos she have: -Long n cury hair nut like snowball -average body but very active. -know play guitar n very full of face expression. -talkative n so noisy. -her skin is very thick cos always say she is very gorgeous,guy will die wen saw her.  (u noe how to die?Cos she like dinosour,guy wil auto die o half die)  Msg For Ben's gang: If u all have visit my site,tell u all wen u all back i wil intro tis gal for u all. Ah Ben i saw u appear at w.maju,where?The tong sampah there have a fat cat find rubbish one.Cos u noe y i say its u,wen i call Ben the cat 'miaw' to me...so he is Banjamin Ong lor...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today start fm the morning nothing to do at all.Y?? Cos my head is not in yet,so i have to wait her back n have thing to do. Firstly i go to help my collegue,afterward they all very busy n not availabke to treat u. So i go back my temporary workplace at meeting room. I play game n online,then look at the KLCC view. Hei~~~nothing to do but other is very busy n me 'eng eng cheng cheng',die la tis time... must be fire very soon lor...cos so free n have time read newspapers. Luck after lunch i have thing to handle,start fm the prepation of AGM doc. Our co. have the free ticket for the staff,tis week is spiderman 2. But tis time ticket giv to accountant dept,but our mgr say tat at Aug-Sept wil have more movie ticket for our dept...i m waiting :) Today i meet Joan at last,abt 1 mth we dont meet,she say have resign the redbox job. Do u believe tat she have the end of her work at redbox??No way,someday she must go back to work. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i feel so surprise tat i know one familiar face at work,yup she is coursemate. Wah!So lucky have ppl accompany me at work n take lunch. I like those senior staff, they all treat u very nice n frenly. Firstday i have a informal meeting in manager room,the environment is good n full of laugh stuff. They all very funny n talkative! Today wat the first task i do for??Oh~~~I make checking on the doc n form whether correct o not. Sound like very easy but...my eyes is so tired now. u have to look thru every doc fm ROC,MA & AA,Forms,Incorporarion doc,notice, minutes, agenda n etc. Dont noe y there r trust tat we can do independence,cos one senoir juz take an eg to guide us then we do the rest by our own. Not all the co. have the same type of doc,today i check for one old co wch commence biz abt 13years then do u know the file is so thick...thick...FInish checking for tis file take abt an hour. The co. is huge cos its cover many biz line like audit,accountant,marketing,IT,HR,co. sec and other. We have our own table n computer,oso new stationery.(All in new even the computer is new purchase) Hope tomorow oso the lovely day for me...cos dunno y i feel a bit not satisfy to get tis job!! Cos tis kind of job i resist to do it after finish secondary so long time ago. But no choice i have to follow my father order,until i lie to ppl who ask me. Tis co interviewee have ask me one Q:"Do u like tis job to become a professonal co. secretary?"--I say 'Yes',but actually i m lie,tis is only the thing i lie to her. So sorry tat i wil try my best to like it!  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Theory of Mr President's Coca-cola&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      曲：周杰伦  词：方文山  编：钟兴民  窗外的麻雀 在电线杆上多嘴你说这一句 很有夏天的感觉手中的铅笔 在纸上来来回回我用几行字形容你是我的谁  秋刀鱼 的滋味 猫跟你都想了解初恋的香味就这样被我们寻回那温暖 的阳光 像刚摘的鲜艳草莓你说你舍不得吃掉这一种感觉  雨下整夜 我的爱溢出就像雨水院子落叶 跟我的思念厚厚一迭几句是非 也无法将我的热情冷却你出现在我诗的每一页  雨下整夜 我的爱溢出就像雨水  我接着写 把永远爱你写进诗的结尾你是我唯一想要的了解  那饱满 的稻穗 幸福了这个季节而你的脸颊像田里熟透的蕃茄你突然 对我说 七里香的名字很美我此刻却只想亲吻你倔强的嘴  雨下整夜 我的爱溢出就像雨水院子落叶 跟我的思念厚厚一叠几句是非 也无法将我的热情冷却你出现在我诗的每一页 整夜  我的爱溢出就像雨水 窗台蝴蝶像诗里纷飞的美丽章节 我接着写把永远爱你写进诗的结尾 你是我唯一想要的了解 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jay new album,this song is quite nice and romantic,giv ur self a chance to open the site to listen to Jay's songs.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When you are together with that special someone,  you pretend to ignore that person. But when that  special someone is not around, you might look  around to find them. At that moment, you are in  love.   Although there is someone else who always makes  you laugh, your eyes and attention might go only  to that special someone. Then, you are in love.   Although that special someone was supposed to  have called you long back, to let you know of  their safe arrival, your phone is quiet. You are  desperately waiting for the call!  At that moment, you are in love.   If you are much more excited for one short e-  mail from that special someone than other many  long e-mails, you are  in love.   When you find yourself as one who cannot erase  all the messages in your answering machine  because of one message from thatspecial someone,  you are in love.   When you get a couple of free movie tickets, you  would not  hesitate to think of that special someone. Then,  you are in love.   You keep telling yourself, "that special someone  is just a friend", but you realize that you can  not avoid that person's special attraction. At  that moment, you are in love.   While you are reading this page, if someone  appears in  your mind, then u are in love with that person.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometime ppl always waiting for something that he/she expected. But thing always happen like that once u have the hope but its never become real. Ppl always wait...Wait for ppl come...wait for live...wait for die...wait for play...wait for sleep...wait for money come...wait for chances...wait for sale... What i waiting for now...i also dont know. Until today i only know i really have somthing to wait...but the actual always like that...nothing is nice happen to me. So i dont want to wait for "it" anymore,cos so hard for waiting and i even wen "it" will become true!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my room...still like that messy...after work really dont have time to clean!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is the magazine i get free for today...b4 i see the advertisements i thought is V mag then actually is M8.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today morning i go to UOA trining viewpoint. Afterward tumbang another AM back to office n call her left us down at Ambank Group. U know wat happen we saw many ppl circle arounf the car...that is Asdvantage magazine promote car. They giv out some gift n prize like Extra chewing gum,drinks,magazines,cd n some poster n also calendar. U guests wat i get??I get the poster first,then is the Extra chewing gum,next is the Magazines...hahaha...i m so lucky la today n also the nice calendar wit the modern car pic one...  Wata nice day happen for me...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    These is Biz Admin COurse n Biz Management COurse of ppl go to the top-up programme. I think they really have a nica trip there...Wish they all the best n quickly camo back loh~~~&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    See how big,fresh,sweet n nice those strawberry. Really Fantasy!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Stawberry's Farm House in Shefield.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday i go to 1-U shoppin,my fren is very excited to buy clothes at there. But i and another fren call Li Hong (not Lee Hom),like to go bread shop to see how tasty those juz baked bread with fair deal px and look nice. We cant finish wall thru all the shop lot,but i also dont want to walk already. Why?Because those stuff very,very,very expansive and not worth to buy as for me. But my fren buy so many,then i juz help them and provide them some idea which one is better lor... N i myself juz buy a necklect,Cost RM9.90 with 10% discount then RM8.65 only. We left 1-U at 9.30 p.m. then go to SS2 take our dinner. We eat at 'New Paris's Restaurant',the food there very tasty;specially the restaurant famous meal Tau Fu gd taste. We have order other meal like the Thai Chicken,Pork Chop,Oyster xiao bai cai,and tien gai(Frog). Actually i want to eat steamboat,but my fren dont wan. Hei...dunno wen i can go to Jalan Kucha Lama's Telephone Restaurant eat the steamboat lor~~~
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If your guy have watch the Fear Factor program,you can get it disgusting! Yesterday nite i watch it at 11 10 p.m. at ntv 7. 1st round is the go-cart speed gear to stop at the right point n stop. Sound like very easy,but after the competition juz left 2 contestant (1 male n 1 female). Afterwards, is the 2nd round as usual is to have some unique n disgusting food eating.This time the game set out is to throw 4 ball into the basket at the wall. Once u lost to goal then have to drink the Special recipe in blended. What is the secret recipe's ingredient? -3 types of diff worm + mascarda crochoches with 4 small bowl. Yuck...Yuck...Yuck...i watch them drink 3 glass of the Special Drink!!! Afterward dont know whether is i to tired o watch until pengsan then i fall in sleep n dont know who is the winner at the last of the result. Fear fator always show the very very very disgusting meal,Hmmm... 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my office i think some unexpected problem arise always! Although not affect me but i treat those case as a reference for myself to be careful and used the proper way to communicate to people. The rice can let 100 kinds of people live in this planet,thus i think we should always be prepared will be faced those kind of 'Small People' at anytime and anyway. For my own point of view i think try to make urself happy and enjoy,if not life its not that easy to continue and survive...... I have the wish to travel and learn the diff living-style of diff country. The country i wish to go are: 1.   Japan      - Spring 2.   Taiwan     - Summer 3.   Canada     - Autum 4.   Korea      - Winter I wish one day my dream wil come true,dream always is the energy to push people towards and become more energetic.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [ 亲近则易生悔慢之心 ]  有时候，我们会对别人授予的小惠[ 感激不尽 ]， 欲对亲人，父母的一辈子恩情[ 视而不见 ]！ 因为，亲人对我们来说，太亲近了，说以我们看不见他们的好、看不见他们的牺牲！我们把亲人幸苦的照顾、爱护，视为[ 理所当然 ]！有时为了小争执，还有[憎恨]他们，而不知[ 心存感激 ]！ 西方有句话说，[ 上帝又两个住处，一个是在天堂，另一个是在感恩者的心里 ！] 是的，常[ 心存感谢 ]的人是快乐的；一颗[ 知恩的心 ]，也就是[ 快乐的心 ]，上帝将住在其中！ 且让我们学习——[ 多想想别人的好，忘记别人的不好 ]、[ 对所得恩典的谢意，能与争取恩典时一样地热心 ]，则我们心中将更充满爱，也将如在天堂一样快乐。  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I always inform those ppl,if u sick dont near me cos i m so easily kena virus. See!Now i am sick already. Dont know why i am 'Suai' to get those offers. What is the 'Sick Package'? -Flu -Fever -Cough -Sore Throat -Headache Seem i know all the disease name,can know that how often i get all the 'Sick Package'. But one thing must be thank you for See Kham,she say want to 'bao tong shui' for me wor. Anywhere i still not alone i think,hope that i will become more healthy i wish!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Can u believe it, actually this is the movie i waiting for long time ago n ago~~~I watch the whole series of the Alien movie start from primary school. So i waiting its back to the big screen,so i must go to watch it...Yeah~~~&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>