<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You… the cryptic smile that sends a thousand meanings through the silence      You… of moonlit eyes so distant and removed, yet possessing the magic of a warm and tender caress      You… the calm center of an ever-present storm, where one finds peace, however fleeting      You… the beauty revealed through every imperfection that makes a world real      You… who enthrall me with every breath that leaves your lips, every utterance a mellifluous weaving of sound and stillness    In You, my soul finds a freedom longed for   
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...July 24, Saturday&nbsp;    &nbsp;  As I type this, I don’t really know what it is I want to come out of this. I just want to WRITE a story. I’m sure I’ve had a go at this writing thing more times than I care to remember. There’s a comic book story about teenagers with super-powers on the run from government agent types (not an original concept, I know)… a novella/screenplay about love seemingly shallow, far-out, all-corny and yet, hopefully,&nbsp;endearing at the same time (with a “kissing” scene that can’t be beat...!). Digging deeper, there is also… yikes. another comic book story, this time about 3 friends from a University who, while&nbsp;acting out their Superbowl fantasies in a muddy field, accidentally find an ancient scarab in the guise of a rubber cockroach with supernatural powers and can turn dreams and ideas into reality (Ian Omero and Charlie Nakar… eto yung&nbsp;story natin!)     &nbsp;  A “frustrated writer”, a “would-be comic book artist” and a struggling medical student who thinks he’s in way over his head… and who hasn't slept a wink in over 40 hours, so i guess i'll have to continue this some other time. (hmm, which story to write, which story...)    &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       or, as i've been humming for the past day or two...  "isang tulog na lang...!" as in that old Jolibee ad on tv.   as (probably) none of you know, i'm a medical intern who shouldn't have the time to surf the Net much less maintain a blog. however, i've been putting this writing thing on hold for the longest time, it seems, and if this is the outlet for me to write, then so be it. enough of this, for now, will just serve up a few tidbits on why this blog exists in later posts, along with other stories, fictional or otherwise.   "isang tulog na lang, Jolibee na naman!  ang araw lulubog, bukas mabubusog...!"   tama ba? anyhoo, one day more and i'm out of the pediatrics ward for good. Good riddance? well, not really, but close enough.&nbsp;pediatrics as a specialization is among the last of my considerations after i pass the board exams for medicine (naks! confident na confident a!). for one, i don't think i have the patience to deal with (at least) 2 patients, the parent & child,&nbsp;for each consult.&nbsp;it's depressing enough as it is to see so many kids (especially in the Philippines) sick and dying of&nbsp;illnesses otherwise curable/manageable/preventable if not for&nbsp;poverty&nbsp;playing such a&nbsp;significant factor. each time i face a patient, whether at the Out-Patient or wards, i have that thought lingering at the back of my mind.   my other rants about pediatrics are much less... serious (significant?), bordering on petty and childish. gusto ko medyo "benign" na rotation, hehe. sino bang ayaw? i don't want to end my day physically spent and emotionally drained with nothing look forward to except&nbsp;lie down and sleep, knowing full well i'd be facing the same situation the following day.   i'm just venting here. i really want to be a doctor, a good one at that, such that wherever you put me, i'll do my best for my patients, even if sometimes the best i can do for them is to "make do" with what i have. there is a silver lining to this cloud, rest assured, which i'll hopefully share soon.   how this post&nbsp;turned out to be serious is beyond me. i just wanted to say, "hey! i'm out of the toxic pediatric wards! i'll&nbsp;finally have some time for myself, my friends, my interests..."   one day more. ang galing lang talaga, 'no? last duty ko bukas, kung kailang shifting out na kami... oh well. ganun talaga e.&nbsp;     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       like a soapy bubble   the kind children create    and play with     &nbsp;  drifting    to where the breeze takes me    content to simply being    afloat     &nbsp;  not really expecting   (possibly, hoping)   to fly upwards just    onwards     &nbsp;  yet mostly just wanting    not to fall...     &nbsp;  hit the ground...     &nbsp;  and inevitably     &nbsp;  burst   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       clothed in indigo   of alabaster skin   crimson lips    and chestnut hair   moonshine in her eyes   pristine feet dancing over   peach pebbles   on delicate blades   and glittering grains      a veritable prize   a fleeting dream   preyed on by sly beasts   and wing-footed hunters alike   still unfazed, ever in control   evading pitfalls   protected by the unseen hand   of an invisible champion      in a different plane   a trading of coins and trinkets   pennies and dimes   tangible   enchanting amidst a sea   of disbelief and disillusionment      a melody thought long-forgotten existing as mere fragments, notes lingering, touching lightly on memory      the promise eager to be heard    spoken of   only in song       the tooth fairy, a wolf-tamer   a thief in the night   my princess unapparent,    unaware  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         ... actually August 2, 2004.       but this was written yesterday, while i was on duty @ the Neonatal Intensive Care Unit.   with a designation like that, and being an intern that i am, you'd think i perform a very vital task related to patient care while stationed there. far from it. so what is there to do when you're stuck in a dead end duty post such as "manong" central?       i could rant about how you didn't study for 4 years in Med proper, toiling to get to internship and just performing menial tasks such as bringing specimens to and from the laboratory (from the 4th floor, you'd have to go down to the 1st floor before climbing up again to the 2nd floor to reach the lab, just because the administration saw it fit to bar the most accesible route...), following up on the results, doing your best to procure vials from other wards because of the lack of supplies in the NICU.       on the other hand, it is quite a "benign" post, you're able to free up up tp 2-3 hours in between your "manong" rounds. this provides an opportunity to catch up on your reading, academic or otherwise. in my case, i bought the day's issue of the inquirer, practically reading it from cover to cover. so now i know that the pink sisters are online, ready to accomodate our prayer requests via their website. there's the news about gracia burnham apparently clearing the military of any shady correspondence witht the abu sayyaf. a controversy's brewing regarding restoration of a mural inside the EDSA shrine without the original artist's involvement or permission. ateneo is now 5-0, (woohoo!) even without captain larry fonacier, who's out for the season with an injury. hehe, pati yung gulo ng mga barreto sa showbiz pinatulan ko! not that i'm saying it's beyond me to peruse the entertainment section every once in a while, hehe.       after seemingly soaking up on every little bit of info from the paper, i proceeded to tackle the day's crossword, which i didn't get to complete. i had to stop when i couldn't avoid peeking @ the answer key, haha! "low EQ ka na D Lo!" i could almost hear my (former) blockmate/crossword puzzle buddy/fellow miniature toy enthusiast Johann Leonardia say...      what to do in a dead end post, apart from ranting and raving and sleeping? i decided to channel my energies to something creative, and this is part of that endeavor. oh, i had planned on writing at least 3-4 pages worth of stories or poems or anything, but just kinda fell short. way short! ending up with just one poem.      so there, tell me what you think, my audience of none. till next time...   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You… the cryptic smile that sends a thousand meanings through the silence      You… of moonlit eyes so distant and removed, yet possessing the magic of a warm and tender caress      You… the calm center of an ever-present storm, where one finds peace, however fleeting      You… the beauty revealed through every imperfection that makes a world real      You… who enthrall me with every breath that leaves your lips, every utterance a mellifluous weaving of sound and stillness    In You, my soul finds a freedom longed for   
    
</post>


</Blog>