<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's 3 in the morning.  Yawns...   I'm so damn sleeeeppyyy that, in a few minutes, I think I'm gonna fall with my face flat on the keyboard. Unfortunately, I still have 2 essays to do. Hay... I barely had time to do these acad-stuff over the weekend. And now I'm squeezing my brain to extract some ideas for my reaction paper.    Arggh!   Studying really sucks!  ... Sorry, nerds.   My weekend was so restless!   My cousin just celebrated her 18th birthday with these bunch of teenagers who speak like Heart Evangelista and Kris Aquino. Ah, and did I feel out of place! Anyways, the food was good, plus the loud music and the disco to end the formality of the program. I must say, it was a cool party after all.    Hay...   I'm really tired. I feel drained.  Ugh!  And a few hours from now, I'd be packing my stuff back to my bording house in the campus. Phew! Don't I ever get a rest? Anyways, the thought that I'm restless - keeps me smiling in a way. At least I'm getting my life in action.    *Yawns*  Good Morning, people! 
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What is the ugliest creature you’ve seen? Can you describe how horrible it looked? Well, I do. Mine was an unbelievable encounter that’s definitely not for the faint-hearted...  It was Thursday night and the grasses in the  UP Lagoon  were wet, held by the soggy soil caused by the rainy season. A friend from our organization had informed me of a meeting to be conducted somewhere in the site.   It was really late, around 7:30 PM, but they had to see my presence. I was reminded of its urgency. So, alone that evening, I was walking silently in the area; my eyes were peeking widely in the darkness. The sounds of the crickets gave me the Goosebumps as I tried to find the meeting place.  A few more walk, then I heard something – a strange sound coming from behind. It sounded like wild, heavy steps in the grass, almost like the sounds of my footsteps.  Is someone following me?   I turned around, but I saw no figure of anyone.  I’m still alone. Where are they?  And so, I went on with my walk. Not long after, the sound came back. I stopped and checked my back for the second time. There was nothing.  Could it be that my footsteps are echoing?   As I turned my head in another direction, a horrible ogre displayed in front of me at a distance of about three feet. I leaned my face upward to see its eyes glowing in bloody red color, glaring hungrily into me. It was enormously tall, about 8 to 9 feet in height, built more like a human, but it’s head more like a horse’s. Its watering mouth, half-opened, had several pointed teeth, which are about the length of my thumb. Its ears were wide and cupped. Its breath stinks like a trashcan that I thought I was going to die in suffocation. Its hairy skin was dark like the color of a charcoal. I saw its tail, moving behind its back like a dog’s, only that it was longer and hairy. It has bloody, long and dirty nails, like a cannibal that rips. I could barely inspect more of its peculiar traits. I just stood there while shaking in horror, gasping for air and wanting to scream. But not a sound could come out from my throat.  A single muscular movement could be my last.   This is not the way I want to die. Not here. Not now, please.   And there I was, shocked and stationary. I was supposed to meet my friends, not a demon. Silence remained for about 10 seconds until a drop of saliva fell from the creature’s mouth. It was disgustingly sticky and stinky. My heart was pounding like a werewolf’s as it moved closer to me. It smelled so bad. Then, its eyes widened a bit more, suggesting an attack.  This is it!  It was going to rip me into pieces. It was going to grab me.  I’m dead . It moved towards my body.  ROARRRRR!!!!!!!!!    AAHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!   I opened my eyes, sweating like a pig and gripping my bedding very tightly as I tried to catch my breath. I remembered to pray. 
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My face was in shadow,  when you threw me the light; You speak of sweet words, from my dawn to my night.  You’ve dried the flowing river, in the windows of my soul; You gave me a haven, And a shoulder to fall.  You knew all of me, yet I’m all a mystery; I was so invisible, yet you see me so clearly.  We had so much together, that we barely noticed, the clock was speedier; It was beauty and bliss.  You’ve mended my wounds, and made me even stronger, but just to see another bid, of adieu from a lover.  I feel so deprived, now that you’re there, and I am right here, feeling lost in the nowhere.  Was it something I said? Was it something I did? From all the places we’ve gone, it ended bitterly as this.  And I want you to know, I wasn’t trying to change you; This place in my deepest, you possess because of you.  How I wish you could hear, my heart breaking like this; How I wish you could read, my mind speaking of bliss.  You’re there and I’m here, feeling so out of place. Tell me, where is the love that lit my blue darkened face?    (a piece I heartily dedicate to someone I used to call “!_@|3z”) 
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here I go again. I'm supposed to go somewhere but I have forgotten the direction to take, the place to go and the thing to do. I’m walking with no decisive destination. I'm having a sudden shiver on my spine and a rush of hotness on my cheeks. My mind is floating again. My heart is skipping some beats again. I'm caught in this tricky feeling again.   My senses are frozen in a flash. This mouth couldn't create a word but a faint smile creating a universe in my eyes. These ears can't hear a friend calling from behind but the sweet melodies of love songs playing on my mind.   My memory is stuck at one particular glance. He called my name, said "hi" and smiled. And now, I'm floating. Ah, I think would be floating for a few minutes more.
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The cold wind of the summer night blew a soft breeze on her calm face as she gripped her furry blanket. Close to her breast was a memorabilia of her life, her loved ones and her moments with them. Her breathing came in harmony as she rocks her chair. Around her was a dim light; dim as her vision. There were no voices but the creaks of the windows and the sounds of the wind. As her shaking fingers flipped the album, dots of thoughts and emotions came connecting on her mind. She missed them. She wanted them near, caressing her soft white hair and seeing her wrinkled face wrinkle even more whenever she smiles. One more flip and there was the face of her husband, dead a decade. Staring at her beloved’s face stopped her blinking and gave her eyes the dryness and the sobs with empty tears. A few more flip and children who look like her appeared. They were all wearing smiles; captured to last forever. And so, there were more flips and more faces. The album was heavy as her heart. And as she closed it, heavy tears suddenly came pouring from the windows of her soul. After a short moment of reminiscing, the door suddenly banged with heavy footsteps and voices laughing and talking. Stuff of different colors suddenly filled her blurred sight. The faces from the album are now moving and smiling. Tears of joy suddenly filled her cheeks as she heard tiny, high-pitched voices shouting, “Merry Christmas, Gram!”
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Under the lover’s sky, beneath the shade of an aged tree, a bright light came to embrace my spirit. I was too weary to free my senses and too hesitant to surrender my soul. But I was touched so deeply, that it opened my eyes wide enough to witness the charm of the blinding flame. Weak-hearted, I saw the bright light... And in no time, it surrounded all of me. It was bliss! And it felt so wonderful – so good that I’ve forgotten every doubt and every pain of my lost spirit. It was beautiful. Every sight was pleasing. But the light didn’t last for long... The darkness of the sky broke into sunrays of dawn. The light that gave me happiness, taught me to fly and brought me to life, faded momentarily... My eyes froze in fear; my body trembled in cold. It was all darkness again. It was all sorrow. It was all pain... I fainted.
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To die slowly, struggling to prolong life, or to die quickly, ending the persisting pain – that is the question. Life could really be tough under best circumstances, but what if you are to spend the rest of your days in a hospital bed, slowly suffocating to death as some fatal illness eats out an organ of your body? You find it pointless delaying the inevitable. You want a little help to end your suffering. Should it, then, be legal for a physician to provide you with such help? The public is warming to the idea of Physician-Assisted Suicide and for years, the society argues on whether it should be legalized or not.   In most states, including our country Philippines, PAS or any form of aiding a suicide is a crime, while suicide or attempted suicide itself is not illegal. Currently, the Oregon and the Netherlands are the only states legalizing Physician-Assisted Suicide, exclusively administered to long-term residents.   Still, PAS and other form of assisted suicides continue to be banned almost everywhere. The state and the church consider it criminal and immoral. Though conditions are still to be met upon conducting such kinds of suicide, the government still argues upon legalizing it. And today, the dispute over patient autonomy extends beyond the right of treatment refusal to issues of Physician-Assisted suicides.  Well, if making life-long decisions is not easy, then how much more if it is life itself that you decide ending? That’s something that is definitely more complicated, isn’t it. But the arguments regarding Physician-Assisted Suicide death arise from the fact that choosing death rather than life is sometimes reasonable under several circumstances. The main problem, however, is the entire constitutional complex itself, that not only criminalizes but also stigmatizes these forms of suicide. My stand on this burning issue is that these kinds of suicide be legalized. If are totally opposed on my propositions, then I would be more than willing to put up some information and explanations to back up my stand. Anyways, on a crowd of occupied people who could only care for their daily survivals, I’d prefer not to make this too complicated.  Issues on the legalization of Physician-Assisted Suicide confront the society with a dilemma on what side of the story they should stand in. However, no one, not even the society, could prevent people from attaining autonomy and freedom from every individual. I firmly believe that the individual has the option to die in a manner he wants. And in the case of a greatly agonizing pain with no chances of survival nor recovery, easy death with an aid of an expert is preferable, given the right measures and restricted by the limiting rules. I, therefore, call for a change in society that these forms of suicide be a feasible practice in the future: legal and socially accepted in a society of rational citizens. 
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      He is a Certified Public Accountant working under an internationally recognized company. Just around 7:00 in the evening, he was walking on his way to his Mercedez Benz, which was parked somewhere near the edge of the road. Wearing an $800 worth of business suite and some good-looking pair of shoes, he opened the left door of his luxury car and popped in. But as he was about to close the it, a huge truck suddenly came zooming from behind, smashing his door on the side and detaching it completely from the handsome Benz.  Oozing with anger, the man jumped out from his damaged car and signaled the truck driver to pull over.  In less than a minute, the driver was negotiating with the businessman, who was constantly yelling like an angry bull.  “Bastardo! You must be the most stupid man in the face of this freaking planet not to notice my car parked in here,” he yelled. “I’m gonna call the police and sue you for this damage!”   “Sir, but…” the driver exclaimed.  “Don’t ‘but’ me, you asshole!” the man interrupted. Don’t you realize how much damage you’ve cost? And could you even calculate? You’re annual salary might not even be enough to pay the half of it!”  “Sir, for a while…” the driver said, trying to squeeze his words on the man’s sermon.  “Don’t even try to defend your position,” the man exclaimed. “It’s your fault, can’t you see? You are the offensive driver here!”  “Sir, pardon. What I’m trying to say is…” the driver insisted.  “What?!?” the man asked, annoyed.  “Sir, I think you better call an ambulance first,” the driver said in concern.  “Ambulance for what?” the man asked, even more annoyed. “The police are on their way to arrest you. You’d regret this.”  “Sir, you were completely occupied by your anger that you probably didn’t notice it,” the driver said. “Your left arm was also lost upon the smash.”  The man, then, looked on his side with an expression of shock.   “Oh, shit! My Rolex!” the man roared.  
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Most English dictionaries define a Christian as a person who believes in and follows Christ, and who belongs in a Christian denomination. Although a variety of definitions extracted from different languages are set into being a Christian, I keep questioning the genuine meaning of this. Is Christianity more to this form of nomenclature and belief?  As a Catholic, I’ve always thought of myself living as a Christian. But for recently, I’ve started to appraise my Christianity not simply by religious classification but also by the ways of living. Like most classified Christians in this world, communal discourse and religious teachings molded my concept on Christianity and Christian living.  Religious ironies are not atypical to every radical mind. Even an innocent child may start to question who created her, how did the universe began and who is her real Father in Heaven. For one, why do we need to reiterate every prayer in the rosary? I’m sure the Blessed Virgin Mary needs to hear us only once. Unfortunately, a lot of people seem to miss the thought. Once but sincere makes more sense than a hundred times but contemptuously idle.  And how does the society define a good Christian anyway? Is it someone who goes to church everyday but corrupts on people just to fund his illegal machinery? Or is it someone who doesn’t even read the Bible but opens his house for people in need?  Honestly, scribbling all these queries gives me the scorch as though I ought to be forked by some demon. But for quite a number of times, I stop and question a lot of things about my faith. By the way, the definition of faith is "something we believe in, even without any proof." I even thought of reading the Bible, going to church everyday, joining worships, and even spreading the words of God. It had only made me feel guilty because I lack time for all these. Is Christianity too demanding, anyway? I used to feel frantic about the issues of devoutness, but I realized that God, probably, does not really require us to be absolutely religious.   This world bears the intolerable, meaning things happen out of evil persuasions, and we must not lock ourselves as though we are living in paradise. This world is never a paradise, if ever Adam and Eve were true. To live as a Christian is not to be apathetic but to get involved. I think that, as long as we are living our lives without aggravating others, then we are living a Christian life. And as long as we know the concepts of right and wrong, and put it to practice, then we are Christians.  And from all these, let me clarify that I am not defying Christianity nor am I denying the significance of religious practices. I only suggest that we ought to know what we believe in. We cannot demand for a perfect world because the world is made of imperfect people. However, it is crucial to keep in mind that none of what we believe in or what we practice would matter unless we are sincere. I stress that – unless we are sincere.
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I've been having a hard time fall asleep during the past few nights. I think my sleep was adjusted. But I have no choice, anyway. I have to stay awake even no matter how hard my eyes demand for a sleep and my body for a short nap. Exams, homework and night activities obligated me to stay up even until&nbsp;3 AM. Ugh! And I think I'm already insomniac. " Mega-insomniac " -&nbsp;I call myself! Haha! Coffee, cup noodles, hot chocolates, crackers and midnight snacks - those kinds of food I wasn't used to - fill my tummy every night and then.&nbsp; Calculus, accounting, sciences, history and other academic books occupy my table almost entirely. Papers due tomorrow and projects due the day after tomorrow drive me nuts. Come inside my room and&nbsp;check out&nbsp;my table calendar filled with "IMPORTANT" and "URGENT" notes.  Phew!  &nbsp; No, I am not crammer and I avoid to cram as much as possible,&nbsp;but what would you expect from college, anyway? It's not like having to memorize word by word and ace the fill in the blanks test with all the obvious answers. &nbsp;  And though I'm merely a sophomore in our country's premier state university, I've learned quite a lot of college strategies, experienced paranoia, and seen some oddness. Having resided inside a dormitory during my freshman year, I was able to point out the big (if not, HUGE) differences between being a high school teenybopper and being a college young woman. I've learned that in college, you can study the whole subject coverage and fail a test; and you can also NOT study the whole subject coverage and ace a test; that you and your roommate will always have major differences which may even lead to minor misunderstandings; that you don't have to stand during class recitations; that you&nbsp;don't&nbsp;have to greet every professor arriving in the classroom;&nbsp;that you can cut classes and throw no big deal; that you have to deal with upperclassmen more often than you expect; that social life is the life; that skipping a lunch (and sometimes, not even having to eat lunch) is a normal routine; that curfews give you the shit; that staying up late with Mr. and Mrs. Algebra is a must or else, etc..  But then, such challenges are what make college life magnanimously incredible. There is more to knowledge than what is echoed inside the four corners of the classroom. As Spiderman&nbsp;once&nbsp;said: "Of great power comes great responsibilities." Our lives are more relevant when we handle responsibilities. Life is well spent when we have a goal - a never-ending goal. A friend of mine, who was our school paper editor-in-chief, also once quoted, "If you aim for the roof, you'd fall on the floor. But if you aim for the sky, you'd fall on the roof." And as for that, I say -&nbsp;it's always worth a try. Like time, opportunities are more precious than gold.  And surely, every effort we exert is effort well spent if we have an objective. And as for me staying up so late, I do&nbsp;have an objective. As a matter of fact, life itself, by the end of the day, is a big objective -&nbsp;an objective that breaks the dawn of a successful tomorrow.   Phew!   Ah, this is it!&nbsp;I couldn't even feel my eyes blinking anymore. I really am insomniac. "Mega-insomniac". &nbsp;  I can see the sunrays now...  The dawn is breaking...  I knew that dawn would break... I always knew the dawn would break...&nbsp; &nbsp;
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Ohh…I’m scared to turn the TV on. Sadako might...  Ohh…I’m scared to look into the mirror...    Ohh…I’m scared to go to the bathroom...     I think watching horror movies are cool, especially when you see people around you freaking out and creeping out from fear. Movies with ghosts whispering the character’s name, zombies looking like garbage, immortals chasing mortals, and demons burning in hell are magnanimously creative. Although some visuals are just neither that realistic nor that convincing, horror movies are hard to imagine. Horrific scenes are brutally clever and artistic. And the hardest task, I suppose, is to draw psychological impacts within the story that would make the viewers remember the creepy segments they’ve seen, and sometimes even relating those segments in their habitual lives.  &nbsp;
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Starlight, Star bright,    Stir my senses with the moon of light.    Heed my prayer and wish tonight,     Where in the world is   Mr. Right?&nbsp;      &nbsp;   Resting my head on a comfy pillow,    I’m thinking again of what’s for tomorrow.    The day was over, and it was all OK,    Yet things were the same as of yesterday.     &nbsp;   So, tell me now and let me know,    Will he ever make it to see my show?    Because there's &nbsp;just no way I’d end my story,    Without him standing at the center with me.    
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Reality bites at the hard court and the UP Maroons Basketball Seniors (Men)&nbsp;must have already been having enough of the wounds.  Ouch!  Apparently, they haven't won any game. Well, not  yet . Let's simply hope for the better...and that is for the Maroons not to end up last on the UAAP&nbsp;67th season overall ranking.  I've watched two games of UP against OTHERS in hopes for a single victory. Unfortunately, tough luck hit other colors over maroons. But that's OK, we have a mighty PEP Squad, anyway. (I must admit that on times like these, it's always better to look on the bright side of things). I'm sure you'd all agree, won't you?  Anyways, the competition has just started. There’s more to come and chances are still big. Hopefully, the first match we’ve had with the "others" would not be the preview of our overall performance for the whole season.  Oh, well. Let's just cheer some more, shall we?&nbsp;  "SHOOT THAT BALL!" 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I’ve written about a lot of other stories but this creepy instance that happened to me years ago. Obviously, this is a true story I am going to share with you. And until now, whenever it crosses my mind, it still creeps me out.  I can’t remember my age but I think I was around 6 or 7 when it happened. I woke up at around three o’clock in the morning, and guess where I found myself? At the bathroom! I was sleeping in the bathroom floor! And I had absolutely no idea how I got there nor how long I’ve slept there. All I know is that the night before, I went straight to my bed and fell asleep with the blanket covered on me. It was weird. Really weird.  The floor was dry and cold and, as I consciously opened my eyes, I was calm for a while. Then after a few seconds, I was completely awake and startled. The coldness of the bathroom, and the realization of having no clue on how I got there, started to give me the Goosebumps. I started to pinch myself, thinking that maybe it was just a dream. But it was no dream. I really was sleeping there!  I went out of the bathroom - shaking. I didn’t want to scream but deep inside I was overflowing from fear. The dawn was very quite that I could even hear the lizards’ tsktsk out on the corners. And do you want to know what freaked me even more? All the lights of the house from my bedroom leading to the bathroom were turned on! I ran all the way to my parents’ room and woke my mother up, telling her what happened.   That morning, after breakfast, everyone in the house gave me a hypothetical explanation – “You probably had a sleepwalk.” &nbsp;  &nbsp;
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I am  not perfect  - not even close.&nbsp;&nbsp;   But I have people who love me despite all my  imperfections . And that realization alone gives me a reason to live.&nbsp;   Love  is not having to accept perfect people but having to accept imperfect people  perfectly .   After all, this world is  never  perfect because it is inhabited by&nbsp;imperfect people.   All humans have flaws and it is  human nature  to make mistakes.    I am human . So therefore, I am not perfect.  And as forbeing&nbsp;human, I may not be perfect but I can  always do my best  to reach the closest spot I could get to perfection.   I may not be perfect, but I could  see more than what meets the eye . &nbsp;   Now tell me – are we having the same  vision ? &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I saw myself halfway through a tough bridge - shaking, gasping from breath, and listening to the voices of my instincts.  This journey is never easy . As I moved a muscle, my mind kept juggling between two options: Shall I go back, avoiding the risky steps and dwelling once more to places where my past relives? Or shall I proceed to the other end, where another world awaits, totally unheard of, and take the all the risks of whatever comes my way? ... I was having a dilemma. I needed to decide fast. The bridge was creaking as seconds of time progress and was getting tougher towards the other end.  If I turn around and return to where I’ve started, I'm sure to be safe because I know very well what was in there. If I make my way towards the unknown world, I might fall from the bridge.  Clueless of what lies ahead, I was starting to feel terrified of all the unknowns that possibly&nbsp;await me.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ugh, it'z mah hell week this week! I&nbsp;have 4 exams on the go. Ahh, so please forgive me if my blogs fail to be posted on schedule. I know I owe at least two for this week. Nevertheless, i promise to squeeze time for these. &nbsp; Tough luck, come hit me! &nbsp; WRITTING ROCKS! take that! (rewind it back) &nbsp; chiao... 
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The last thing I’d want is to earn enemies; the worst nightmare I could have is having a friend turned into an enemy; and the worst poison I could swallow are the bitter words I would never wish to hear coming from a friend I've known for an ample period of time.  I'd rather have an enemy for a thousand years and win him as a friend in the end, than have a friend for years and lose our friendship over unreasonable matters. Why can't people just look more on the bright side of things rather than wallow in misery because of the dark sides of it. Life is too short to waste over hatred.   I find it so hard to forget, but that’s not my point. I probably just don’t get it. Is it really that hard to forgive?  And after all that we've been through, I think nothing could ever be more stupid than to throw everything down the drain and forget all the places we've been in just a snap. Life really sucks under best circumstances, but why look at it that way?   i want to be heard. i want to be noticed. i want to be answered.  Apparently, they eyes were blinded for my appeals and the ears were deafened for my voices.  And now, my eyes are fuzzy from tears.  
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I love concerts ! In fact, I could hardly enumerate the concerts I’ve seen with my friends (and with a special someone…hehe). All I know is that every crowd was alive, every performer was kicking and every rhythm was beating.  Argghh, they do rock ! 	 Most of the concerts I’ve seen were held in an open field. And people like it that way, except probably those who tire easily from having to stand and having to stretch their necks just to get a glimpse of the artist on-stage. I also think that being in an open field is better, even when it rains. Actually, I like it when it rains. It’s when the power of youth, despite the hassles of getting wet, elevates for the music. 	 May it be RNB, hip-hop, reggae, alternative rock, loud rock, punk, punk rock, pop, slow, jazz or acoustics, being in the concert crowd could never feel any better. Everyone deserves a little break and a chance to break free.    Rock on! 
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was riding on an FX this morning when a woman beside me was singing along with the " Sasakyan kita, sa lahat ng gusto mo... blah blah " song being played on the sounds system. As another man on the back seat hums along, I was like ,  what the ****?!?! Aren't there any other stations with a taste in music?   ugh!   The song makes no sense at all!    Yuck!    If there are local singers and composers that I would wish to stab in the mouths, on my list would have to be those who sang and composed  Spagetti, Otso-otso, Sasakyan?, Jumbo Hotdog,  and other  I'd-rather-be-deaf-because-I-can’t-stand-it  compositions. And I mean no offense to anyone who loves to patronize such genre of music. Sorry, but I just hate it. My ears get irritated with such crappy shits. I swear, they suck!   Everytime I hear the " Apear tayo, sumakit ulo ko....blah blah " on the radio, I go like " Bullshit! Cut the crap! " I mean, so what if  sumakit ulo mo at mag-appear kayo ? The song makes absolutely no sense and the lyrics just stink.  BIG TIME!  And no, I am not discriminating our local singers and composers. Some of them just happen to play non-sense. I find it pathetic that our music industry feeds the public with such IQ-degrading,  multiple-meaning  melodies, which, by the way, even make it to the top of the charts. And you wanna know what's worse? None of the meanings make sense! I find it completely - a  garbage .    Ugh!  I must say, such songs are better off without the lyrics. What do you think? 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I lost my cellphone. I never  thought I'd lose my cellphone. Had I known, I shouldn't have followed my sister and my cousin at the mall.  And to worsen the unfortunate realization, it was my younger sister who actually lost it. I didn't! I just somehow feel responsible because I handed it to her. We were browsing at the mall when we stopped at this "Cardams" botique to try on some footwear. Since I wasn't carrying a bag, I asked her to put my phone in hers. I didn't have any pocket, either so it was uncomfortable for me to try on some sandals with my other hand holding my phone.  Then, that was it! That was the last time I saw my phone. An hour ago, I asked her to hand it to me. I thought I was probably having some messages by then. When she dug for my phone in her bag, it wasn't there! It was neither on her pocket nor on my cousin’s.  I was calm for less than a minute then I almost went hysterical. She even assured me that she tucked it inside her bag. But the thing is, it was under her premises and it was no longer inside her bag! A theft couldn’t have possibly snatched her bag. It was zipped very tightly. Besides, had a theft stole it from her, he or she would have stolen her wallet and other valuables as well.  Anyways, there was nothing we can do about it. Even if I scold my sister, who was obviously in denial for misplacing my phone, it would not bring my phone back. And in such a crowded mall, it was impossible to revive it. Good citizens, especially here in the metropolis, are as rare as diamonds.  Now, I’m back to zero. I’m gonna have to do the arduous task of searching for contacts. Thank God my mom lend me her phone for a while. I really need it.
</post>


</Blog>