<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FUNNY STORY: On my last night in Chicago, i stayed at my aunt and uncle's house, and they have a big golden retriever named Bailey.  Bailey is really nice, but so god damn energetic.  ANYWAYS. That night i went to sleep and i closed my door like usual, cuz i dont like to have it open when i sleep (yea...) and some-freaking-how, Bailey opened the door (did i mention he (yes, he.  bailey is NOT a boys name) is smart?) to my room in the middle of the night, took out two pairs of my underwear (new too, how SAD) from my opened suitcase, and proceeded to chew the living (well, not really) daylights out of them.  So i woke up yesterday morning, went to take a shower, opened the bathroom door, and what do i find?  guess.  Well, if you guessed my dead underwear, u were right.  Lying o-so-lifelessly on the floor of the bathroom.  rip pretty new underwear.  HAH.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am home.  yay.  Chicago - family sucked; made me miserable.  But shopping was good.  Saw the Blue Man Group, 4th row seating; awesome.  yes.  Just found out im working next on Friday at 7, so u should show up.  i kno im working on fourth of july, but i dont kno whether itll be at the afternoon game of the evening one.  hope the afternoon one!  home hasn't been a whirlwing of excitement quite yet. gotta say, hate how everyone, well a lot of ppl, r doing ss.  it sucks.  i think i'll go running soon.  get in shape, lol.  well, ttyl.  btw, roger, 1984? wth?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am in the big ol' windy city of C-H-I-C-A-G-O.  What a blast!  not.  but it isnt so bad.  Yesterday i went shopping down the big fancy (not really) magnificent mile (a.k.a. downtown)  I got a cartigan and shirt.  like u care.  yup.  And Colleen, i was encompased in retro wow i will take pics for u not to worry.  Last night i went clubbing (HAH, no) to the bar/teeny club (lol loud music n dancing and drinks and all that fun stuff haha) with my bro and sis and cuzes.  Fun stuff.  I just got finished running on a treadmill for 30 minutos, so i am POOPED.  AnD, my internet time is up right now.  well, i really could go as long as i want (i love charging stuff to whoever (whomever?) is paying for the room)BUt ive gotta go get ready to go eat n go to the taste of chicago and FERRIS WHEEL (yes, i bet u are all bubbling with jealousy right now) well, ttyl.  love ya.  leave a post, or gimme up a call cuz i love u.  buhbye
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, actually it's not very short, but that's cool.  The lady at the haircutting place gave me 7Up.   It was good.  Colleen has the fab, fab, fabulous idea of a bbq and formal with the crew.  what fun we will hae such a blast.  I was gonna go to the crabs game aqui, but colleen backed out, danielle backed out, alex backed out, jackie backed out, and laura backed out.  what losers (wow, JOKING.  i love you.) I tought Roger how to properly play mancala, and of course, he caught on and decided, correctly, that my way was better.  CHICAGO TOMORROW.  Ill try to find some internet cafe to log on to, we'll see.  My parents promised me a comp, preferably laptop, "by the time i got to hs" but of course, NO COMPUTER IS PRESENT FOR MUA.  Wow, i cannot wait to hang out with my sister and her boyfriend.  Yea.  Right.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHAT FUN.  Today i venturued over to Crayzbaby's casa and we partayed it up.  THERE WAS AN ICE CREAM TRUCK (truly, i did not know those still existed) and it was driving by and i went out and flopped my arms and i got its attention and boy, did we get ice cream! then we watched Bend It Liek Bekhman. It was good! but i bet all of you out there have already seen it.  well GUESS WHAT.  im just a little slow, OKAY?  Juicy juicy mangos.  THE JAW.  wow, what fun.  im tired, but im not gonna go to bed, because, for all of you out there who realyl care, i am talking to my friend in San Louis Opisbo about coming to visit and taking the trolley.  yes, TROLLLEY.  I think Arcata should get a trolley.  that would be THE BEST.  What great fun.  I think i say that a lot.  what fun.  well, leave a comment and when i see you i will give you a great big hug.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning someone IMed me and they said they knew me but they wouldn't tell me who.  Have you ever had this happen to you?  WELL IT SUCKS.  its mucho annoying.  check out the convo:  Bubblebutterfly3: Hey Maya WoLFieCHiCk 11: hey WoLFieCHiCk 11: who is this Bubblebutterfly3: someone...  Bubblebutterfly3: hehe WoLFieCHiCk 11: lol who? Bubblebutterfly3: somebody who u kno WoLFieCHiCk 11: right Bubblebutterfly3: i don't go to ahs...yet WoLFieCHiCk 11: uve got me stumped Bubblebutterfly3: lmao Bubblebutterfly3: i have red hair Bubblebutterfly3: my name starts w/ a "K" WoLFieCHiCk 11: uhh WoLFieCHiCk 11: what grade ru in Bubblebutterfly3: i haaaate sheep Bubblebutterfly3: 7th Bubblebutterfly3: i have many freckles Bubblebutterfly3: i kno lura..and sienna Bubblebutterfly3: laura** Bubblebutterfly3: and Jayme  Bubblebutterfly3: and andy Bubblebutterfly3: and alex Bubblebutterfly3: and jackie WoLFieCHiCk 11: wow i dont kno Bubblebutterfly3: and colleen Bubblebutterfly3: and matt Bubblebutterfly3: and i think uir really PRETTY Bubblebutterfly3: ur* WoLFieCHiCk 11: haha i have no idea im totally clueless tell me Bubblebutterfly3: who do u like the most out of the ppl i listed?? WoLFieCHiCk 11: laura Bubblebutterfly3: yay!  Bubblebutterfly3: least...? WoLFieCHiCk 11: hah can u guess Bubblebutterfly3: sienna...or jayme... WoLFieCHiCk 11: not jayme Bubblebutterfly3: andy? WoLFieCHiCk 11: no Bubblebutterfly3: lol...sienna, right? WoLFieCHiCk 11: eh, i guess but i still like her, just not as much as everyone else Bubblebutterfly3: lmao kk WoLFieCHiCk 11: who is this?? Bubblebutterfly3: some ppl call me quail WoLFieCHiCk 11: wtf WoLFieCHiCk 11: lol Bubblebutterfly3: lmao, lmao, lmao  Bubblebutterfly3: L. Bubblebutterfly3: M. Bubblebutterfly3: A. Bubblebutterfly3: O. Bubblebutterfly3: whoa, girlie WoLFieCHiCk 11: yea? Bubblebutterfly3: uther?  WoLFieCHiCk 11: what? Bubblebutterfly3: u there*  WoLFieCHiCk 11: o yea Bubblebutterfly3: YES Bubblebutterfly3: do u think im a psycho?? WoLFieCHiCk 11: no, but ur driving me insane lol i wanna know who this is Bubblebutterfly3: just call me quail... WoLFieCHiCk 11: quail... WoLFieCHiCk 11: what the heck Bubblebutterfly3: i love you Bubblebutterfly3: i want your babies Bubblebutterfly3: lmao,  Bubblebutterfly3: kidding...duh WoLFieCHiCk 11: lol Bubblebutterfly3: Gotta Go Bubblebutterfly3: luv u! WoLFieCHiCk 11: k WoLFieCHiCk 11: cya Bubblebutterfly3: c u sooner than u think... WoLFieCHiCk 11: uh huh Bubblebutterfly3 signed off at 11:45:37 AM.   Well guess what.  i don't kno any 7th graders with red hair whos name starts with K but who ppl call Quail (wth) with red hair and who hates sheep...I THINK IT IS ONE OF YOU OUT THERE SCREWING WITH ME.  I mean seriously, how could a 7th grader possibly kno all of my friends unless they stalked me.  well i dont think theyre stalking me, i think its one of my friends out to make me feel stupid. well guess what, ITS WORKING.  God, see you sooner than you thinK!?!!??!!!?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i went to our cabin in Redwood Valley (near willow creek) for Father's Day.  It was hella nice out - sooo hot at the water!, but at night when i was inside i was in a rocking chair and i just kinda leaned to one side (not all my body weight, really), and guess what!?!?  The chair fell over.  It was a ditress.  I hurt my arm and it was sad.  But it doesn't hurt anymore so it's all good.  and i kinda have a tan.  but w/e.  This trip to my cabin today in now way topped Colleen and my experience some weeks ago.  We had   A BLAST   with electrical piping, i will never forget it.  and when we go there again, we are going to make a horror film in the deserted church with the world dictionary.    WHAT FUN  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone i just finshed makign a photo site, so if u wanna check it out, go here: http://photos.yahoo.com/wolfiechick11.  Some of the photos r pretty old (beware) well, hope ya like it!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mom told me today that i was forbidden from taking Sudafed anymore.  I asked why not, because it helps and no allergy medicine does.  She said its because Sudafed is a stimulent so I am essentially taking an upper so sudafed gets me high.  Yup, thats my mom; the genius.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning i was sleeping peacefully in my bed at the early hour of 9:30 when i was woken up by my dad screaming "MAYA.  ARE YOU HOME?!?!? MMAAAYYYAAA!!!! IF YOU'RE HOME COME OUT HERE RIGHT NOW!!!!!!" So i groggily got up pissed off at being woken and came out to see what all the hubub was about.  Turns out my dad had been cutting up frozen fish food with a just sharpened knife and the knife had cut through his fingernail right down to the bone.  o uck.  So i became Dr. Maya and got him fixed up and everything and yelled at the guy at HealthSport to get my mom and she came home and drove him to the hospital.  I was left at home with the wonderful task of cleaning up the bloody fish food.  grand.  So i did it, all the while being deathly afraid of getting AIDS.  Then i went back to sleep, but since it's garbage day the damn garbage trucks kept on driving up and down the streets and i couldnt go back to sleep for very long.  I was very dissapointed.  And my dad lost the tip of his finger.  Very very sad morning.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, not much is new from my homefront.  I just got done mowing the lawn, but before i did that i had to fight of a wild deer to get to the lawn mower.  Well, actually i was too scared to, so i got my mom and she came out and when the deer saw her, boy did he run.  So i got to the mower and now our lawn is nice and short, but when i went to put the lawn mower away there was mr. deer again, guarding the mower's home.  Well i wasn't in the bravest of moods, so i parked the mower right where i was and ran for my life.  Well, now i am safely inside.  Hip. Hip. Hurray.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night Alex and I went on a trek (well actually a car ride) to matt's house.  It was great fun. When we got there we saw what appeared to be three youngsters (in alex's opinion, peter l. and matt "say what" munther), but we were in for a surprise.  It was none other than matt, jon, and clayton.  What a blast.  Then i got my chunk of school stuff (save my autographs page thingy, which matt decided to keep for himself, so he could finally write in it *wink wink*), got back in the car, and chuga chuga'd (great car noises) back to my home sweet home.  What a lovely evening.  But wait!  It wasn't over just then.  We made the first photo page in our summer scrapbook (titled "Tigers! Last Days of School" for all of you out there who were just tingling with curiosity).  Then we proceeded to look at my bunches of photos, which is always a blast, and saw grand pictures of sam, alex, sienna's nose, and much, much more.  Oh, and i can't forget that one kid.  His name is Ryan, alex.  (Just thought you should know)  Then we did optical illusions, and when our brains got too tired, we went to sleep.  I proceeded to sleep 3 and a half hours more than alex, which was great fun.  Then we ate a cumulative of 5 pieces of toast (mmm) and watched Dawsons Creek and the ever-popular saved by the bell.  How fun.  Then the Alex went chuga chuga back to her house and i walked to my scheduled piano lesson which was no longer.  I got in the house and no one was there and it was grand; no piano lesson for today, whoop whoop.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ryan, you've motivated me to talk about the oxygen bar. I can't wait to do it. The Facts: The oxygen we breathe on a day-to-day basis is about 26% pure oxygen. The oxygen you breathe in the oxygen bar is 96% oxygen. It's a rush to your system to breathe such pure oxygen, and it gives you a "healthy, happy high" that's completely safe. The Process: You know the tanks of oxygen old people breathe? Well, that's essentially what happens.  You can chose a scent of oxygen (Lol) and then the people at the oxygen bar stick tubes up your nose (like the old folks have) and you inhale the healthy happy oxygen. The Cost: For 5 minutes of breathing the oxgyen, the cost is $5, and for 10 minutes, the cost is $9, and you get the point. Try it out...it'll be a blast.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha, what a great title.  But the UPS Truck really IS here.  I will be right back, got to go chat it up with the chap.....I'm back.  What a jerk.  He wouldn't give me the package because i am supposedly under 21.  What does he kno.  I miss my old UPS man.  He would give my doggie cookies, and we would give him presents during the Holidays.  RIP Old UPS man.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm on a roll! Watch out; here comes my fourth consecutive blog entry for today.  Just thought id add in some things on my summer to do list: -Make a video (Colleen is opting for Harry Potter) -Go Rollerblading (anyone care to join?) -Stay up all night -rent a bunch of movies and have friends over...movie fest!       (haha wow im a big fat dork) -Oxygen Bar (FUN STUFF) -make a website -make a summer scrapbook My actual list is so much longer, but i think ill save u the boredom by only posting this chunk of it.  Exciting, huh?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My hair sucks.  It refuses to lighten.  I'm really tempted to cut it all off because its so frustrating,...but i won't.  I have used like 4 lightening products on my hair; the most recent ones have bleach in them, and guess what!?  THEY DONT WORK AT ALL.  What a load of crap.  Bleach is supposed to BLEACH your hair, and it wont even lighten just the teensiest bit of my hair. Pisses me off.  oh well, i guess ill just have to live with it.....darn. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just need to give mucho credit to the late (well not really) the great Alex Zielinski (hmm im a bad speller is it right?) for the wonderful site name, Lookee Heere.  You're a genius, Alex.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow so i finally made a Blog.  I kno, i kno, i'm a little behind the herd of people who have long since made their own, but, well, o well.  A little about myself - My name's Maya and I'll be a sophmore at Arcata High in the fall. um, summer plans...chicago for my cousin's wedding, sacramento to surprise my brother for his bday, workin at the crabs, and hopefully NOT going to some lamo camp in santa cruz....anyways.  Summer has been a blast so far.  Lots of Birthdays - Alex's and Colleen's and Molly's 15th bdays parties.  fun stuff.  Working at the crabs has been fun so far.  Well, that 8th grader kinda scared me (thanks a lot jesse) and last time i worked i was FREEZING MY ASS OFF, but w/e, atleast ill kno to layer next time.  I actually haven't been to Hanks at all this summer, amazing, isn't it?  My Hanks buddy is in SLO, or long beach...u kno i really don't kno where. (i miss ya Shawna!) this entry is all over the place. I think i'll end it and come right back and make a new one.  Tata for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow, that's hella frustrating.&nbsp; i just wrote a long post and then published it but somehow it didnt publish and instead erased it all.&nbsp; DARN.  &nbsp;   anyways....     &nbsp;  I'm leaving tomorrow to go to camp in Santa Cruz, and i would love it if you would all write to me.&nbsp; Ill be at camp from July 17 to August 8.&nbsp; Three weeks, so letters would be grand!&nbsp; Ill also have my cell phone with me if you want to call me.&nbsp; (707) 496-9877.  &nbsp;  My address will be:  &nbsp;  Maya Wolf  Atten: Kate Quigley  Johns Hopkins CAA Summer Program  UC Santa Cruz  1156 High Street  Crown College: Harvey Building  Santa Cruz, CA 95064  &nbsp;  Yea, long address...Well, i hope to hear from you all soon, and that you're all having a good summer.  &nbsp;  LOVE YA    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night i had a dream.  I was in the mall, and my mom was with my dead grandma and one of my moms friends and my mom was the dj for the radio.  I was walking to a second hand store to look at a vintage suitcase, and there were all these mentally challenged people around me doing the worm.  Most of them were doing it in pairs, and i remember feeling sorry for the losers who were doing the worm by themselves.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow, been a while.  missed me?  what am i doing.  11:58.  no one is one.  roger, you're letting me down!!! well, im leaving sat for US Santa Cruiz.  Bioethics, YAY!!!! NOOOOOOOOO.  Ill get the addy up here in blog asap so u can send me mail!! ill call ppl when i can, ill be gone from july 17 to august 9.  hey!  gimme ur addy so i can write u :)  im crotcheting a scarf and listening to Matchbox 20.  fun stuff!  I had a piano lesson at 1 and then with shopping with me momma til 5:30.  I got bunches of stuff for camp.  shopping makes the pain of leaving a little smaller.  haha.  oh, you wanna know what i got? well hey, i'd never want to deprive you, so the list goes a little something like this: candy, sheets, blanket, shirt, stickers, yarn, hair gel, face cleanser, loofas, purrdy nail polish on sale for a buckeroo, umm...fabric, well, whatdya kno, i forget the rest.  then after that, MICKIE D'S! yay, finally!! (they actually had fries this time) boy was i hungry.  i scarfed down a hamburger, 8 mcnuggets and a large fries before pulling in the driveway.  can you say Y-U-M (its really fun, colleen) btw colleen, i have your bottle and your cds.  gotta cu!!!! well, ciao for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To Colleen and Jon: ur comments are nonsense.  Colleen, train??? and, err, jon, just what was up with the whole thing.  I DON'T GET IT.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, what a fun one it was.  I worked in the afternoon, then went to the festival on the plaza (where i proceeded to get a henna tattoo, and, oh yea, and major rager of a sunburn on my face) then at nice, guess what i did!?!? hah, yup u guessed it. Colleen, IT WAS A BLAST.  wow, i was sooo hyper!  Sorry to any of u if i was a tad (or more) bit annoying.  hah.  Well, sorry your bracelet is missing jon.  Wow, i dont think jon even knows i have a blog.  how depressing.  anyways, today me and colleen tried to make BEAUTIFUL henna tattoos ourselves.  Well, um, not quite sure it worked so well.  COLLEEN you ruined my first sun!! ahh!! no, just joshin, im not mad :)  Your star is the best, and my second sun isn't too bad either, besides the fact that you can barely see it.  And tennis was a BLASt.  Me and colleen suck though.  its cooool.  Alex, YAY that your guests are gone. I'm happy for you, now you can DO stuff.  Ok everybody, NEXT weekend, my cabin? sound good to anyone? YESSSSSSSSS.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, i haven't written in so long! well, for any of you who care, here's my schedule: Period 0 - Orchestra - C. Jacobson Period 1 - America in the Modern World - S. Myer Period 2 - Spanish 2 - K. Fernandes Period 3 - Photo - D. Michel Period 4 - English 2 - P. Cavanagh Period 5 - Trig/Advanced Algebra - W. Bagnall Period 6 - Chemistry - G. Hildebrand Grr....HISTORY FIRST PERIOD!! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>