<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As everyone who uses the Internet is well aware, people love to download music. Most people don't see anything wrong with downloading a song off the Internet for their personal use, justifying it by telling themselves "I wouldn't have bought the CD anyways, so they're not losing any money." In fact, most teens today see nothing wrong with downloading music and have come to expect to be able to get their songs for free.   However, as everyone who uses a file sharing service knows, the Internet is riddled with terrible sounding copies of songs. Downloading a song is a virtual crapshoot, as you may end up with a copy someone made off the radio or a corrupt copy that is no more than bleeps and static. For many, avoiding the annoyance of downloading multiple copies of a song is what drives them in the end to music stores such as Apple's iTunes, not the threat of litigation that the RIAA has been pressing lately.  The balance of ease and price is the key to convincing computer users to pay for their music. Relatively few people fear the RIAA, as they have only sued a few of the hundreds of millions of downloaders thus far, and have largely been unsuccessful in trying to get the large ISPs to turn over names and addresses of their users. Furthermore, the RIAA's relentless focus on poor college students is not helping their image either. While the recording industry is attempting to solicit sympathy by showing the "little guys," prosecuting college students in an attempt to get them to settle for thousands of dollars is not helping them out.   If the recording industry wants people to download music legally, they must entice people to use the legal services by offering a smoothly integrated product that everyone supports. When users realize the relatively low cost of the product and the ease of use and time savings that come with it, users will eventually migrate over to the legal alternative.  Online stores such as Apple's iTunes are a good start to such an initiative, but it's still not the first stop for those who want to download music. By exploiting the inherent problems of a file sharing service and making an alternative that makes those problems disappear, the industry will lure those people who value their time, although the kids without any money will continue downloading, even with the threat of lawsuits looming.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Along with my class on alternative dispute resolution, I'm an intern this summer at a midsize lawfirm in midtown Manhattan. Although the law firm occupies an entire floor of an office building, there is always a lack of space for the interns. Furthermore, there are too few computers for all of us to be using at the same time.    The IT manager has repeatedly attempted to get more computers in order to supply each intern with a place to work. However, her efforts have generally been futile. Two interns each day sit computerless at desks in the library, unable to do computer research or type memos and the like.   Furthermore, the office culture in the law firm is one that is not open for communication. Work is done for the lawyers and there is no feedback. I can only assume that this lack of communication extends to the partners themselves.   Because the heads of the firm don't have any contact with the interns, they don't have much incentive to ensure that each of us have a computer. The IT manager has repeatedly tried to get them to purchase new PCs, but she is continually unsuccessful. She's told me that she thinks they're cheap and not willing to spend the money.  It's in the firm's best interest to have the interns be able to be productive. Perhaps they see us as free labor that doesn't add much to their environment. We know that the firm bills clients for the time we spend doing research and we expect to get something out of the benefits we bring to the firm.  As unpaid interns, we work for free, but as one of my colleagues has said, "we don't work for nothing."  Without a place to work and without positive feedback and constructive criticism, there is no benefit to working here other than getting some experience doing research; experience we could get elsewhere in a much more supportive environment.  As a law student, I feel that everything I do this summer should be a learning experience. Instead, it has been a vexing experience. I do my work (when I can get a computer) and I turn it in. I never hear any feedback, so I assume I'm doing a satisfactory job. However, I am not satisfied with satisfactory, I want to learn what I need to do better. I might as well work from home in my pajamas if there's no benefit to having face to face contact.  I know that my experience at the firm is not unique. Many other interns feel the same way about their jobs and the administration of the firm and the experience in general.   As the lowest of the low, us interns don't have much bargaining power to change the current situation. Furthermore, most of us will be gone in a month or so, so there's not much incentive to argue and try to have them order more computers. This seems like a case where the best alternative to negotiating an agreement is better than going through the hassle of trying to change things.  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The following saga took place over three days.   June 20, 2004 	Today I went apartment hunting with my potential roommate/classmate Josh. We’re looking for a three bedroom apartment to share with another classmate of ours. I’m flexible with almost all aspects of the apartment (Location, size, etc). Josh has his heart set on the Greenwich Village area. Although I’d happily live in that area, I don’t value that location over other places we’ve seen, such as SoHo. In fact, I’d prefer to live in SoHo. Today we toured a three bedroom in a great neighborhood in SoHo, right near three train lines and very quiet but close to all the bars and restaurants. Because he previously lived in a larger apartment, Josh has furniture that he wants to bring into the apartment. This apartment we saw had three 100 sq ft bedrooms, two bathrooms and a 150 sq ft common area, with a kitchenette on 2 walls. It probably wouldn’t fit his couch. Or it might fit, but it’s not likely to be comfortable to live around.   	I really liked the apartment, but Josh decided we should look at other places before taking this one. The apartment was considerably cheaper than the others in the same price range we had found listings for on the internet, and the apartment we saw today had no brokers fee either, which was a big savings. Afraid that if we waited, the apartment would slip through our fingers, I asked Josh if he was willing to take the apartment and sell the sofa or put it in storage. He told me he loved his sofa and didn’t want to get rid of it or take a loss on the sale.  	Placed in such a situation, I recalled the methods outlined in Getting Past No, a book about negotiating with tough opponents. However, with such time pressure, it would be unlikely to gain much headway, especially with Josh’s optimistic “wait and see” attitude. He clearly was looking for an apartment with a larger common area and was willing to pay for that luxury. However, my goals were met perfectly by this apartment: location, price, location, and location.   Following the advice of the book, I held back from immediately trying to coax him into giving up his sofa and seeing things from my side. He kept on talking about how we were going to be contacted by an agent we had talked to that had an apartment that we could see. I reminded him that that apartment would have a brokers fee and be considerably more expensive than the one we saw and probably not as large. He maintained his position that he wanted to see other apartments first. I said that I would contact the management company of the building to see when they needed an application by and then left for home.  I was really holding myself back when I was talking to him. As I considered what I could do with the $200 savings on rent each month, I was thinking of strategies to get him to see my side. Was it really worth $2400 a year to him to have his precious couch?  Why couldn’t he put it in storage at his parents’ home in New Jersey? He wants to move in at the beginning of august, yet myself and our other roommate don’t need to move in until after the 15th. I was beginning to start fuming and needed to cool down. I think that if I reason with him by putting the savings into monetary terms, he may relent. I don’t know how much he values having that couch though.  Tonight I sent him an email outlining the points that I see as most important in finding an apartment and that this place fulfilled all the requirements I could think of. Let’s hope I can build that golden bridge.  June 21, 2004 	I talked to Josh and made the point that Jay and I were giving him a lot by getting an apartment on August 1 instead of August 15. He was reasonable and realized that his couch wasn’t worth that much in the long run. (An 8’ couch! Who has one of those in Manhattan?!)  Today I went back to the apartment to get measurements of all the rooms. I like the apartment more than ever. Josh said that he lined up some apartments for us to see tomorrow and then if everything is not as good, then we’ll take the one on Thompson St. that I like so much. Hopefully it’s still available on Wednesday.  June 22, 2004 	I went to the agency handling the Thompson St. apartment this afternoon after Josh decided he would be OK with the apartment. There was already an application in. We were two hours too late. I was angry, but I realize that there are other options out there.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A month or two ago, the LA Philharmonic was playing a concert of music from the Final Fantasy video games at the brand new Disney Concert Hall in LA. Some of my friends, being huge FF fans decided to go to this concert. Brian, one of my close friends from high school, was to buy tickets for his friends and their friends. Long story short, Brian ended up with two extra tickets, which were originally allocated to a friend of a friend.   Not needing the extra pair, Brian decided to sell the tickets on Ebay. Since the concert sold out, he was pretty much guaranteed to make a profit on the sale. However, once the person for whom the tickets were originally purchased got wind of this, he decided he wanted a piece of the action as well. Brian, being a self described "nice guy" decided it would be only fair to split the profit 50/50.  However, as a law student, I instantly remembered a lesson from my contracts class which stated that there has to be consideration for a promise, and I told Brian that there was no way that this other guy could get any claim for the tickets and that he wouldnt have to share the profits with this "friend of a friend."  Brian immediately rebuffed me and told me that I was being an asshole (which is probably true), and that he felt that it would be the "right thing to do" to split the profits.  A few days later, as Brian's other friends who told him about the concert got wind of this, they decided that they too were entitled to a part of the profits. Brian had a dilemma. What would be the best way to satisfy all his friends? Valuing his friendships with the other concertgoers over the money he would make from the sale, he decided that they would all split the profits from the sale evenly. With that, he thought it was over and settled.  But it was not. When other friends who had nothing to do with the concert got word of the situation, they also wanted a piece of the action. Deluged with complaints, Brian decided that it wasn't worth the hassle to deal with all his friends' complaints and in the end decided that anyone at all could contact him for a share of the profits.  He ended up selling the tickets for $360.00, a 200% profit ( urlLink here ). I'm still waiting for my 50 cents 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       	Reading about negotiation tactics and the methods uncooperative people use to get their way reminded me of a situation that would often occur between myself and my friends when we were planning a night out at the movies.  In Los Angeles, where I’m from, the geography is separated into the Valley, where many of my friends live and the Westside, where I live. When planning a movie, I always prefer to watch it at a west side theater, but my friends generally prefer to stay in the valley. Of course, the quality of the theater is the first determinant, and if a film is playing at the Mann Village in Westwood, we will generally see the movie there, as the Village is the best theater in LA. However, when a movie is playing at a lesser theater, both my friends and I try to get the other side to come over the mountains to see the film.  	Often, my friends will dig in and say they aren’t willing to battle traffic to the Westside to see a movie that doesn’t look so good in the first place. To that, I would reply that the traffic isn’t any better for me. We’d end up in the usual back-and-forth using dining locations, access to parking as well as size of screen, stadium seating, bitching about having to drive, opportunities to carpool and access to things to do after the movie as bargaining chips.  	During high school, when my group of friends was evenly split between the Westside and the Valley, the bargaining that went on wasn’t much of a problem, as we would go to one place one week and the other side the next, as the school was on the midpoint between the Westside and the Valley.  As my friends moved out to college, on the occasions we would get together over the summer or during holidays, I remained the only one left on the Westside. Being so outnumbered, often my best option was to meet halfway rather than to attempt to get a bunch of my friends to brave traffic and save the times when my friends would drive over to movies that were being screened at the Village. Lately, I’ve been driving to the apartment of one of my friends who lives close to the halfway point and carpool with them to a brand new theater that is deeper in the Valley. This seems like a decent compromise, as it keeps everyone from having to be behind the wheel too much and we end up at a theater we all can accept.  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       	I ride the subway every day. I only ride the bus sometimes - when I need to go crosstown or somewhere the subway doesn’t go. One thing I’ve always noticed is that people are always more willing to give up seats on the bus to the elderly than on the subway. Both forms of transportation reserve seats for the disabled, but only on the bus do I ever see people take pains to keep those seats empty.   	When riding on the subway, all seats are fair game. Even if there are few people on the train, the reserved seats are generally taken by people who want to sit by the door or away from the center of the car. On the bus, even when elderly people get on, they try to take other seats than those reserved for the old or disabled.  	For some reason, I think that people feel that the bus is a more personal experience. The driver sits right at the front of the bus and isn’t segregated from the passengers like a motorman in a subway car.  Perhaps it is the scarcity of the seats on the bus, or the higher percentage of older or disabled passengers who ride the bus.   	Personally, when I ride the subway, I don’t even raise an eyebrow when someone occupies a reserved seat, but when on the bus, it’s like I’m standing up for the rights of the disabled by raising my eyebrow at a seat taker.   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       On Wednesday afternoon, I was waiting for my flight to Boston at LaGuardia airport. Apparently, due to inclement weather, a bunch of flights to the Midwest had been canceled. Watching stranded passengers attempt to get the most out of gate agents as possible was quite the display of negotiating skills.   	A middle-aged man was headed to Chicago with his daughter on a flight that was no longer leaving New York. When told of the situation, he took out his gold frequent flyer mileage card and started waving it in front of the gate agent. He used his special status to be rebooked on another airline to Washington DC which would then let him connect to Chicago. Apparently the airline realized that they did not want to lose him as a customer, and this traveler knew that he was going to get what he wanted from the airline.   	Another lady in line had arrived to LaGuardia on another flight and had missed her connection to Boston. She didn’t have an arsenal of elite mileage cards to wave around, so she just stood there waiting for the gate agent to tap out whatever she could on her computer. After a few minutes of typing, the gate agent said the best they could do was put her on the waiting list for the next flight to Boston, which incidentally was also delayed an hour. The passenger looked as if she didn’t have any other option, so she accepted the situation and sat down to wait for her name to be called after all the ticketed passengers had checked in.  	By the time I got up to the gate agent, I could see how exasperated they were. Dealing with a day of passengers who each think they are the most important passengers on the plane clearly affected them. I quickly got my boarding pass and got out of their way.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday I participated in the mock arbitration that I mentioned a few days ago.&nbsp; I really enjoyed being the arbitrator and being able to make a decision on what was presented to me. Surprisingly, I found myself not to be biased by my previous experience as a "lawyer" for the defendants and was able to remain neutral.&nbsp;   The arbitration started off with opening statements by each side, where the lawyers representing the parties were able to state their cases. Surprisingly, the plaintiffs in the arbitration decided to abandon their claim for relief from the defendant's alleged abandonment of the "know your client" rule and had decided to proceed on fraud charges alone. During the subsequent direct and cross examinations of witnesses, I began to really enjoy my role as an arbitrator. Being able to stop people from talking and to interrupt with questions was refreshing, especially for a law student who never had any authority to do such things ever before. Quickly, I saw the differences between arbitration and mediation. The parties were much more adverse and no longer working together. They were simply there to convince the arbitrators that they were right and deserved to win the case.   A couple of times during the arbitration, the situation became very similar to an appellate argument. One of my fellow arbitrators was especially keen on prodding the lawyer for the plaintiff for information after the lawyer had finished closing statements.&nbsp;The situation became very heated and my professor even commented on how the situation had surpassed the general boundaries of arbitration.&nbsp; Of course, none of us had ever participated in an actual arbitration before, so what we saw as proper was shaped by our prior experiences with judges and in courtrooms.   After the parties had finished, the three arbitrators went to another room to discuss what the verdict should be. Each of us decided to give the plaintiff the fees that the brokerage charged, but we were not compelled to award punitive damages, as the plaintiff had not been damaged financially. In the end, we awarded the plaintiff the transaction fees charged by the brokerage and attorney's fees. We then went a step forward and fined the brokerage $250,000, to be payable to the NASD. Although we were in doubt about whether we could award a fine, we decided that we had the power to do what we wanted and went ahead with our plan anyways.&nbsp; The plaintiffs seemed happy with the result, as they got what they wanted, and their attorneys were paid for. The defendants were not pleased with their loss, but were satisfied with the fine, as they did not feel that the plaintiff should be rewarded for their actions.   Overall, I relished the opportunity to be in control of the situation. Being able to ask parties questions whenever I had something to ask was especially rewarding, even more so after having to go through a mediation where I had to hold back on asking questions that would seem impolite or unbecoming.&nbsp; I now see why arbitrators are willing to work for free or for a small honorarium, being able to feel the power to judge is definitely an ego boost.   &nbsp;     
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A few weeks ago, one of my friends who works at a TV studio in LA was telling me about a contract negotiation that went sour between an actress and the producers of a new TV show. The show will premiere on the fall schedule of one of the major TV networks and filming had already begun before the final contracts were signed. Initially, the actress’s agent had closed a deal with the studio, but left some “I’ll see what I can do about it” wiggle room about the actress’ credit as it would appear in the opening of the show. The actress wanted an “and with…” credit at the end of the list of names. However, the studio was not willing to give her such prominent placement, as this actress wasn’t a household name by any means and the standard studio contract gave the studio discretion as to where actors would be billed.    After the contract appeared to be signed, the manager of the actress contacted the studio and demanded the final credit, but the studio was unwilling to consider it. The two parties went into a negotiation for a day simply to iron out the terms of the actress’ credit. After a day of heavy negotiating, both sides remained at odds. The actress was key to the production of the show, and without her, the show would not be able to continue, so the studio could not walk away under any circumstances. Similarly, the actress seemed set on having the special credit at the end of the opening sequence and was not willing to budge. The studio offered the actress fifth billing, ahead of all the other supporting cast members, but the offer was rejected.    The situation seemed bleak. After the first day of negotiations, the studio found out about this problem somehow and the overall mood of the negotiations and at the office became very dark. The studio’s representative feared that he would lose his job because of the inability of the parties to come to a compromise. The atmosphere of the negotiations became extremely tense, as both parties knew that the actress was an indispensable part of the show and losing her was not an option. The negotiations continued for three more days, without any result. It was clear that the actress wanted recognition for her role and that the studio was unwilling and unable to change the structure of the credit listing. After taking a day to reflect on the situation, the parties got together again. With pressure on both parties to reach a compromise, the studio again offered to give the actress fifth billing, placing her above all the other supporting cast members. The actress finally relented and decided that being at the top of the billing for the supporting cast would be the best the studio would offer her.    Perhaps the actress realized that her best alternative to negotiating an agreement would be to walk away, and that would place her in a much worse position than taking fifth billing. The studio certainly could have given her the last billing, but the heads of the studio saw no reason to bend the rules for this actress. The studio didn’t see any reason to give a supporting actress such due and did not think she deserved to have a unique credit. They put an immense amount of pressure on their representative to get the actress to fall in line with the other cast members and not request anything extraordinary. In the end, by expanding the pie to give the actress some special recognition by placing her above the other supporting cast members, the parties were able to come to a conclusion that satisfied the studio and gave the actress satisfaction.    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Next week in class, I will be playing the role of an arbitrator in the model arbitration that we will do. The facts for the arbitration will be the same as in the securities mediation, but this time, there will be three arbitrators who will make the final decision. As I reflected on what the role of an arbitrator brings with it, I wondered why people become arbitrators. Last year, in Civil Procedure, Lela Love, a noted ADR scholar came to talk to our class. I remember her telling us that many arbitrators work for free because they enjoy the rush of power that comes with the job. Certainly, that is one of the perks, as the jokes between me and my classmates about the forthcoming gift baskets and boxes of chocolate as gifts to the "arbitrators" would illustrate, but what drives someone to become an arbitrator.  &nbsp;  At the firm I worked for in LA, disputes would sometimes be arbitrated and&nbsp;I would witness the lawyers trying to decide on an arbitrator. Most of the arbitrators were veteran judges who had retired from the bench and had decided to become arbitrators, as it is a relatively low stress job and does not require the formality of reasoning out decisions on paper and following the strict rules of court. The lawyers would pare down the potential arbitrators by looking at their history of decisions and trying to recall any past experiences with them. This process was always very careful, as it was one of the most important decisions that the lawyers would be making. Like choosing a jury, every factor of each potential arbitrator was questioned, but unlike a jury member, the arbitrators had a history that the lawyers could look to.  &nbsp;  Once an arbitration starts, the arbitrator is king (or queen). Having the ability to single handedly come to a conclusion that is binding to the parties is an extreme ego boost, and as Lela Love said, something that many arbitrators will forgo a fee to attain. A statement by Professor Baum stating that many arbitrators go on gut feelings stuck with me. These arbitrators, who are so powerful, aren't bound by much. There is relatively little recourse that the parties who are dissatisfied with an outcome can take. The fact that the parties can't appeal a decision makes it even more important for the lawyers to choose arbitrators who they feel will be fair and neutral.  &nbsp;  Going into the arbitration next week will be an exciting event for me. As a party in the negotiations, I have and intimate view of one side of the argument already and I wonder if I will be naturally biased towards the side I was on in the mediation. However, as an arbitrator, I will consciously try to be a neutral party to the entire proceeding. It should be an interesting process, as there will be three arbitrators in the proceeding and we will each have to make up our own minds about the result.&nbsp;I can't wait until I am given the opportunity to have the final say on the issue however. It should be a good experience.     
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday in class, I participated in a simulated securities fraud negotiation. In the case we were assigned, a broker had sold shares of a customer's stock after it had lost a great deal of money without her permission and bought shares in another company which then rose in value and made up for the loss. The broker then sold the shares that went up and bought the stock in the old company again, trying to mask the fact that any activity had gone on at all. In the end, the customer wound up with more money than she started with, and everything was well, until an internal audit revealed that the broker conducted these trades without the customer's permission. The customer and the brokerage firm entered into a mediation in order to try to come to a settlement.  My partner and I represented the brokerage firm, and two of our classmates played the client and her father. Another classmate acted as the mediator. Both sides clearly had much different views of the situation. Whereas my partner and I felt that what the broker did was beneficial to the client, although illegal, the other party felt that they had been wronged substantially and were entitled to punitive damages, as the stock that the broker bought and sold in secret had gone up even more after he sold it.  As representatives for the brokerage, we thought it was ludicrous that this client felt entitled to gains from a stock that she never would have bought in the first place, and that she already gained from the actions of the broker. However, one of my classmates playing the other party had been working in the securities industry and knew that large brokerages are willing to pay exorbitant amounts to keep clients who have been subject to illegal transactions quiet, so she wouldn't accept that the firm was not liable for punitive damages.  As a goodwill measure, the brokerage eventually offered to refund the brokerage fees for the transactions that the client did approve (as the illegal transactions were not charged for) and in addition, offer $4,000.00, ten percent of the value that the illegally traded stock had gained. Needless to say, the offer was not accepted. My partner and I felt that the other side had been inflexible and unwilling in the negotiation and that they weren't seeing the situation from all perspectives.  Later, I was told how such negotitions end in the real world, where even when an illegal trade benefits a client, the firm still ends up paying a great deal of money to keep the client quiet. Not going into the negotiation with such information, the two sides were not able to see each other's interests clearly and understand the bar set by real situations.   The mediation quickly broke down into adversarial arguments because both sides had different ideas of what each side wanted. The client thought the brokerage would want to protect its public image, while the brokerage saw the client as greedy and trying to have its cake and eat it too. I think that if the mediator had tried to clarify the interests of each party earlier in the mediation, the process would have become smoother, but in any event, without the real world knowledge, it would have been difficult for my partner and I, as the brokerage, to offer anything more than the amount we ended up putting on the table. 
    
    
</post>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was checking weather.com to see how fricking hot it is outside today (89 degrees with 77% humidity..."feels like" 94 [according to weather.com]) and I saw this ad  on  the page:           Who the hell gets away to Columbus, Ohio??  Cleveland is bad enough, but at least they have the rock and roll hall of fame there! Somebody at an ad agency in Ohio needs to get fired.    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just went to see Harold and Kumar go to White Castle. Very funny movie. I havent seen that many asians in a movie theater since...ever. It was really funny though. Now i want to go to white castle. and get some  lap dances...  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The age of innocence is officially over. Krispy Kreme? WHY!!!! WHY!!!!! So now the donuts are tainted with the shame of securities fraud. Talk about glazed. More info  urlLink here .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I had a nice lunch at  urlLink Amuse . They extended restaurant week till Labor Day, so i had a 3 course meal for $20.04. Its a really great deal. I had the gruyere and ham appetizer, the striped bass entree and a really nice creme brulee for dessert. You should go there if you get a chance. the menu is available  urlLink here .
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is what happens when you mess with the iPod...      Apple Probes RealNetworks Concerning iPod Thu Jul 29, 2004 09:01 AM ET    NEW YORK (Reuters) - Apple Computer Inc. (AAPL.O:  urlLink Quote ,  urlLink Profile ,  urlLink Research )  on  Thursday said it is investigating RealNetworks Inc. (RNWK.O:  urlLink Quote ,  urlLink Profile ,  urlLink Research )   for releasing software that allow users to transfer songs  purchased on the RealPlayer Music Store service to Apple's  iPod.  "We are stunned that RealNetworks has adopted the tactics  and ethics of a hacker to break into the iPod, and we are  investigating the implications," Apple said in a statement.  Apple said that once its iPod software is updated, it is  highly likely that RealNetworks technology will cease to work  with current and future iPods.
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw Napoleon Dynamite. It's one of the funniest, most heartfelt movies i've seen in a long time. It's SWEET. And Pedro says you should see it. All your wildest dreams will be fulfilled. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhhhhhh...can you hear that? its the sound of Ryan Seacrest's tv show being flushed down the toilet. what an annoying little twat. And the ratings of KIIS FM have dropped since he replaced rick dees. heheheheh. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a pretty cool phone with bluetooth, huge screen, really thin metal case...too bad it's running Motorola's stupid menu system..and it's going to cost $700 (not that cost has ever stopped me before).  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is seriously one of the coolest things i've EVER seen:  urlLink How to turn your iPod into a universal remote control .   . 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
               You're Japan!      You tried to beat everyone around you physically, and when that didn't work, you turned to mental arts. &nbsp;Not only is this more acceptable to those people, but you're really good at mental arts. &nbsp;Somehow you're able to fit a great deal of industry into small spaces, and this has generated a lot of income for you. &nbsp;Now if you could just stop eating whale meat, you'd be making real progress.   Take the  urlLink Country Quiz     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I showed up at work today at the usual time, settled into my desk (since the paralegal who has been stealing it from me 3 days a week doesn't work on Mondays), sat around doing nothing since my boss and her paralegal didn’t get in yet. I find out that the 2 other interns who were in Summer Institute ended last Friday. So I'm thinkin, hmmmm. I took last thurs and fri off, so I don't mind being there. 10am my boss' paralegal comes in and I ask him where my boss is. Apparently she's in north carolina. And she didn’t leave me anything to do. So I decide that I should just go home. so I did. I went to get a haircut.  And I had a nice lunch in chinatown and got some groceries. Mmmm. Today is a really nice day too. Ahhhhhh, summer.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm finally done with that ADR class. That means no more journal entries. So i'm keeping my blogspot address for my own blog. you can read the old ADR entries  urlLink HERE . 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't think it's ever right to start a war over BLTs. Even if there's mustard in them.    Just wanted to let everyone know that. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stopped by the new Roosevelt campus at UCSD today for the first time. It looks so cool. the dining hall is awesome, all glass with views of the ocean and the apartments look really nice. Even the lounges look comfortable. what a change from the old campus! Too bad I'm still not in college. damn. 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my new powerbook today. its the 15" with the dvd burner. its sweet! 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's so nice to be back in LA. The weather is fantastic, I'm back in my house, I get to see all my friends that I haven't seen in a while... Last night I went to the Dodger game. The dodgers won, of course, so it was pretty fun. ahhh... its good to be back 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      as i'm writing this, i'm 40,000 feet above the ground. yes, i'm on a plane. no, i dont have an internet connection. but it would be cool if i did. i ran my ipod battery into the ground so i'm listening to music off my ibook. oh well. thankfully i got upgraded to economy plus. i'm actually in the front row of economy. its not so bad. they showed eternal sunshine of the spotless mind on the flight. I saw it already, so i didnt need to see it again. I think they should stick to action movies and broad comedies on planes. or just install little tvs and give us a 40 channel selection like Virgin Atlantic does. i wonder if the airlines could give out tickets for free in exchange for watching ads the entire flight. It would be like Ryan Air, where the inflight "magazine" is just a catalog for stuff they sell. in any event, in flight entertainment needs to be revamped. Apparently United is launching PS service between NYC and LA in the fall, which is basically a 3 class service with flat beds in first class, international business class seats and all economy deluxe in the main cabin. that should be interesting. i wonder if people are willing to pay more for a domestic flight. it's going to be aimed at business travelers mainly. they'll have the in flight high speed internet on board those planes too. and regular outlets. finally. i wonder if i could use my miles to get on those flights. i bet they're going to be red eye flights though, or else whats the point of flat beds. and i hate flying overnight. even in first class i can't sleep a wink. maybe if i got a private jet...hahah. I can't believe how many flights i've been on in the past year. Eleven round trips to various places. ridiculous. too bad i'm not loyal to any one airline. heh. or else i'd be flying for free right now. oh wait. i AM flying for free right now (thanks to the star alliance). apparently we're above the grand canyon right now. not that its very exciting from an airplane. looks like a crack in the ground. which is what it is. hmph. ok. well i'm done with this stream of consciousness stuff. see ya on the ground.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i'm watching the local news on CBS 2 here in NYC and Sarah Hughes, the olympic gold medalist in figure skating is doing featurettes on local athletes at the summer olympics. It was ok, but it's obvious that she's new at this gig. After her little segment, all the "host chatter" was about where she keeps her gold medal. Oh well. i guess its better than sitting on your ass the whole summer. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I moved into my new apartment. Currently, i'm subletting it, as I have my old apartment for this month also. Check out some pictures:  urlLink HERE . 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was watching the Travel Channel last night and they had a show about how there are people who are huge fans of disney world in orlando and how they tackle the theme parks there.  The show basically followed a family around while they went through the park. The father of the family was a minister at some church in middle america and he had brought his family of 5 to disney world. These fans aren't content to use the fast pass and leave it at that, the father wrote out a schedule of EACH RIDE according to a map of the park and when and where to get the fast pass tickets to each ride. He basically ferried his family around from ride to ride running around to get the fast pass tickets between lines. goddamn it.  Now folks, I enjoy an amusement park as much as anyone, but seriously, this is more like work than a vacation. RELAX. freaks. 
    
</post>


</Blog>