<Blog>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last time I checked, aviator sunglasses were in style. So I went to the mall and bought a pair.  Of course there happened to be a pair on sale for 11 bucks. TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE! What kind of company sells designer sunglasses for 11 dollars? So I come home thinking :             "we'll see how they work out" I spent the day feeling cool (something that is rare in my life) until they broke. Yes, they broke on the first day. I felt like I had just bought something from one of those traveling salesmen on the beaches of Mexico. " senor, you buy! You buy! Only 11 pesos !" "ok why not."  CRAAACK . "Shit." So here I stand, with my allowance gone, holding a pair of knockoff aviators from a mall kiosk. This is one of those moments where I wish a was a blonde girl, then I'd have an excuse. In the end, I stole 5 bucks from the change drawer and bought some super glue. Nobody will ever know...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Taking a break from trashing people. This is my journal from boot camp.  Day 1 Found out that i was being shipped off to boot camp.  Day 2 Arrived.  Day 3 First day, ran really hard, got yelled at.   Day 4 Weekend pass revoked because the seargant found my playboy.  Day 5 Slapped Sgt. on ass and recieved a sound beating.  Day 6 Got the idea of running away.  Day 7 Recieved severe beating for planning to run away.  Day 8 Ran away.  Day 9 Seargant found me laying on ground,exausted, 40 feet from the camp.  Day 10 Recieved a sound beating for running away.  Day 11 Put a snake in seargant's pants.  Day 12 Recieved beating for putting a snake in the seargant's pants.  Day 13 Spent the day in medical tent due to my severly bruised body.  Day 14 Recieved beating for spending previous day in medical tent.  Day 15 Beat up seargant.  Morning-Day 16 Handcuffed to cement wall for punishment by firing squad. Afternoon Day 16 Firing squad arrives but taliban invades camp.  Day 17 Recieved beating from taliban.  Day 18 Tried to commit suicide by hitting head against brick wall.  Day 19 Didnt work.  Day 20 Sang songs to taliban guard.  Day 21  Recieved beating for singing to taliban guard.  Day 22 Shipped to taliban headquarters in afgahnistan.  Day 23 Recieved beating from osama himself.  Day 24 Asked for another beating.  Day 25 Request granted.  Day 26 Asked to join taliban.  Day 27 Not a good idea. Recieved beating.  Day 28 Recieved first meal in 4 days, and a beating.  Day 29 Asked guard if he'd seen who wants to be a millionaire.  Day 30 It was his favorite show.  Day 31 Guard and I played mock game of millionaire. We began to bond.  Day 32 Asked if i could phone a friend. Recieved beating.  Day 33 Went "sight seeing" with taliban soldiers.  Day 34 We ended our sight seeing trip at a large pit.  Day 35 Who wants to be a millionaire guard told me to stand at edge of pit facing away from them.  Day 36 Asked him if that was his final answer.  Day 37 Shot into pit.  Day 38 Only wounded, layed in pit for the day.  Day 39 Heard engine sounds so i gathered my strength and gripped the top of the pit and pulled myself up. Hands ran over by a tank.  Day 40 Layed in pit again.  Day 41 Body began to eat itself.  Day 42 Skin saturated with sand.  Day 43 American soldiers find the pit.  Day 44 They bury all the dead taliban on top of me without noticing.  Day 45 One of the taliban men still alive.  Day 46 Nursed survivor back to health.  Day 47 Survivor and i talk and plot to get out.  Day 48 Dug part of tunnel with hands.  Day 49 Tunnel filled in with sand overnight.  Morning Day 50 Survivor started to look like a sandwich.  Afternoon Day 50 Ate him.  Day 51 Pit discovered by local people and i am pulled out.  Day 52 Declared dead by village doctor. Just in case, recieved beating.  Day 53 While my grave was being dug i made a sound.  Day 54 Nursed back to health by afgahn family.  Day 55 Progressing health.  Day 56 Man of family decided that i was becoming too strong.  Day 57 Crippled by man's beating.  Day 58 Slit wrists with plastic spoon.  Day 59 "saved" by village doctor.  Day 60 Jumped out of 3 story house head first.  Day 61 Didn't work. Survived because of hay bales below window.  Day 62 U.S. Marines come to village.  Day 63 They find me.  Day 64 Shipped back to U.S.  Day 65 Allowed one week of free time.  --------- Day 72 Hauled back to old boot camp for unknown reason.  Day 73 Cuffed to same old wall.  Day 74 Prayed for taliban to come.  Day 75 Firing squad arrives and sets up to fire.  Day 76 Shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok time to open up another can of whoop-ass on a social group. REDNECKS. Nobody is quite sure why we call them rednecks, but im guessing it has somthing to do with their necks being red. If they really are red, why don't we just put them in the same racism class as native americans and call them "INJINS".   Have you ever noticed when you meet a redneck and his wife, they look suspiciously alike. Inbreeding. Ehhhh. Even the indians knew not to do that.  We think our kids in our urban neighborhoods are messed up. Obviosly most of us havn't met the redneck kids. The first words i ever heard out of a hick-child's mouth was "Hey sir, would ya like a chaw of tabaccy?" Good lord, if my 9 year old nieghbor offered me tobacco the whole city would be up in arms. Which brings me to my next point. If you are ever out in hick country, feel free to murder someone. The criminal justice rate is somwhere around 2%. And they only found that criminal because he was killed in the crime.   It is redneck tradition to drink milk straight from the utter.  But then again, it is also tradition to marry your sister. And to kiss all family members with your tongue instead of on the cheek.   I think that rednecks have an unfair advantage on us. We are all pasty white during the winter, but they have so much dirt from the summer caked onto them that they're tan year round.  Leave those people alone you say? Muahahah, careful, your people might be next.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Please listen to the dramatics song "stupid girls" to get the full deal out of this entry. www.thedramatics.net   Ok, lets talk about the endangered species: preppy girls. With only five cents, you can feed a starving prep girl 3 meals for a day. A mint, a goldfish cracker, and a piece of gum. This is more than she would normally eat in a month. So please, gather the change off of your dresser and send it to: "Savetheskinnies" non-profit organization.  We will send you a picture of your prep girl and a little info on them. After all, there isn't much to tell. "This is Amber, she likes to breathe and go on diets. Her favorite food is air, and when asked what her favorite color is she says: blonde." Damn I feel bad for those poor little things. Designer clothing companies should start sewing a donation cup onto all of their jeans.   -In a recent study, it was proven that preppy girls main food sources are lip gloss and chapstick. Also proven in a recent study: you're a dueshbag. -60% of all prep girls have considered suicide at some time. Also proven: 87% have considered running away and taking all of their stuffed animals with them. - 1 out of 5 preppy girls who took a survey said they knew what multiplication is. -The other 4 thought it was a synonym for sex.    Thankyou.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well my first subject of many (about society) to come will be breeding. I decided that it needs to be controlled. We have too many people in this world. I have nothing against the act of sex, but for pete sakes dont have a kid!  "oh! but we are in love and want to start a family!"  - cliche'd couple  Congatulations! Have a kid then. And by "a kid" a mean ONLY ONE. The last thing we need is another set of triplets living across the street. I know i sound like a jackass, but come on people you know it's true! So lets have a kid each to pass on our genes, but thats all. STOP AT ONE! The overpopulation problem that will hit us around 2040 will be less severe and everbody looks back and says "wow, good thing we only had one kid each for the last 35 years, we'd be screwed if we had kept up the triplet trend."   Point #2 on breeding: Don't murder your kids. I do belive that we should cut down on how many we have but its so damn cold to kill a baby. Not cool man.   #3: Once you have a kid, if you  can  take care of them, you better do it! People who put up babies for adoption that are perfectly able of parenting piss me off. It's yours! TAKE IT! People who adopt babies are the best because they fix sombody elses mistake.   I feel older than 14 talking about this shit but hey, its on my mind. My negative approach is the only way to say it. You are now experieced.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, i'm sure i am the only person who will ever read this but fuck that i have no life anyways. So this will be the place where all my attempted theories and thoughts go...should be fun to read if yer someone just randomly checking it out. Please recognize that I am not insane, i just think insanely. Yer the insane one if yer actually reading this. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So, there i was, in an empty bootcamp with no idea of which way is home. So i did the first thing all animals naturally do to survive. I went to the Mess Hall (eating room) and ate. I ate everything from dishwater to crusty macaroni and cheese. When i finished i looked out the window. Dammit, another army had come for me. But this time it was a bunch of assholes in grey uniforms. They threw me into a time portal, and yeeeehaw!  &nbsp; I came to my senses in a hay stack. The mooing of 500 cows around me woke me up.&nbsp; After a brief walk, i concluded that it was 1942 and I had been teleported to Normandy Beach on D-Day.  &nbsp; I thought i saw somthing in the bushes but i kept walking, maybe it was just a large animal with hand-grenades and the letters ARMY written on it's back. I realized my mistake and turned to face the bushes. Kapow! Fierce beating. &nbsp; Tune in later for part3 of  SAVING PRIVATE LOMMEN  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I am confident that if you are reading this, you have read my boot camp journal. If not, do so. It's a couple entries back from this.   So as it turns out, the firing squad never got around to shooting me. My good friends, the bloods, stepped in and gunned them all right before the fire at will command. Yes, that's right, the bloods. The huge gang. A few years ago i was walking to the subway in manhattan when i saw two big white guys beating the hell out of a black man in a back alley. I thought "hmmm, this could be a good show." So i took the nearest seat which happened to be on a 2-by-4 plank that was protruding from the wall. What i didnt know was that on the other end was a huge sack of nails. On contact of my ass hitting the plank, the nails were flung teter-toter style into the whiteys. They instantly became human porcupines and fell dead. The black man was ruffed up but ok. He said "hi, I'm DeAndre of the bloods." I said "Congratulations." Of course i recieved a beating for this smart-ass remark and woke up 3 blocks away in a dumpster. DeAndre stuck a nail through my finger to hold in the note he left me:  I am forever in debt to your punk-ass   After the bloods had put 27 bullets in each member of the firing squad, DeAndre came over to free me. He said "I don't owe you nothin' no mo." Still in my handcuffs I said: "I didn't need your help, i could have taken them."   And so is the story of my escape. Tune in later for part2 of   SAVING PRIVATE LOMMEN 
     

    
</post>



<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yyyuuuuuuupp  tyler  p.s. sublime is sooo gooood. and flowers too 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      people who like america are so gay. Its the worst. Everyone's so arrogant and trendy and dumb. Im movin to canada as soon as im 18. Or possibly germany. Or antartica. Anywheres better than here. Also - did you know theres a library at southcenter mall? thats where i am right now.  tyler FO REAL!!!  p.s. thats the other reason america's stupid. Everybody thinks they're a gangster. SHUT UP! YOU LIVE IN SUBURBAN MAPLE VALLEY!!!!!  p.p.s. go terrorists  p.p.p.s. the titles of my last two entries rhymed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;Osama bin-laden has been added to MLB's hall of fame after hitting 114 home runs at the home run derby. When asked how he did it he replied: "The fans are behind me all the way, thankyou" Yes osama, we are right behind you...  WITH A GUN UP YO' ASS!  -lommen (this may be the stupidest thing ive ever written) 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if i was the president of  pep  si  i would put on the bottom of all the caps: &nbsp;  You Win!!!!!! YAY!!!!!!!!!!!  &nbsp; even if there was no game. but not coke cause coke's  gay . &nbsp; &nbsp;  mawhooooooooooooO    &nbsp;  -tyler  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, the three coolest things in the world are music, flowers, and of course sublime. And burritos.  &nbsp;  'everybody seems to think im lazy, i dont care, i think they're crazy. Running everywhere at such a speed, till they find theres no need...'  &nbsp;  gimme burritos. badmintons rad. im gonna go get my nap on. Have fun.  &nbsp; -tyler  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It begins. I'm not quite sure what this blog while turn out to be, but with the endless, mindless humor of 2 dumb kids it should be alot of fun. Tyler Pierce, Zak Lommen, and one blog.   YOUR MOM  &nbsp;  &nbsp; -ZAK &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;  if, and only if yer too&nbsp;curios for yer own good:   urlLink  http://www.youdoyermomonweekends.com    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      holy crap...whoever invented burritos...if you're watchin or whatever...please, like slaughter me and piss on my corpse...id be so honored...  tyler 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just wrote a 2 paragraph story on a picture and then realized that i can't post pictures on here so it's usless.  -Lommen 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i aint gettin outta bed today.  tyler 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      man, summers the greatest. dont have to shower, go to the lake. Dont have to sleep, watch late night tv. Dont have to write - i tried writing somethin the other day and i could barely read it. I mean, i can barely read it anyways but this was especially bad because i havent written anything in like 4 months. Also, did i mention all the otter pops you can handle?  tyler 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its like 3 in the morning. ...  ...  ...screw you guys im eatin otter pops tyler p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.s.p.ps.p.sp.sp.sp.cps.cp.plvomsa 89we 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      one time when i was three, i locked myself in the trunk of the car. Like, i had the keys inside the closed trunk with me. so......the towing company had to come and drill a hole in the trunk and convience me to give them the keys. when i came out my parents gave me a hug. Could you imagine doing that now? they'd probably smack me upside the head. Also, when you're 3 you can get lost like everyday and people will just think its cute cause you're being adventurous. Get lost now and i'd be reported as a runaway and taken downtown without passing go OR collecting $200.  ...(sigh) tyler 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my dads really old and talks to himself. A lot. Out loud. im building a tree house 16 feet off the ground and he says its too high.  tyler 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was a warm day in august. The time: 11 AM. The place: the floor of zak's room. A lone soldier stepped out of the western town's market. He looked out across the dusty plain before him. He spit the excess tobacco that was newly purchased. It was a hot one alright, a real fryer. Then he heard something...Was it a gunshot? He concentrated yet again on the dusty plain. All he could define was a few tumbleweeds and a withering cactus. Wait. No sir. There it was. The cause of his curiosity. A band of military skirmishers. "WELL DEVIL'S DANY DICK!" he yelled, and ran to the general's quarters. Unfortunately the general was having a ride on the town whore and after the soldier reported his finding, he was shot in his genitals. The general put on his trousers and walked outside. Before he could decide what to do about the dozen men pointing rifles at him, he was hit between his eyes. Amber (the whore) ran out to where he lay and busted out her throwing knives. She hit 12 men with 4 knives.  AND SO BEGAN THE BATTLE FOR TEXAS' INDEPENDENCE.        Ok, so what really happened: Tyler and i discovered a bag with every army man/cowboy/pirate/knight/injin ever collected by the 3 brothers in my family. We couldnt resist. We set them up, and fought a battle. I can honestly say it was fun as hell, and i'm sure there will be another. Tyler, we are the men...  -Lommen 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so this morning my mom woke me up at 9 to clean the house. Im like 'why do we need to clean it?'  'because its dirty' 'at 9 in the morning? when you have to go to work and i need sleep?' 'tyler stop being disobediant'  what a dumb broad. Thats my favorite word ever. Broad.  tyler  p.s. i needed my sleep too, after that tough climb the previous day... 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tyler just came over, and when he came up into my room i told him to sign my signature wall up on the top bunkbed. It was rad. The poor kid struggled beyond control to get himself upon the bedding, due to a lack of a ladder...When he finally accomplished the top of the bed, he said "Wow, i was thinking about setting up base camp on the bottom bunk and heading for the summit in the moring" Hahahaha what a good kid...sad too.  -Lommen       
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      buddah-"everything is as it should be" jesus-"shut up buddah"  i cant wait till im a buddist. it'll be hardcore. in nepal - where im-a gonna live - theres no war, hunting and deforestation are illegal, theres no pollution....all because of the buddists. Like everyone there is buddist.  tyler  too bad im soooo cool 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>