<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Clean up for the self-important.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What Pete wrote about drivers in the Dallas area is absolutely true. That is not an exaggeration. I have seen people driving and have been on highways all over the world. With the exception of the Swiss on the autobahn in Germany, I've never seen a larger amount of people driving so badly anywhere else.   The trouble is, most area drivers don't just drive too fast, that would be way too sensible.  They also hold the record for the most incredibly stupid stunts imaginable. Swerving in and out of the lanes, totally ignoring weather conditions, tailgating, driving in inappropriate or even closed lanes, or deciding to turn off at the very last possible instant available that won't wind the bozo up in a meat wagon.   In many cases, they do actually end up in a meat wagon or at the city morgue. In the latter case, there is a company in Dallas that specializes in suicide and homicide clean up. I'm sure they would be most happy to clear away the debris. For a small fee.   Just in case you are wondering, yes it is true- there really is a suicide & homicide clean up business. Pete took a picture of the billboard advertisement which I will post when he finds it. (Thursday note: The picture was located and is now posted above this article.)   If people would just slow don't a bit and more importantly stop driving with their heads up their asses, we wouldn't have the huge number of accidents that we normally do in the Dallas/Ft. Worth area. I have seen cars and trucks turned upside down, autos on fire, a car smashed beyond recognition, a truck that went over a bridge and landed nose first into the top of a car completely crushing the car and most likely anyone inside. Fortunately I didn't get close enough to see that.   I think that I rode a bicycle in another life since that seems much smarter and safer to me. Safer in another state or even another country- not in this area. That would be totally insane which, while some of you may think I am, in reality, I am not. And just for the record, family and close friends may comment if they choose but remember that eventually some of you will have to eat my cooking again at some point.  I frequently worry about Pete driving across town and have considered having a suped-up Hummer designed especially for him. It would be a bit more like a tank really since I'd like it built of solid stainless steel reinforced with kevlar. It would have a cattle guard on the front and I'd have him a kevlar helmet made or just get an Army surplus helmet.   Maybe I could also get some retractable armament installed as well. Like a small cannon or a grenade launcher. Even both. Where the sun roof is I could have a gunner turret window installed too. Then mount a 50 caliber machine gun and VOILA! Insta-death on wheels! You could bet nobody would be running this guy down for sure! The road warrior would have nothing on him.   Ok, maybe the armament is a bit much but it's a thought. At least I wouldn't worry so much about Pete driving across town on highways clogged with moronic drivers. He would be safe while happily blasting his way to and from work everyday. There may be a market for that kind of Hummer, I think true gaming addicts like Pete would appreciate a setup like that. Serious Sam for real! What do you think? The lines are open!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I thought I'd chime in with a thought I had...  ---- I'm ordinary.  Let me explain that. You see, every time I drive to work and back I see all these other people who must be really important. You can tell it by the way they drive.  Go down I-635 (aka the Lyndon B. Johnson Freeway, or just "LBJ") any time and you'll see what I mean. It's a 60 MPH zone along there but you'll see all these people with jobs so important that they have to go faster. The trouble is there are so many of them that the road is clogged, so they tailgate the car in front or change lanes all the time, so that everyone can see how important they are.  And their jobs must be important, right? So important that they'll risk their lives to get there as quickly as they can. So important, in fact, that they'll risk your life too. It's nice to know that if I get walloped into a hospital bed, or a wheelchair, or a wooden box, that at least it was because the driver who did it was an Important Person with an Important Job. I'm just as sure that my family will see it the same way. They'll say, "We're just so happy that he was walloped into a hospital bed/wheelchair/wooden box by an Important Person on their way to do an Important Job - at least it wasn't a waste".  The thing is, how is it that so many people have such Important Jobs? It seems that more than half of the drivers on the road at that time of the day are Important People. All I can tell you about these people is that most of them probably work in downtown Dallas, because so many of them rush importantly down I-35E and leave LBJ free for mostly Ordinary People like me (there are still a few Important People zooming along LBJ; I guess they have Important Jobs around the airport)  There is another possibility, of course, and that's that a lot of those people aren't really important at all, but they like to look as if they are. To that end they drive like real Important People and hope the rest of us don't notice the difference. In other words they'll risk death ("Death: the permanent cessation of all vital functions; the end of life") for themselves or others rather than admit that they might not be Important People.  I'm sure I'm right. Because to tell you the truth, I can't think of many jobs that are so important that a sane, rational person would risk their own and other people's lives to get to it. Thinking about it, it isn't even logical: if you have an Important Job and kill yourself trying to do it, then it doesn't get done, right? Because you're dead, right?  Ergo, there can't be any such thing as a job so important that you'd risk your life to do it. If any job was that important, then there would be plans, organizations, maybe entire government departments devoted to making sure that the people doing it stay alive. That's why the President has a herd of Secret Service guys around whenever he's in public - because his job is so important.  (Note that I say the  job  is important, not the President. Any other time I would say both were equally important but in Dubya's case I think the Secret Service guys should be replaced by a troupe of, say, Agent Smith action figures. But I digress.)  So if there can't logically be a job that's so important it's worth dying for, that can mean only one thing. We have large numbers of people driving around who only  think  that they, and their jobs, are that important.  These people need our help. The rest of us - Ordinary People like you and me who accept their jobs for what they are; just a way to make the money we need to finance our lives outside the workplace - must find a way to help these poor victims of self-importance. To that end...  I'm starting a campaign to help these people. It's called People For Ordinary Rational Driving, or PFORD for short. The campaign needs your help, and more than that it needs your money. Make checks and money orders payable to PFORD. Send cash. It will all be going to a good cause.  It's important. ---- 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Over the years I've often wondered how Alfred Hitchcock came up with the idea for his movie, "The Birds". Maybe he had a nightmare or maybe something else happened that gave him the idea. Personally I think he visited Texas and experienced the evil treachery of birds first hand and decided that it would make a great movie.  The treachery I am referring to are the winged demons that inhabit every available nook and cranny around North Dallas. It seems there are huge hordes of birds this year, more so than normal and besides making some of the residents very ill, they crap on absolutely everything. Nothing is sacred.  I think they fully understand and enjoy making pests of themselves. You can see them looking at each other as if to say, "Hey Carl! Watch me!" while diving bombing anyone foolish enough to wander innocently into the yard. Even Ginger the cat runs away in terror.   About a week ago, I saw him slinking along the patio after a bird. Slinking that is, until he got within viewing distance of the fifty or so birds that were all lined up on the fence watching him. The cat's ears perked up and he turned, looked at me with a distinct "Oh my god, help ME!" look, then escaped blasting past me at warp speed.   The birds also use the swimming pool as a giant birdbath and screech at us if we make any attempt to actually get into the pool. I briefly considered equipping the pool with a smallish alligator. While that thought had obvious appeal, the plan was quickly vetoed since it could make swimming a tad on the tricky side. Then there are the cars.   Sometimes the cars look as if they have custom paint jobs. You end up with solid color cars with paint splattered all over them. People pay big bucks for those kind of paint jobs. But of course what we get isn't paint. It's bird crap deliberately deposited by the tweeting, feathered cretins just to irritate me. I regularly try to squirt them with the garden hose so I know they watch me and want to get even.  Now you may be thinking that I'm being unreasonable or unfair to the birds but in reality, they only have themselves to blame. If they would just fly next door and use my neighbors pool and crap on his Lexus, I wouldn't have any problems with them at all. But they don't. They do all that at my house. This is why I think the birds have it in for me after all the hosing incidents.   I suppose I should give them a break and maybe the car (and everything else) will be crap-free sometime in the near future.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes I have indeed made a wish. In fact, I've made several real wishes and I hope at least one or two of them come true. I also hope that everyone else's wishes come true as well as long as they are good wishes and don't cause harm to another.  Part of my Solstice will include gathering the growing abundance from my small garden. Most of the plants are in large pots, "container gardening" but it works just as well, less weeding and certainly well enough to produce enormous foot long, crisp cucumbers.   The tomato plants have begun producing loads and loads of small tomatoes. The pimento and bell pepper, yellow and zucchini squashes and cantaloupes are also covered with blooms but haven't made fruit yet. The watermelon plants have two tiny melons growing on them. They are the first melons I've grown so it's fun to see them grow a little every couple of days.   I have already had one harvest of japaleno peppers and a small batch of banana peppers as well. The bushes are already covered with blooms and small peppers again that will soon be fat and ready to pick. The strawberry plants are covered with small berries that will turn red and sweet soon. Vegetables aren't the only thing growing wild at the moment most all the flowers I've planted are in bloom.  All the extra rain this year has really given the flowers a boost since they are positively thriving. The plants get the hot sun and loads of water. The oriental lilys are gorgeous and are the size of a small plates this year. There are more than last year so I hope the new plants bloom next time.   I also have blue nile lilys that have a few small blue star shaped blossoms and tuberoses. No blooms on the tuberoses yet but there will be soon. I have sweet scented four oclocks blooming and the banana trees seem to grow a foot or more a day with the rain and heat. There are vines and ferns that have grown over the sides of large tubs and are now growing into the yard. My avocado tree is getting bigger this year. I threw the seed out last year just to see what it would do and it started growing! I seem to have a very green thumb!    Even though my garden is small, I know it will yield loads more than we can eat so there will be lots to share with other people. That is also part of my Solstice- to share with others.   It is such a lovely time of year and one of my favorites. This is the time of abundance and I hope other people realize that as well and share with those that have less. I wish you all a prosperous and wonderful summer. BB*   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Make a wish !! Make a REAL wish.. it's midsummer eve.. mind out those donkey ears ! I always take the solstice off.. so I am going to swim tomorrow in a freshwater bathing lake then off to the seaside. Have fun one and all xx
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, when I was invited to join, I warned the main author of this blog that I was prone to random rants of no particular relevance.  Now I'm an operator on a great little IRC network.  I get to see the good, the bad, the ugly.  Recently, my job has been irritating as at 6:30AM CST, every day, for about a week, this twit from Kuwait joins on and floods our servers with bots, causes technical havoc, and evades bans.  We have another such twit over in Estonia, and three here in the US.  HOW DO THESE PEOPLE GET LET ONTO THE INTERNET?  WHY DOES SOMEONE NOT MAKE THEM LISTEN TO YANNI WITH DISNEY CARTOONS ON IN THE BACKGROUND FOR A MONTH STRAIGHT?  &lt;/rant&gt;
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Volunteering in Australia   Kathrine Ford Saturday, April 3, 2004    I was sitting here looking through a student travel site and found a section on volunteer work. To my surprise, the age limit for this particular volunteer work is 18-70! Even at 45 I could volunteer to do something nice sometime. I noticed that Australia was listed so I thought, "Great! I'll have a look at that." A dear friend's family is in Tasmania and I have a few other Aussie friends so a volunteer visit might be really nice sometime. Once I looked through the site though, I really had to laugh.    What Australia is in need of are people to do "Conservation" work. And can you guess why? That's because no Aussie I know would be stupid enough to go out into the blazing Australian sun to conserve anything. So they kill two birds with one stone.  I have to hand it to the Aussies it's certainly a brilliant plan-avoid the poisonous livestock and the wearing of Kevlar underwear to protect themselves and get rid of pushy Americans at the same time.  Australians sit in air-conditioned houses watching telly and playing on the Internet while silly Americans go out and fry under the lethal sun wearing Kevlar underwear while running away from 99% of the most venomous of everything on earth. Now I ask you, is that a plan or what?   The site lists volunteer activities:  Reforestation, (where the most deadly funnel web lives, even MORE deadly than the regular old not-quite-so-deadly funnel web.)  River and creek (where the huge salt water crocs live and are regularly fed everything, most especially irritating Yankee conservationist/tourist type people.) preservation. Walking (This gives wombats and Tasmanian devils ample opportunity to tear large hunks out of your legs as you try to run away. I understand running away only infuriates them.) trails. Then there is the wildlife data collection.   In my minds eye, I saw myself walking along roasting in my Kevlar underwear to keep all (Douglas Adams, Hitchhikers guide to Australia volumes 1-42, "What's poisonous in Australia" comes immediately to mind) the various poisonous things away from me. I also saw a flash of my diary of field notes from observing the fauna... that being the final trailing off of my writing as I describe the deadly snake that has just given me a less than friendly love tap to let me know how very unhappy it is that I happened to be "observing" in it's neighborhood.   Let's see now, lovely gold and brown stripes a tiger snake perhaps? Or is my eyesight failing from the copious amount of neurotoxic venom the snake just harpooned me with and maybe it was actually the lovely iridescent Taipan? Who can tell? And it doesn't really matter because I have no anti-venom to inject and wouldn't know how to if I did.  So much for that $2.49 snakebite kit I brought with me.  While you may begin to feel that nothing else lives there except deadly snakes, they certainly aren't the only things to worry about. There are vicious birds as well. Let's not even think about the cassowaries.  Well, ok, we have to think about them since they also roam the forests of Australia. Cassowaries are enormous VW-sized birds with heavy armor plating on their heads and the largest toenails in the solar system.  They are very angry birds with bad attitudes especially when you look at their toenails. They either head butt you or they use their razor sharp toenails to rip you open like a big sack of Idaho potatoes. Who knows, maybe they head butt you THEN use the potato-sack openers. In any case, I think a very large pair of nail clippers is in order for the "Things to take to Australia" list.   The site also says that equipment and training are supplied at each project.  The equipment being sticks, large pieces of pipe, a hammer, extra-jumbo toenail clippers, and fluorescent tape. Sticks, pipes, and the extra-jumbo toenail clippers are very obviously for protection.  Everyone knows this.  The hammer is to knock yourself in the head with after you realize what you've really gotten yourself into. The fluorescent tape is so the Australian forest rangers can find your withered body complete with snakebite, cassowary head butt bruises and a wombat hanging from your Kevlar underwear. All after only a few hours of observing the interesting wildlife.  Unlike throwing a few more shrimp on the barbie, this certainly isn't the most cheery way to end an almost one day stint of Australian wildlife observation but at least they have part of a page in an otherwise empty field diary for posterity.  I wonder if a nice funeral is included.   After thinking it over, I believe I may hold out for the possible future invitation from a friend to visit lovely Australia rather than risk life and limb to visit under the pretence of a volunteer conservation visit.  To all my Aussie friends and everyone else, please forgive me, neither my Kevlar underwear nor me wish to encounter quite that much wildlife in one day.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I seem to be a magnet for every germ known to man. At least that's how I feel at the moment. I've been taking antibiotics which seem to be doing nothing at all since my temperature keeps going up and I feel very much as if I have been hit by a train.   If any of you have a good cure or you know of the train that hit me, please let me know. I would be ever so grateful.   This post isn't my best since it is very boring and static with me rambling on about not feeling well. Such is life. I feel like being babied and pampered and spoiled rotten. Oh wait! I AM! HA!   Ok, perhaps tomorrow I will post something interesting or at least slightly humorous. Actually, I suppose I could post one of my stories. Sound good? Course it does. Ok, it's settled. I'm off to root among my literary works and post something here. Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bear in mind that Zero probably didn't understand a word you said, because he doesn't have any ears. :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Kate, is this a topical or the usual random natterings of Oui_the_ppl? -Marty
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, once again I have tried to feed Zero, the Ball Python and yet again he turned up his nose to the hefty ratcicle I served him. I thawed it out and got it nice and room temperature just like you're suppose to but he was having none of it.   Then Pete came up with the idea to put the rodent in a freezer bag and place the bag in very warm water to heat up the rat. Still nothing. I honestly think Zero can tell that it isn't a fresh, as in mostly still kicking rodent.   Out of sheer frustration, I gave Zero a stern lecture about how little snakes in China would be happy to have such a lovely rat for dinner but it made no difference at all. He sat looking at the rodent much like the child who refuses to eat his spinach. ...(Ok fine Mr. No recess for you!)...   See, the real problem lies in me. I really have no desire to dispatch a live rat since we've had a couple as pets and they are very sweet and loving. So I am left with the moral dilemma of to clobber or not to clobber.   I suppose that I can get Donny's friend to come and dispatch the rodent in a very quick and semi-humane manner. When I had asked her about helping me before, she seemed far too eager to help with that particular chore which I find rather odd. I think I'll try warming his ratcicle again and see how that goes first.   I think getting a lizard would be easier since I wouldn't have to feed him or her rats. I'm open for suggestions! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first post on my first blog. How about a nice round or applause for me? No? Well then how about a song. Lets sing to the tune or Rawhide- the old TV western. Aone and atwo and here we go... blogging blogging blogging, keep those posts a' bloggin, keep them posts a comin'... BLOGGIN! We're on the web to wander, no need to surf and squander, we've got a place to blog away the night! BLOGIN!! There. Now wasn't that fun? Yes, yes of course it was. Now on to some really, really, really interesting stuff.   My friend Dean told me about this blogging service- that sounds rather dodgy but I'll stand by the phrase, "blogging service". Anyway, Dean who, is a wonderfully talented singer ( http://www.funk.co.uk  and for the streaming music  http://funkbaby.com ) and musician pointed out what great fun blogging could be and since his own blog looked so nice, I thought I would give it a try. Lo and behold, it IS fun! Imagine that! You simply can't imagine how life has been up to this point. Just so...so... blogless. Now I have a brighter blog-filled future with post ideas coming out of my ears. Well, not literally coming out of my ears but you get the idea. By the way, I highly recommend the streaming music on Dean's site. Excellent music! Kickin'! Follow the links people and you'll be streamin' in no time.   So I send many thanks to Dean. May his blog always be swamped. Hmmm... a swamped blog... That sounds kinda nasty doesn't it? Well I suppose it could be if you were to fall into it. Oh NO! I've fallen into a swamped blog and I can't get out!! See? Not a pretty picture is it?  That's about it for the first post on my blog. To blog or not to blog, that is the question. I think I have answered that one rather well. If anyone has any ideas for posts, feel free to send a note and let me know what floats your boat. We can talk about it on here.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Zero the ball python&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just for those who don't understand my love of reptiles, snakes in particular, I am writing this is response to a note that was posted by a friend.   I do understand why some people fail to see the attraction in regard to snakes. They are cold-blooded. They aren't loving and don't come to you when you call them. They aren't cuddly or cute in the sense that a dog, cat or even a mouse or rat is. Snakes feel no loyalty to those who care for them. There are venomous snakes that kill within minutes.   The  urlLink Inland Taipan  of Australia is one of, if not the most venomous snake on earth. Right here in the United States we have a variety of Rattlesnakes that cause serious illness and death when the bites are left untreated. Eastern diamondback, Western diamondback, Southern Pacific Rattlesnake, Mojave Green Rattlesnake as well as others.   We have the Coral snake which is in the same family  (Elapidae)  as Cobras and Mambas. While docile and very reluctant to bite, the Coral's venom is highly neurotoxic and can be deadly without proper treatment of a bite. Learn about  urlLink venom.   Therefore I can understand why some people don't see the attraction for snakes as pets. However, I do feel there is nothing wrong with a person having a python, boa, or most any non-venomous snake as a pet. On the other hand, some of the species of  urlLink constrictors  that grow to be very large, I feel should be left to expert snake handlers and herpetologists since they can be just as deadly as venomous snakes. Ball Pythons don't grow to be a dangerously unmanageable size. They are shy and prefer to stay away from people. That's how Zero was. While he may not have been a cuddly dog, he was shy and gentle and never hurt anyone.   Zero was definitely a real animal. A living, breathing animal. You would have to love snakes and reptiles as I do to understand. But that's just me. I love animals. All animals. Not just a select few that behave in such a way that rewards me. Or animals that are cute, cuddly and playful. But all animals. That includes snakes.  There is much to learn about snakes and so much more to be truly admired about them. Please take time to  urlLink learn  about them and appreciate them as they are then perhaps my love of snakes will become a bit more clear.       Learn more    Reptile search: urlLink  Herpsearch  Thinkquest: urlLink  Snakes  Reptile urlLink  Database  Society for the  urlLink study  of amphibians and reptiles     In tribute to a great herpetologist    Dr. Joe Slowinski's  urlLink site  Outside Online:  urlLink Bitten  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        It saddens me to say that my son's snake died. We think he may have contracted a respiratory infection but I'm not sure. Anyway, I've been SICK about that. Just sick. I'm going to get my son another baby python but it's not the point you know?  &nbsp;  I let the little snake down by not recognizing that he may have been ill.&nbsp;More important, I let my son down. The whole thing has just made me cry till I'm sick. I love animals and reptiles very much and when I am responsible for the death of a living, breathing animal, be it from lack of knowledge on proper care and signs of illness or my own stupid carelessness, it simply wipes me out.&nbsp; I plan to make it a point to learn all I can about pythons and possible illnesses.  &nbsp;  And as if all that is not bad enough, at 3:33 am Saturday, a guy called our house wanting to talk to my son Donny- he just kept on and on about it. I wouldn't say anything about where Donny was because the guy wouldn't tell me who he was or anything. He finally hung up.  &nbsp;  He called back not one minute later asking for Donny again. I said, look, I'm not tellin you ANYTHING till you tell me who you are and what you want. He says, "Look, Donny owes me money and I want it. If I don't get it I'm gonna kill him. I WANT MY MONEY. I'LL FIND HIM AND WHEN I DO, I'LL GET HIM." Then he hung up.  &nbsp;  Donny wasn't home and no one that knew him could find him. I panicked- I started calling his friends to try and find him to make sure he was ok. I had to end up getting the police to find him and&nbsp;bring him home from across town.  &nbsp;  With the police involved because of the threat, they located the guy that called. Supposedly, it was a joke. The police didn't think it was a very funny joke any more than I did.&nbsp;They explained that since he had made a threat all he has to do is move wrong and he's going to jail. If that guy does anything else or calls or comes around our house, he's going to jail.  &nbsp;  My son as well as several of his friends have said that the person has (seriously) psychiatric problems. That still concerns me since we really don't know what he might and might not do. The police are watching him so I hope this is over.  &nbsp;  All in all this has been a very sad and worrying week. Send me good vibes and blessings please!  &nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't mention it before but I had a similar experience in regard to Jc getting a jury summons in the mail. The day before it came, I was actually thinking about him getting a jury summons. I knew he would. Other people have seen this from me as well.  Pete knows how many times I have been thinking not only something similar to his thoughts but the exact same thing. It really never ceases to amaze me the number of times this happens to me. People have asked me what it feels like.  It's very difficult to explain. The only way I can even attempt to describe the feeling is that it is like something you already know, such as your own name. The thought is simply... there. Known, accepted.  So, coincidence? A divine gift? A curse? Rogue chemicals in the brain that affect or even control this sort of thing? Perhaps a combination of chemicals, specific metabolic states and outside stimuli that result in what appears to be psychic ability?  In any case, I find it interesting as well as curious when this happens to me. I would like to find some well-written information about this but I don't really know of any good reference sites on the subject.  If anyone knows any websites that address this sort of thing, please leave a post. Also, Deek if you happen to have info or thoughts/ideas on this, by all means write. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I go any further I have to say up front that I do  not  believe in telepathy, prescience or any other of the pseudo-scientific junk that flies around these days. I  do  happen to believe that sometimes people can be sensitive to things going on without knowing why - this is, I believe, what we mean when we say someone's psychic. Maybe one day I'll write a proper article about the background to that, but not right now.  On the other hand, when something weird happens you have to take notice. And over the last few days something has been bothering me.  On my way home one day last week I was listening to the radio and on one station somebody mentioned the phrases, "under the radar" and, "red alert". I don't remember what they were talking about specifically and at the time it didn't seem significant.  A bit later I slipped a Rush CD in the player. The first track is  Distant Early Warning  and includes the lines  Cruising under your radar  and  Red alert, red alert . Spooky.  About an hour ago I had a team meeting and our team lead mentioned a new project to do with advertising ocean trips. The project's in-house codename is  Cruise Under The Radar .  At this point I knew I had entered the Twilight Zone.  So here it is, official. The time as I write this is 2:16pm Central Daylight Time on July 14 2004. If something very big happens in the next few days that involves something cruising under radar and a red alert, I will be officially going in for the  urlLink JREF  $1 million paranormal challenge. Take note of when you read this, because I may need witnesses.  I really hope I'm wrong, because in this time of terrorist threats all over the place I'd hate to win a cool million as a result of someone getting hurt. But phrases like "cruising under radar" and "red alert" have an ominous tone. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rooting through my mail I found this nifty catalog of really expensive junk that I thought would be fun to look through even though I'd probably never but any of it.  One item they list is a $375.00 "pen safe" What the safe consists of is a small box that will display 12 pens in view and 12 hidden in a bottom tray. The ad states that the pens will be kept under lock and key. I found that odd since the safe has a thin glass top.   I imagined an angry, frustrated burglar saying, "ahhhh nuts!! and me with no key" the imbecile never once considering that a slight flick of the thumb and middle finger would end the pent up frustration and give him access to the wonderful array of genuine imitation plastic pens.  This sort of incident is normally reported on the "Stupid criminal of the week" report.  Another item was a gargoyle pencil holder $29.95 each or $27.95 each for two or more.  Right away I began a list of lucky recipients for this incredible gift.  The catalog had both front and side views of the holder. I suppose this was so that they could be assured that one side looked just as ridiculous as the other. The pencil cup is to the back of the gargoyle and he has a space in his mouth that holds another pencil. The expression on his face is one of, "Oh please, please, please ..not me please...". It seems the logical thing to me would have been to put the hole for the extra pencil through his head ala Steve Martin style. Perhaps that would have helped alleviate a bit of his pained expression.  And last but certainly not least is the bookmark. $16.95 each or $14.95 for two or more. This treasure of the literary world is made of very thin solid brass and has two strips of leather to mark pages.  The brass handle, did I say handle? That's probably because it looks very much like a handle and along with the strips of leather, looks much like an extremely cheap whip of some sort.I can see Conan the librarian standing in his barbarian garb, cracking his bookmark/whip saying, "Read!...read... READ !!" Since I like Conan the librarian, I might not mind so much, but for 17 bucks? I think not.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it was bound to happen sooner or later. I knew that eventually my husbands  urlLink brain  would go after living here longer than a couple of months. He has and is experiencing what we native  urlLink Americans  refer to as "normal American citizen behavior".   This ususally happens within a few months of living here while experiencing all the marketing hype that companies shove down our throats in order to make us feel worthless unless we buy/eat the crap they are trying to sell us.  It would suffice to say that he probably drove by Arbys one too many times and some vessel or something imploded in his cranium when he saw the "Low-carb  urlLink Arbys   plate" that is now available. I blame Arbys for this.   They have changed something that is a basic part of my husband and that is what I like to call the "Roast Beef", or "huge slabs of meat", center of his brain. This area of the brain is controlled by a very basic and primal function which cannot be controlled by anything other than shovelling large hunks of beef into him.   While I try to create dinner menus of lean chicken with lots of healthy  urlLink vegetables  served raw, steamed, grilled or stir fried, his brain throws heaps of some strange unknown chemical into his vessels telling him, "FORGET THE VEGETABLES, EAT AN ENTIRE  urlLink COW ".  Then again he does have a point. Diets that rob the body of  urlLink nutrients  that it needs and gets normally causes health problems. But then it shouldn't take a  urlLink rocket scientist  to point that out.   I am actually considering trying The Fatkins Diet myself. I'll let you all know how it goes. For me, I know it will be difficult to stay off the vegetables but I'll do the best I can.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These days there's no way that there is anyone left on the planet who hasn't heard of the Atkins&trade;&reg; Diet.  This, the latest in a long line of fad diets guaranteed to kill tens of thousands before sense prevails, tells us that  carbohydrates are bad  and  lots and lots of protein is good  and that all those namby-pamby nay-sayers - like  urlLink doctors , nutritionists and hospital workers - were wrong all along.  The "diet" works this way: you eat loads of protein - meat, eggs, meat, fish, meat, and so on. This induces Ketosis, in which your body dumps water to help dispose of all that extra protein. As a result, your weight takes a nosedive. After a few weeks of this you've lost all the water you can spare, so your weight levels off.  All the same, from a dieter's perspective this is great - at last, a diet that actually  delivers  on the promise of immediate results! It's a miracle!  It's also a miracle from the point of view of all those food companies that sold out to the "diet", too - they're making money hand over fist from low-carb snacks, low-carb soda, low-carb beer... even low-carb sandwiches and burgers (basically, take a sandwich, ditch the bread and dump what's left on a plate.  Voila . If you think I'm kidding, check your nearest Arby's restaurant).  This means that lots of people are making big money from this "diet" and that's good for the economy - and in the US at least, the economy is  everything . If something is good for the economy, it's good for everyone. And if a few thousand people end up suffering from diabetes, high blood pressure, heart problems, high cholesterol, death and so on, that's okay so long as the fat cats are getting their slice of the low-carb pie.  Well, I think it's time for the  sensible  alternative to the Atkin$ Di&euro;t&trade;&reg;. I bring you...   The Fatkins Diet   Like all good diets, the Fatkins Diet is a combination of diet and exercise. So:   Diet   If we're going to cut out carbs then we'd better go the whole hog, so to speak. So let's get rid of all the other bad things: protein can go, for one thing. And there's no point losing water... I mean, weight, if all you're going to do is put it back on as soon as you drink anything. With that in mind:   Breakfast:   - Lard, with sugar on top  - 6oz glass of corn syrup   Lunch:   Entree: Lard  Dessert: Sugar cookies   Dinner:   Starter: Sugar cubes in vegetable oil  Entree: Lard  Dessert: Brown sugar, with white sugar garnish  The large amounts of fat and sugar induce a condition known as "diarrhea". Weight loss is natural and, in fact, inevitable and unstoppable. (These statements have not been evaluated by the FDA, which is probably a good thing.)  From this you can see why the Fatkins Diet is also known as "the Lard-ass Diet".   Exercise   I've found that the best thing is to run as fast as you can, for as long as you can. Whenever I do that I keep going, past the so-called "pain barrier", until I'm shaking, all my muscles ache like hell and I'm short of breath. It feels terrible, but once the heart palpitations have stopped I always tell myself that pushing myself that ten yards is doing me good.   In summary   So there you have it - the Fatkins Diet in a nutshell. I'll soon be expanding this basic diet sheet into a full-blown marketing campaign, so watch out for Fatkins books, Fatkins lard-bars and Fatkins vegetable-oil sodas in the shops soon. Also, watch for the forthcoming new McDonalds&reg;  GreaseBomb with Cheese and No Bread &trade;, which should be hitting restaurants (splat!) soon.  In the meantime, you'll find me in the bank. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I would never  urlLink flame  your post nor delete it. Feel free to rant anytime you like. As you can see from my own posts, I do the same and quite often.   Ranting and kooky behavior is I believe the result of a good mind stressed from the stupidity of the mundane, monotone and ordinary. And as we know, stress can make us do some really odd things at times.   Odd as in singing while holding  urlLink rice paddles  above my head and doing the  urlLink  Saturday Night Fever  boogie dance while cooking dinner. Actually, I thought holding the rice paddles up was a rather nice touch. Be One with your paddles! Everything  urlLink Zen .  Giant mice? I think perhaps a vacation is in order. Deer-sized  urlLink mice ... Now  there's  a horror story.        
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well folks, been a while since I've posted anywhere, I've been enjoying the funs of life.  Or is that runs.. who knows?  After recovering from a 1.5 week migrane, I travelled to a wedding.  Well attempted to- seems someone decided to put a herd of cows in the highway, seriously.  Stupid drivers?  Who needs them!  Bovines running at 15mph down a narrow twisty two lane highway always makes interesting things happen.  Heck, we were a car back from the black blob of Buger King Beef.  Reminds me of  urlLink this famed incident  in my history, when my roommate (usually back by 5pm on Sundays) arrived closer to 1am.  Brian is a great guy, and articulate at story telling.  The wonderful thing about that link is he doesn't exaggerate at all- I can attest to his personality, and the facts that were relayed to me only shortly after the event.  Now, Harry Houdini House Guest below here also gets me thinking- what if mice were large enough to make you avoid them with vehichles?  Like raccoon size.  No, wait, let's go a little larger, more like a 6 month old deer.  *shudder*  Haven't seen Kate online in a while, and haven't really gotten to meet the rest of you yet... in fact, since the wedding I've been hiding.  I only crawled outta bed to post my inarticulate rant and see if there is still a world out there.  Judging by the record low 408 people on the IRC servers right now, I'm beginning to wonder.  Oh, final "rant" note- if you know anyone needing a jack of all trades IT person, contact me! :)  (/troll)  Back to my cave.  I expect to wake up to see this deleted.  Or spammed with flames.  Either way, I'll at least have that warm and fuzzy feeling of "Did I really make that post?"  EDIT:  Somehow this didn't post the first time.  Grr. -Goalie
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Kathrine Ford  Well folks, it’s time for yet another commentary on what I consider to be an interesting or unique find.  I think this one leans more toward the interesting as it isn’t terribly unique.  The object I’m writing about is none other than a “humane” mouse trap.  I have a problem with those nasty snap traps because I feel uncomfortable about killing the mice.  There are glue traps that aren’t much better.  You place the sticky trap down and the unknowing rodent is drawn to the bait and once he/she steps onto the sticky gluck, they are there to stay.  Unless you want to remove the rodent’s feet and I personally feel that this isn’t the best of options.  I would then feel really guilty because I would have footless mice roaming the house on tiny crutches.  Well crutches until someone designed prosthetics for mice.         This humane, miracle of the new age trap consists of a see through plastic tube/box with a swinging door that allows the rodent in and once he/she enters and retrieves the tasty prize of bread, cannot exit and is trapped until it is released totally unharmed as well as fed, into the wild again.  This sounded great!  Finally, an easy, safe way to rid my house of the tiny unwelcome guests.    I “armed” the trap with a small piece of cheese.  The packaging suggests smearing peanut butter around the outside of the door in order to attract rodents.  Since this was too messy and we all know how much mice love cheese, (at least in cartoons anyway) I smeared a small amount of cheese on the trap door in order to lure the tiny beast into the trap.  Now comes the hard part, the wait for an occupant.  After a couple of hours, what I got when I checked was nada.  Now for those of you who don’t know what “nada” means, it means “nothing”.  And that is exactly what I got- nothing.    Disbelieving, I peered into the box and lo and behold, my eyes weren’t deceiving me, it was empty.  No rodent, no cheese, no nothing.  I picked the box up and inspected it but found neither defects nor any large holes gnawed in the sides where a jail break may have occurred.  The tiny escape artist had apparently left the way he/she had come, through the trap door.    I was amazed that what I thought to be a trap was in reality, a small rodent dining car.  Rather like a Hyatt Rodency.  Accept that little Harry Rodini had vacated the dining car while dragging along a hunk of cheese.  I couldn’t believe it.  The furry little ingrate had ripped me off yet again!  I put the trap down and threw my hands into the air and pretty much gave up on even the slightest chance of any successful rodent removal.    Later that evening once my frustration had subsided, I decided not to give in to the fact that I would be “rodentized” regardless of my good intentions, so I gave it one more try.  I re-armed the trap and placed it back in the same spot.  Hopeful that yet another member of the Rodent Club would venture in for a midnight snack at the bar, I went to bed.    I slept that night and dreamt of large mice with hacksaws sawing their way to freedom from a cage with plastic bars.  There was a big bar/club in the middle complete with tattooed (bearing the word “Mom”) bartender serving several rodents who were having drinks, smoking big cigars and chatting.  This was to say the least, an odd dream.  Upon wakening, I decided that mouse or not, this day was the end of it.       Sleepy-eyed I walked into the kitchen and opened the cabinet and there in the Hyatt Rodency sat a calm and collect rodent still clutching and nibbling the cheese he/she was lured in there with.  Now I don't know if the mice sensed my agitation at having one escape and simply felt sorry for me and decided to stay, but in any case, there it was.  I could almost see the outline of a map to get back to the house in its tiny little pocket.    That the rodent might come back didn’t deter my glee at having captured one of the annoying beasts.  If anything it had given me a jump-start on capturing more.  The mouse was taken to a location of relative safety far away from the house and set free to roam the fields and begin a new life.  Hopefully one that doesn’t include my house or me.  I went home and replaced the cheese that Harry Rodini had taken to tide him over until his crops come in and began the long wait for another dinner guest.    These are the times that animal lovers dream of.  A safely released rodent and the knowledge that more would follow.  It made me feel good that my plan to use a humane mousetrap had indeed succeeded and that I could help relocate wayward rodents and their families into a new life of rural farming.    That’s it for now on the home front of the strange and unusual, until next time.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just realized that this website has put snake-related ads at the top of my blog. Ordinarily I wouldn't have a problem with that except that the products are for "Snake Away" which states, "Safe for Humans & Animals. Protect Your Yard from Unwanted Visitors!" This might be true but what does it do to the snakes? Information on the ad says that it affects the snakes sensory perception. Is this safe for the animal? Are there lasting affects to the health and well-being of the animals? If anyone knows, please let me know.   Not all and in fact very few snakes are really dangerous. Snakes help rid us of the omnipresent large rodent population which, left unchecked would easily overflow and cause serious health risks. Not to mention the damage rodents do to food crops etc.   The other ad is for "Texas Rattlesnakes" which boasts, "Real Head and Tail Keychains Full Rattlesnakes." The sale of this sort of thing makes me sick. I do realize that rattlesnakes are highly venomous and should always be given a very wide berth, however there is still no real reason to exploit these animals in this way. It's sad and cruel.   I wish Mark OShey or Steve Irwin and Wes Manning could see some of the garbage that is allowed in regard to snakes in this part of the USA. Maybe they could actually help get something done to stop this stuff from happening or at the very least, educate more people about snakes so that the desire to harm them is greatly lessoned.  One thing I know is that if people adamantly refuse to buy things like keychains bearing a rattlesnake head or tail dangling from it, then there won't be as much of a demand for that sort of garbage. That practice is a sad, sickening waste of a beautiful and fascinating animal. It's not only snakes that are in danger from exploitation, but alligators as well.  This past June, I saw an ad in a local sale paper for a well known chain of sporting good stores. Right in the center of the ad there was a page that explained how to enter their "contest". The prize was a trip to hunt and kill your own alligator. Afterward,you could have your own custom cowboy boots made from the skin. I was sickened and appalled that *anyone* would host such a horrid thing!   I don't understand what the attraction is to destroy an animal. I see no glory or manliness associated with it either. With the exception of hunting for food. If it is really necessary, I have little problem with anyone hunting to feed themselves or their family. That however is quite a different matter. The sport of it just isn't in me.   Exploitation of reptiles and animals in general won't stop until people become more aware of what they are losing when those animals are finally extinct. Please, think before you buy animal-related products. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>