<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well here we are after my husbands father leaves, and my dh is acting exactly as he always does when one of his parents come around. It happens every time and yet it always catches me by surprise. Maybe it is because he is normally so much fun to be around, now, well not so much. Maybe it is the crappy upbringing he had, the feeling like he disapoints them (which he doesn't) No matter what it is, it isn't our fault yet we pay. Normally I would blow up and there would be a big fight but I just hate to fight and would like to maybe ride this one out. Lets see how it goes. My gut instinct is to punch him in the mouth, but I won't do that either. The far reaching effects are the children, because of his mood they are clingy, whiney, and all around ornery.  He is bitchy because I am on the computer, WTF! We are in the same room, just not with my eyes on the same screen. If I did go and sit with him he wouldn't speak to me anyway. I should realize that is not the problem, the problem is he has a wild hair up his ass and until he gets over it this is the way it is going to be, fun week ahead, whoopie!  Well and the friends comming over my darling husband put his charming spell   on that one and insisted we go pick up his truck at the dealer RIGHT after work!!!!! So no friends over, I had to call them. Instead I got to look at his shining face growl and pick at everything through dinner at the crackerbarrel. I can't wait to go to sleep tonight LOL! Whoo I hope this passes quickly. Don't get me wrong he isn't abusive or anything, just being all around cranky. When he used to get like this I walked on egg shells to keep the peace, after a few days I would blow up. Now fuck it, I won't make it my problem, not after 12 years of dealing with it. I will just keep my distance, hopefully it will pass before the argument. 
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I woke up on the proverbial wrong side but thank goodness it has turned around. On the bright side the baby only woke up once and that wasn't until 4am.  Poor dh there are days I could strangle him and he doesn't even know it. For instance I woke up to him taking my truck to work leaving me stranded, this wouldn't be all bad but he knew I had places to go today, and to top it off he has a perfectly beautiful motorcycle sitting in the garage (his baby) that I can't strap three kids to and motor to the mall but he can plant his ass on and take to work! I really hope no rain comes today as I am forced homebound. It is much easier on all of us when we have the pool as distraction. Last night we went shopping for fathers day. My father wants a portable radio (read boom box) I had no idea these are almost nonexistent, wow I am old..............He also gets his new bike today so I stopped at the harley dealer to pick up a few doodads from the boys for his for fathers day, viola they were having a tent sale. I was able to pick up a few small things I was thrilled. Went to target and it seems they are going to hell in a handbasket. The place was a dump and they very limited on their selection. I used to like shopping there, now, not much. I refuse to go into the wallmart supercenter, I will not support bad business.  Tonight we have friends comming over for pizza, I really hope it doesn't rain so we can be outside.
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I seem to be losing pleasure again. Nothing elicits excitment. Just the mundane running of a smooth household. Today rambles into yesterday, into tomorrow. This I will hide like I always do and I will smile a toothfilled grin kiss my children, make love to my husband and all will be well with them. For me this is my life, where I love being but yern for some excitment, some impromptu reaction. The washing machine drones on, the stove burns, I remain still waiting to be heard or seen, recognizition is so over rated I guess. Daily I scramble to the top, like an unseen race. Maybe here I am creating my own thrill. Pushing to see if I can make it, see if I can win. But tomorrow arrives and the diapers pile up the laundry is never completely done. The beds are a mess again, the booboos need to be kissed, and I run again to some unseen trophy. The crown I wear is stretchmarks, and fat. Oh gosh what am I, I am suppose to be mother and wife, but I am tired so very tired, here the smile will grow and I raise my head above the ashes I create in my mind, and I forge ahead. Some days I look at yesterday, at youth and wonder what if, but there is no glory there, no lonliness, no work, just the rosy glow of yesterdays dreams. Then I snap back to reality and remember this IS my dream, what I work for, this is my glow, and I smile..................
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well pop comes today with his new wife Doris, what a lovely lady. Of course I must do the "me" thing and be really anal about the house.........................  You know no matter how big that hole is in the toilet boys always manage to miss it, why is that?  The dog goes to the groomer today and while she is there I will venture to the grocery store, wow what excitment   Until later!  Ok My FIL and his wife just left. What a wonderful time we had! His new wife is just the most lovely woman. I so wish she were my MIL. Good thing they did come and visit, I thought Fathers day was next week, what an oops that would have been, egg on my face.................. Armed with this knowledge tonight I must venture to the mall with the children.   The boys were angels while they were here and boy are they making up for it, fight fight fight!!!!!!! Maybe the distraction of shopping tonight will turn this around, either that or duct tape.    
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My first blog day!  Today is the first day of my weight loss journey. I am fed up with being fat and not following through with anything. I set myself excercise goals today and did some of what I planned but not everything. The kids, oh my, not good today not good at all. They were difficult at best, good thing tomorrow is another day. Now why, why are friends so damn difficult, especially women? Why can't you simply disagree and leave it at that, why must it be taken as a personal affront????? This is the second good friend in a year to act like this. The first wanted me to call a woman where her dh works and hang up when she answered, WTF! Imagine that! This one accepted dubious info just because it fit her belief and now won't speak when I pointed out the flaws in the logic. No wonder I love my kids so much they are easy to talk to. Swimming was nice today but the pool is cloudy, I hope we can clear it up by tomorrow. Gosh I have such an exciting life LOL! Oh in the fall we are going to my sils wedding in Marthas vinyard, am I the only one to not like the vinyard???????
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      First of all let me say this is more of a tata to an era gone by so to say. Do I believe in soul mates yes will all my being, why because I have experienced it, lived it, and excuse the cliche, loved it. No, I am not married to my soul mate, I am married to the love of my life though. My soul mate was a beautiful man in looks and mind. Deep dark and mysterious, a poet, a writer, passionate, like a dream he was. It lasted a few years, until I wanted the whole fairy tale, marriage, children, the pickett fence, and my patience wore out. My attempt at making him pay attention to my needs were stupid, I cheated, and kept cheating until I hated him, and myself in one heartbeat. This is the one thing in my life I am so very sorry for. He didn't deserve to be treated so badly, he loved me so completely, and I didn't realize it at the time I loved him even more. It took me years to realize this, when I came to this realization I was emotionally devastated, entangled in a good marriage with a man I loved, one child, and another on the way. Talk about fucking up your own head. I became desperate to reach him just to say I love you and I am so sorry, thank goodness I never found him. One Sunday there was his picture in the paper he was getting married, I couldn't breathe, I cried for days, I kept that damn picture for years at the bottom of a junk bag for years. During this period of self destruction, my self loathing started, I let myself become haggard and very heavy. This continued for 5 long years, lessening as the minutes ticked by. I did see him once, about a year after the birth of my second child, I think my heart stopped. Now years later thankfully I can think of him with no yearning, or sorrow of what could have beens. I love my life, my husband while not my soulmate is more love then my heart can contain. The part in the wedding vows "till death do us part" isn't enough. My love will carry on into heaven, for this I am eternally thankful. My wish for my soul mate is the same, I pray his love for his wife spills over into eternity. I am so thankful I was able to see touch and feel my soul melt with another, everyone should have this privedledge, it is astounding. My thoughts of him are more fleeting now like the bittersweet wings of a butterfly. Someday I pray to have his forgivness. My selfish side wants him to feel nostalgic about me too. 
      
</post>


</Blog>