<Blog>


<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I went to two graduation parties which i guess where fun. Well to tell the truth one wasnt but I won't say which one because i dont want to offend anyone. One of them i went to a pool and had alot of fun. ok i gave a way which one was boring but I don't think anyone would get mad (hopefully). The pool party was fun and i ate too much of the cake so I think the Grad student mom disliked me becuse she was eyeing me. So I stopped. Both parties had their advantage though. The first one i went to everyone knew me so i didnt feel left out but the second one i was kinda ignored. boo hoo goodbye for now kiddies ill be back soon
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Have you ever wondered why you think your ugly then all these girls start swarming to you? I hate it! its of course june 24 and that means the first month of summer is almost over!....groan....god please rewind time! Things start to go slowly now though hopefully i wont get chased by the people i fear! bleah
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is what a post looks like!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome to Kaboomafoo's Blog website! Here you can say and post your own notes to the public for free! If you have any questions or comments you can email me at b909website@hotmail.com
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok some one left a message for me earlier but I have no friends named vikram so Jeev, please give up your lame as heck don't even try. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok should i forget about this webiste? should I huh? ok i am because no one visites this and i have another one which is way better ok foos ill leave a message later
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just saw Spiderman 2......can you spell kool? It was one of the best movies I've seen but of course theres more movies out there that i want to see(The Chronicles of Riddick, Harry Potter, The Terminal, and Shrek 2 to name a few). I just got some money today, I was Estatic. ok. Thats enough. I wasted more of your time. Leave a message k?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Bah! I have totally forgotten this website as you notice....for five days!!! I am sitting here with my cool cousin (not the other one) and we're playing some games. I have been keepin my other webiste up to date `cept for this one.... bah to life!!! ok im really pissed off because I want to see SPIDERMAN 2 but i cant because i dont have anough money (of course! im a poor colored kid) and no one is willing to drive me to the theaters(yes again! a poor colored kid without a permit) ok foos ive wasted a few seconds of your life leave a message at the tone
     
    
</post>


</Blog>