<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What does it really mean to take 4 hours from one's day to attend a birthday party where perhaps 15 minutes of conversation is shared between you and the guest of honor?  Is this not merely a charade of society with no depth of relationship involved? Tonight a surprise party gave a young girl a shot of self worth.  This esteem booster was not administered via a "perfect" gift or an incredibly wise word but through the willingness of busy people to stop their tasks for a few hours to simply be "there."  She indeed lacked the time to sit with any one of these special guests for very long.  In fact, a few were left to discuss life and share jokes amongst themselves with little more than three or four words with the birthday girl.  But their presence was immense.  She felt more important than she had ever felt when she experienced the offering of a few hours of their time.  She told me so. So often I am too busy for those I truly care about.  I wonder how unimportant I have made them feel. 
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The sound of rain being poured out on a roof has always been a sweet sound that seems to relax every fiber of my soul.  Childhood contains lots and lots of memories of falling asleep in a warm, dry tent with the drumming of millions of raindrops all around.  Closing my eyes, I could hear the music of God in their symphony.  So tonight, in a small neighborhood bar, with the same sound of water vehemently falling drop by drop upon the roof, my heart snuggled in with the warmth of friends.  A meal, a drink, a conversation of past, present and future, brought a good day to a sweet end.  One new friend, one old friend, and one mother/friend reminded me how benevolent creation is to those who will stop and feel its harmony.  I heard once that it never rained in the Garden of Eden.  Perhaps paradise lacked a blessing or two after all!
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Imagine the charred, wounded dirt after a massive fire.  Lifeless remains of its fertile past crunch beneath the feet.  The flames lapped every droplet of life's juice out of its being.  Desolate, desperate, and deserted the land cries for mercy, for a miraculous touch.  Overhead, quietly, a single cloud forms.  Not yet worthy of attention, it hovers over the expanse below.  Days pass; desolation remains; the sky darkens from its gathering forces.  An impending storm threatens to ravage the badly wounded surface, bringing further destruction.  The black sky, surrounding the blackened dirt, thunders a war like cry to announce the outpouring of its gathered forces.  Rapid shots of light assault the darkness and torrents of water spew out on the already forsaken sight below.  The deluge cuts long winding trenches into the earth.  Water follows the trenches, thus carving deeper paths into its flesh.  The earth bows its head and weeps for the depths of its despair.  The deluge silences and a breath breathes gently over the land.  The air, cleansed from the aroma of smoke, rests gently on the surface and waits.  Somehow it knows.  The trenches inflicted upon the barren expanse now flow continuously with clear water, dancing and singing over itself.  Inflictions and assaults along this river very gradually begin to find new blossoms of luxurious flowers appearing within themselves.  Suddenly, the destructive acts of uncertain origin transform into purging and renewing works.  The ultimate revolution of God is to turn destruction into new beginnings.  It is what He does best!  May all our new beginnings flourish and blossom with the exotic flowers that bless those who pass by and see.
      
</post>


<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK, so we need to try something new.  What? When? Where?  Let's brainstorm . . .  And then let's   do   it!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When you stand before God, what do you want him to say about your life? What did you do for those that were put here around you? Did you offer a cup of cool water or did you tell God that I need to do a back ground check on this person first before I even consider opening my door?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You're right, Tynah. The church should be the water, not the mold that the water is poured into. Great analogy! I think that's the way that Jesus looked at the world-- tattoos or outcasts, people who looked different or acted different -- "come to me, all you who are burdened and heavy-laden and I will give you rest." I think the rules probably started in the early churches -- the "don't do this" and "don't act like that." It seems like it's way past time to go back to the teachings and actions of Jesus and accept everyone, regardless of appearances and actions. Isn't that what the gospel message is all about? And, I don't even think it's a generational thing, this judgementalism. It crosses all boundaries and I think it's time we became more accepting of one another. After all, aren't we all created in the image of God? And didn't God see that it was good?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My generation has been brought up with the view that churches are very stuffy, you are not to talk, no clapping, and especially under no circumstances were you to question anything. "Questions are from the devil!!!" And no matter how modern churches have become now of days that policy seems still to stand strong in some way or another. But no matter what, we still have questions running around in our minds about many different topics. Is God real? What does the Bible have to do with me? How does this issue fit in the Bible? And the list goes on and on. We as a generation face things day to day that weren't as obvious a decade ago. So where can we go to have others help search for the answers? Somtimes there is no written in stone answer because our minds our to finite to truly understand, but don't we deserve the right to try.  We also have tattoo's and earings and wear clothes that the older generations aren't use to and some won't accept. Where can we go and be who we are and not who everyone wants us to be? Sometimes it almost feels like they are close minded to our differences but want us to be open minded to their close mindedness. In other words they're aloud to totally shut out our ideas and some of the things we do but we have to listen and consider all their arguments.   Yes we have Youth Groups but those are usally for kids already in church. What about the ones that aren't? Don't you think that even we who are looked down upon have some intellect and want to share it with others and have others stretch us?      A church should be as water to fill us the vessels and not the mold to force people into. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Do we really need an alternative to the established church? After all, isn't "church-as-we-know-it" working for lots of people?  You bet. But be honest: don't you also know many, many people -- co-workers, friends, family members -- who'd never feel even remotely at home in "church-as-we-know-it"?  There's a huge disconnect somewhere.   In the 1980s and 90s, the "seeker movement" swept through the American church. Following the lead of pioneering churches like Willow Creek Community Church in the Chicago suburbs and Saddleback Community Church in southern California, many churches experimented with worship services and programs that were "seeker-sensitive"; i.e., designed with spiritual seekers rather than mature believers in mind.  The seeker-sensitive model encouraged churches to get rid of anything that might "scare off" a spiritual seeker:  *  sanctuaries were stripped of crosses and other religious imagery *  hymns were replaced with worship choruses set to up-beat "adult-contemporary" music *  teaching emphasized how the Bible provided clear answers to life's toughest problems *  those who attended were treated mainly as spectators, watching a religious presentation put on by others (band, drama team, preachers, etc.)  The seeker movement reached vast numbers of people who had been turned off by traditional churches. It spawned hundreds of "mega-churches," boasting impressive campuses, big auditoriums with theater seats, dynamic children's and youth ministries, and a whole panoply of other programming. It was an amazing phenomenon, and probably a genuine work of the Holy Spirit. It's scary to think of where the American church would be today if the seeker movement had never happened.  But is it possible that the seeker movement has had its day? Could it be that God has something completely new in mind?  Certainly there's a growing sense of uneasiness within the movement today. Church leaders are realizing that many of the people who've flocked to seeker-oriented churches are actually "alumni" of smaller, more traditional churches -- they've just traded in their former churches for something more stimulating and exciting ("pickles and sauce for bored church-goers"). And even the most successful mega-churches admit to having trouble attracting young people. In 2002 the Gallup organization reported that, among Americans from age 12 to 30, some 80% have NO connection with a church. As I said, there's a huge disconnect somewhere.  Observers suggest that it's really not a   generational   divide. A person's age can certainly influence how they relate to the established church. But there's something more important going on: a fundamental shift in the way people relate to the world.  Simply put, what's happening is a movement from a "modern" to a "post-modern" worldview.  Tons of stuff has been written about this transition. But to vastly oversimplify, the shift from the modern to the post-modern era can be seen as a shift . . .  * from monotheism to pluralism * from reason to experience * from religion to mysticism * from propositional to narrative * from systematic to fluid * from local to global * from individualistic to communal/tribal * from truth to preference  Many people (including many young people) still operate mostly in the "modern" mindset. But our culture is increasingly "post-modern" ("pomo," for short) in its orientation.   As you can see this shift poses all kinds of challenges to the established church. And in many ways, the changes we made as part of the seeker movement have left us   less   prepared to meet those challenges.  As Dan Kimball (a leading EC pastor) has written, "Many of the very things that we removed from our churches because they were stumbling blocks to seekers in previous generations are now the very things that are attractive to emerging generations. . . . A post-seeker-sensitive worship gathering promotes, rather than hides, full displays of spirituality (extended worship, religious symbols, liturgy, extensive prayer times, extensive use of Scripture and readings, etc.) so that people can experience and be transformed by the message of Jesus." Dan adds an important caveat: "This approach is done, however, with renewed life and is still 'sensitive' as clear instruction and regular explanation are given to help seekers understand theological terms and spiritual exercises" ( The Emerging Church , p. 26).  Any reactions to this analysis?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Some questions to ponder (feel free to add your own) . . .  1.	What does your dream congregation look like?   2.	What’s your dream church’s attitude toward the culture around it? Is the church involved in a “culture war” against a corrupt, pagan culture? Or is it fully engaged with that culture, finding Christ (and being Christ) in it?  3.	What role(s) do women have in your dream church?  4.	How much structure does your dream church need? What does that structure look like?  5.	How does your dream church approach scripture? Is the Bible an “Owner’s Manual” with explicit instructions for every aspect of life? Or is the Bible a “conversation partner,” to be respected, struggled with, and sometimes disagreed with?  6.      How open is your dream church to gay and lesbian people? Does your dream church “lay down the law” with regard to sexual matters? Or is it willing suggest guidelines and then let/help people find their own way with regard to sex and sexual expression?  7.	Which paradigm is more important? a.	The Reformation Paradigm, that says, “Above all, the Church needs to have the proper beliefs/structure/practices”?  b.	Or the Missional Paradigm, that says, “Above all, the Church needs to be in mission, constantly asking: ‘What is Jesus doing in our midst, and what work is he calling us to join him in?’” 8.	What’s the place of ordained/professional leadership (if any) in your dream church?   9.	What’s your dream church’s definition of success?  10.	Where does worship fit in? Is worship “the most important thing we do”? Or is worship something that comes later, flowing out of the interaction of real community / engagement / compassion / mission?  11.	What kind of facilities (building, etc.) does your dream church have? Does it need its own space to meet, store things, base mission efforts, etc.?  12.	What does your dream church need in the way of finances? How much? Where does the money come from?  13.	Does your dream church have a denominational affiliation? Why or why not?  14.	Is your dream church affiliated in some way with another local congregation? How? Why? How does your dream church relate to other Christian groups in your area?  15.	A Binghamton-area issue: What’s the relationship between your dream church and The Link (and its legacy)?   16.	Is your dream church a place where you  go ? Or is it something that you  are ?  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One of the most challenging books written about the church in recent years is  Liquid Church , by Pete Ward.  Pete, who's a college professor from England, describes the established church as "solid church," a relatively stable, restrictive, "heavy" institution. Solid church assumes that:   1. Attending Church Services = Faithfulness.   Solid church always has the goal of getting people to attend Sunday services. "Gathering in one place to do the same thing together is one of the core values of solid church" (p. 17). And it leads to a numbers game in which success is measured by whether attendance is increasing or decreasing.   2. Size Counts.   Solid church loves big buildings and a big list of programs and activities to fill those buildings.   3. One Size Fits All.   Solid church values uniformity in the way people worship and in the way they proceed on their spiritual journeys. This can lead to a "lowest-common-denominator" approach to worship and spiritual growth, with innovation discouraged for fear that it will offend someone.   4. Everybody Needs to Join the Club.   Like a Kiwanis or Rotary Club, solid church is "an exclusive club run for its members and organized by a team of voluntary helpers. Long-term service gives a degree of authority and deference on the part of others. For many key club members, organizing the club becomes an end in itself" (20). Solid church creates a "small pond" where leaders can become "big fish." It places high value on getting people "more involved," and may encourage busy-ness for its own sake.  By contrast, Pete believes that we need a "liquid church," a church that can take different shapes and forms. One of the chief characteristics of liquid church is its ability to move. Pete quotes Zygmunt Bauman:  Fluids travel easily. They "flow," "spill," "run out," "splash," "pour over," "leak," "flood," "spray," "drip," "ooze"; unlike solids they are not easily stopped -- they pass around some obstacles, dissolve some others and bore and soak their way through others still (40).  Pete goes on to say:  If we are to envisage a liquid church, then movement and change must be ... [a] basic characteristic. We need to let go of a static model of church that is based primarily on congregation and buildings. In its place we need to develop a notion of Christian community, worship, mission, and organization that is more flexible and responsive to change. The idea of  flow  is central in this shift of emphasis" (41).  At least three things are clear about liquid church:  1. In liquid church, relationships have central importance. It will be relationships, not buildings or programs, that bind the liquid church together.  2. In liquid church, membership rolls will be irrelevant. The life of the church will be lived out through informal contacts and relationships that evolve naturally. Liquid church is all about decentralization. Like the internet, it depends on the creativity and energy of individuals, networking together.  3. Liquid church will have what Pete calls "fuzzy edges." It's not the weekly service that defines the church; instead the church is a web of informal relationships. Pete says:  When we start to regard the network itself as church, then the notion of insiders and outsiders starts to break down. Instead, we have a network of communication and relationship where Christian love and mutual support form part of the flow. The boundaries have started to become more fuzzy and less well defined (47).   What do you think about the concept of "liquid church"? How does it make you feel?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a perfect title!  The church, at last fluid (not rigid) enough to quench the thirst of every passerby that desires to partake!  We are a thirsting nation.  I heard one lady say that Americans are on survival mode--we are desperate for a fresh and honest and clear spirituality.  Calvin Miller describes us as simply one leper offering another a drink of water.  This is a way of life I could be emersed in!  How awesome to see an Aqua Church flow to every person, no matter who they are or where they are or how wounded they are!  Perhaps that church would even be Christ-like.  Is he not the Living Water?!?  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First we started hearing whispers about something called "Emerging Church" (EC, for short). It was church/not-church; it was ancient/modern; it was coffee/candles/and-God-knows-what-else. But whatever it was, EC seemed to be a special kind of dream: a dream of a home for people who are NOT at home in the world of the established church.  So we got a little conversation going, partly by reading some EC books, partly by surfing some EC websites, partly by attending a big EC gathering in Nashville, and partly by talking with each other. We learned enough to know that we've got a lot to learn.  Now it's time to expand the conversation.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mark asked for our reactions to the concept of Aqua Church. On the one hand, I think it's what many people have been doing all along -- going about their daily lives trying to live as we believe Christ would have, and forming relationships with others on that basis.&nbsp;On the other hand, it's radically new in its approach to worship. It's still really hard for me to imagine an interactive worship service, because for me&nbsp;interactivity has&nbsp;been something reserved for midweek Bible studies and Vacation Bible School.&nbsp;I still love the "show" aspect of the seeker-oriented church and probably always will,&nbsp;but&nbsp;I would sadly have to agree that it&nbsp;does set&nbsp;up a kind of wall between&nbsp;the seeker and the "performers."&nbsp;(Which doesn't make me love "performances" any less;&nbsp;I'd rather hear a live band than eat,&nbsp;but that's just me.) I'm eager to discover what an actual interactive worship service would be like, but for me, right now, I'm more excited about the&nbsp;evolution of the community.  Someone&nbsp;asked in an earlier post how the Aqua Church related to the legacy of the Link. It seems apparent to me, after several weeks of analyzing it, that the Aqua Church has inherited a core group of people associated with an earlier movement that was very close-knit and a little edgy for its time. Otherwise, I don't think there is really any more of a relationship than that. The Aqua Church&nbsp;seems like it will be&nbsp;something totally new to this area, and&nbsp;its purpose&nbsp;is fundamentally different from the Link's, except for the common desire to be a reflection of Christ. But how the two churches&nbsp;see Christ reflected, and what that perception&nbsp;leads believers to do next,&nbsp;is quite different. I loved, loved, loved, the Link; but it had its faults, it's over, and it's time to move on. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As we begin to think about launching a flesh-and-blood Christian community with a weekly, real-live worship gathering, we need to visualize what that worship gathering will look like. From Dan Kimball's book,  Emerging Worship,  here are ten principles that are being followed in many "emerging" churches around the country:    Emerging worship moves away from a spectator type of gathering.  Instead of emphasizing the production, the excellence and the way things are programmed, it emphasizes coming together to express our love for God and experience God's love for us. It's the opposite of putting on a "show."   There is an organic design to the worship gathering.  It's not a linear, boxed-in kind of&nbsp;design. Many elements are woven together throughout the meeting, people are given lots of different ways to participate.   A sacred space is created for the worship gathering.  The space where worship takes place is very important. Visual elements are taken seriously -- lots of art, creatively-rendered images and scriptures, video images, candles, darkness, crosses.    Emerging worship takes a multisensory approach to worship.  Traditional worship is focused on listening (to music, prayers and teaching). Emerging worship involves the other senses as well. Meals are frequently part of emerging worship. Musical styles depend on the local setting, and vary from place to place. Opportunities for artistic expression are provided for all during worship; prayer stations are set up where people can write prayers, journal, draw, etc.   Emerging worship values freedom of movement in worship.&nbsp; People aren't forced to remain stationary in their seats for the whole meeting, nor do they rush out the door when it's over.   Emerging worship has a different focal point.  Instead of focusing on the band or the teacher/preacher, the leaders are in the midst of the people (or on the sidelines). The speaking is shared as much as possible. Sometimes the band plays from the rear, rather than the front.   Emerging worship is seeing a revival of liturgy, ancient disciplines, Christian seasons, and Jewish roots.  Even hymns!   Emerging worship emphasizes prayer.  It provides numerous opportunites for the people to intercede for others and get on their needs to confess their sins.   Communion is a central part of emerging worship.    Emerging worship makes Jesus the centerpiece of worship.  The prayers, the symbols, the de-emphasis on preacher and music leader -- all seek to put the focus on Jesus.   These are just commonly-seen values, not "the Ten Commandments." Your reactions? 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow! We've got ourselves a Mission Statement, AND a mission!  At&nbsp;our get-together tonight at CyberCafe, we decided that we're ready to commit to an actual mission -- and we put it down on paper.    Our Mission is to become a caring and accepting community where people meet Jesus and make friends for life.       &nbsp; How does that sound? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A couple of weeks ago, I mentioned a piece by one of the founders of AA. Here it is:      I Stand by the Door    by Sam Shoemaker  I stand by the door. I neither go too far in, nor stay too far out, The door is the most important door in the world — It is the door through which people walk when they find God. There's no use my going way inside, and staying there, When so many are still outside and they, as much as I, Crave to know where the door is. And all that so many ever find Is only the wall where a door ought to be. They creep along the wall like blind people, With outstretched, groping hands. Feeling for a door, knowing there must be a door, Yet they never find it . . . So I stand by the door.  The most tremendous thing in the world Is for people to find that door — the door to God. The most important thing any person can do Is to take hold of one of those blind, groping hands, And put it on the latch — the latch that only clicks And opens to the person's own touch. People die outside that door, as starving beggars die On cold nights in cruel cities in the dead of winter — Die for want of what is within their grasp. They live, on the other side of it — live because they have not found it. Nothing else matters compared to helping them find it, And open it, and walk in, and find Him . . . So I stand by the door. Go in, great saints, go all the way in — Go way down into the cavernous cellars, And way up into the spacious attics — It is a vast roomy house, this house where God is. Go into the deepest of hidden casements, Of withdrawal, of silence, of sainthood. Some must inhabit those inner rooms. And know the depths and heights of God, And call outside to the rest of us how wonderful it is. Sometimes I take a deeper look in, Sometimes venture in a little farther; But my place seems closer to the opening . . . So I stand by the door.  There is another reason why I stand there. Some people get part way in and become afraid Lest God and the zeal of His house devour them For God is so very great, and asks all of us. And these people feel a cosmic claustrophobia, And want to get out. "Let me out!" they cry, And the people way inside only terrify, them more. Somebody must be by the door to tell them that they are spoiled For the old life, they have seen too much: Once taste God, and nothing but God will do any more. Somebody must be watching for the frightened Who seek to sneak out just where they came in, To tell them how much better it is inside.  The people too far in do not see how near these are To leaving — preoccupied with the wonder of it all. Somebody must watch for those who have entered the door, But would like to run away. So for them, too, I stand by the door. I admire the people who go way in. But I wish they would not forget how it was Before they got in. Then they would be able to help The people who have not, yet even found the door, Or the people who want to run away again from God, You can go in too deeply, and stay in too long, And forget the people outside the door. As for me, I shall take my old accustomed place, Near enough to God to hear Him, and know He is there, But not so far from people as not to hear them, And remember they are there, too. Where? Outside the door — Thousands of them, millions of them. But — more important for me — One of them, two of them, ten of them, Whose hands I am intended to put on the latch. So I shall stand by the door and wait For those who seek it. "I had rather be a door-keeper . . ." So I stand by the door.   Sam Shoemaker, founder of Faith At Work at Calvary Episcopal Church in New York City, in 1926, was also one of the spiritual leaders who helped draft the 12 Steps of A.A. Reprinted by permission of Faith at Work.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The next Aquachurch gathering will be on Tuesday, August 17, at 6:30 PM at the CyberCafe, 176 Main Street, Binghamton. Everybody's welcome! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We had a really interesting meeting tonight, on several levels. It wasn't particularly focused -- okay, it wasn't focused at all. But during the rather lengthy time we were there, we talked the difference between confessing sins to one another and sharing personal "burdens" (as Sarah Anne pointed out, they're not the same thing at all, but both have a place in a Christian community). We discussed Christ's love demonstrated in the Gospels as opposed to the legalism I saw in the Pauline epistles (Rachel said it was a false dichotomy and went on to explain why). We discussed the occasional neccessity of "tough love" when running an organization versus the need for understanding, compassion, and forgiveness when relating to individuals one on one (Barb asked whether we could think of any instance in the Bible where Jesus actually reamed out a particular individual the way he did entire groups, and the only one we could think of was Jesus telling Peter "Get behind me, Satan!"). We discussed the necessity of our group having a really simple identifying "doctrine" -- something we all agree we believe, around which we can rally -- and Rachel identified the Trinity, the Resurrection, Salvation, and (sorry Rach) I forgot what the fourth one was. But I think the consensus was that we need to keep Jesus at the center and obey all local, state, and federal laws (good point, Tynah) but the theological fine print is essentially small stuff about which it's not necessary for us all to agree. In short, we talked about a lot of different kinds of "confessing" -- from confessing sins to confessing belief. We also prayed for the absent Mark and Nadine, and for an injured bicyclist or pedestrian John had seen on the Vestal Parkway earlier that evening.  After this the discussion sort of degenerated into a lot of silly and often hysterical laughter that had nothing to do with faith whatsoever but nearly threatened to get us thrown out of the Cyber Cafe. On the other hand, though, Barb, Dave, and I agreed afterward that this is not necessarily bad. (The laughter part, at least.) We are clearly forming a community that is growing increasingly comfortable with one another. And maybe, we concluded, we've already found what we were searching for. Maybe we don't need to form a new "church" at all; maybe we need a group of Christians who meet every Tuesday at the Cyber Cafe, in full view of everyone, bring Bibles and maybe even refer to them once in a while, discuss whatever comes up, pray for one another, and feel free to get silly (thanks, Julie and Erin, for your "unusual" communion stories). Maybe it's time to invite others to join us, making sure they understand that this isn't a Bible study, a prayer vigil, or a religious service in any sense they're used to. It's a group of Christians who love being together, and you know what happens when two or more are gathered in His Name. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>