<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey dere!!okae,i noe..i didnt blog for two daes.kindda tired lately.i guess i haf to list down loads of stuff dat i've been gone through last few daes.Loads of things i wanna share..okae,on the 25th of June,went out at bout 12pm.both me & Lila met Amni at Admiralty PLace.Fydah didnt manage to turn up.so did Mar & Az.we were late for the 12:30pm show.so we watched the 2:30pm show.okae..wondering wad movie we watched??wad else,Harry Potter and the prisoner of azkaban.the show kindda great but not much action.the three of us really did haf fun.well,we watch it at Yishun Golden Village.Felt so tired.damn tired.plus sleepy.i really did haf a good rest & early bed-tyme.Still thinkin' bout' the answer 4 me to give to Hisyam..scared i broke his heart.okae..so,dat was on Fridae.Now let's talk bout yesterdae.hmm..basically i haf ma O.O(official opening) training again.or should i col it as practice?hehehe..Lila also involved for the practice.she's in the fancy drills.i'm very happy for her.went to skool wif Mar & Safiah.saw Teck Hong sir taking his breakfast in the canteen.he's taking a heavy breakfast.can't believe it,man..he alwaes took a heavy breakfast.Mar & Safiah said dat he kindda heavy eater despite his skinny body.hehehe..funny.he is actually damn skinny.at least yesterdae wasnt ma bad dae.okae..now i do remember wad's the gerl name.the one i mentioned b4.okae..her name is Jiamin(i think i spell wrongly).Chee Wei sir do turned up.at last!!i think he kindda gain weight.Okae..i get to touch T.H.'s cap.talk to him.not dat much.sum ppl said dat T.H. is CUTE.okae..guess wad??i'm damn JEALOUS.suprise,huh.went to causewae & library.me & Lila kindda stalk T.H. Saw Kok Siang.He's cute.kindda pity T.H. coz i realized dat he dun really haf much palz.Thursdae haf the O.O training again.okae..now let's talk bout todae.well,nothing much happen todae.i finish up ma holidae assignments already.but i still haf not prepare ma skool stuff.i mean tyme table.talked to Amni on the phone bout' skool stuff & Hisyamuddin.well..i'm stuck now.dunno wad's the rite answer 4 me to give him.scared dat he'll be heart-broken.he's kindda emotional type of guy.2morrow is the dae 4 me to give him the answer face to face.i guess i'll juz haf to posponed the date to dunno wen..oh..help me!!but i dun haf any feelings for him..he's juz one of ma best fren..okae..i gotta knock out. 
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Early in the morning,woke up at bout' 6am.luckily i had ma breakfast todae.juz a light breakfast..glad dat dad can ride me to skool again todae.one of the reason is,i won't be late if he ride me to skool.i brought ma full-uniform along but wen i reached skool,i can't see any G.O.H contigent brought it along.kindda paiseh at dat moment but luckily nobody saw me brought dat thing along.so i juz place dat thing in ma bag.usually first thing in the morning,wad i would see is T.H. but todae i can't see him anywhere first dae in the morning.wen doing drills,dere's dis one chinese gerl in the G.O.H contigent.i can't remember wad's her name.she told me to do ma drills properly.okae..i take dat as a comment and try to learn from the mistake.But sooner,each tyme all of us wanna fall in,she's the only one who alwaes reminds me to left up ma legs 45% properly.Totally frustrated i tell ya.i'm sure non of us lykes ppl to remind us our mistake.okae..since i'm the front row gerl doesn't mean ppl haf to correct ma mistake wen dey themselves make mistake..huh!!Arghh!!frust,man...okae,let's not talk bout dat anymore.i found out dat T.H. is sick todae.poor him..i really pity him coz he haf to shout wen he's sick.but not dat tired as usal training todae..here me blogging while talking to Sir marcus and watching "all that" show.chat wif sir marcus is damn fun!!he's very gentleman..sort of.talk to Amni bout tomorrow plan.guess Fydah can't turn up since she still in the mood of her grandfather's death..pity Fydah..her beloved grandfather is now not by her side..maybe only me,Lila,Mar & Az turn up 4 tomorrow.Amni not sure if she is coming.Not enough money.juz now talk to Amni on the phone bout Hisyamuddin.Huh..as u noe,he's into me.i mean he sound stead me last saturdae but i haf not yet give him the answer.i'm sure the answer will be no..he's juz ma best buddy but not ma crush,admirer or sumthing.i only regard him as ma best pal..u noe,sort of bestfren but now he's into me and i feel awkward wen toking to him..now is a kindda problem to me..guess i haf to stop now..ma lil' bro need to use the comp..play games,wad else..   
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Totally tiring dae for me..Woke up at bout 8:45pm den start away take shower.mum prepared a special meal for both Lila & me.We had Mum's American breakfast.it's damn delicious.Lila & me in hurry coz we wanna meet up wif Amni and Fydah.but unfortunately,Fydah didnt manage to turn up coz her beloved grandfather juz passed away.i think her grandfather juz passed away dis morning.i felt so sorry for her..i noe how she felt coz i once gone through dat kindda situation.me & ma beloved aunt..still remember her..okae,let's talk bout the field trip which i juz went dis afternoon.it's damn FUN!!but kindda bored at first coz Fydah didnt turn up.but afta a while,we did enjoy.took a ferry but was a bit giddy at first.everyone felt the same wae...eat a lot of snacks while on the wae to St John island.once reached dere..weather not dat good.but the scenery dere was awesome.lyke it veri much.we get to see dis cute little colourful fish.wish i could touch it.den we get to go to the place.i forgot wad was it col.we get to do some discussing but of coz nobody do really care bout dat.but we did haf fun at dat moment.den we went to so col an area where dey held those experience.we get to see the most biggest fish dey breed dere.but those fishes so rough.we also get to see the giant clam.so huge.one of the tour guide told us dat some ppl do eat those stuff.i felt so disguisted.YUCKZ..finally,we get to the lab where we get to touch some sea creature.so COOL!!i get a chance to touch a shark.of coz it's a baby shark.Not only dat.also i get to touch sea cucumber,starfish and loads more.afta dat,we straight away head to the jetty.took the ferry again.dis tyme non of us as giddy as we were the tyme we came.we watched the story col "volcano".bet many enjoy the show to coz all of us didnt really realize wen we reached S'pore.dat was the fun trip.i bet.i didnt went back home straight away since i'm starving at dat moment.so head to the fast food restaurant(KFC).okae den..ma lil' brother wanna use the computer.kids dis dae..   
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Okae..early in the morning i send my lil' brother to his religion class.Den fetched him bout 10:20 am.kindda late at dat moment.i saw  Putera at McDonald.i mean..he's a McDonald Boi.hehehe..he kindda shock to see me.Now his quite tall..guess he grow so fast.Den i saw Hanafi near the supermarket.reached home,first thing i do is col Amni.She didn't manage to turn up.Not dat she's not free..but she not comfortable coming alone.so we juz chat on the phone for hours.on wat to bring for tomorrow,things lyke bout Hisyamuddin..and life.I'm kindda bored at dat moment..so Amni kindda cheer up ma dae.we lykes to jokes around,and dat's COOL.i've got nothing much to do,so i clean up ma room..the entire ROOM!!!i make-over the whole into kindda funky one.it's pretty nice to juz hang out in the room and admiring it..den i realized,dere's still plenty of tyme..so i decorate ma new diary.Luv it veri much.while decorating it,i set up ma hair.it ended up ma hair turns all curly.but it's pretty nice.can't wait to show Lila our room being make-over & ma new hair style.i bought quite a lot of snacks for tomorrow field trip.gonna enjoy dat trip.todae not a good dae for me..mum kindda naggy all dae..while dad at sticking at home the entire dae..BORING,rite?wateva i do todae,mum will haf sumthing to say..sumthing dat hurts ma feeling..an irritating comments...juz can't wait for skool reopen ..i juz dun wanna stick ma butt all the tyme at home..it's irritating!!okae..juz keep up the latest up date.many to tell..pretty sure.coz tomorrow out of S'pore.hehehe..going to St. John island for field trip.can't wait to meet up wif the sea creatures..okae..gotta knock out b4 the naggy thing appears again..cHiaO!!      
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Okae..i feel so bored!!i'm alone at home.not exactly alone.Mum & dad going out for some bussiness stuff.Nowdaes mum is so buzy wif her work.almoz everydae she go out.Lila went to camp at woodgrove sec for red cross.gonna miss her for two daes.both of us juz cant leave without each other.we're as close as...hmm..dunno wad to say.but we're juz lyke twins.isnt it great??she's having fun..while me..at home,gonna finish up ma holidaes assignment.juz a little more den dat's it.todae i'm gonna sleep alone.and conquering the whole bed.it's sounds pretty good but not for me..dis week gonna be a buzy week 4 me..hmm..todae course cancelled again.guess juz stuck at home again.tomorrow nothing on.but definitely i'm gonna get ma butt out of the house.maybe i'm gonna hang out at the mall or sumthing wif palz.but amni said dat she wanna come over to ma place.sounds COOL!!we gonna hang out and working on our gang's website.i'm not a homey gurl or an indoor gurl.so whenever i haf nothing at home..i would prefer doing some sports lyke playing soccer or hang out..okae..gotta knock out..loads of things to finish up..ByEzzzzzzzzzz 
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Hey dere..At last i get to blog again.i'm kindda sick for the past 3 daes!!Can't believe it..i haf no flu,fever or cough.Wondering wad kindda of sickness.Me not sure.Maybe ma stomach is kindda upset wif me.It's all started on the night of 16 june.Ma stomach is making me SICK!!i try to lay around all over ma room but juz can't keep ma eyes shut.ARGHHH...!!(FRUST)Dunno..suddenly i rush to the toilet and VOMMIT!!YUCKS....Everything i ate came out.I vommit more den 5 times..Basically i'm very weak at dat moment.The next dae i'm suppose to attend an NPCC course .But to bad..i'm sick.So far, the past 3 daes basically i'm juz lying at ma bed..didn't eat anything juz drink..Now i'm glad dat i can eat wateva i want!!Todae is the dae 4 me to enjoy ma meal once again!!   Okae..on Fridae,18 june,Amni and Fydah came over to ma place.Although i'm sick but i still haf to carry on wif the project stuff.Now Lila,Fydah,Amni & me are so close.Almoz everytime we hang out at either one of our place..it's COOL.Dis coming week will be a buzy week for me.Having NPCc training for the Official Opening,Npcc Course(luckily they change the date to tomorrow),activities,Field Trip,Family outing & FRenZ dae out!!Hmmm..yesterdae Hisyamuddin sound stead me.I dunno wad answer to tell him.Huh..i juz treat him as normal frenz..We are so close dat he end up falling for me..okae..i guess i haf to stop here.So many things to do!!Lila need ma help 4 her camp stuff.Guess i'm gonna miss her for two daes...  
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        HaHAHa!!First time Blog.Basically me on the wae back to homeland..Kindda miss hometown,Frenz and Family!!Tomorrow still haf to turn up for a course.Huh..tired,man.Not sure if i can wake up early tomorrow.Juz wish me Gd Luck.  Still thinking bout' ma CRUSH!!Miss him...Dunno y.he's face alwaes in ma mind..okae..guess gotta go.. 
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Todae is YOUTH DAE!!Now i'm downloading pictures.Nothing much happening.it's juz dat mum went out of S'pore doing some business trip.She'll be home by tonight.Dad also went out to work.Guess dat only left me & ma siblings alone at home.Oh yeah..i think i haf to update ma blog for the past few daes..   Mon,28 June 04' It's first dae of skool.early in the morning got caught by principle.i pass the answer via Amni.Hisyam totally over-joy.By the wae,i haf ma own novel.Still working on it.i col it "Puzzled..Help!!".   Tues,29 June 04' Well,todae is ma 2nd dae wif Hisyam.B4 i forgot,todae is also ma 1 month havin' crush wif T.H. ma class get selected to go to SYF opening ceremony.   Wed,30 june 04' 3rd dae wif Him.we didnt communicate wif each other yet.discuss bout 'Creative Dae'.Went to Civic Library.Mar fell down near the carpark.Hurt very badly.   Thurs,1st July 04' went to skool felt panic.i forgot to bring ma npcc belt.for the first tyme,i forgot to bring npcc stuff o skool.dad sent the stuff together wif ma skool bag.Ms Yeo cancelled the G.O.H practice since dey onli concerntrate on the fancy drills ppl.    Fri,2nd July 04' Wow!!Creative dae & Be Yourself Dae is held todae.two events on one dae.ma class dress as HIPPIES.all of us look so slack.but fun.Mr Harizan didnt managed to turn up coz he's going to Hong Kong to visit his wife dere.Reporters came to skool to take some pictures.For the Be Yourself Dae,i wore a black 3/4 shirt wif ma violet clr pants.Went to Cwp afta skool wif Lila,MAr,Az & Fydah.we took pictures and haf fun.    Sat,3rd July 04' Early in the morning went to skool.Both me & Lila over-slept.We woke up at around 6:15am.Haf npcc training & also O.O preview for principle.Kindda nervous coz i'm in the Guard of Honour contigent.the main & important ppl.But everything went very smoothly.Afta dat rush home quickly coz we had to reach skool again by 1:15pm.Loads of ppl turned up for the SYF opening ceremony.The show kindda fun & boring.very proud coz sum of ma skoolmates involved in the parade.i saw dis cute chinese npcc instructor.He's kidda cute.too bad i didn't take a picture of him.Haf fun wif all ma palz.On the wae back,i alk non-stop wif ma classmates.we played sum games.funny thing is dat,Amni fall asleep.she told all of us dat she's tired.dunno tired bout wad.if i'm tired it's kindda acceptable. okae..dat's all,palz..i need to continue wif ma novel stuff.. 
      
</post>


</Blog>