<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey People!  &nbsp;I'm stoked! Because my mom is finally taking me to go get The Homeschoolers Cd! Now I can listen to The Homeschoolers without having to deal without all this crazy music stuff on my computer.&nbsp; Now something completley different, Pepsi can keep you up for a really long time. I drank like 3 cans and I've lasted this far. Pepsi's the new Mountain Dew. lol! I'm thinkin of goin over to my cousin Danas house and just hang out for a bit and play some b-ball with my nephew. He's got some kool moves that he made up.&nbsp; Now Jerons world!! All I know so far is that he got his haircut, he's read this blog, and hes super busy! That's all I know so tune in later to find out what happening in Jeron's world here on Jeron_blog.blogspot.com, I'm reporter Hyper offPepsi! Thank You and Good night! lol! I've always wanted to do that! I'm gonna go play some addicting Neopets now! So as they say in Italy or France, Chow! ~Reporter Hyper offPepsi~  Which color is your favorite? Red Green Yellow Orange Blue Navy Blue Purple   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey ppl! (or person since Laura is the only who reads this so far, LOL!) On Thursday my brothers had drumming practice, native american drumming. They rode their bikes to practice and my mom thought that my younger brother walked so we waited for them to come out so we could give him a ride but he had ridden my bike. So I tried grabbing my bike from my brother but then he pulled my hand off my bike so I was gonna get out of the car to chase him cuz the last time I let him ride my bike he popped the back tire and almost got it stolen! So anywho, when I was getting out of the car my shoe wasnt on all the way so it slipped sideways and I had put to much force into opening the door and it came back and socked me right in the head! It hurt really bad! So now I have a big ol' bruise on the top of my head! But now something totally unrealted my brother and I rode our bikes up to French Island to see our cousins and Adina cuz she lives with them for the summer. So we had to spend the night cuz it was to late for us to ride our bikes home and our mom couldnt pick us up so we had to spend the night. When I was sleeping this morning, at 5 A.M I might add, my stupid brother and cousin put one of my cousins toy on me and they had pulled its tail and ran cuz once you pull its tail it vibarates so I woke up and they did it cuz they wanted to go on a bike ride! So now I'm super mad at them! I was in the middle of a good dream too! lol! J/P! Well now Im gonna go get some breakfest so, Later dayz! TNT, ~whatever H-a-l-e-y spells~ I.H.N  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is just like the Travis Blog except its for the one and only,... Jeron! Jerons a great guy. Hes the koolest friend anyone could have! Well I g2g before I pass out on my keyboard..... Flip U on the catch side! ~Haley~ I.H.n  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey,    Well as most of you know today is Jerons Birthday!!! Yeah! Yippee! Woohoo! Hip Hip Hooray! Ok I'm done know. Jerons 19 now. I would say something funny right now but my brain isnt workin as well as it usually does. Well I dont got nothin else to say plus I have to get off-line now, so Laterz!  *Halez*  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         What's up people?  I am now joined on to haley's blog thing.  I am kinda excited just got done with a party we through at my house for my cousin adina and ashley's birthday's.  It was great!  My baby niece's and nephew were so cute playing in the water.  Well don't know what else to say.  So I am going to go now.  Buh byez.          ~Lacy~     
    
    
</post>


<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First Travis, Then Jeron, And Now.....JON! I have to stop making so many blogs.&nbsp;I think I'll make one for Tylor and Andrew. As soon as I meet them!lol! Jons.........well Jon, of course! He's like, a one of a kind person. Well from what I know anyway! Hes gotta weird, but funny, sense of humor.&nbsp; But I gotta go, so Laterz! In his name, *Haley*&nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey, It's been awhile since I posted in this thing so I figured I might as well. Nothins goin on really just three things mainly, waiting for the homeschoolers concert, the claiming nothing concert, and the claiming nothing cd to come out. That's it. sounds boring huh? Well it is. But anways I've seen Jon twice this week. Which is wickedly awesome by the way, to me anyway since I rarely ever get to see them! Well the first time I got to see him was Sunday at Myrick Park, He was at a party. I was gonna go up and say hi but he looked tired and when I was going to go up and say hi to him a bit after I first saw him it appeared he was sleeping on the park bench so I thought I'd better let him get his beauty sleep. Then today I saw him downtown while I was spending a dreadful day with my dad and my brother. Only cuz it was cold and I didnt feel well. But I said hi to him that time and he said hi back. He had a box and he was doing sumthing, dont know what but it was probably sumthing amazing cuz everything Jon does is amazing. lol. But Im gonna go write some things called songs even though I'll never have any use for them and there completly stupid and dont make any sense.lol. laterz. *Haley* I.h.N 
     
    
</post>


<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ppls! I have never been so bored in my life! Well maybe I have, but I don't know or care! lol! I need to tell ppls about this blog cuz the only ppl reading it is Travis and Lacy. Thanks for the support Travis and Lacy. I think I'll say something on Laura's blog since she is like world wide and all and plus this computer won't let me comment on the homeschoolers website so Laura is like my only hope, isn't that sad? I have to help my aunt and my cousin and my sister, Adina, move stuff. Cuz my other cousin is moving upstairs and this computer room is going downstairs so if I have the time to get on the computer I'll write something for ya Travis and Lacy! I got my highlights and a hair cut yesterday from my cousin Dana. She used to work at a Hair Salon places then she got into a different career thing. So now I am not just a Brunette or h/e u spell it I am a blond and a brunette. Change is good as they say! I am about to pass out on this keyboard I am so tired. Lacy I changed my password so U can't read my mail anymore. Sry! If I can get Jeron to e-mail me back I'll get him to look at this too, were in a weird state right now but if he e-mails me back then I'll ask him to look at this cuz I NEED MORE PPL VEIWING THIS THING! And if u do read this Jeron, I'm sry!! Well I got a new puppy on Tuesday. His name is Scooby Lou. He is a Black Lab/ Pittbull. He's adorable. Unfortanutly my cat got hit by a car and she's my baby so that makes it worse. But her leg is only like sprained a little. So I'm spoiling her more than I usually do. U ppl should go to addictinggames.com then go under everything else then go to driver's ed and play it, it's very fun. Well hopefully I'll see whoever reads this tomorrow, I.H.N ~Haley D~
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey ppl! I just finally found out my password so you ppl can continue to e-mail me at milkynative@yahoo.com or milkynative1@yahoo.com, which ever one you please but I mostly read my mail at Milkynative so just tellin' ya ppl! The whole name thing Milkynative, well I'm Native American so that's the native part and the Milky part is my nickname from my nephew, kool, huh?  Well TNT, (till next time) ~Haley~
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey ppl! I got some bad news, I forgot my password to my yahoo account! I've tried and tried the password over and over again so now it is disabled and I have to try back later. I didn't get to go to church yesterday cuz I'm stuck up here in Black River Falls, babysitting. But it's all good cuz I love my neice! Even though she can be a little brat sometimes I still love her! Well I got to go and make her some Mac & Cheese for when she wakes up from her nap! OH yeah hope you have fun in Madison Lacy!  Till Next Time, ~Haley~
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, Hey, Hey! This blog is of course about the one and only, Travis. Of course it is. You can talk about Travis, do anything but it's gotta be some what related to Travis. OK? K. see ya later fellow Travis fans! ~Haley~ p.s. when ya check my pro im not really 13 im 11 turning 12 and im the year of the monkey too.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Sry about the whole 2 same polls in a row thing the first one didnt show up a day after and they usually do so I thought it didnt publish so I made another one and then they both publish so thats why there is two of the same polls in a row. Anywho, I have nothing to do today, as usual. But I'll manage to find something to do, I always do.&nbsp; Since I have nothing else to say Im gonna go. Ovua! (or however you spell it) ~Haley~ I.H.n 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is your favorite animal? Cat Dog Gerbil Guinea Pig Hamster Fish Goat Rabbit Llama Horse Cow Chicken Whale Shark Dolphin Octupuse Jellyfish Stingray Wolf Lion Tiger Leopard Ocelot Other 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I have nothing to say I made up this poll!  What is your favorite animal? Dog Cat Gerbil Hamster Guinea Pig Horse Snake Iguana Lizard Fish Bunny Horse Goat Cow Pig Dolphin Whale Shark Octupuse? Stingray Jellyfish Wolf Lion Tiger Leopard Other 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hi there boys and girls, ladies and germs! One and All!   I am bored out of my mind! So I figured I might as well as post since I have nothing else to do, besides talking to Brandon! Same here Laura I havent heard from Travis in a very very long time! Or from Jeron, or Jon. I miss them.:( Andrew and Tylor dont know me so I dont&nbsp;care that I havent heard from them cuz I never talked to them before! Hopefully, I'll start church this week. Middle School, not High School. I'll try to be at black river beach on the 8th dont know why you want me to be Laura, but I'll try! I went to go see Spider-man 2 like last week maybe? I dont know when but it totally rocked! Adina's b-day is on the 21st, shes turning 18! But she is isnt goin to be here so Im guessin were havin her birthday party on the 20th then! I was mad yesterday cuz I was practicing for basketball and I shot like 30 shots and only made like 6 of them! I used to make almost all of the shots I made but now I can barley make any! SAD! :'( LOL! Well Im gonna go now so have fun ppl and I'll try to too. TNT   ~Haley D Littlejohn~ I.H.N  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there Hey there Ho there!,    I had alot of fun last night. I went to the La Crosse Speedway races last night with my mom. It was really kool!The racing was kool especially in the beginning, cuz there was this guy who had pulled over to the side and another person was turning the corner and he ran into the guy who had pulled over to the side and the dude who had pulled over his car went on top of the dude who ran into him. Then there was drag racing. A guy who dressed up as a girl said his name was Sue and wore a dress. He said that his husband thought he was in the bathroom so he took the van out and dragraced it and lost. He was kidding the whole time though. Then this other person went off a ramp and drove right into the vans windsheild. Then there were some lame bus races. After that there were these ppl who rode in complete darkness, well they had these humongous lights on the top of their cars so it wasnt complete darkness. Then there was these wicked sick fireworks! It was awesome! And there was this big ol' monster truck that ran over cars. Then we went home. But now I'm sitting up here at Lacy's house babysitting her. lol! J/P! I'm babysitting my neice geneveive again. She's such a little sweetie! I'm probably spending the night here since there is always a big fourth of July party. Yeah that means I cant go up to my cousin Ians house, But hey make the best of what u have! Ur right Laura ur blog isnt really bout the homeschoolers alot and mine hasent really had that much to do wiht travis lately either. I didnt go to church cuz Adina never came back from her friends house until after church.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey ppl! This is just another boring post that starts out with nothing to do with Travis even though it should! Like maybe 2 hours ago I first signed on and went straight to the Jesse McCartney site. Only for 4 reasons, I like his music,not as much as the homeschoolers though!, The new t.v show,--> Summerland, The website is cool, and He's hott! LOL! Then I went and played some games at addictinggames.com first I played Driver's ed, even though I had played it up at my cousins house this weekend and had gotten my drivers liscene or h/e u spell it. Then I played Insanequarium or w/e its called. Then I played make-a-flake. But now I'm done with that. I'm checking my mail on Yahoo now. But its all bulk. :( Somebody please email me! lol! Ok im done checking my mail. Now I'm seeing if Travis wrote a new blog yet... nope. :( I'm going up to my cousin Ian's house for the fourth of July. He lives by the river so were gonna go tubing which is really fun! Hope u ppl have fun with this fourth of July weekend with w.e ur doing too! All right I'm gonna go now, TNT, ~Haley~ I.H.N
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey,   It's been awhile since I posted. Lacy's been postin lately. Well I invited Laura and Travis. There still pending. But anywho, after this I'm gonna go finish cleanin my room. Cuz supposedly its supposed to be clean. Crazay! My birthday is tomorrow. Its not that big of news though. I'm gonna go to the concert on Saturday. Of course Im going to. Duh! Well I dont know what else to say so later dayz!!! I.h.n ~Haley~ 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey people!  What's up?  Yes, Haley has invited me once again to join travis' blog.  Yesterday I went to Valleyfair and spent an entire day with some of my family and relatives.  It was really fun!  I was very adventrous when I was there too.  I am very scared of heights and so is Haley.  My cousin's that I went on rides with are not.  So I decided that I would try all the rides that I would have never tried before.  So I went on the Corkscrew for the second time, which Haley did go on too, and I went on the Wild Thing as well.  Sad to say Haley didn't go on that rollercoaster.  That was extremely scary, but I must admit I did have fun.  Then I was debating on if I should go on the Power Tower.  I let two of my cousins go on it first since they haven't been on it in a while.  Then we went on more rides.  Before we left I decided to try the Power Tower.  So my two cousins and I went on the blue one.  WOW!  That was even more scary then the Wild Thing.  But once again, I did have fun on that ride.  I would try all those rides again, probably.  So much fun!  Even the ride up there and back was exciting although we did get stuck in road construction and almost got lost.  Well that was my excitment so far for this week.  I am going to go now.  So buh byez, one and all who read this.      ~Lacy~  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>