<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to the cinema to watch Shrek 2 tonight. I've been in a bad mood all day so I'm hoping a few beers and a comedy will sort me out.  Theres also a train crash waiting to happen when I get there...  More when I get back.  Jingo
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As many of you remember, my old site www.jingo.tk was basically a site created by me to display my extremely fucked up life.  I also wrote songs but generally it was about what was bothering me at that time.  This is what this shall now be.  Regards.  Jingo x
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting here and its quite late. I'm listening to Snow Patrol - Run, well I was and now I've got Evanescence - My Immortal.  Don't know why I'm listening to such sad depressing songs, I ain't even feeling that bad. Had a good night on Thursday - even if she did keep the lion lol. Just reached into my pocket and pulled out the tracing paper. I guess I'll have to work on that next week.  One thing I knew, is that you love me.  Another thing I knew, is that another loves me. And I'm so sorry. I hope you get over me, and realise that I'm not who you need.  Eels - I Need Some Sleep.  I seriously need therapy.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Decided to grab the best 5 poems off my previous website and add them here.   Don't Let Her   You see, things are never quite as they seem, It doesn’t matter who your are or where you’ve been, Cause things that happened in the past, Will come back to haunt you, and then at last, You’ll realise what you wanted before, Isn’t what you wanted now because you want more, But hey these things happen; there isn’t much you can do, If that person you love, doesn’t love you, You’ll just have to dust yourself off, Pick yourself up, and forget what you’ve lost, Cause in the end you had your chance, There’s no point standing in the same stance, You know the one, full of sadness and despair, Cause hey, your still breathing the air, Which means there are other things to be done, Go find someone else and let them be the one, Because that door behind you is now closed, So go find the next one and let it be exposed, That’s right; open that door full of opportunity, Its not gonna cause anymore harm you see, Its gonna let you decide your own future, So don’t let that girl be the one who beats ya, Because when you’re with that someone else, You won’t be thinking about her, That girl who left you down there, But she’ll be thinking about you, trust me, Because I know the score, I’ve been here before, And I know what you’re going through...   Untitled   Hey  My name is James, And I'm an alcoholic,  Your not really busy, So don't try and ignore it,  Don't just sit there, Hiding behind your screen,  I'm trying to tell you something, So stop being fucking mean,  This is what we do everyday, Sitting here typing,  Either planning what we're gonna do, Or listen to constant sniping,  People bitching about nothing, But making sure the people get hurt,  Spreading lies and rumours, Or just dishing daily dirt,  Or lying about stuff, You're supposed to have done,  Or telling people you don't know, About the person you call the one,  Or telling other people, All the crap you've heard,  And getting random people, Call you a fucking nerd,  Why do people use this thing, All the fucking time,  Suppose its better then going out, Committing some stupid crime,  But that doesn't stop some people, People that I hang with,  Going out and robbing people, People they used to hang with,  But this idea isn't completely good, Cause it does some bad things too,  It lets people say things, That they normally wouldn't do,  Some may view this as something quite cool, But not when you get upset from it.  When someone plays you, fucks you around, And keeps treating you like shit,  So this has some good and bad points, But to leave it behind wouldn't be fair,  Cause when you have nowhere else to turn, It will always be there,  It was great talking to you, But now I have to go,  Glad I got to tell you things, I'm glad you got to know.  Bye   Tomorrow   Why dream of tomorrow? When today's still the same, Different sorts of problems, Still the same old pain. Why dream of tomorrow? When there's nothing to gain, Still getting all that crap, And the same cold rain. I don't know why I love you, Or feel the way I do, When all you've ever done, Is denied your the one, I don't know why I love you, When I'm played the fool, But I can't do nothing else, When I'm still under your rule. So why dream of tomorrow? When today isn't fair, I dream of all my ambitions, You feel my anger in the air, Why dream of tomorrow? When you still don't care, I still hold all these feelings, My side still lays bare. For forty days and for forty nights, There was nothing in my sights, My mind still sticks on you, I just don't know what to do, I feel used and outspoken, My heart's weak and broken, Yet I still feel this way, I need to make you pay, So I stood outside and waited, Oh yeah I stood outside and waited, Why dream of tomorrow? When today's still the same, Different sorts of problems, Still the same old pain. Why dream of tomorrow? When there's nothing to gain, Still getting all that crap, And the same cold rain...   Catch Twenty-Two?   This is goodbye, the end for you and I, Its not fair to take anymore, Its not right seeing you cry, This is the way to go, I know I'll miss you so, Its easier this way, Its easier I don't stay, This is goodbye, the end for you and I.  Walls come crashing down, Destruction all around, Those plans we made so long ago, How they'd end we'll never know.  Walls come crashing down, Destruction all around, Those plans we made so long ago, How they'd end we'll never know.  Can't cry for yesterday, tomorrow another way, Its time for me to change, For new times me to engage, Have the time of your life, that's right, Climb the tallest mountain, Play another game, This is goodbye, the end for you and I,  Walls come crashing down, Destruction all around, Those plans we made so long ago, How they'd end we'll never know.  Walls come crashing down, Destruction all around, Those plans we made so long ago, How they'd end we'll never know.  Catch twenty-two, don't know what to do, Its gonna be hard, We're gonna be apart, It's better to break, you know what's at stake, See you in a few years, Free of those tears, This is goodbye, the end for you and I.  Walls come crashing down, Destruction all around, Those plans we made so long ago, How they'd end we'll never know.  Walls come crashing down, Destruction all around, Those plans we made so long ago, How they'd end we'll never know.   Hope   Ok so we’re at the beginning, When I had something to go for, Something to look forward to, Hoping to be with you, After these last few weeks, This is the peak, Where the level of expectation is good, And the chance at its max, Not even thinking about if all this goes wrong, You’ll find that in a later song, Because it feels so right, To try this one last time, And finally make you mine.  And this hope, That keeps me holding on, And this hope, That makes me carry on,  I was so excited, I surprised myself, My face showed it all, Today is a great day, For these things I want to say, Nervous, of course I was, This was it, all or nothing, Because I wasn’t going to try again, Because I’d done all the running, And frankly I was tired, Because we’d got no nearer, no clearer, To finding the solution, So this was why I was hoping, To fix this, good or bad, Cause I’d thought bout what we had, Make no doubt about it, I didn’t want to spoil things either, But you didn’t make it any easier, Because that question still existed, And that’s why I persisted, That’s why this song is written,  And this hope, That keeps me holding on, And this hope, That makes me carry on,  Because although you hope and wish, To have that first kiss, Take a long look at what you may lose, And this decision maybe easier to choose.  And this hope, That keeps me holding on, And this hope, That makes me carry on, And this hope, That keeps me holding on, And this hope, That makes me carry on... 
    
</post>


</Blog>