<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I called Registration Services.  If your GPA for the year is 3.410 or higher, you are considered a Harlan Fiske Stone Scholar, or just Stone Scholar, which means you are - more or less - in the top third of the class (33% to 30%).  If your GPA is 3.8 or higher, then you are a James Kent Scholar, or Kent Scholar, which means you are in the top 1-3% of the class.   As the distribution of grades varies year to year, the percentage ranking can't be determined precisely.  Registration Services said that it will be posted to the transcript eventually but may not be posted prior to interviews, and thus students can calculate their own GPA and put it on their resumes.  I should further mention that grades are weighted per the number of credit hours. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Check it out. It's the article that I assume the writing competition was based on.  http://www.columbialawreview.com/pdf/Wen.pdf 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       not because I want to join, but because it's funny:  http://members.aol.com/schwenkler/scalia/ 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think I remember reading that professors had a definite deadline of June 30th so that the Law Review would have our grades in time. Does anyone else remember that, or am I just hoping that the waiting will soon be over?  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       http://www.gop.com/kerryoke/ 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Does anyone have any information on the Stone Moot Court? How we sign up, what kind of a time commitment it is, etc. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Looks like Schizer is not teaching tax in the fall. My alternate was Fed Courts, so it looks like I'll be taking Corporations, Fed Courts, and Property. Definitely not the easy load I was expecting. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So for my birthday, I signed myself into the Republican party.    I feel so free!  I'm no longer a closet Republican.  Yeah, people may choose to make fun of the things I talk about and the people I choose to associate with (just to mention a few lifestyle choices), but at least I'm no longer ashamed to stand up for what I believe and want from my government.  No discrimination is going to keep me from expressing myself they way I want to!  I just want to encourage all the other closet Republicans to step out in to the open and enjoy the fresh air (provided by Bush the First via amendments to the CAA)!    Hint, hint Alan.  By the way, are there any good reasons to vote for Kerry? 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Check it out. I just uploaded it yesterday.  http://www.columbia.edu/cu/law/fed-soc/index.htm 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       From the 2Ls, how do you like your firms, any advice for interviewing now that you've been with the firm? 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A guy at the firm showed me this nice website for all of your bluebooking woes:  www.law.cornell.edu/citation I hope it helps! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Now that the deadline is upon us, what classes and professors will everyone be taking in the fall? 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm curious what everyone thinks the most pressing issues are both in this election and in American politics in general. National security/war on terror? Economy? Racial equality? Gender equality? . . .   Here is my list to start.  1. National security 2. The family 3. Economy 4. Racial equality 5. Gender equality 6. Federalism (state sovereignty, etc.)  I have to qualify the economy, since I don't think that racial and gender equality should always be subordinate to the economy, only that racial and gender equality are less important than an economy that provides jobs so that people can take care of their families.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       REPUBLICAN NATIONAL CONVENTION SCHEDULE  New York, NY  6:00 PM Opening Prayer led by the Reverend Jerry Falwell  6:30 PM Pledge of Allegiance  6:35 PM Burning of Bill of Rights (excluding 2nd amendment)   6:45 PM Salute to the Coalition of the Willing   6:46 PM Seminar #1 Getting your kid a military deferment   7:30 PM First Presidential Beer Bong   7:35 PM Serve Freedom Fries   7:40 PM EPA Address #1: Mercury - it's what's for dinner.   8:00 PM Vote on which country to invade next   8:10 PM Call EMTs to revive Rush Limbaugh   8:15 PM John Ashcroft Lecture: The Homos are after your children   8:30 PM Round table discussion on reproductive rights (MEN only)   8:50 PM Seminar #2 Corporations: The government of the future   9:00 PM Condi Rice sings "Can't Help Lovin' Dat Man"   9:05 PM Second Presidential Beer Bong   9:10 PM EPA Address #2 Trees: The real cause of forest fires   9:30 PM Break for secret meetings   10:00 PM Second prayer led by Cal Thomas   10:15 PM Lecture by Carl Rove: Doublespeak made easy   10:30 PM Rumsfeld demonstration of how to squint and talk macho   10:35 PM Bush demonstration of trademark "deer in headlights" stare.   10:40 PM John Ashcroft demonstrates new mandatory kevlar chastity belt   10:45 PM Clarence Thomas reads list of black republicans  10:46 PM Third Presidential Beer Bong   10:50 PM Seminar #3 Education: a drain on our nation's economy.   11:10 PM Hillary Clinton Pinata   11:20 PM Second Lecture by John Ashcroft: Evolutionists: The  dangerous cult  11:30 PM Call EMTs to revive Rush Limbaugh again.   11:35 PM Blame Clinton   11:40 PM Laura serves milk and cookies   11:50 PM Closing Prayer led by Jesus Himself  12:00AM Nomination of George W. Bush as Holy Supreme Planetary  Overlord  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been recently reading a lot about Bill Clinton's presidency and I am increasingly more impressed with the strong President that he was and the amazing legacy that he has left us.  I am mostly impressed with his excellent track record on the war on terrorism, where even though he had little indication that there was a terror movement afoot, especially with Al Qaida, he continued to act bravely and forcefully and saved our country from so much destruction and heartache. There was the first attack on the World Trade Center where President Clinton bravely spoke about "bringing the terrorists to justice." I think he even went so far as to indict Osama bin Laden, for which we are all eternally grateful. There was the attack in Yemen on the Americans, the attack on the building in Saudi Arabia, the bombing of the two American embassies in 98. After finding out that these acts were perpetrated by Al Qaida, Bill Clinton bravely sent some planes and dropped several bombs on the terrorist camps. We should all be forever grateful that those bombs probably postponed September 11th for an extra couple months. Although a harder response to these terrorist attacks would have certainly helped us avoid the September 11th tragedy, we would probably have had to act unilaterally, and would have injured the human rights of the terrorists.  North Korea is another situation where we are forever in debt to the Clinton Presidency. During his administration he brokered an excellent deal with the North Koreans to protect America's national security. Though the cost of the deal was high--several billion dollars--he successfully fought off the threat of a North Korean nuclear threat until the end of his presidency. Taking a harder stand with the North Koreans before they developed enriched Uranium would, of course, probably been more effective, but it would have certainly hurt the feelings of the international community. Good thing President Clinton avoided that.  He was fortunate to choose a running mate, then Senator Al Gore, that would go on to invent the internet, which ended up inflating the economy and providing prosperity to so many Americans.   These policy stances, coupled with my great respect for Mr. Clinton's moral integrity make me proud to have lived during such an excellent era of our country's history. Thanks Willy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Maren and I have a crib that we'd be more than happy to part with for bargain basement prices (read:  for free).  Good crib, brand new four years ago (for stacy) from RC Willey, all pine wood construction, includes hardward, etc.  Would be willing to deliver if you can wait for me to come back from Texas with the car.  If Alan, Blaine or others (Nancy? :p) are interested, let me know.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This one is actually pretty accurate and respectful.   urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/07/31/science/31gene.html?pagewanted=1&amp;hp   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We're getting rid of our desk to make room for the crib. Any takers? Free for the taking. Take a look at the pictures and let me know.   urlLink http://www.columbia.edu/cu/law/fed-soc//desk1.jpg   urlLink http://www.columbia.edu/cu/law/fed-soc//desk2.jpg   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that the names of Blaine and Alan's new kids should be decided by popular vote of the JReubs.  For Blaine, in honor of his fascination with dead presidents, I propose Madison, Reagan, Grant, Tyler, and Van Buren.  So that Alan can continue to sing the Wiggles' theme song as he studies, I propose Greg, Murray, Jeff, Anthony, and Captain Feathersword.  What say you?  p.s. i bet it would help if we knew if they were going to be girls or boys  p.p.s. maybe we could just use an old favorite and name both Isaac.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have a job after graduation.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jon Olsen will be getting into the city on August 12th, but most of his stuff won't be coming until later.&nbsp; He wants to have a couple of smaller items shipped to the city and waiting for him when he gets in (air mattress and stroller).&nbsp; If anyone is willing to accept shipments for Jon, please contact him on his cell at 509-460-1328 or at  urlLink jonolsen10@hotmail.com .  He would also really appreciate if someone would provide a place for his wife and child to&nbsp;rest that morning while he makes the arrangements with housing.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; As I understand it, they're flying in early in the morning and he has an appointment with housing at 9:00.&nbsp; We all know how housing can be.&nbsp; So if you can accodomate them, please contact him.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/07/29/national/29mormons.html?adxnnl=1&8hpib=&amp;adxnnlx=1091128886-fRospEATufXbL+Ee5qmmQw   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone know when they're going to tell us whether or not we got the classes we requested?  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, sorry to use this for solely personal reasons (again), but I just bought a car.&nbsp; Slight problem:&nbsp; the car is in Texas.&nbsp; Friday is my last day at work, so I'm planning on going down to Dallas to pick it up and drive it back within about 10 days or so - and Maren want's me to take somebody with me so I don't....well, I'm not exactly sure why.&nbsp; If anybody wants to go (I'll pay for the plane ticket there, etc.), let me know.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You can see the Vault online for free via the Columbia Career Services website.  Go to CLS homepage, click on "careers" then on "career services" then on "2L/3L calendar of events" username: 2l3lcareer password: events then click on "commercial career resources" on the right side.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Read these:    urlLink http://www.techcentralstation.com/071504B.html     urlLink http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A16811-2004Jul26.html    The articles show how the Kerry/Edwards platform is ridiculous on trade and the economy.    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Someone mentioned investing their student loan money under the life insurance entry.&nbsp; What do you all think about that?  Stafford loans are under 3% and some private student loans are under 5%.&nbsp; There's plenty of ways to invest money and get a better return than that.&nbsp; Has anyone thought about borrowing to invest?  The financial advisor guy we talked to said his hard and fast rule is "Never borrow to invest," but overall, I think he's a very conservative investor.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://abcnews.go.com/sections/politics/Vote2004/kerry_poll_040726.html   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sharra and I are meeting with a financial adviser this afternoon who I'm sure is going to try to sell us some life insurance.&nbsp; Is anyone else worrying about getting life insurance yet?&nbsp; Anyone got any advice or wisdom to impart on the subject?  Whole? or Term?  Start early? or Wait?  Do firms usually include life insurance in their benefits packages?  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/07/25/weekinreview/25bott.html   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've already talked to a few of this, but I was wondering how many of you are golfers.&nbsp; I've been doing a little bit of research, and it turns out that Bethpage isn't all that expensive (20 bucks or so for 18) AND it's available on weekdays for golfers.&nbsp; Since I'll have a car soon, I wonder if we can't get together a foursome or two and golf the green or yellow (the easier)&nbsp; courses a few times this semester.&nbsp; Sort of a Jreub golf club.&nbsp; None of the people I've talked to are very good - me included.&nbsp; General handicap seems to be in the area of 35 or worse.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Here's my final list of firms I'm picking.  Now all I need is for the site to work.  Anyone else having problems accessing the bidding site today?       1: Davis Polk (NY)   2: Debevoise (NY)   3: Sullivan Cromwell (NY)  4: Wilmer Cutler Pickering Hale and Dorr (DC)  5: Weil Gotshal (NY)  6: Arnold Porter (DC)   7: Simpson Thacher (NY)  8: Milbank Tweed (NY)   9: Williams Connolly (DC)   10: Sidley Austin (DC)   11: Latham Watkins (NY)   12:  Piper Rudnik (DC)    13:  Kirkland & Ellis (NY)    14: Foley Lardner (DC)   15: Wilkie Farr (NY)   16: Mayer Brown (NY)   17: Hogan Hartson (DC)   18: Akin Gump (DC)   19: Hunton &amp; Williams (DC, Richmond, McLEan)   20: Gibson Dunn (DC)  21: Quinn Emanuel (NY)  22: McDermott Will &amp; Emory (NY)  23: Dickstein Shapiro (DC)  24: Nixon Peabody (DC)  25: Steptoe Johnson (DC)  26: Cahill Gordon (NY)  27: Shaw Pittman (DC)   28: Stroock (NY)  29: Kilpatrick Stockton (NY)  30: Proskauer (NY)       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Check it out:  urlLink http://weblog.herald.com/column/davebarry/archives/2004_06.html &nbsp;and hit Control F and look for "Connie".&nbsp; Connie's blog also has some snapshots from my wedding, if you care.&nbsp;    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This article was forwarded to me by my officemate, the most passionate liberal I know, as an example of why he supports racial profiling.  urlLink http://www.womenswallstreet.com/WWS/article_landing.aspx?articleid=711&amp;Titleid=1&titlename=&amp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My favorite Apostle.   urlLink http://deseretnews.com/dn/view/0,1249,595079013,00.html   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A post on the  urlLink Leiter Report  discusses a book called  The Black Book of Communism , which is apparently a book detailing all the deaths that can be attributed to communism. I thought many of you would find this interesting in light of our discussions last year on Communism and the law of consecration. Leiter also notes that such a book about capitalism could also be written . . . an interesting thought.   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, so I know that th at not everybody on this blog is a BYU fan, but this seems to be the best way to throw out the idea.&nbsp; Is there anybody interested&nbsp;or planning on doing the same sort of setup that we had at Drew's place last year for watching games?&nbsp; I know a couple of people from the ward who'd like to chip in, plus there's always the first years.&nbsp; Do we even think the team will be good enough to warrant watching?   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Although I am aware that not all of you are Federalists, I want to let you all know that the Federalist Society Student Symposium is at Harvard this year. It's awesome. And if you sign up for the national organization ($5), Fed Soc will help pay your travel expenses to the symposium. We're trying to work a deal to get them all paid for. &nbsp; So, everyone plan on coming. We're going to have a huge Columbia group there.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm getting into this whole EIP lottery thing.   I feel like I'm the Charlotte Bobcats in the expansion draft.   Here's a tentative list of the top 20 firms I'm picking:    1: Davis Polk (NY)  2: Debevoise (NY)  3: Sullivan Cromwell (NY)  4: Arnold Porter (DC)  5: Wilmer Cutler (DC)  6: Paul Weiss (NY)  7: Milbank Tweed (NY)  8: Simpson Thacher (NY)  9: Williams Connolly (DC)  10: Sidley Austin (DC)  11: Latham Watkins (NY)  12: Convington &amp; Burling (DC)  13: Wilkie Farr (NY)  14: Fulbright Jaworski (NY)  15: Hunton &amp; Williams (DC, Richmond, McLEan)  16: Dickstein Shapiro (DC)  17: Mayer Brown (NY)  18: Gibson Dunn (DC)  19: Hogan Hartson (DC)  20: McDermott Will (NY)    Others to consider  Shaw Pittman (DC)  Kilpatrick Stocton (DC)  Quinn Emanuel (NY)  Proskauer (NY)  Hogan Hartson (NY)    Others I wish I had room on the list for:  Weil Gotshal (NY)  Hale &amp; Dorr (NY)  Morrison Foerster (NY)  Sidley Austin (NY)  Cleary Gottlieb (NY)  Fitzpatrick Cella (NY)     
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There has been some good discussion on the amendment on  urlLink Bcc &nbsp;and  urlLink The Volokh Conspiracy . I am not a huge fan of the current amendment (the one that just failed to pass), but prefer it to nothing, since I hate the idea of the Massachussetts Supreme Court being able to export its definition of marriage. And I don't trust DOMA. My vote would be for DOMA in the form of an amendment.&nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/2004/07/14/opinion/main629681.shtml  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just wanted to mention how living in Utah has made me appreciate New York.  Now, I'm not saying that Utah isn't a wonderful place, and the perfect place for many people.  I just feel more comfortable in New York at this point in my life.  Eryka agrees.  We enjoy the culture of the city, the multiple entertainment options, and all of the shopping (Utah's most glaring inadequacy: no Chinatown).  Oddly enough, I find living in New York easier than living in Utah.  Maybe that's just because I don't like driving.  Of course, It also might have something to do with me being a student in New York, and not a working professional.  I'm anxiously anticipating a new school year.  I even get excited at the idea of working in New York after graduation.  But I think something is wrong with me.  Eryka cringes at the thought of me spending my waking life chained to a desk at a firm downtown.  I'm wondering what everyone thinks about the looming prospect of putting in gruelling hours for often thankless work?  I know there are attorneys and bankers in the ward who do it and try to simultaneously raise a family.  Those of you in New York for the summer have had a first-hand glimpse into this where I have not.  I appreciate any opinions as I consider a career in the cutthroat legal capital of the world. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Normally I don't think the New York Times is worth the paper it's printed on, but I did find an article that supports something I have thought for quite a while:  urlLink http://www.nytimes.com/2004/07/14/movies/14MOVI.html  What do you guys think?  I'm not trying to turn this into a "Mormons don't watch R-rated movies" debate (heaven help us all if it goes that way) but I have been thinking for a while that the ratings are getting considerably more loose and arbitrary.  (According to the MPAA, the Patriot should be more offensive that Austin Powers?) 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Did all of you get the invitation?  Are any of you going?  If you didn't get it and you're in New York, let me know and I'll forward it to you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm so excited about the speakers we're getting lined up, I have to let y'all in on the list.  Richard Posner (7th Circuit COA) Doug Ginsburg (DC Circuit COA) David Sentelle (DC Circuit COA) Richard Epstein (Univ. of Chicago) Eugene Volokh (UCLA) Judge Kelly (10th Circuit COA) Terry Pell (Center for Individual Rights; litigated Grutter and Gratz)  Still hoping for: Justice Scalia Judge Luttig (4th Circuit COA) Robert Bork Senator Bennet  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i assume you all were having the same weird formatting problems that I was. i changed the look to fix it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I know that you guys are either completely overwhelmed with the recruiting idea or really, really tired of thinking about the whole thing, so I'm either sorry or glad to provide you the following information.  I just found out that there is a survey that all summers from large firms across the nation fill out that will be available in Octoberish or so for you to read in American Lawyer.  The summers rate their firm on several different qualities.  I'll be taking mine today, so I'll know more later, but I thought you'd want to know.  The survey is available in American Lawyer (or some similar sounding publication) which is evidently available by the mailboxes on the third floor of Greene hall. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone? Favorite Blogs? Here are mine:  Church Blogs:  Times and Seasons  (www.timesandseasons.org). This is great. Really smart and very respectful of the brethren, yet healthfully critical. Patriarch Bushmann writes on it sometimes.  By Common Consent  (http://rameumptom.blogspot.com/). Pretty good, yet sometimes overly-pessimistic and critical of the brethren. Some of the liberal discussion I really appreciate and some of it is pretty bad.   Law-Related Blogs:  Tutissima Cassis  (http://www.tutissima.com/). Really good. Kept up by Nate Oman who also writes for Times and Seasons. The church finds its way into discussion at times.  The Volokh Conspiracy  (http://volokh.com/). Professor Volokh at UCLA (who will be speaking fall semester for the Federalist Society). I think he's tied with Dorf for being the most-cited professor who started teaching after 1992.  The Curmudgeonly Clerk  (http://www.curmudgeonlyclerk.com/weblog/). I don't read this one very much, but others seem to like it.  Three Years of Heck  (http://www.threeyearsofhell.com/). Kind of weird, which you will understand if you know Tony Rickey, the blogmaster. Still, it's interesting b/c it's about Columbia.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Several of you asked, so here is a link to the AmLaw 100.  Use it with caution - like any other statistical survey, it doesn't tell the whole story and/or may not be completely accurate.  You'll need to register to access some of the reports.  http://www.law.com/jsp/law/amlaw100.jsp 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Congrats to Blaine, Alan and Heather on making Law Review.  Way to represent. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blaine, you lucky dog.  http://money.cnn.com/2004/06/29/news/fortune500/mattel_barbie/index.htm 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I do believe we're being insulted by a 15 year old!  (At least those of us who are Federalists)  Anyway, congratulations to Nancy and Brad! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, as many of you know, Maren and I are getting a car here shortly.  We're looking for a cheaper sedan that's going to last at least a couple of years or so - do any of you have any dirt on: Nissan Altima Dodge Intrepid Ford Taurus  Year model is approximately 1997-2001.  Let me know if you know anything word to mouth or if you know of another good sedan I should look at. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So today is the big day.  I heard from JTL this morning.  I've unofficially heard from another.  I'm still waiting to hear from the rest.  Any thoughts on which journals are the most prestigious or the most interesting (besides Law Review)? 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       http://www.lds.org/newsroom/showrelease/0,15503,3881-1-19733,00.html  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here is part of the email I received upon signing up:  The office of Student Services very much appreciates each of you volunteering a couple of hours (to talk about yourselves to high school students who want to be like you!) for the Thurgood Marshall Program.  The high school students, from diverse backgrounds, attend NYC public schools.  You supply the inspiration based on your personal success stories/experiences and we play host and supply the pizza & soda.  We are looking at July 15th, William & June Warren Hall (103?), from about 7:00 pm or 7:30 pm until about 9:30 pm, pizza/soda.  More details will follow.....  By the way, we have just one guy on board (thanks Joe!) but if you know of a couple of other guys who might be interested ask them to contact me via email....  Thanks.  If I can be of further assistance please do not hesitate to contact me.  Nneka Elizabeth Pope Columbia Law School Ph: 212-854-6955 Fx:  212-854-8843 npope@law.columbia.edu 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Article on some of the problems with a Kerry/Edwards ticket.  http://www.nationalreview.com/kudlow/kudlow200407070839.asp 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Has anyone heard any advice what to look for in a good law firm?  Anyone have any good info on the firms that are coming to EIP? I've been looking through Vault.com and NALP and a couple of books my dad gave me.  Does anyone know any other good sources of info on firms?   I'd be particularly interested in seeing how young assoiciates rate their firms. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So what's everyone doing this weekend?  Since (presumably) none of us drink, we can't engage in the most common 4th of July activity, so we have to find another way to have fun.    We're going to our nation's capital to see the fireworks and may head out to Virginia Beach, but the plans are up in the air.  I just want to hear some wild stories on this blog! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The churchwide J. Reuben Clark Law society is having a lunch next Friday.  Who's going?  I plan to be there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Is anyone trying to work any of their connections in the upcoming interviews?  If you know someone in the firms you're applying to, what can you do with that?  Is it appropriate or helpful to name drop in interviews?  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sorry I didn't reply to the post below - I was in Texas getting a car (which is another story altogether).  I echo what Steve said - don't try to fake it.  My impression is that a lot of the interview is about making a personality connection - will this person fit in with the culture at our firm.   You shouldn't forget the typical tricks, though:  make sure to make good (but not too much) eye contact, be bright and cheerfull (but not bubbly or scatterbrained), don't have anything on your resume you don't feel comfortable talking about for a couple of minutes, sit up straight, have immaculate grooming, sound intelligent (but don't put on airs) and don't be afraid.  Recruiters seem like wild animals - they can sense fear from a mile away.   The most important thing that I learned from the whole interview process last year was this:  Never fly in from Tokyo the day before EIP.   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Six families are pulling into Manhattan as we speak.  They're coming in on two trucks, so luckily they have each other to help move in.  But they're sure to appreciate anything extra you can give.  Their first stops will be on 119th and 122nd.  If you can help, call Phil Scarborough on his cell phone at 801-592-9801.  Also, they would like the phone # of the Elder's Quorum President.  I don't have my ward directory with me, so if anyone could call Phil with his number, that would be great.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I always struggle during interviews to think of good questions to ask the interviewers. Any good ideas? I always ask about their summer program and how they train their associates, but never seem to have anything great.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I know Nate is planning on interviewing with DC firms.  Is anyone else?   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Isn't this great?  Technology sure has streamlined and simplified our lives.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Before getting too excited to read the 100+ pages, I decided to call Brenda of Registration Services at 212-854-2668.  She says that I'm registered for the one week course.  I thought some of you may want to call her before doing the reading.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone have any good advice to share on how to succeed at the EIP interview process? Jake, do you have any secrets to impart, having been through the process before (besides the pink tie).  The question that I know I'm going to be asked that I don't yet know how to answer is, "What type of law do you want to practice?"  I'm already sick of answering that question.  I have no idea.  Anyone have any good ideas about how to break the ice and make a connection with the interviewer?  Blaine, got any more pirate jokes?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://lds.org/newsroom/showrelease/0,15503,3881-1-19896,00.html   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Comes out  urlLink tomorrow!  (Monday)  Remember when the new US News law school rankings came out while you were deciding which school to go to? You hoped that the new reports would bring to light something that would make your decision so much easier. Well, the new Vault Guide will likely be equally unhelpful.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Robin rented "50 First Dates" with Adam Sandler and the girl from ET (forget her name). It was pretty funny and it doesn't have to go back until next Sunday. Anybody who wants to watch it in the meantime is welcome to come borrow it.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>