<Blog>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On dates:11, 12 and 13 of June...  those were the dates that when 3 hearts were broke... Shattered! I wish i could turn back time and i wouldn't fall for him in the first place... I fell for the very same guy my best friend did... He belonged to nobody, nobody until... Until we found out that he had went steady with one of our good friends...  Who might have thought? But we knew that it was useless to comtinue anymore... The day that we found out about it was the day me, my best friend went out... We were sad, real sad.. we were eventually lost... We saw them together... we really wish that we could juz make ourself blind and had never seen them... Our good friend chooses not to tell us as she was afraid to break our hearts... But she didn't know that she has the key to me forgetting him in the first place...  i don't know why but she kept it from me... why?! On 13 of june, my another friend's heart was indeed shattered terribly... he likes her... he actually like her... He didn't take it easy... He didn't... He wish god has taken his heart away...  Love is never good neither bad... It's selfish! It's cruel but yet, we love it... Why?  I wish i could turn back time I wish i had not like him i wish i  couled erase wat i've done... But there's no way i could do it  Well, basically, i had liked somebody else before him but, he eventually had a stead too...  Haiz... I wanted to excel in a lo of things.. I had great ambitions... I had wishes that i knew i could never realise... Cuz' i prefer to dream... I prefer to soar in my dreams instsead of my real life... Sometimes, it's better to dream and soar i your dreams... but, it's also better to juz realise that you can do it... and continue to persevere...
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Life is sometimes never ending to us... But we sometimes realise that we have no where to go but juz to continue... All of us have our own ambition to fulfill but it's juxz up to us whether we will make it... Juz like as though there's somebody out there who might be willing to read this blog of mind...        Have you ever wonder wat is life? Life is full of choices... Life is a filled with obstacles that you can't even think of... But the people around us can help... it's juz that matter of the choice on whether they want to help or not... Sometimes we feel as though we can fly to the moon... we can spread our wings and soar above the sky... it's just the matter of time...        I had never thought of how tomorrow is going to be without fulfilling of what i'm going to do today... sometimes it's better not to look into the future if we are not completed with our present...       Have you ever tried to kill yourself but was being stopped by others? Have you ever thought you were useless? Have you ever thought that you're alone?
    
</post>


</Blog>