<Blog>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello! Oh my goodness! I just went to the college board web site and got my latest SAT scores... I did a lot better in verbal, but worse in math. URGGGGHHHH! I am 10 points away from a full tuition scholarship to Lee!! I just made a 1220 and I need a 1230... If you combine my highest math and verbal, however, I have a 1290! But they won't let me do that! Urgghhh! So frustrating! Well, I'm gonna go... enough venting for now. BYe bye! ~Jenna
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone! I had a great night tonight... Fusion was wonderful. Then I had a blast with those who stayed to play volleyball afterwards! Thanks for cheering me up! It's 3:33 am (make a wish!) and I can't sleep! Talk with y'all later. yahoo-carolina_girl8604 AIM- palmettogirLEE 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi! It's Jenna. This is a site I began to talk with current friends and make new ones! Talk about anything... your likes, dislikes, what's going on in your life lately... whatever you want. It'll be a fun way to stay in touch! Love, Jenna
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello! Wow! I just got back from Lee University's Summer Honors program a few days ago... it was so wonderful! I had so much fun and met so many great people! I leave for Pittsburg Saturday for a week... I'm flying from ATL! I love to fly, so I'm psyched! haha... How is your summer going? Post a comment! Love y'all! ~Jenna
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Well, I only have 2 days after today left in Greenwood. I'm so excited, but it's killing me to say "goodbye" to so many people. Tomorrow night will be my last Fusion service... that is going to be THE WORST & HARDEST "goodbye session" of ALL!! Then the grads are going over to Pastor Keith's afterwards to spend one last night with him &amp; Lindy. They are two of the most beautiful people I know, and I'm going to miss them so much. Thursday is going to be a day full of goodbyes to all of my friends & family. Then I'm leaving bright &amp; early (6 AM) Friday morning... What an exciting day that will be!     I'm sooo full of emotions right now! It's overwhelming... excitement, joy, nervousness, sadness, hurt, anxiousness, happiness, relief, anger.... you name it, I've felt it this week! haha. The future is bright &amp; coming quickly... I'll write more soon. Love, Jenna :) 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          I can't believe I really have less than a week till I move to Lee!! I've been having a lot of fun lately. I spent the night at Angela's the past 2 nights along with a bunch of other Fusion girls... we stayed up late both nights & had "girl talk." There was also some late night swimming, batter-eating, cooking, scary phone calls (which turned out to only be Nathan), chick-fil-a runs, movie watching, & video camera mishaps (sorry Jess! haha) So much fun...     Tonight was Danielle's birthday party. We had fun hanging out, dancing (cha-cha slide rocks!), and eating. I'm spending the night with her tonight... so I gtg b/c I gotta get up for Sunday School in the morning. Bye bye! Love, Jenna 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey hey! Wow! I can't believe it's already August. I have some "happy birthday" shout outs!  Gan (my grandma)- today! Aug. 3- she's 78! Pastor Impellizzeri- Aug. 4- 54th b-day! Stevie Marinaro (my lil brother)- Aug. 5th turning the big 15! Danielle Davis- Aug. 8th- congrats, girl! you'll be 18 & legal! David Impellizzeri- Aug. 17th... i think he's 25 (?) Brooks Cain- Aug. 23rd also 18 &amp; legal! Emmie Davis (my lil sis)- Aug. 27th the big 15 as well!  If I left anyone out, I apologize. Please let me know. Anyway, I move to Lee in only 10 days! I can't believe it. That's crazy... but SO exciting.  More later, Jenna xoxo 
      
</post>


</Blog>