<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       cool 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is what I want to do. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink ComputerZen.com - Scott Hanselman's Weblog - The Syllabus for CST407 - Learning C# with .NET   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Visual C# .NET is the latest addition to the Visual Studio suite of powerful programming languages. The Visual C# .NET Getting Started guide walks you through how to build a Visual C# .NET project by implementing a simple QuickSort algorithm. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       SharePoint Thoughts - A blog centered on Windows SharePoint Services 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Channel 9 : "We think developers need their own Channel 9, a way to listen in to the cockpit at Microsoft, an opportunity to learn how we fly, a chance to get to know our pilots. Five of us in Redmond are crazy enough to think we just might learn something from getting to know each other. Were we wrong? Time will tell." 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This list will, of course, never be complete. If I'm missing anything please let me know. These are links to major collections of feeds, not individual feeds. This list will eventually be turned into a database. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Topix.net - News organized by topic and location 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink ForwardShift  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink ForwardShift  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Sysinternals web site provides you with advanced utilities, technical information, and source code related to Windows 9x, Windows Me, and Windows NT/2000/XP/2K3 internals that you won't find anywhere else. Mark Russinovich and Bryce Cogswell alone write and update everything here. We welcome all suggestions and comments. Before you enter, please read our Licensing terms.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Testing Software Patterns - Microsoft Patterns & Practices 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Satire and commentary on dotnet development. Seeking a small but devoted audience. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Test driven development (TDD) is emerging as one of the most successful developer productivity enhancing techniques to be recently discovered. The three-step: write test, write code, refactor – is a dance many of us are enjoying. This site is dedicated to promoting techniques, tools, and general good will in the test-driven community. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Test-Driven C#: Improve the Design and Flexibility of Your Project with Extreme Programming Techniques -- MSDN Magazine, April 2004   This article discusses: A comprehensive description of test-driven development The benefits of TDD and extreme programming An introduction to NUnit A comparison with traditional development techniques   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Meet Scout... my dog. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink       Firefox 0.9 is the award winning preview of Mozilla's next generation browser. Firefox empowers you to browse faster, more safely and efficiently than with any other browser.   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       HP Parts Store  317188-001   AC power adapter - 120 watt output with power factor correction (PFC) 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This SDK contains conceptual overviews, programming tasks, samples, and references to guide you in developing solutions based on Microsoft® SharePoint® Products and Technologies. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Add features to your SharePoint sites through reusable Web Parts by Jason Mauss   For This Solution: C#, Microsoft ASP.NET 1.1, Microsoft Windows SharePoint Services Beta 2, Microsoft Windows Server 2003, IIS 6.0, Microsoft Visual Studio .NET (2002 or 2003)  With the release of Microsoft ® Windows ® SharePoint TM Services 2.0, both developers and users will have a much more powerful way of pulling information from multiple locations into a single display. Included is an extensible infrastructure (including a .NET object model) for building components from which users can assemble their own sites.  At the heart of this infrastructure are three things. First, there are Web Part Pages, which are the pages the end users see and can personalize to fit their needs. Second, contained within Web Part Pages are Web Part Zones, which are the containers of the third item, Web Parts. The focus of this article is to show you how you can build Web Parts that users can then add to their Web Part Pages, customizing the look (if desired).  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       SharePoint allows information workers to create powerful personalized interfaces by simply dragging and dropping pre-defined Web Part Components. Web Parts are components that enable non programmers to gather information they care about and customize the appearance of Web pages. For example, one Web Part might display a user's appointment calendar; another might create a graph showing current sales figures; and a third might show a list of new business topics, each of which functions as a link to a video or audio presentation. Developers can create these Web Part components and make them available to SharePoint users, letting them build customizable pages that meet their needs. This article shows you how to build and consume a simple Web Part. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Suraj Poozhiyil Microsoft Corporation  March 2003  Applies to:     Microsoft® Windows® SharePoint™ Services and Web Parts      Microsoft Visual Studio® .NET  Summary: Learn how to install and use the Web Part templates for Visual Studio .NET. Use these templates to create Web Part libraries containing Web Parts and Tool Parts for Windows SharePoint Services. (4 printed pages)   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink GIMP - The GNU Image Manipulation Program : "The GIMP is the GNU Image Manipulation Program. It is a freely distributed piece of software for such tasks as photo retouching, image composition and image authoring. It works on many operating systems, in many languages." 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       John and Barry talk with us about Test-Driven Development, Unit Testing, and other aspects of Extreme Programming that are being used today. We had given lip service to unit testing in past shows, but John and Barry were able to explain the benefits as well as the how-to of test-driven development 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>