<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        You belong in the world of balance, where everything has two sides and everything is not always what it appears on the outside. Of course, if you have a sense of humor, you may find employment as a sarcastic comedian. If not, enjoy the choices that are presented to you through life, they will always have two sides to them,one which leads you to the light, and the other which entrenches you in darkness. Walk on with hope, my friend.    urlLink   Where do you belong?(ANIME IMAGES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        PASSIONATE LOVER. You love to love, always looking for a relationship. You cannot live without it. Your lover must be passionate  and you want that you and your partner melt into each other. He/She should not try to take the domination . You dont want a relationship without passion, and the sexuality plays a big part. The first moment you meet him/her is one of the most important. There has to be something between you , you cannot explain. From the first moment on everything must fix. But when this passion disappears you disappear to. For you it is better to leave than to see your love restrained.  PLEASE VOTE, I want to know what you think about my quiz, I worked hard on it.You can always message me or tell me how I can improve that quiz. Ill sure write back.    urlLink   	~THE big LOVE TEST!! What do you need? With PICS! For girls and boys!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       You belong in the world of balance, where everything has two sides and everything is not always what it appears on the outside. Of course, if you have a sense of humor, you may find employment as a sarcastic comedian. If not, enjoy the choices that are presented to you through life, they will always have two sides to them,one which leads you to the light, and the other which entrenches you in darkness. Walk on with hope, my friend.    urlLink   Where do you belong?(ANIME IMAGES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       your asshole.    urlLink   What swear word are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla        You enter the door .You see the higher being and listen to what it says to you: I have already been waiting for you.You ask yourself why, dont you? Let me explain: You should know that I am  not the highest being I am just one of the nine servants. And I am sent to make you think about something but I am not here to answer your questions. I can not tell you too much but I will come again. So listen what I have to say! I am the higher being of  fun. And I am  sure that you have much of fun every day. And you have a couple of friends beside you, you are not alone. But I have to warn you I see a time coming that wont be that easy. I dont want to scare you, but I want to say that in this time you need your friends and your family a lot. So do not try to isolate yourself from them. Tell them what you think. Just hold on then everything will turn into fun again Thus spoke the higher being of fun and now wake up If you want the higher beings to come again please rate this quiz. It will may take some time but I have to work hard. Messages are also welcome!    urlLink   ~Visit the higher being in  one of your dreams and listen what he says to you !!!WITH PICS!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla        You belong in the world of balance, where everything has two sides and everything is not always what it appears on the outside. Of course, if you have a sense of humor, you may find employment as a sarcastic comedian. If not, enjoy the choices that are presented to you through life, they will always have two sides to them,one which leads you to the light, and the other which entrenches you in darkness. Walk on with hope, my friend.    urlLink   Where do you belong?(ANIME IMAGES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, I almost forgot about this already. Go me. heh. Lessee, party tonight. wheee. Maybe. Depends on how tempers are tonight. lol.   July 12: My planned sleepover with people. More or less an 'I love the 90's' party. But hey, we're cool like that. *shakes head*   Welp, gonna go. Ja ne!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yeah, I'm cool, I have like....three journals now. w00t. Still dunno how to add friends.....wish I did though, cause then I could feel all smart and spiffy
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      squee? Yeah, just....testing
      
</post>


</Blog>