<Blog>


<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As some of you may have known, I was off in the wonderful world of vacationing. While I was sitting around I came upon some interesting concepts which kept me quite occupied. What are they you ask? Well, let me tell you...        Chris' Vacation Thoughts:   - Dairy Queen is a dirty resteraunt franchise.. Under all of the DQ signs you always see another sign underneath that says brazier. What the heck? What do ladies undergarments have to do with ice cream?  - Clint is such a balla name! I wish my name were Clint... Everybody would throw me parties... or name a sandwhich after me... Yeah, I love sandwiches.  - What's the deal with that Oprah chick anyway?  - If I had any super power it would have to be the power to ROCK! I would just whip out my guitar and strum such a fine ditty that everyone would be way better off than before. I would also solve world peace with my Rockin' power. And make a fine chicken scanty!  - Notable observation: Why are there no pretty girls in Colorado? I swear! I was there a whole week, and do you know what I saw? NOTHING! I'm dissapointed in you, Colorado...  - What was the name of that 80's sitcom with the family that had a pet sasquatch? I used to love that show!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This Being my first entry and all, I really have no idea what to say! However, being a man of many words I'll be sure to fill up a little bit of space. To start off with, I'd like to thank Jennifer for referring me to Blog. I greatly appreciate the thought. Secondly I would like to thank Yanni for being such a balla android. Thirdly I would like to mention ballacrosse, the greatest game ever! If you'd like to know more about that, please contact me via e-mail: Chris@prj7.com. I think that about covers everything for right now. Thanks for your time!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I was in the same room with all three of the Hillsboro Jr. Miss representatives. Thank you, thank you... 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        So I've been trying to think for a while how I wanted to sum up my experiences at the leadership camp and I have come to the conclusion that it's made me learn as much about myself as it has about other people. Some people change, some never do. Acquaintances are always worth making. Judgements can really hold you back from knowing how awesome a person can really be. And sometimes the greatest things in life are merely taken for granted.  Thoughts often flashed through my head about how in the earlier years of highschool I was the one who put myself into seclusion, not anyone else. People I may not have talked to a year ago turned out to be my best friends on the trip. Especially you Neil. Haha. I don't know what I would have done without the support of another black man like myself. This experience really has me amped to go out and meet new people this final school year. Time is starting to run out. I need to leave my mark with people.  The couple days also brought about different&nbsp;feelings concerning friendships. How am I going to deal with leaving all of my friends after high school ends? I'd like to think we could all stay in touch, but I know it just won't happen. A question came up that went like this: "When was the last time you laughed the hardest and cried the most?" After a little thought which strayed some from the original question I began to wonder if I would cry for the loss of a friend. I came to the conclusion that I would, for 1 person. I decided to bring this up in hopes of eliciting a responce from you. Would you cry for a friend? Perhaps more than one?  But enough talk of sadness, I want to end my post on a happier note. Avie makes me smile. I realized just how much I missed her over the summer. It's such a great feeling you get when reuniting with old friends. Maybe not even old friends, but ones that you love.  And there you have it ladies and gentlemen. I've just shed a tear...    
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       well, it would seem everybody's favorite Nys, Brandon Nys, has made his entrance into the blogging world. Feel free to check out  urlLink his site&nbsp; and prehaps even add it to your favorites. I think you'll enjoy what he has to say.      
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       No more posts for a couple days. Gots a fun packed week of leadership camp... My only question is if we are supposed to be leaders why are we going to be schooled in the ways of leading? Shouldn't only those in the know be placed in such positions? And while we're on the subject I should be zzz... zzz... zzz...    
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Lenny, today you brought a smile to my face when I looked at your links section. It's really amazing how one simple word can change the mood you're in instantaneously.  And God Bless America! (I hate you Evel Knievel...)    
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        So I posted a blog earlier this week mentioning this game I like to mess with on the internet called Nation States. WEll, the game is good, however I am not. I have been informed that the link is no good. Upon further inspection I found this to be true, and so I felt it my duty and obligation to bring you the true  urlLink hyperlink . There is a region which you may join called Ballatopia (Yes, I did create it). feel free to join in if you ever get the urge, hankering, or if you ever&nbsp;just get&nbsp;that bored.   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Some of you may have noticed one of my earlier transgressions from yesterday. That being, that I played Lenny's game wrong. I would like to make it known that I now see the errors of my ways and plan on seeking treatment in an attempt to disuade myself from responding in the previous fashion henceforth. I know that I can't take back what I've already done, but let us all hope that it never happens again. Let us all learn from this mistake. People, I&nbsp;emplore you... Read the instructions before you sign your John Hancock. Or in matters of Lenny's game, your abungas.   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I should really read my previous blogs before posting a new one...   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Just wondering if anyone else has ever heard of Nationstates.com? I think it's fairly humorous and perhaps even wort taking a look at. =) I also wanted to mention that I'm going to start toying around with a website of mine, perhaps replacing my blog? We'll see. I know for sure I want to start taking pictures of places I go and people I'm with to place in a section of my site. Another peice will definately go to Yanni, and of course a third to the wonderful world of ballacrosse. Any other suggestions? Feel free to posr them herrre, and I'll take a gander later on. CHUCH!    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        So I'm creating my own webpage (which should be a link somewhere on this post?) and I thought it was worth mentionung. Eventually I'm going to add some more pages besides the main one and it will be pretty balla. Perhaps a page in devotion to Yanni... Haha. Well, that's all for now.  Keeping you posted:     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        For those of you who read my crap, I've decided to utter unto you a new complaint. That being children and coffee.  What are pre-pubescent youngsters doing with so much caffeine anyhow? Truly I say to you, we are raising a new generation of yuppies and trend followers. Taking a small survey of those awake during the time of this posting I find that a whopping 100% don't truly drink what is commonly known as coffee. Instead we murder the good name of caffeine by plagiarism it under the revamped aliases of frappachino and mocha latte's. Loading these "drinks" with enough sugar to bring about a debate as to whether the "high" comes from caffeine or that cup of caramel you just needed to have added to your three ounces of coffee.  And what ever happened to the good old days when one could go down to the local diner, order a "cup of joe," and sit at a booth to read his local paper? The trendy thing to do now adays is to sit in a crowded cubicle sipping your javas and cuppocinos, seeing who can hold their sugar better. Perhaps we should all start playing more drinking games during these times. Last one to name all 50,000 blends in the shop has to take a triple shot!  I feel aggravated to reminisce back to the days of middle school. To hear all the children brag about how much coffee they drank. It's no freaking wonder that parents don't know how to handle their children. Little Timmy has a hard time concentrating in class! Let's dope him up on some pills to fix everything. Has anyone else noticed how much sugar Americans consume in an average day? The numbers are probably staggering. I myself am included in this group. And in being so, I now realize the importance of distancing myself from too much of this vile... glucose.  A trendy addiction has the youth of America in it's vice. And so I conclude in this little&nbsp;monologue, lose the disillusion. Go drink some water for a change. Maybe some milk. By God, half of you are going to end up with osteo perosis...  Tune in next time for another edition of... Chris Ch@! (Oh Lenny...)       
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sometimes I think I may be much like my idol, Yanni. I say this because I feel that emotion may have escaped me in much the same fashion it has my android counterpart. Upon inspection of my inner self during a conversation I had with Jennifer tonight, I find myself to be more shallow and introverted&nbsp;than I had ever imagined. Have I nothing better to talk about than the goings on of other people? Where is my life? Lost in the limbo of peer comformity. In an attempt to mingle with the crowd I have given up my own morals and identity. I find myself to be moreover, cynical of others attempts to find themselves while I sit back and neglect my own needs and desires to become an individual. Props to all of those who found their way allready. I think I have a long road ahead of me. But not all is lost. Now that I've realized a small piece of my discontent, I feel that what was once a&nbsp;no-through sign is merely now&nbsp;a&nbsp;yeild to oncoming traffic&nbsp;on my way out of this parking lot of self doubt and worthlessness. And Yanni, I believe that one day we shall both learn to love others as much as we love the music. &nbsp; I would also like to apologize now to all of those people I've made fun of in the past. My bad guys... &nbsp; "Gee,I have great thighs!" - (Thanks, Pavel) 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I felt a strong compulsion to respond to a certain entry in a friend's blog today on the topic of rejection. I'd like to say, you're right. Rejection totally sucks. I&nbsp;never mean to hurt anyone's feelings. However, people aren't always what you hope them to be. I'd really like to start off with apologizing for my less-than-perfect explanation when you told me. I felt like such a jackass afterwards. I wish that I could have explained my self a little more clearly. Better. However, I'd like to save that for an opportunity outside the posted word.  &nbsp;  My main concern&nbsp;now is&nbsp;that it feels like I've lost a good friend. I was excited about the invite&nbsp;to your party actually (I even managed to call off the ballacrosse, haha). You may have noticed my lack of gift though. And I think that actually signified the biggest problem I had with your statement the other night. That being, I don't know you. What do you really want? Who are you? What's YOUR deepest darkest secret? I'd really like to know more. If you desire attention and approval I'll be here for you. But for the time being I think&nbsp;the third is unavailable.&nbsp;&nbsp;        
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ever feel like you really put your foot in your mouth? I hate that!  And who took my cereal?
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Officially speaking ballacrosse was truly invented by a trio of ballas. Cara Miller, Jon Viducich, and myself all worked together to make this game possible (much props). Truly the greatest game ever invented within the last forever. I feel it is now time to release some rules out to the public, so as to even further spread the influence of Ballacrosse.  Ruleses:  1: Ballacrosse may be played anywhere under the conditions that you have a) a ball, and b) a court (any size/shape). Latest courts have been portions of football fields, soccer fields, and tennis courts. 2: Said Court must have a series of containing lines dividing the court in half and tracing the outside edges of the court. 3: Service must be from the back of the court, allowing the ball to drop once before kicking to the other side of the court. 4: After the serve teams may feel free to juggle the ball (without the use of hands) by or between any amount of individuals on said team. 5: the ball may be allowed to bounce once before a team makes contact with it, but it musnt touch the ground again until transferred into the other teams quadrant 6: All lines are played as redo's. The ball is returned to serving team and put into play. 7: Teams my chose to play a ball which has hit the line, but forfeit the right to a replay in doing so. 8: A ball may be played outside of the court. However, to pass to the other team requires that it be played from within boundaries during the pass. 9: Score is kept like old school volleyball (No rally scoring). At 11 teams switch sides of the playing field for the next round of play. The winning team must be ahead by 2.  And there you have it... I would like to thank all of those who have made the game great. Let's have a balla good time this summer tearing it up with the Balla action. Pharrelll!  Goldfish taste bad.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What is truth but a series of coordinated lies?  Wishing I could sleep... -Chris- 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, ladies and gentlemen, I have now joined the ranks of the employed as my first day at Dairy Queen has come and gone. What a great feeling to know that someday you may have money. What a terrible feeling to know that that day has not quite come yet... I met  a nice guy name Julio. He's tight. Karen is also really nice. I think I shall enjoy the benefits of employment.  I have also come to the conclusion that nobody needs plans. At least it always seems to be the case with kids these days. I say, whatever... To you sirs and madams who tend not to have plans.... ever.   I want to work at the circus and wrestle lions. Thank you.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I feel right now like I have a billion different choices and no idea how to discern the good ones from the bad ones. I'm in a strange dream. I wish I could be everywhere at once and yet at the same time nowhere at all. Why can't I just be the center of the universe? things would be much simpler then I think.  I start a new job over at Dairy Queen tomorrow. I'm a little bit indifferent to it though. No jitters, no excitement. I would have thought I'd have some kind emotion concerning this. Sometimes I questoin myself about how I can feel so indifferent about swerious occurances in my life. it's like I have no frontal lobe at all. However I find my autonomy distressful and then realize that I am not a robot after all. None=the=less sometimes, I wish I had the ability to cry. Is that strange to anyone?  To conclude my thoughts, let's take a break to the lighter side of things and speak of ballacrosse. I love to play with my friends! It is the greatest game ever. In fact, some day I will post some rules on this site so that all may play. How exciting! haha. Today Scott, Jacob, Kara, Bryan, Brandon and I played for about 2 hours I think. The most intense it has ever been. I only hope to play more ballacrosse all summer long.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's always good to find out that people don't suck as much as you thought. That is all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Having choices really sucks. That means you then become responsible for the outcome of them. You can't say it's not your fault. You can't look like a rebel when breaking them. You can't leave everyone happy when deciding on one over another. The time is coming to start making choices. I must prepare. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I've got half an hour to waste here before going to work, and I thought to myself, what better way to spend 30 minutes than writing about crap in your blog? Good idea, Chris!  so my glasses came in yesterday, and I must say, sucksta. I truly apreciate my contacts for their superior qualities. When you wear a pair of glasses you have to turn your entire head to look out of what might only otherwise be the corner of your eye. I find it quite annoying. but on the upside, it doesn't take a minute to install them. Enough of that, on to something else.  I'm headed in to Best Buy today to try and con one of the managers into giving me an interview. Maybe they'll see me walking in and decide to give me the job right on the spot. Yeah, that's prolly what'll happen... My biggest fear about getting the job would be talking to Sue (my manager over at DQ). I think the ensuing conversation as I gave her my two weeks notice might potentially be deadly. Can't tell for sure though, I only hear things. Damn you, rumors!  Ballacrosse will be this Thursday at 6:00 PM. You should come. I won't be your friend if you don't. Well, maybe, but you'll need to give me a dollar to make up for it.  My brother thinks he is gangster now. What a strange kid. He also spends more time with the Mexican family down the street than with ours. I'm not really depressed about it right now. But when he comes back for school... Even more gangsta rap to feel through the floor boards.. W00T...  I like making new friends sometimes. This feels like one of those days. If I don't know you, maybe we should get together some time. We'll do lunch. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In place of some article of self discovery I've decided to post a story that I think up as we go along here. OK, here goes:  There once was a young lad named Larry. Larry didn't have any friends because he smelled bad. Even invisable friends didn't last long for poor Larry. One day Larry was walking down the street, much to the distaste of the townspeople nearby when somethign amazing occured to him. In order not to smell bad Larry would learn to sew!  Needless to say, Larry was incorrect in his assumption. However, he did now posses a nack for sreating fancy embroyderments onto fine table cloths. He began to sell his items at market in hopes of making human contact, but alas, the only person willing to go ner his tent was an old woman wearing a gas mask.she was quite polite though, and Larry thought to himself, "If only I can be just like that old bag..."  So Larry went off to find a similar mask of his own. From town to town Larry traveled in search of this facial ornament. Eventually he came upon a store called GAS MASKS R U. It was a wonderful shop in the ghetto. All the locals can attest to the handiness of a supermarket where one can get his salads and ammunitions in one convienient setting. So Larry found the gas mask isle and found one he fetlt suited him and was soon back on the road. This time he was being chased by cops because he hadn't paid for the merchandice. Soon Larry became tired and came to a halt where he was promptly run over and then shot.  The moral of the story? Chris is a twisted individual... He needs help and lots of love. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, everyone reading this (Those of you who actually know me in person)…I want you to tell me about the first time you remember seeing me or meeting me and the fondest memory of me you have. Then put this in your journal. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today has been great so far. I went to Target to pick up a couple pairs of underwear and when I get back in the car, my cd player, which I thought was broken, spits out The Darkness (a cd of Jacob's), and it suddenly works again! All I can say is, balla. Yesterday was pretty great too, now that I think about it. In fact, everything seems to be going my way lately. I wonder how long this trend will continue?  On a side note, I'm still waiting for my new set of contacts to come in. What's taking so long? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I just found this drawing. Good memories...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I've made an important realization. I... am... a... follower... A follower?" you ask. Yes, a follower. I do things in order to be one of the group. I change myself to blend in. However, I am no chameleon. I rather consider myself to be a poser. Changing myself to appear as if I am one of you. Upon self discover, I keep finding this not to be true. You and I only have one great commonality. That being the desire for acceptance.  But how do we rid ourselves of this lust for companionship? My first answer would be to have companions. Mission accomplished. Now what? This is the answer that I lack. In an effort to try something new, I've made the decision to stop following people. That includes you. I will not smoke. I will not make fun of others. I will not keep interests in things that I have no interest in. Two monosyllabic words come to mind right now which I feel very well describe my notion. Fuck it. I don't need to worry about what some group thinks anymore, I shouldn't have ever had to.  The time has come to sift through my friends. To see who is and is not worth giving attention to. Those who give acceptance without the accompanying expectations of uniformity within their clickes must truly be the kind of company I desire. However, that may be an impossible persuit... For those who still abide by others rules, I hold nothing against you. I may very well be wrong. Society might only be held together by the bonds we fashion for ourselves. Alternatively, they may be the only walls holding us from reaching a higher level of spiritual achievement. Only time shall tell as we all create our own paths in life.  God, I'd like to have a chat with you when you have a couple minutes... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    As my first picture post I wanted to throw in smething flashy and exciting. Naturally, I turned to my good android buddy here, Yanni. w00t  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just a quick post, if anyone should happen to have either Ms. Denny's IB Language Arts summer reding list or Mrs. Erwins TOK 2 assignment sheet I would greatly appreciate barrowing them to make a copy. Thanks. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>