<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I sat here last night here in Casa de Wootang, I was watching Raw with 2 favorite pals Steve and Johnny for those of you who haven't met Johnny he's slightly more outspoken than me.  He says what's on his mind and says who cares what people think they cant understand me anyway I have CP  Raw Started off with there Usual thing by this I mean Evolution came out (AKA Collection of Old Need to Be retired wrestler who need to be retired and 2 young Muscle heads that are on enough steroids that I cant count that high)!! And What is up with Kane and Lita Come on now do you actually think us red blooded American males are going to fall for something like come on now I am from the swamp and I want even for fall for that one. All though I do a few people who will for that !! And what's up with Bischoff and his so called nephew Eugene I believe that he's trying to portray this character as a person with an innelectual disability personally I think he should've asked for advice from some disability advocates like myself we all know that a person doesn't act like that with a disability like they portray  Who ever reads this post should send them an email And last but not least Major props to that good ole boy Chris Benoit thanks for kicking that big freaks ass Kane and making him tap. Kane you tapped and cried foul afterwards  3 words from good ole Wootang GET OVER IT you lost  Woot 10 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all  I came back from my latest escapade of prewedding family stuff Oh happy happy   The wedding invites are picked out those people who are firends of mine watch mail they will be coming in the coming week or so  Those of you who havent emailed me with current info email me  Looking forward to Vanhalen I owe steveo and his pal jayme have never been to a big name concert in awhile sure wish I knew who opening act will be oh well dont walll kill the anticipation   Although will try not to burn self with a lighter during concert   urlLink    Also am looking at diffrent color schemes for my chair if you have a  sugguestion send them to me   Peace and hair grease   Woot 10
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gee...  Where Do I begin oh well here goes How bout them Pistons   Having said that I will now give you my take on the game all games last night Shaquille Oneal's Last Stand  Well truth be told I never can watch a whole NBA game just never have been a a true 82 game fan but I decide to call a few friends over to "Casa De Wooten" (for those of you who don't know what that is its my apartment here in Albany) After going and making a run for the border and picking up some tacos, I come back and flip on Abc to see whats going on with the game and who are the the two people in the crowd that have actually done something for the music industry in the last 5 years and not 25years Detriot's Own Kid Rock, who I will see one day live might have to rob a bank to go but i will get there Might have to drag my trusty sidekick steveo with me but he will most likely come.  The camera pans to Kid's right and who do you think is sitting on his right  A true Country Singer Hank I hope I dont have to say his last name but in case I do for those of you who dont follow Country music Hank Williams Jr was there!!!  Lets see Jack Nickalson compete with those two!!  I dont think so he was his old pissed off self last night almost fell out laughing at him. Glad to see the Pistons win a championship they havent won one since 1990 thats longer than me and my sidekicks been I alive was in 8th grade at Center Jr High the last time they won!!  That is my take on the game from a slightly mechanically advantaged point of view   Woo10
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I sit here unwinding from another day of my travels through the wraths of The Black Hole AKA Albany Tech was just sitting  here wondering what I can put on my new blog to please my readers and get new hits Hope to be posting somemore new stuff here in the future  "Life is short dont use all your key strokes"  Woo10
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm Making My First Post, essentially just to make it, so that i can have a post up to adjust my settings by! Stay Tuned!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>