<Blog>


<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        right now i am at my auntie's house.. lol. fun fun. sorry bout not being able to write in this lately. i talked to zach friday.. ;)!! i miss him lots and y'all too!! im leaving tomorrow to go to d.c. im soooooooooo excited!!! :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm finally leaving today to go on vaca to Missouri and Washington D.C. I think that I'm going to have lots and lots of fun, espceially in d.c., but I are surely gunna miss everybody!! :( I love you guys!!   Zach:I love you lots and I will miss you lots!! Hope you have fun on your vaca too!! Can't wait to see ya when I get back.. I call ya!! ;)   Court:I love you lots and I will surely miss ya too afterall you are my sis!! ;)   Brett:I love you lots and I'll miss ya too!! I'll be sure to write ya and liz will too! ;)   Josh:I love you lots and I will miss ya lots!! I didn't get to say bye.. sorry!! :(   Thrash:I love ya lots and I'll miss ya too!! Have fun on your vaca too!! ;)   Queas:I love you lots gurl!! I'll miss ya too!! I'm sorry that I didn't get to talk to ya before we left!! :(     To everybody else: I love ya!! I'll miss ya!! ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today I have to go to Birmingham for my eye doctor's appointment. We are suppose to schedule when I am going to have my surgery in July. I'm scared as usual even though it's not going to be that bad. Dad said that Zach could go with us since we are leaving tomorrow for vaca, but I don't know if he can. I ask/told him last night when I was about to leave then his mom came in and asked about it then my surgery and she didn't say whether he could or couldn't so I don't know. But I really hope that I get to see him before I leave bc I will reallly really miss him lots!! I will also miss all of y'all too!! ;)    Last night: I went to Zach's to cook. Liz and Brett couldn't come, so it was just me and Zach. We both went to walmart to pick up all of the stuff and when we looked outside when we got done it was a pouring down rain. So we ran to the car.. lol. We both got soaked. We got home and made the Jumbalyia, that was an adventure.. his mom and dad crack me up!! lol.. then we had dinner then me, Zach, and Wyatt watched Ace Vencura!! ;) Nice and very funny movie!! lol.. well thats all for now.. hope I get to write tomorrow sorry if I don't. Bye~! 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ya know what today is... Cooking Fest at Zach's again, (every Tuesday)!! Except we don't exactly know what to cook tonight.. so that's why I was gunna write this.. anybody got any suggestions? lol.. the first night we cook tostadoes (dont know if i spelled it right) with refried beans, chips, and salsa.. the second night was pizza.. the third night was taco salad.. the fourth night is tonight, lol. ;) hmmm..     **IM LEAVING THURSDAY AND WON'T BE BACK UNTIL THE 16TH OF JULY**   Yeah I'm sure gunna miss everybody!! Zach is going on vaca too.. but they are leaving the day before I get back.. so I miss them by a day.. :( oh well!! I just hope that everybody has a *GrEaT* time on vaca this summer!!     WeLl ThAtS aLl FoLkS!! ;) over and out!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well this morning started off kinda bad. I went to look at the list dad left me and Liz to do, it wasn't bad at all. All we needed to do was do the laundry, water the plants, and for liz to find her wallet. Well.. dad left some clothes in the laundry room it wasn't that much so I figured that they all needed to go in one pile. Well, obviously they didn't and I was wrong and I put them all in the washing machine and I told Liz and she got all mad at me. Well, I'm sorry it's not like I really meant to do it.. and it's not like I knew.. ya know?? I was just trying to help.. :(!! So, please.. *Cross your fingers* so it will all turn out ok.. Thanks!! ;)    Tonight I think I'm going back to Zach's house to watch 50 first dates with him, Brett, and Wyatt. That movie is really good. Last night kind of stunk though.. but I aint gunna say nothin on here bout it. Anyways, I saw Dusty yesterday.. I haven't seen him in forever. I really wanna go see the Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban movie really badly!! I'm leaving Thursday to go to Missouri and D.C. and I ain't gunna be back until the 16th of July!! I'm really gunna miss everybody!! Especially Zach, Brett, Queasha, Josh, Julie, Jess, Wyatt, Courtney, and Thrash!! And all my other friends since I can't put everybody bc it would take forever.. lol!! ;)  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today I have to take my mom to the airport and I'm driving. I have never drove to Huntsville before so I hope that I do good. Happy Fasha's Day to all the fathers out there. I hope y'all have a good day. We aren't doing anything for fasha's day because since is leaving this morning and dad is playing golf today, we went out to eat last night. I'm gunna call Zach later and surprisingly, I actually have something to say.. lol. Today me and Zach have been dating for four months.. go us!! lol.. that's the longest for me. Anyways, I'm not going to the movies anymore tonight so I don't know what I'm doing tonight.. maybe I'll have some new plans who knows. Oatmeal is some good stuff lol. Blah!! I don't really know what else to say. Oh yeah, Court!! I watched 28 Days Later last night after we got back from Huntsville, that is a scary, freaky, and confusing movie.. lol. I was scared to go to bed lol. The other night when I was leaving Zach's after we watched the Texas Chainsaw Massacre I was scared to drive home.. lol. I have to go now.. tah tah for now!! ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       That is how I feel right now.. considering part of July Mountain has NO running water.. woot!! But anyways.. my great uncle Tom doesn't feel well so we aren't going to go over there tonight. Zach called while ago and asked if I could serve for him so I'm going to. Then he said I could go over to his house afterwards.. so I might do that but I don't know yet.    Last night:Fun stuff!!   LoL!! I went over to Zach's and me, him, Trent, Wyatt, and Brett all watched The Texas Chainsaw Massacre. Me, Trent, and Brett have all seen it before.. lol. Wyatt got scared, (awww..). Brett was rubbing/tickling my leg and knee.. lol. But it was fun!! ;)Oh and FYI (we didn't kiss)!!    Well I guess that is all since I don't know what else to say. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today is gunna be a good day. Last night I went over to Zach's to play Man Hunt, that was the funnest game we ever played.. jk lol. Brett kept on telling me to kiss Zach but I got to scared and was like well I don't know. Well apparently Brett told Zach to do the same to me too but he didn't because he even gets scared when he's holding my hands.. lol. So, I got a plan and hope it will work.. but I don't even know why the heck I'm saying this on here but anyways. Today is gunna be a good day. I'm going to movie gallery sometime and picking out some scary movies because I'm going to Zach's again and me, Trent, Brett, and Zach are all gunna watch movies.. Courtney if ya wanna come ya prolly could say I invited ya ;)!! Me and Trent talked about movies last night and we have no clue. I looked this morning but I could was "Children of the Corn", "The Birds", and "The Haunting" and I don't know if they will like any of them so I don't know. I'm hungry.. lol. I'm talking to Phillip at the moment. Hey Philla!! My neck really hurts bad and I don't know why. Lalalalalalalala...BLAH!! Anyways, if y'all can think of a scary movie just call me or send a message. Have a *good* day. I love you all very much!! ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        First I got up at like 9:30.. (that's early for me), then I took and shower and got ready and sutff then left. I went to Movie Gallery to drop off the movies, Walmart to buy the stuff on hte lists, then I went to Kim San.. I *LOVE* Chinese food..lol. ;) Now, I'm here eating my Chinese food and talking to my good friend "Thrash". Ha, I mentioned ya!! ;) Much love to everybody and have a good day today!! Adios!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was so boring that I have no idea of what to do tomorrow. I was talking to Courtney earlier about what to do. I have to go to Walmart for sure. I also want to go to Kim San and pick up something to eat and go to movie gallery to drop off the movies and pick up some new ones!! ;) Well that's all I guess for now.. y'all sleep tight!! Luv ya's!! ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey there! Sup everybody? I'm just listening to Ashlee Simpson!! Today has been ok I guess. I didn't really do anything besides go to walmart and buy a cd. I called Zach to see if him and Brett could go skate at the High School, but Zach couldn't. Last night me and Liz went to Zach's to skate. I like skating better than skateboarding.. it's cool. I used Liz's old ones and they are bad, but oh well..lol. I can do a toe/heel mannual!! Hmmm.... I don't know what the heck else to say, oh yeah!! Zach gave me this cute ankle bracelet and he also gave me a t-shirt that is so totally awesome..lol. ;)  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey y'all!! I'm back home and I'm so excited!! I missed everybody soo much!!  Um.. let's see. We went inside the White House and we got to see the vice president.. that was awesome!! I saw the movies "The Terminal" and "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban". They are good good movies!! ;) I talked to Zach and I bought him stuff. I missed him soo soo soo much!! He is on vaca now and won't be back til the 20th of July which isn't bad, but I haven't seen him for about a month. Brett is over at my house right now and him and Liz are playing a game on the xbox. I don't really know  what else to say.. sooooo later gators!!!!     
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       We arrived here on Monday and now it is Thursday. We have been having fun so far. We went to the Holocaust Musuem, Union Station, Air and Space Musuem, Vietnam Memorial, Veterans Memorial, Navy Archives, Jefferson Memorial, Lincoln Memorial, Kennedy Memorial, Old Post Office, Capitol, and we are going to see the White House (acually go inside it), and the Washington Monument tomorrow. Fun Fun!!   Right now I'm in an apartment! lol.. I just got through swimming. I miss my Zachary soo much!! I just wanna go home! I bought some new clothes today. Mom let me and Liz drink the other night so we actually have had alcohol. Um.. I'm trying to think here. I met some new kids.. Julie, Amanda, and Richard and they are sooo awesome and sooo nice!! ;) They live in Huntsville which is cool. Well kidos.... I guess I'll go.. adios!! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>