<Blog>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      By: Mariel G. Calalo (September 3, 2003) *Something  almost  autobiographical.  Just when he thought I didn't see, I caught a glimpse of him and kept that picture forever in my memory. Just when he thought I didn't hear, I was listening with all my heart. Just when he thought I never cared, I spent my days and nights writing about him.   Fourteen months ago, I felt a mad rush for something, which I thought was missing in my life. Most of my friends are either getting married, having kids or getting into serious relationships, while I remain to be the standard bearer of non-committals. I joke around saying that I just needed to find Mr. Right Now, a crash course on romantic relationships, which is supposed to last for two weeks. I thought if only God would send me someone who can be "All Things Good," then maybe, just maybe, I might give it a shot.  Just when I thought that finally finding the guy I want would be the best thing that could happen this year, WOW MALI!   I felt lonely and left out for having a stagnant love life and yet relieved because of one boy, who was there to listen to me as I whined about being unattached.  We would talk about his potentially functional pseudo-relationships, mutual understanding agreements, and my general disappointment on the male species, which I was always my reason for choosing to be unattached. We console ourselves saying that we are better off unattached than to be in a relationship that we can never survive. We convinced ourselves that being alone. In fact, it has it's advantages like not having to consider anybody when you make one of those life's major decisions, mas matipid at least pang isang tao lang binabayaran mo sa sine at sa kain, wala kang anak na pinapaaral and other seemingly cynical remarks.  While some of my friends have become married smugs, this boy to me was life the beacon of hope who keeps on reminding me that being unattached isn't exactly a lonely place to be in on the 21st century. In between coffee, second-hand smoke and glutonny, I jokingly told him that the last hing I want is to end up with a guy like him. Though I considered him as one of the closest guy friends I've got around, I totally loathe his attitude about relationships --- never committing, always denying. No expectations. No promises. I've known him for four long years and I just thought I had him figured out.  I believed that some people are meant to be together, while some people are meant to be alone. I was so resigned to the idea that I belong to the second set of people. I was prepared to face the future alone.  For four long years, I didn't feel any sort of attraction, physical or otherwise. At that time, I enjoyed his company but never once did I felt emotionally drawn to him --- until recently.  It started out like any of out psycho babbles about failed relationships. It was a rainy Friday night and we had nowhere else to go, so we just wasted time chatting about our own emotional woes. He opened up in a way that he has not done before. This time, he was honestly talking about his own failed relationship. There was something different about the tone of his voice, a certain sadness that I've never sensed before. For a moment I could feel his pain. There was just something about the things he said  that night that kicked some sense into me.  Hearing him talk about a girl he once loved like hell gave me a shiver. I felt fear... Fear that one day he just might decide to decide to risk all hell to be with her, and the very thought of him promising forever with all certainty to another girl was revolting. I was almost shattered and the a lump was on my throat.  I wanted to cry but no tears came down from my eyes. I kept my composure. I felt confused. Could I have loved him all this time and never knew it? Did I realize it too late? We never talked about it again. In fact, after feeling what I felt that night, I decided not to spend as much time with him as I used to.  After a hundred gloomy days and sleepless nights, thinking about that one incident, I seemed fine. I am convincing myself that maybe, just maybe, I was just confused. I was perhaps of moving forward and being left alone. I was in denial. The time I spent apart from him, I prayed and contemplated about my feelings for him. Not a single day went by that I didn't miss him.  Now I am sure, I love him. I realized that during those times when I absolutely didn't make any sense, he was the only person who kicked sense into me. I realized that during those times when I felt absolutely alone, he was there to make me laugh and smile. I realized that while teh world saw him as this emotional git, in my world of swirling mass of contradictions, he was my hope.  I never thought that I could love as much as I love him. I never thought that I could be this scared to say I Love You or even imagine loving this much. Worse, not being brave enough, prepared enough to say it. If and when I do find the courage to say what I feel, would he reciprocate my feelings? Perhaps not, for I am complicated for his own good. I am a maverick... and I have already made it difficult, if not impossible for him to love me. Now I am hanging by a moment. Not wanting to say what I want to say. Torn in seeing him proceed with his pursuit for happiness. Only time will tell whether this story ends with a happy ending. One thing is for sure, I love him...
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      By: Mariel G. Calalo  Sometimes we live in other people's expectations. We place our happiness in other people's hands. We get caught up chasing these dreams that we fail to realize that we are blessed with so much more.  I have been praying for the longest time for a loving relationship most people my age have. As far as I can see, my current situation is far more conducive for such. I am in my twenties, with a stable job and wihtout what others might term as "complications." As a teeneager, I led myself to believe that I must concentrate on my studies, get a a job and then get a boyfriend. My life was already planned. Be a CPA at 20, boyfriend at 25, marry at 30 and be a mom at 32. Every details has been carefully thought of and only the execution was yet to be done. The orchestration of the greatest plan I have in mind is NOW.  Things went well for a while. I was absolutely sure that when I reach the age of 32, I would look back at my life and say to myself "I have lived my life as planned." I failed to realize one thing. Life is that which happens to you as you plan. Well for the CPA part, it was easy as things were within my are of control. I only needs one person for the plan to push through... ME.  Phase one implemented as planned. I conceived little projects to get my so-called loving relationship. I've held on. I've let to. I've tried almost every rule written on the book. Nothing seemed to work. I fell in and out of love but "The One" was nowhere to be found. I still haven't found that person that would make me want to be a better person, the one that would make my life seem more colorful. I started to feel impatiend and questioned what was wrong with me. I just don't get it. I did everything by the number, of what was expected of me and here I am, still alone.  I was in between heartaches going through my own quarterlife crisis. The that pivotal moment hit me, I had a LIGHTBULB MOMENT.  I realized that life is never gonna be perfect because I am not perfect myself.  Life can never be planned because it is full of wonderful surprises. We must allow spontaneity and serendipity into our lives because most of the time it is in life's unexpected gifts that we find God's most wonderful blessings. While having romantic attachments could sometimes be a blessing, it's never enought to fill the voids that we fiel. One person is not enough to make us feel complete. We need to be complete by ourselves before getting into "The World of Two," otherwise, it would be just a parasitic relationship where the only reason the two of you are together is because you're both insecure. One has to feel secure with himself first before he can actually give security to another.  Sure you can't help feeling sorry for yourself sometimes, we you see couples walking past you, with all your wishful thinking. The thing is, no one can ever pick you up from your sadness but yourself.  If you have a family, a great job, wonderful friends and so much more things to do, then you should feel blessed. It's a less complicated, less "risky" situation to be in. Realizing this, I felt blessed beyond measure, the voids are complete and I AM COMPLETE.   *************************  P.S. I wrote this when I was 23, when I had a wonderful friend who made me realize that life is beautiful. Now he's not so wonderful anymore, it makes me want to sing "Wow! Mali".
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      By: Mariel Calalo  I am 25 years old, an NBSB-ANP (No Boyfriend Since Birth, Alpha No Papa). Always the friend, never the girlfriend. Yup that's me. I guess I am still caught up with my idea of what is ideal, the boyfriend from Utopia. I guess we all want love to come along, it's just that we dictate the package it should come along with. When I was 20, I only asked God for 10 "Must-Have" Traits I'm looking for in a boyfriend. I like to keep things simple because I think it's much easier for God to answer my prayers with a YES, if what I asked for is simple!  Here goes my top 10 back then, in no particular order, with my not-so-brief rationale for each. Brace yourself.   1.  HE SHOULD BE A FRIEND .  I don't believe in the traditional "courtship" our parents knew. I'd like to see a person in the raw, how he truly is. To watch him grow and just be himself. No pretenses. None of the sugar coating. By being friends first, I'd see all the good and the bad in him. And should the friendship be brought to a different plane, then I know what I would be plunging myself into and loving the good and bad in him won't be that difficult to do. Perhaps, being patient and understanding would be much easier to do.  2.  HE SHOULD LOVE AND RESPECT HIS OWN MOTHER AND SISTERS . The best way to see, I believe, to see how he would treat you is to see the way he treats his mom and his sisters. It takes practice to be tender and gentle and I would very much rather if he cultivates these traits by practicing with his mom and sisters. To understand women means to be educated by women.  3.  HE SHOULD KNOW HOW TO HAVE FUN . Imagine how boring life would be if I would end up with a person who only thinks about work. Imagine how life would be like with a person who works even through the weekends. I need somebody who knows how to have fun and knows how to laugh hard. Laid back kinda guy, low key and yet driven. I don't intend to be with an irresponsible ball and chain, but I also don't want to be with a total bore who's highly intellectual but cannot function in the world where normal people live.  4.  HE SHOULD BE ABLE TO MAKE ME LAUGH AND SMILE.  I'm not looking for a clown in a million. I'm not looking for someone who looks so funny I can't help but laugh. I guess what I'm trying to say is that, help me be a happy person. No one can ever make you a happy person but yourself, however, it helps having someone positive and cheerful around.  5.  HE SHOULD BE ABLE TO SURPRISE ME WITH SMALL THINGS.  I guess, I'm not the kind who gets surprised by a diamond ring, or chocolates, or roses. It's the small unexpected gestures that I cherish. Things like carrying my laptop because it's so heavy, asking me if I want water on a really hot summer day, or buying me my happy meal (congee+raddish cake) on a really, really bad day.  I need to be with a person with whom I constantly discover something new everyday. I don't need expensive stuff... I think I can afford those things. All I need is somebody who surprises me with small things... Small things that would make me say "Now, that's my boyfriend!"   6.  SOMEBODY WHO WOULD GLADLY GO TO CHURCH WITH ME.  Catholic or otherwise, it doesn't really matter for as long as he believes in God and has a personal relationship with him (in layman's term, he prays).  7.  HE SHOULD BE FINANCIALLY RESPONSIBLE . Between a rich kid and a financially responsible guy, I'd choose the second one. A rich guy who's not financially responsible ends up penniless because he doesn't understand what his financial priorities should be. I don't want to be in love and in debt all at the same time, I guess.  8.  HE SHOULD DO THE BEST JOB HE KNOWS HOW TO DO.   Of course no one wants to be with a bum. I just want to be with somebody who has a pleasant attitude towards his work.  I need to be with a person who will make me appreciate my work too.  9.  A MAN OF INTEGRITY. Mabigat ata ito. Mahirap hanapin. I guess, I want someone who does what he says and means what he says.  10. LAST AND CERTAINLY NOT THE LEAST, CHUBBY, FAIR, CHINITO AND NEARSIGHTED.  A difficult combination no. Pag yan talaga tinamaan ni Lord, baka hindi lang ako Sunday mag-church, pati Tuesday and Thursday. Why Chubby? I certainly don't want to feel like a make-over project just because he's so vain. Why Fair? Aba iba na ang maputi. Period. Chinito and nearsighted? Don't you just love and hate a moment when a guy's eyes turn into slits as his dimples gloriously show, as the walls of your emotional defenses melt. Ito lang ang logic diyan, ang pangit naman kung may boyfriend ka nga di ka naman kinikilig. The best example I can think of is RJ Ledesma and Robert Chien. = )  Today, at 25, I think hitting 10 out of 10 is like winning the Lotto, 93 million pesos, tax free. Hitting 9 out of 10, is a wonderful blessing. 8 out of 10 is still a wonderful thing to contemplate. 0 out of 10 means, it must be LOVE!
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Being Without You.... By: Mariel Calalo  Being without you felt like being sure the sun would shine and yet feeling unsure whether warmth could be felt.  Being without you felt like being free yet wanting to be isolated, incarcerated.  Being without you felt like having enough air to breathe yet suffocating to death.  Being without you felt like I wanted to smile yet knowing my heart drowns in tears.  Being without you felt like I just won the lottery only to lose my winnings the next day.  Being without you felt like being deaf, blind and unable to express myself... completely helpless.  Being without you felt like it was the most intelligent choice I've made, yet feeling stupid all at the same time.  Being without you means being sleepless in Seattle, freezing in Cincinnati and paranoid about New York.  Being without you taste like congee without soy sauce, coffee without my sugar and cream.  Being without you is scary, sad and quiet.  I guess I never noticed what it was like to be without you. I guess I never took the time to take notice. So come back, make me feel what it's like to be truly free. Turn my nights into days, The cold into warmth. Take away my stupidity. Help me find my courage, my joy and my music. And let me not spend another day of being without you.     
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Gago, Tarantado, Sira Ulo  By: Mariel G. Calalo  She went half way across the world in the hope of finding "the one" only to realize that it was in front of her the whole time. She missed all the signs. She found him... only to lose him again.  She believed in fate, in destiny, in love at first sight. She believed that when she finally finds "the one" She'd  know right away because her heart will just tell her so. Probably, it would be easier to say "yes." Well, her heart's not just stubborn, it's actually dyslexic. "Cold" is an understatement.  Peel her to the core and you would realize that "non-committal" is the more appropriate word to describe her. The first sign of a possible romantic entanglement, and you'd see her running on the opposite direction. Siguro hindi niya lang gusto ng komplikadong buhay. Every attempted I Love You was responded to by "Gago. Tarantado. Sira ulo." She has spent her days waiting for love but afraid of being close where she needs to be the most. She was waiting for lightning, listening for thunder just to finally realize she has  found the one.  Somewhere, thousands of miles from the life she has grown accustomed to live, she did found someone. He was simply perfect. He was warm, friendly, funny, patient, driven yet able to have fun. He wears eyeglasses but even with those spectacles she  just couldn't help but marvel at his deep-set eyes and long, curly eyelashes. He made her laugh  and the things she would normally find annoying in a guy, she found them cute in him. He was a perfect gentleman. He opened doors for her, carried her stuff, he even volunteers to get her water. He was at her beck and call. He was handsome, too handsome it felt like being punched everytime he smiles. Life could not get any better than this; he filled her winter mornings with so much warmth it felt like summer. There were times when she would just gaze, stare, almost in awe, watching him glide among the crowd and convince herself that life could not get any better than this.  She has never met anyone as agreeable as this and there were times when she  wished that she didn't have to go back to her old life. However, at some point, reality had to walk in and she had to say goodbye to this perfect stranger.   Her life has been a long, continuous process of hellos and goodbyes. He accompanied her to the airport and they said their goodbyes. She offered a handshake, instead he asked her if he could hug her goodbye. She was floored. On an ordinary day, she would have said "Bakit??? Gago, tarantado, sira ulo!" He wouldn't understand it anyway so she thought "well, why not?" She took a step forward and he hugged her goodbye. She hugged him back and it was the longest 15 seconds of her life. It was like a near-death experience, seeing her entire life flash before her. At some point in the longest 15 seconds of her life, she somehow wished she was hugging someone else. She wished she was hugging that "gagong tarantadong sira-ulong" she was scared to be with, the one she has always been afraid to hug because she feared she might not let him go if she did. If the only consideration in finding "the one" is her state of bliss when she is with that one person, then the choice would have been easy to make. Resistance is futile. She knew that it had to be that "gagong tarantadong sira-ulo." He had to be "the one."  She spent four hours in the airport trying to understand what just happened to her. First, that was unpredictable of her. Second, it was just so out-of-character for her to just hug a guy she barely knew. She has known someone for five years and she had always made sure he never violates the "1-foot away personal space" rule. Third, it was just so out-of-character for her to miss someone who's not exactly synonymous to the word "good boy", the kind you'd want to bring home to your parents. She has always believed she was too wise for situations like this.  It was confusing. She wanted to get the first flight home because she needed to find out what could be the cause of this anxiety and she's damn sure she's not gonna find it in New York.  It was a long flight going back home. It has given her enough time to contemplate. No matter how much her head argues with her heart, the latter always found a way to win. She knew she had to come home to the uncertainty. She practiced clever lines to say. She wanted to say "I'm sorry for screwin' up. I think leaving you behind had to be a sin." Or "Starbucks in every corner of New York City will never be the same without you." Or "I've just met this incredibly perfect person who's just so handsome it feels like a punch in the face. But you know what? I had to come home to your smile because it feels like soft breeze across my face." She knew life was never gonna be the same without "gago, tarantado, sira ulo." At the back of her mind, she knew, "gago, tarantado, sira ulo" is not exactly like that. There must be something, so much more, that she refused to see the last time she looked at him. She didn't want to be a fool wondering what might have been. Maybe, just maybe, this time she'll say "yes."   For the first time, she allowed her heart to see. She had seen him too many times before but never really SAW him. As soon as she got the chance, she asked how has he been getting along with life, waiting and hoping for him to tell her how much he missed her. Apparently, he was getting along without her very well. And missing her never crossed his mind, not for one moment. And so, in the moment of truth in every lie, she decided to stay silent. She decided not to say any of the lines she practiced. She chose to leave them unsaid. What is the point of saying the truth if nothing could be changed? What is the point of saying the truth if the truth would only cause pain? There are certain things in this world that are better left unsaid, things left undone, thoughts left somewhere in the back of your mind, never to be thought of again.  She wanted to believe that life is better off uncomplicated.  The problem with this story is that it ends right where it should begin. Perhaps, someday when love outweighs  fears, when certainty is far stronger than the shadows of doubt, when faith and hope rings true, this story will have the ending it deserves. Until then, both characters continue being lost in the limbo waiting for lightning, listening for thunder, praying for love to come their way.   
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Things I Learned From Intergender Frienships By: Mariel G. Calalo  The premise of this article lies on the principle that sometimes, loving a person doesn't mean it has to be romantic and loving a person for the rest of your life doesn't mean you have to end up marrying them. Can a man and a woman just be friends? I'd say YES and THEY SHOULD BE.  Kung Ako Na Lang Sana is a story of a barkada in their college days as we witness their lives from their early 20's to their 40's. Among the barkada, the movie focuses on two individuals EMMY (Sharon Cuneta), a manang type who is domineering and focused on her career, and VINCE (Aga Muhlach), the cool chickboy who is laid-back and has a stoic attitude towards life until much later in his adult years.   Emmy and Vince started out as casual friends until parallel events in their lives drew them closer to later become the best of friends. Even if they weren't physically close and not constantly communicating, they still manage to affect and influence each other's lives. This is when they find themselves falling in love with each other. With the fear of losing their friendship, they chose not to let each other know of how they really feel…until much later on. Familiarity breeds both contempt for these two friends, but love gets the better of both of them.   I cried buckets of tears when I watched this movie. I cried because I can relate with Emmy. I cried because I know it's just a movie, pop culture at it's finest. I cried everytime Aga smiled. I cried every time familiar lines were delivered. I cried because if I had been watching this movie with my college barkada, they would remind me that they truly believe that I should end up with someone like Vince. The day I watched this movie, I would have probably agreed with them.  I cried because I know that as similar as I am with Emmy, my life is not a Star Cinema Production. The guy friend I was with while watching this movie, is no closer to Aga Muhlach. He can't even relate to Aga. Instead, he wants to be Sharon and he wants Aga... badly.  The movie left me lovesick for days.   Here are some of life's lessons... Precious lessons I learned from intergender friendships. Very different from how Star Cinema depicted platonic relationships... but I'm sure you can't help but agree with me.  THINGS I LEARNED FROM INTERGENDER FRIENDSHIPS  HINDI DAHIL KINAIBIGAN KA, LILIGAWAN KA NA. Not every guy who befriends you has an ulterior motive. Get over yourself. Don't flatter yourself. There is a reason why he befriended you, but don't automatically assume that it's because he wants to be your so-called boyfriend. If this will be the principle you'll follow everytime someone asks you to be his friend, you're gonna miss a great deal from the friendship. HINDI DAHIL MABAIT SA IYO, NILILIGAWAN KA NA. There are people who are naturally sweet and kind. There are people who are innately good and that no matter how wicked you seem, they just find it so easy to be kind to you. It doesn't mean he is courting you. Don't put yourself through unnecessary stress trying to figure out if he's courting you or not. Because I think if he is, you won't have to guess, you'll know and you'll be very certain about it. HINDI DAHIL HE TALKS TO YOU A LOT, HE LOVES YOU NA. You don't befriend a person if you absolutely abhor him, right? Chances are you make sense when he talks to you, or you're probably very patient listening to him. The two of you probably connect on some level but why does it always have to be assumed to be romantic? Being two intelligent, mature human beings, you need to accept that it's nice to share a cup of coffee over a stimulating conversation, and that you don't have to automatically put romantic connotation to it. Relieve yourself of the pressure. It's just coffee and a shared interest. HINDI DAHIL CUTE ANG FRIEND MO, CRUSH/LOVE MO NA SIYA. This is the most amusing thing that hit me lately. People always assume that because your friend is cute or should I say, HOT (because cute is a word you describe your high school crush while HOT is a word you use to describe a hunk), "lakas amats mo na for repapips!" Let me just say this, at least from my own personal experience, I'm just nearsighted, I haven't gone blind. I can still appreciate God's creation! However, there will always be weird things, crazy things, stupid things that will keep you, believe me, from having a crush on him. First of all, you'd know his history with women, enough to judge what's good for you. Second, don't you just hate it when a guy who's absolutely always put together, who looks intelligent enough pronounces the word Country as "Kawntri" and the word Mango as "meynggo." Call me crazy for judging a person just because he can't pronounce these words right. I admit, I'm crazy. HINDI DAHIL YOU HANG-OUT WITH EACH OTHER MOST OF THE TIME, YOU'D END UP BEING BOYFRIEND-GIRLFRIEND. Self-explanatory... There are a thousand, no million different reasons why things don't always turn out that way. There is no one proven formula. For all we know, the reason why he likes hanging out with you is because he likes getting kikay tips from you. He probably plans on being kikay himself and he needs a mentor. A DINNER WITH A GUY FRIEND DOES NOT NECESSARILY EQUATE TO A DATE. Especially if you're paying for your share no. Hello? Three things to consider: the place, the topic and how the two of you actually planned to meet. First, how it was planned. If it were a date expect that he would ask you out at least three days before the actual date to give you some lead time, to give you the notion that you are not just a filler on his schedule. Second, the place. If it were a real date, the both of you would want real food and a place where you could really talk things through. Don't go out with a guy to a movie on Friday night if you're really serious about him. Going to a movie is more like treating him like a "filler" just because you had nothing to do on a Friday night so you might as well go out.  Topic. Ha! You wouldn't be talking about chikang artista, chikang opisina, or argue if the one girl's boobs are real or not. You would be probably talking about sensible, quite personal stuff.  I, therefore, conclude that platonic relationships are never complicated, people just have tendencies to complicate them. 
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I Choose... By: Mariel G. Calalo  I choose to love you in my silence, for in  silence I feel no rejection. I choose to love you in my loneliness, for in  loneliness, no one owns you but me. I choose to love you from afar, for having you  near would never let my heart let you go without  shedding a tear. I choose to love you despite of what people say  about you, for I know you in your entirety. I choose to love you even on days when you are  absolutely unlovable, for I love the good and the  wicked in you. I choose to love you even if those wrinkles start  to show and those muscles sag, for I know that  the years have just shown me how you've grown in  beauty and bloom. I choose to love you as a friend, for friendship  is  a far stronger bond than romance and  passion. I choose to love you for all sorts of reasons. I  choose to love the way you talk, the way you  walk, the way you smile, the way you complain. I choose to love the quirky little things about  you, your verbal mishaps, and on days when you'd  make me cry, I'd still love you just the same. I choose to love you despite of you childish  ways, for I believe one day, someday you'll come  through shining. I choose to love you even if your heart breaks,  cries for somebody else, for my love I give  without expecting anything in return.  I choose to love you, silently, in solitude, from  afar... even if it means being lost in the limbo.  I choose to love you today, tomorrow... forever,  for once you start loving a person, you never  stop loving them. Maybe a little differently or a  little less but you never, never stop loving them. 
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ALWAYS THE FRIEND NEVER THE GIRLFRIEND  By: Mariel G. Calalo  It's sad that I had to fall for a friend. I gave my heart when all that's needed was my hand. I gave my love when all that was needed was my friendship. I have always been the friend... Yet surprisingly, never the girlfriend. Yup. That's me. Always the friend and never the girlfriend. Funny, while platonic-turned-romantic relationship works for other people, I can't seem to get that to work for me.   Sometimes, my guy friends even doubt my own "sexual preference" because at my age of 24, I've never had a real relationship with a guy. I guess the world expects certain events to come at certain ages... Hmmm... like a boyfriend in your twenties...  Some of them (the bravest and the curious, I guess) have tried the tender trap of being "friends today, more than friends tomorrow." That trick never got to me though. Just when I am close to falling, something happens, just enough to disrupt the momentum.  I'd like to believe that I have a healthy ratio of single, available, "crushable" (if not adorable) guy friends.  "Crushable?" Hmmm... Well, let's just say that these guys are classified by the greater majority of the female population as "every-girl's-dream-come-true"... Typical young urban professionals... Guys who are techy, wear preppy clothes, nice cellphones, nice cars, hunky, "bootylicious(?)"... Good boy image.  Oops! Did I say good boy image? I guess that's how other people see my "crushable" friends... Good boys... "The" few good men left in this planet... Hahaha...In fairness, some of them are...But with some of them, I know better.   So much has been written on the hang-ups of being a "girl friend material."  But I am telling you from the POV of a true-blue girl friend material, the advantages outweigh the disadvantages.  These guys have a lot of "stuff" going on under their sleeves. I am Yoda. I am the Godfather (Godmother, rather). I am the "Confidante." Being the "Confidante" comes with being a true-blue girl friend material. It is a big privilege because by nature, guys don't really open up about romantic stuff (kuno)... Not even to their unsuspecting girlfriends... a privilege, indeed, to be able to take a peek of what goes on inside the mind (and heart) of the "good boy."  Taking a "peek" opens you to two possibilities, though... Either you look at that person in a way you have never looked at him before. He'd earn your highest respects or worst case scenario, fall for the guy if he does turn out to be the conventional good boy he poses to be... Or you could end up being cynical about men such that you look at them as lower level organisms and bottom-dwellers, if it turns out that a "good boy image" is all that there is to them.  Okay... so how do you know if you are a true-blue girl friend material? Well, I guess if these circumstances often happen to you, chances are, you are a "girl friend material.  Your guy friend breaks up with the irritatingly perfect girlfriend and guess who he runs to for "venting?" Or the irritatingly perfect girlfriend leaves him for some other bootylicious guy, guess who he runs to for "comfort and ego-boosting words?" Ha! I knew it... You. He calls you every night to tell you he's mending his broken heart... and a few weeks later he calls you tell you of the countless dates he's been having to help him get over her.  The moment his "prospect" officially declares "sila na" you'd be the first person he would call to tell this three tragic words to... "Pare, kami na!"... Ouch! Yes, you are his ever reliable "Pare."  Kaibigang iniiyakan, pero di hinahagkan. Kaibigang kinakausap pero hindi niyayakap. I guess it becomes tragic only if you have fallen for the tender trap.  Sometimes, it's not really a trap (guys will have to agree with me).  Maybe he really is just sweet-natured and caring... And you, the assuming little creature, convinced yourself that there's really more to his actions than what they really are.    He is suddenly metamorphosed (at least inside your head, from the boy barkada to the crush boy.  And what's more tragic, now that you have fallen so deep in love with him... Friendship is really all that he can offer. At some point, during your lowest, most confusing, most vulnerable moment, you wanted to ask him "IF I had not been me, and if you had not been you... Do you think you even consider me a "potential?" or just blatantly blurt out "Damn! You should have chosen me instead."  But then, you are much too embarassed to ask and too scared to even try...   Just when you thought those actions are enough to make you believe that this one's "in the bag..." The music stops. Everything that was once animated, suddenly looked bare and common. Reality steps in, the dreaming, the anticipation just stops.    The thing about men is that they are so mathematical when it comes to relationships. No matter how sweet this boy could be... sweet enough to give you diabetes... Unless you are asked to take a chance on him... Unless you are asked to be his girlfriend... Unless everything is in "black and white"... Never... Ever expect.  More than being the seemingly perfect crush boy, he is just human. Like girls, guys are also flaky. They could be judging you a "potential" in one minute... A "Pare" in another.  Assume that their love is written on sand instead of stone, can be blown away by the wind, washed away by the sea.  In fact, some of them like having a "Pantawid-Gutom" around them...Someone who can satisfy their emotional needs without the perks and demands of being in a real relationship. This is more of what you call "Hassle-Free Vendo of Opportunity."  I am not undermining friendships between males and females...straightforward friendships are healthy but unless you can be a friend without ever wanting to be more than that, do not forge dangerous liasons... Exercise caution.  Unless you are willing to take the risk of free falling for a person who can never reciprocate your feelings, be objective with the way you see things.  And a word of caution to "metamorphosed barkada boys to crush boys"... If you do not want your "girl barkada" to assume things you wouldn't want them to assume... If you do not intend to disappoint them... If you do not wish for them to think of you differently, please do not give them a reason to. =)  
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Love is Like Shopping for Shoes By: Mariel Calalo  It is a truth universally acknowledged that a girl in possession of a mid-year bonus must be in search of the perfect shoes. People consider shopping as a complete waste of time... But for me, I have learned love's greatest lessons from shopping.  I consider Glorietta-Greenbelt-SM-Landmark chain of establishments as my home away from home.  I practically buy most of the stuff there. Sales people in those shops where I buy my "kikay" stuff are practically on first name basis with me.  If there is any part of shopping that I enjoy the most, it would be shopping for the shoes.  Shopping for shoes is something I consider sacred. Shopping for shoes requires commitment, commitment of your resources to get the best shoes your resources can afford.  I like shopping for shoes alone because it gives me the freedom to choose the shoes without having to worry what people think about it.  It gives me the freedom to decide based on my idea of a good pair of shoes, and not based on what other people think the perfect shoes should essentially have.  After months of waiting for the midyear bonus, I finally got it. Now it is time to pack my bag and head for my Glorietta to hunt for the perfect shoes.  I don't plan to spend my entire bonus on shoes. I only wanted to buy one pair of black leather shoes... The pair I'm going to wear daily to the office. Hmmm, it should be sophisticated enough for the office and yet, comfortable enough for daily wear.  I guess I have a fairly good idea of what I would like to buy. Since I normally wear pants to the office, a good pair of boots will do.   So I set off to the first shop I could find. I scanned the shop for the shoe I would like to buy. Well, no boots here but I sure fancy the mules. I just had to try them on... So I asked the sales lady for my size, fitted the shoe and walked in it back and forth. Well, the mule was sophisticated enough for the office but the heels are killing me. I can imagine myself wearing this but the thing is I can't wear it for a long time, how much more wear it daily? I knew this shoe was just not it. Moving on to the next shop, I found a great pair of black leather shoes, asked the sales lady for my size and fitted the pair. It's a great pair alright, but when I looked at the tag price... My budget will be busted. It's price is thrice of how much I currently have.  It's a good pair but I think I can do without it, if it means busting my budget. A part of me feels bad because I think this is a good buy... But overspending isn't what I have planned for my shopping activity for this particular day.  So I hop from shop to shop, finding shoes of different sorts, some of them almost the same as what I have in mind, but then something is not quite "it." I went back to some of the shops I went to a while back, fitted the same shoes I fitted before, thinking to myself that maybe I need to give these shoes a second look to convince me that I ought to buy them.  By 3:00 pm of that Saturday, I felt exhausted and frustrated. I wanted to buy a great pair and I just couldn't find one.  It's either I totally don't like the style or the fit or I totally don't like the price.  I told myself "just buy a pair! Whatever pair and go home!" For a minute, I wanted to agree with my sore feet. Yeah, maybe I should just buy a pair for the sake of buying, wear it once in a while and get on with my life. However, when I think about not getting my money's worth by buying something that would not completely fit what my idea of great shoe find would be... I just couldn't buy a shoe for the sake of buying.  Perhaps I haven't seen all the shops... Just when I was ready to give up and go home with a box of donuts instead of a box of shoes... There they were... A pair of black leather wedge boots... Great for slacks and denim... I knew I just had to try this pair. So again, I ordered for my size and fitted the pair. Yes! This pair is perfect. They're comfortable enough to be worn for more that 8 hours a day, sophisticated enough...  I checked the price... Hmmm, exactly fitting my budget criteria.  I just knew the moment I fitted this pair that I just got to have them. I just knew that if I'd come back tomorrow in this shop and not find this pair, I'd be regretting it until the next bonus. I just need to purchase this pair... NOW.  Shopping for shoes is much like finding love. Don't try to fit it if you're not going to buy it. Don't buy it if you have reservations. Don't buy it when it's "almost but not quite." You judge the best pair based on your own criteria because you will be the one to wear it everyday. When you buy a pair of shoes, you need to be commited, at least, your feet should be committed to wear them, if needed, daily. And when you finally get the perfect pair, and you know you just can't do without this pair... Go for it before you actually regret it when somebody else buys that shoe.   
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Unconvetional Choices By: Mariel Calalo  	Sometimes, there are small things we only hear from one person; most of the time those small things are enough to fill the voids in our hearts.  Somewhere in between heartaches, I found the imperfect, the complicated and the unconvetional beautiful, thrilling and comforting. Surprisingly, I felt the most undefined kind of love in my life.  	I met Heath when I was 20.  My first impression of him was not exactly favorable.  I've always seen him as flirtatious, exagerrated, narcisstic and immature.  I've always preferred the goody-two-shoe-kind-of-guys.  Obviously, Heath was not my type of guy. I've always believed that guys like Heath don't really fall in love.  They only play with love. I believed there is no way I could ever fall for a guy like Heath.  I was certain my heart was safe.  	Time passed, Heath and I became good friends. I still see him as flirtatious...but I saw some goodness in him.  When some goody-two-shoe guy broke my heart, he was there to let me crash and burn.  He was there to listen to my foolish talks. He was there to let me be myself in the face of defeat. He was there to let me speak my mind. He sympathizes, he wallows with me... He was just there... to be the friend that he is.    	Getting over Mr. Goody-Two-Shoe was not exactly the easiest thing to do.  I would have dark days of despair.  Thanks to Heath's willingness to stand by me as I go through it, I was able to survive those days, with my sanity intact.  He would be there to make me laugh when I needed to have a good one.  He would be there whenever I would have those so-called "quarterlife crises", always reminding me that life is beautiful... That I still have a long way to go... That I am not alone. He was my wonderwall.  	Sometimes, his presence is so comforting that I felt like he was the older brother I never had.  He was caring, protective and genuinely concerned.  I felt blessed beyond measure.  I have a friend and a brother to whom I can share my thoughts, my fears, my pains, my joys, my success... I have friend who lets me be myself... We all have our evil selves; he knows mine and he doesn't care. He loves me as a friend and as a sister. I still see him as flirtatious, though.  	Things were going great for a while.  I was happy and contented with this straightforward friendship that I had with Heath.  I was contented to hear of his flings and dates, and I was thankful that I was spared being on the long list of women who had their hearts broken by this vagabond.  Things were stable, ideal and conventional until the night he bared his heart.  	I was down with a cold on a Friday night. He started the conversation which eventually led to a confession I've never thought I would hear from him. Looks like I am not the only one nursing a broken heart. My dear friend Heath fell really hard for this girl. Unfortunately, the girl had other priorities and had to go to the States to pursue what she believed was the best for her.  Now he doesn't know whether to follow her of to stay. For the first time, in a while, I felt my heart twitched. I felt bad for my friend... I've been there... devastated, flat, broken and wasted... The only thing I can offer was to be strong for him as he was with me. He stopped being flirtatious... He said even if he flirts till it hurts, it doesn't make him happy knowing that the only girl he ever loved was  thousands of miles away.  	Days passed, we continued being there for each other as we both nurse our broken hearts.  The complicated thing is, as I get closer to him, the more real he becomes. Everyday he unfolds before me and all I can see is the beauty of his heart.  Heath has is actually a good-natured person, honest, trustworthy, reliable... I don't know... but he just leaves me wonderfully depressed and confused.  I'm seeing him in a way that I have never seen before.  I have always looked at him...but never really saw him. He is my friend and trusted me with his deepest secrets but here I am feeling something I am not supposed to feel for him. I beginning to love him in a romantic, totally non-platonic way.  	Though I was 99.99% sure I would never fall for him... The .01% was just triggered by the string of events that have taken over our lives. Sometimes, he would look at me and asks what's the problem... How can I tell him that the problem is him and the feelings that I have for him?  I've always thought it would be easy for me since we have this open communication, this connection that I have never had with any of my other friends... Alas, it wasn't easy. Everyday, I had to come home feeling happy because of the light moments, wonderful conversations, fun and laughter we had for the day... but I also had to remind myself not to expect.  I had to continually remind myself that yes, he does love me...as he would a sister and a friend.  	Now I am lost again... I am confused with my feelings for him. I don't exactly want him to be my boyfriend, but I do know that I would hate for him to find someone that he really loved because that would mean I would lose him.  His priorities would change and I would be in the secondary list. It's unconventional to say, but I like this limbo that I am in.  It feels like the scariest roller coaster ride I've ever had, and yet I don't want to get off, because it is both thrilling and fearsome.It gives me that adrenalin rush... It was the most wonderful feeling I've ever felt.  	One day, someday I know I'll be able to tell him everything... This is probably just a phase I'm going through.  Maybe his presence has become too comfortable that I misconstrued my feelings for him as love.  I know perfectly that if I told him everything now, our friendship would never be the same. Is that something I want to risk? Honestly I don't know. His friendship is one of those very few friendships I'd like to keep 'till my dying days so to risk losing this friend is something I don't even want to think about.  For now I shall stay in this limbo that I am in... choosing to free fall with this unconventional choice, hoping that the good things we have now becomes better. 	
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      God hides things by putting them near us. If at first you didn't see, look again and you might find love... at second sight.  So there you are telling the whole world that you'll never get married... that you will never let any girl catch your heart, make it a prisoner and order you around like your own mother did when you were seven. You'd never subject yourself to the torment of love, to the agony of loving another person, to the risk of giving another person to hurt your feelings and break your heart. You treat dating as a sport, people loving you as conquest. Everytime you think about committing, you think about all the other girls you've never dated.  Eveytime you think about spending each day of the rest of your life with only one woman, you want to run for your life.You were never emotionally vulnerable. You were always logical and mathematical. You never allowed people to really hear you say what loving and living is all about for you. You never defined your own measure of happiness. You just live your life in the here and now, having a ball, and believing you are living it to the fullest. You tell yourself that you can do what you want, buy what you want, be where you want to be. This is the kind of happiness, the kind of success you believe in.   There are nights, however, when you feel empty, incomplete and lonely. You have your party friends, but you knew they were not genuinely interested to listen why you feel this way. Your circle of so-called friends just don't have the time and energy to listen to your whining. There are days when you don't want to go out and party 'till dawn, days when all you want to do is hangout at home and have a quiet meal with people who are geniunely interested to hear how your day went, good or bad they want to listen to you. There are days when you know it's most economical for you to stay single so as to support your expensive, party-till-your-head-hurts lifestyle... and yet, there are days when all you wanted was to find someone to come home to, someone who thinks it's her joy to hand you an aspirin when you're stone drunk and could barely make it to the door. Well, if at first you didn't see, look again...  There just might be someone who loves you unconditionally, loves you even if you smoke like a train and drink like a fish. There just might be someone who loves you enough to wait for you to come home stone drunk at two in the morning and not throw pans and dishes on you, who thinks handing you that aspirin when you've got the worse hangover as one of her life's simple pleasures. There just might be someone patient enough to listen to you complain how bad your day was, hug you at times when other people would have skinned you alive, and give you silence when you should have been nagged. There just might be someone who thinks the mere image of you smiling back at her is enough to give warmth to her heart. There must be someone who's joy is to pack your luggage when you need to go away on business trips, drive you to the airport and pick you up when you come home... such that you'll think the best part of the trip was coming home to her. There must be someone who can drive you nuts with her irrationality and complex personality and yet you would still believe that she was the best thing that ever hit you. There must be someone out there, other than your mother,  who would be willing to love you on days when you make a big fool of yourself and are totally unlovable. There must be someone who's willing to risk her heart just to believe that you can be a wonderful blessing in her life such that she'll love her mother-in-law more than she loves her own, just for bringing you into this world. There must be someone so amazing, so wonderful, so incredible that you can't imagine what life was before her.  Look again, and look around because she could be anyone. Look again because you would be a fool to leave someone like her out there, alone. She could be out there searching for you as well, feeling empty and lonely and as jaded as  your are. Or she could be beside you now, waiting for you to be the best person you can be. Look intently so that you don't miss the signs. Don't be afraid to gaze and find yourself seeing forever in her eyes. Don't be afraid to feel vulnerable, to risk your heart and expose yourself to the possibility of feeling pain. Open the doors of your heart to the countless possibilities that abound. Look again and you just might find love... at second sight.
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Of Love and Coffee By: Mariel Calalo  What is it about coffee that makes people have great conversations and "Aha! Moments?" Brewing coffee is much like concocting love... except maybe the latter may be much more complicated. This article is about finding love, losing it and possibly finding it again, in the eyes of a self-confessed caffeine-addicted writer.  In order to concoct the best love story, you will need the following ingredients: 1 liter water, purified of all doubts, past hurts,insecurities and emotional baggages 1 cup of grounded coffee beans, bursting with flavor and aroma of a potentially functional romantic relationship grounded on solid friendship Sweetener composed of promises made and kept, thoughtfulness and unwavering commitment. Bring to a boil... This could take from 2 weeks to 2 years, even 2 decades. Hey! Love stories like these don't happen overnight. It's a slow process to ensure that the boiling water extracts the exquisite flavor from your coffee beans...the aroma stimulating your olfactory nerves. Sometimes it could be slow to the point of madness... a love that is not based on first sight but a love realized after so much "sights" and analysis, sometimes even overanalysis. Sweeten as needed by text messages with animated bears and smileys, romantic comedy analysis, constant communication and mushy theme songs played over and ovet as you drive home. And this will guarantee you an "espresso perfect romance", right? Well, not quite.  Sometimes, no matter how much you follow this instruction to the last letter, things don't pan out the way you planned and pictured them to be. The boy who gladly shared "after seven Starbucks Moment" (moments of extreme pressure, disappointments... low, sad moments in general) is nowhere to be found. Possibly, he's out there screwing up. You suddenly realize that you are no longer needed because everything in his life is going great & he doesn't need you for "after seven Starbucks Moments"... and what's left in your mug is a day-old coffee, cold and stale. Your initial reaction was to reheat your espresso. You cry and pray to God for an instant replay of your so-called potentially functional relationship... and all that might have been. All to no avail.  So what's a girl to do? You wipe away your tears, take your half-filled cup of stale espresso, throw away your espresso and wash the cup to remove yesterday's coffee stains. Take another liter of water, your coffee beans and your sugar. Brew a fresh batch and while you do, close your eyes and savor the aroma of your fresh coffee. And as you sip your freshly brewed coffee, you'll realize that throwing away yesterday's espresso was a good thing to do, otherwise you won't be enjoying this fresh cup. In terms of love, you'd realize that by ditching the jerk, you actually did  yourself a favor. You'd realize that you're not going to settle for that jerk, nor kiss a bunch of other losers. You'd realize that savoring this freshly brewed cup feels like coming home... Whether it's the coffee or the person in front of you, in your heart of hearts,you're convinced that THIS IS WORTH ALL THE WHILE I WASTED WAITING.
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In love and basketball By Klariz Randee Valdepeñas YOU contributor  NEARLY four years ago, I fell for this guy. I thought that my feelings would at least be reciprocated. But I guess God didn't want him to fall for me because then I would be so in love I wouldn't know what to do. So maybe God kept it that way. Me waiting, expecting something to turn out, and him so clueless of what I feel for him. Stupid, really... but hey! I'm only human. For months, years even, I tried very hard to hold on to the smallest thing that gave me a bit of hope that somehow, somewhere in his heart, I have a space. It's a mixture of feelings... one side of me trying very hard to make me believe that he likes me, and the other saying mainly that I wasn't his type. It was hard for me to be so near to him yet I couldn't even hold him. It was even harder when I was so heartbroken and he was asking why. I mean, how could you possibly tell the person that he broke your heart? He'd probably laugh at me. Imagine the humiliation. Somewhere along the way, I lost hope. I don't know what really happened. Maybe I got tired of waiting… maybe I lost him… maybe I was hurt in the process. I opened my heart to this person. My whole heart. And unknowingly, he came in. And all so suddenly, he went out. I don't know where he went. He just went out. Maybe he didn't like the way I wrote his whole name in it. I was hurt. I guess I'm still a bit hurt. He hurt me so bad I didn't know what to do after that. I needed a diversion, an outlet. Something that would keep my mind from thinking about him. Something that would help my day go by. Basketball. I trained. I played. I failed. Again. Heartbreak. At some point, I began to hate my coach. Maybe I still hate him so. But the game for him was a game that needs winning, a game of perfection -- no room for mistakes. My game would be a game of passion. I'm not like them. They who are molded to play the game. I hated my coach so much he disgusts me! He still does when I look at our pictures. I believe he doesn't belong with us. Our team plays with our hearts. After every practice, every game, our hearts are wounded. Coach sees to it that he says something hard even to the person who played harder than everybody else. But, win or lose, we stayed together. Or so I thought. Then it was time to leave. I was sad and happy at the same time. I was glad I was leaving because then I would never have to see or hear coach again. He made me sick. I was sad because I was parting with my dear teammates. When I graduated, I thought that basketball was a bad idea. I thought I would never hold a basketball ever again. But I did. I didn't shoot, I didn't even dribble it. I just held it. For a minute, I guess. And it felt good in my hands. And so I thought, maybe it would also feel good if I had somebody to call my someone, somebody to hold my hand. Love is basketball. When you play the game, you get hurt. When you play with your heart, it hurts even more. When you're down, try to get up as carefully as you can so you wouldn't drop to your knees once more. I know it's easier said than done. But hey, there's no harm in trying. Once you're up, you're ready to play the game again -- the game of love. And you're facing a new challenge. Getting hurt is a bad, bad, bad feeling. But winning this time would be such bliss. Wish me luck!  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       By: Mariel G. Calalo   How often have you caught yourself having an imaginary conversation with your own soul, trying to figure out if you are happy or not?&nbsp;You're not exactly happy but then again, not exactly miserable. You're somewhat in&nbsp;between, in the meantimeness of these two opposing emotions. If there&nbsp;are&nbsp;words to describe what you are feeling right now, it would be "just okay."   When asked the question"how have you been lately?",&nbsp;we sometimes feel a sudden panic, a mad rush to come up with an elaborate answer to describe our situation.&nbsp; Well, we do come up with creative answers like "Getting along with life," or recount your recent visits to Paris, New York and Tokyo just to give your listener a feel that you are living a charmed life. Why is it ever difficult to just say that you're&nbsp;just   "okay"?        Being "Just Okay" means you're contented.   Being just okay means you take what comes your way and make the best out of it. Being okay means you long for&nbsp;the same achievements, the same blessings, the same riches as other people have but you're not exactly green with envy that you would be willing to kill or compromise your principles just to get them. Being just okay means you know and importantly, have accepted your own capacity and limitations.     Being just "okay" means you know that shit happens sometimes  . Have you ever heard of "Murphy's Law?" It's a principle that states that no matter how much you try to prevent things from going wrong, if there is a&nbsp;probability of things going wrong, no matter how small that&nbsp;probability may be, things are going to go wrong. Well, guess what? It's true. Shit happens sometimes, no matter how much you tried to prevent it from happening. And when things do go wrong, being&nbsp;just okay&nbsp;means you have the grace to bear the pressure; you have the optimism to stand up and say "oh well, I've seen worse days." As you get older you'll realize that no matter how bad things are today, if you hang on a bit in there, things are going to be alright, eventually. Being just okay means that even if everything sucks, you know you're going to be fine. Being just okay means you know you can make a mistake and be able rise above it.     Being just"okay" means you are not rushing  . Enjoy the journey. It's not going to be smooth sailing but I assure you, the journey's worth it. Sometimes, you need to experience sadness to be able to differentiate it from happiness. Sometimes, you need to feel a little lost to appreciate what it's like to be found. Sometimes, you need to make mistakes because sometimes the best way to learn is by making mistakes. Being&nbsp;just okay&nbsp;means you're past the starting line but not yet on the finish line. Don't mind if life has to make you wait a lifetime to get what you want. Chances, are the waiting would only make the finding much sweeter.     Being&nbsp;just "okay"&nbsp;means you're okay.   Being just okay means you're okay. You don't need prozac and sessions with your shrink to keep your sanity intact. You don't need to drown yourself in your own tears out of self pity. You don't need to be rich to feel valued. You don't need plastic surgery to feel beautiful. Being "Just Okay" means you're not afraid to be "You."   So the next time someone asks you how have you been lately, or how have you been feeling lately, give them the simple answer, because being okay means so much more than just a four letter word.     
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      By: Mariel G. Calalo  I used believed in that "if you love someone, set him free" crap. I used to believe in fate, in destiny, in happy-ever-afters. I used to believe that I'm suppose to find true love the year I turn twenty five and marry that person at thirty. After every heartbreak, I believed that the person I'm letting go of, would eventually find his way back to me. I built my life on the belief that love always finds a way. And then one day, I stopped believing in all these things.  I realized today that it's been two months since I last cried. Yes, I keep track of the dates I cried better than my unpredictable menstrual cycle. I cried that day because it felt like I was breaking up with a person who never was my boyfriend. It felt like I was being let off the hook and I don't want to be let off the hook. It felt like I was being given my freedom from this spell of eternal confusion, a chance to be saved from the limbo and yet not wanting that salvation. It felt as if I was being told to pursue my own happiness when my happiness is right in front of me, it has always been, I was just too blind to see it, too cold to let it show itself to me. The very thought of me spending the rest of my life, my permanent future with someone else was revolting. I didn't want to go home that night. All I wanted to do was sit in front of him, silently, and just watch him, stare into his eyes, and not let the evening end... a view so amazing that not even the stars could equal such magnificence. I cried the moment I got home. I cried as I wrote in my journal because I somehow knew that this is the last time I'll ever have these philosophical conversations about love, life and everything in between. I cried because in my heart of hearts, I knew, that the love I feel for him is so real that I just wanted to run away from his side and linger there all at the same time. I cried myself to sleep, drowned myself with my own tears.   I knew I had to let myself cry. It's called symbolic purging. In the process of letting go, I had to cry all my emotions out. I cried myself to sleep every night, wondering, praying, believing that love would find a way, believing that somehow, someday, the curtain of self-doubt and fear would be lifted and we'd both realize that the love we both have been waiting for has always been beside us, right in front of us. Maybe then, I'll stop being cynical and sarcastic and just accept things at face value. Maybe then, I would be so understanding and never holding up his past crimes against him. Maybe then, we'll both be brave to say that things we never said to each other. And then one day, I just woke up, all cried out and I just couldn't cry anymore. I kept myself busy filling up schedule that I don't even have the time to feel sorry for myself. Everyday was just like other days, like a machine, I had to discipline myself to get things done. I was getting along without him very well.  One day he shows up with his philosophical nuggets and asked me if I was happy. My answer was this: I have everything I could possibly want and more. I am happy with what I am now, and with what I have now. I am happy in the here and now. And about the future? I think I've tortured myself long enough to think that what's waiting for me is possibly worse or maybe not, but the thing is, not knowing about it now makes living easier.  You see, you'll know you're growing up when you know that after every bad thing that goes wrong in your life, you somehow know that everything will be alright. Everything is 20-20 in hindsight. Be sure to make mistakes because the only way to learn is to commit mistakes. It's called growing up.   
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      By: Mariel G. Calalo   My greatest fear in life is neither death or not ever finding my ideal man. Rather, it's finding the exact opposite of my ideals, living and falling madly in love with him, and casting all else aside. Some days, it's the scariest thought that keeps me awake in the wee small hours of the morning. Love is an adrenaline rush, an exhilirating roller coaster ride that makes you brave enough to dare and dream. It a wonderful experience to feel it. It brings you happiness, jealousy, sadness, excitement and every other emotion that makes you human and feel alive. Here are my two-cents worth of learnings from loving.    Love has to be tested  . As fire purifies gold, trials and difficulties can either strengthen the love you feel or ultimately show you that this love isn't true. It's always easy to love a person when everything between you is calm and okay. However, it is difficult to love someone when you are going through tough times. It's difficult to love a person when the world seems to pull the two of you in different directions. If you are able to rise above the challenges, with your love for each other unwavering, then consider yourself, blessed beyond measure.    Love is defined by balanced exposure  . You can't really be sure if love is what you feel if you're always together doing the same things. You'll know it's love if after being away from each other for some time, if after meeting different people and if after pursuing your own passions in life, and you still carry the torch for the same man or woman, that's love. Absence makes the heart grow fonder. Sometimes, you need to give the other person the time and the space to think things through, to finally put the gray areas of your relationship in black and white, to hear his thoughts more clearly, and of course, to miss you.    Love is acceptance  . Love is not about "Superman Complex." You don't love a person because you think he needs rescuing. You can't change a person, you can only love that person enough to make him want to be a better man. Love doesn't have to feel like you're settling. It's about feeling like you've just found one of the world's greatest treasures and not wanting to exchange it for anything in the world. Someday, someone funnier, sweeter, richer, more responsible, much more charming, much more beautiful would come along. Unless you find the person you love perfect just the way he is, perfect in his own imperfection, you would never be contented and happy in this relationship.    Love really begins with friendship and familiarity  . I used to think that platonic relationships gone romantic, is like putting vinegar in congee. It makes something warm and comfortable, sour. I was foolish in believing that familiarity breeds contempt. I guess, I know better now. The only way to say that you truly love a person is if you know him and what better way to do it than being friends. It relieves you the pressure of being at your best all the time, of being too perfect, of being too good. No pretenses. Seeing the flaws in a person will help you asses if this is a person you see yourself growing old with, someone you think you could listen to, someone you can respect. If the love of your life is also your best friend, I think it's one of the best evidences that God does exist and looking out for you. So often, he or she has become a source of encouragement and comfort, warm feelings or a good laugh, just at the right moment. Often, talking to that person helps you hear your thoughts better and figure out the answers you need.    Love is not automatic but manual  . You need to work it girl! Love is tough and it needs hard work. Love is like a rose. You need to take care of it or else, it dies. You need to decide and love that person even on days when he's absolutely unlovable, on days when he absolutely drives away every drop for sanity in you, and on days when you just want the earth to swallow you alive. I guess, Love is lifetime effort.  After all these learnings, it's difficult to imagine why I'm still loveless. Well, I'm only loveless, not hopeless. Love moves in mysterious ways and I truly believe that a wonderful blessings on his way to find me. After all, it is in the hope that dreams would come true that makes our lives more interesting. 
      
</post>


</Blog>