<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Experienced pure torture at lunch today.  I sometimes can't believe that I actually pay somebody $65 to rip all the hair out of my 'delicate' areas.  And not just rip out the hair, but get into some seriously compromising positions with a perfect stranger.  It's very hard to look cool when she says 'Ok bend over.' And why the hell is it called a 'Brazilian'?  Looks more like a mohawk to me, or do a lot of Brazilians have mohawks these days?  Who knows.  It is actually very amusing to think about the motives behind why women put themselves through this kind of torture.  Someone (who I want to kill right now) at some point decided that women's (whistle whistle) are only attractive without much, if any, hair.  I mean, I thought pubes were as simple as parsley (everyone just pushes it aside before eating).  But nooooooooo, now we can't have any at all (yet, if you went to a restaurant and received your plate sans garnish you'd be like 'Where's the parsley?').  I blame the porn industry (whenever there's anything wrong, you always blame the porn industry).  I definitely didn't even consider trimming the hedge, if you will, until I started watching porn.  My girlfriends in college and I used to always be amazed and very impressed by how well these women were able to be hairless.  If you don't wax, there's some seriously difficult angles down there to attempt maneuvers with a razor, and I mean, this is all blind too.  Have you ever tried shaving 'down there' with a hand-held mirror in one hand and a Lady Bic in the other??  You know how in the mirror everything is actually opposite?? OUCH!  We used to joke that porn stars probably put an add in the paper 'SWF needs man to shave my sn*tch' Guys would be lined up around the corner!  But I think it all goes back to the same idea as the jackass in the red convertible playing his music at decibel levels rivalling a jet engine...because there's always that chance he'll drive by a really hot girl who then thinks to herself 'I really like that song, I want to have sex with that guy now.'  Whatever torture we put ourselves through to look better, it's all just about sex really isn't it?
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got shit on by a bird today.  I just burst out laughing.  I was sitting in Jason's car while he pumped gas and the car was almost entirely covered by the roof of the gas station except for the exact trajectory of whatever the bird let rip from its ass.  I'm gonna have to go with one of those 'planets in perfect alignment' type scenarios and have decided that it means good luck.  I'm not sure what this bird's been eating, but when we discovered the full extent of the 'damage,' the bird had somehow managed to splatter the entire inside of the passenger side door, my pants, and a large portion of the window as well.  I think he needs to cut back on his nightcrawlers myself.  Why exactly is bird poo black and white anyway??  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So Friday night I'm at this party in Boston and I only know 1 person there, my friend who I went with.  I am wearing a T-shirt that reads 'Toys' on it.  I begin talking to a random guy who then says to me (while looking at my...shirt) something to the effect of 'That certainly is a nice set of toys.'  Exactly how are you meant to respond to something like this?? 'Gee, thanks' and take it like an appreciated compliment?  Just prior to him making this comment we were discussing the different types of engineering we do (I believe we were the only two engineers at the party).  I wonder what is going through a guy's mind just seconds before these words come out of his head.  I wonder how he was able to speak in complete sentences just nanoseconds prior discussing engineering concepts when he was clearly just thinking about my tits.  Why do guys think this is a compliment?  And more specifically, what makes an engineer think that an engineer would find this a compliment?  For all he knows, I stuffed my bra with socks that night.  (For the record, I haven't done that since I was 15 and it was a dare).  He could have been complimenting my bra stuffing abilities.    So the debate is....Should it make a difference that my T-shirt actually fully reads 'Toys in Babeland New York' and was bought at a sex toy shop?  Do I have the right to be irritated with comments about my breasts when I'm wearing a shirt advertising a sex toy shop?  It's not like there's a picture of a dildo or anything, it's just red letters on a white T-shirt with black sleeves, in fact it's even hard to read it because the font is kinda funny.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Man, aren't all the best ones already spoken for?  Jason has this friend who, ever since I met him, can't stop thinking about him.  I'll just call him D, in case his wife ever reads this.  Actually, speaking of his wife...she was pretty cute too.  Maybe at Jason's 4th of July party I can get them a little tipsy and cross 'Have a Threesome' off my list of things to do....And Don, when you read this, keep dreaming!!!  you dirty little perv!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jesus, how am I gonna get through today?  Went out with Jason to Martha's Exchange last night, which I was very much looking forward to because I just looooooove breweries.  Well, I think they got their plumbing screwed up or something, cause I swear I was drinking piss.  And we were naive enough to think at the end of each beer that the next one on the list would be better, so we were pounding our beers just so we wouldn't have to keep tasting it (the philosophy seemed to make sense at the time) most people would probably think to switch to bottled beer, but hey.  And with all the pounding going on, yeah, we were wasted after 4 beers each.  I don't think that's happened for me since 1996 (except this minor incident in England when I didn't realize I was drinking the strongest beer ever brewed and hey, their pints are 20 oz!!  but I'm still claiming food poisoning).  Anyway, so then we spotted our kickboxing instructor and by our reaction, you'd think he was friggin' Brad Pitt or something.  We're all 'MATT MATT WE'RE IN YOUR CLASS!!!' and pounced on him like little friggin' second graders spotting Miss Smith at the grocery store on a Sunday.  I'm sure he was impressed.  And will probably switch gyms now.  But anyway, it's time for the Friday song.  C-c-c-can't can't stop the beat.......
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm an engineer and I work at a small company.  There are so few women here that we each get TWO of our own personal stalls in the bathroom.  Obviously, as an engineer, being the left-brained individual that I am, if there are two toilets....one is clearly meant for No. 1 and the other meant for No. 2.  It's that simple, right?  And I can't even properly express how satisfying it is to enter your stall and see the seat up, knowing that no one has been there since the cleaners and your ass cheeks are going to be the first to make contact with the seat when you're ready to do the deed.  Well, I just had to take a piss, but as the day is drawing to an end (the work day anyway) and I haven't shit yet today, I decided to give myself the OPTION, so obviously I went straight for K8's No. 2 toilet....only to find in my absolute HORROR, the seat was already down.  Whoah there buddy!!!!  Who's being greedy?  or a better question...who ate mexican last night and already used both theirs today....needless to say I was far too stressed by the whole ordeal that I guess I'll have to wait to drop the kids off until I get home.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The boss took me and Jason to lunch today.  We thought for sure it was something bad, we goof off too much or something, but he just wanted to talk about work stuff.  Phew!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok there is a snake sitting next to me.  I'm not sure what the deal is, but Jason likes to hiss at his wife on the phone.  I don't know if it's some weirdo foreplay thing or what, but when it happens, it sometimes sounds like he's having a seizure or something over there and I don't know if I'm supposed to run over to try to shove something in his mouth so he doesn't bite his tongue off.  At least, that's what we were told to do with the kid who had epilepsy at my school.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's Hump Day.  I wish it really WAS hump day....when you're single, just about everything you do makes you think about sex (or is that just me??) My mom once told me that when you travel, you need to eat as much as you can when you're able to because you don't know when you'll get to eat again.  That's my theory with sex and being single.  I deal with valves and really exciting stuff like that at work.  Lots of them are flanged, some of them are male/female connections.  I wish I could have a male/female connection.  It is hump day after all, what's a girl to do???
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jason just left the office 10 minutes early.  What a slacker!  I want food.  I don't even care what, just a big pile of food.  I have kickboxing tonight.  I think I'll keep visualizing beating up the fat bastard still (not Jason, a different one) because he's the last person who's been a real dick to me (even though it was over a month ago and I'm sooooooo over him), and I have to visualize beating up somebody or else I won't make it through the class!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My roommate hijacked the keyboard during my previous post and wrote that I can't drink and then published it.  Blasphemy!  I'm going to have to say that beer trumps Barcardi Breezers or Schmirnoff Twisters or whatever the hell they are any day of the week.  Oh yeah, also for the record....when I said roommate's girlfriend's little brother, we're talking 22-year-old brother, not 12-year-old brother before somebody out there calls the cops on me or something.  Nice guy too.  I feel bad, I think I traumatized the poor boy.  I think I'm just too much woman sometimes.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In my efforts to get the teachers wasted last night I ended up just getting myself wasted and woke up this morning with my clothes from the night before still on and my contacts still in, like 'What the fuck happened last night???'  My roommate convinced me that I'd made out with my other roommate's boyfriend and now she hates me.  I believed him.  My roommate, a special ed 3rd grade teacher managed to down 19 coors lights.  jesus!  I'm impressed now I must say.  I also managed to molest his girlfriend's little brother, great way to make a first impression.  Someone peed on the stairs, I really hope it wasn't me.  In my defense though, I did drink on an empty stomach, and most of them were drinking Bacardi Breezers or something which is the equivalent to Boone's Farm in my eyes.  My roommate says bullshit, and i can't drink!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My roommate is a teacher and it's the last day of school, so he's having all his teacher buddies over tonight to celebrate.  Well, I say tonight, but as school gets out at 3pm, they'll all probably be wasted by the time I get home at 5:30.  I'll make them all keep drinking til they puke.  And it will happen.  I don't see elementary school teachers having the highest of tolerances.  This engineer will certainly show them what's up!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jason helped me pick out new glasses today at lunch.  I chose transition lenses, the optometrist assured me they wouldn't transition indoors.  I better not be walking around all day with half-dark glasses because of the bright lights in the office or there'll be hell to pay!  Jason ate TWO burgers from Wendy's today at lunch AND finished my fries.  Fat Bastard!  Today marks the last day of Jason's bad luck.  He marked off too many days on his calendar by accident.  Now he can't mark any more days until we come back on Monday.  This morning Jason leaned on the wall of my cubicle and almost knocked the whole freaking thing over.  Fat Bastard!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jason just got TWO donuts on our excursion to Heav'nly Donuts.  Fat Bastard.  My eyelid is starting to scab over from my eyebrow waxing incident two days ago.  I can't believe I pay $20 to have my eyelids burned off.  Maybe I should just go back to having two furry caterpillars living on my face, this is getting way too dangerous.  I think it's time for the Friday song now.  Everybody move your feet and feel united oohohhhohhhhh......
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jason didn't tell me about the folding trick, my fingers are numb now.  Bastard.  Jason thinks I'm a traitor for going out to lunch without him today, so he ate a big greasy burger from Wendy's.  Fat Bastard.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All I keep hearing about lately is blog this blog that.  So here's mine.  I'm at work right now.  I sit next to Jason.  I like to listen in on his phone conversations.  He's talking about insurance now.  I saw Franz Ferdinand last night in Boston.  They rock! It's Jill's birthday today.  Happy Birthday Jill!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So Thursday I went to the Projekt Revolution Tour. I honestly can't put into words how much fun it was. Obviously arrived hours early to tailgate, got incredibly drunk, and then proceeded to pass out in my chair as soon as we went into the concert. I was still holding my beer and my friends thought it was the funniest thing and kept trying to take the beer out of my hand so I wouldn't spill it all over myself. I'm not sure if I had a death-grip on it or what, but I guess they failed every time they tried, and I kept waking up and pretending I wasn't in the middle of totally passing out and taking a sip of my beer and then passing out again. So finally my friend Jason pried the beer out of my hand, but in my passed out state I didn't realize I wasn't holding it anymore and my hand stayed in perfect cup-gripping form. Nice one. I guess I was passed out so long that my friends kept getting up and walking around and at one point I was left there by myself just looking like one of those hobos asleep on a park bench or something. When I woke up, I didn't even care, cause I woke up just in time for Snoop Dogg. Allll riiiiiight. Next up was Korn and they did an amazing cover of Pink Floyd's  Another Brick in the Wall  (Part 2 to be specific, yes, I did just look it up on Google, dork). Anyway, it was fucking amazing. So obviously Linkin Park headlined, and I just want to say, I now want to have Chester Bennington's babies. Well, maybe not actually have his babies, but a  lot  of practicing!!!! Yum, give me a hot, sweaty guy with tattoos any day of the week. God I need to have sex.  Anyway, then we of course were stuck in the parking lot for about 2 1/2 hours after the show. The group I went with decided to split up and have a girls car and a boys car. My  gorgeous  friend Caitlin was driving the girls car, and needless to say, we  kept  getting harassed by absolute freaks the whole time. But actually there were these nice boys who gave us chocolate chip cookies. Oh yeah, and when we were tailgating I did meet these two little hotties who I started talking to and found out they live in Beverly which is where my sister is about to transfer to (Endicott) so I obviously had to get the ball rolling to try to hook her up with one of them. So I told them to come out for her 21st birthday and we exchanged digits. God I am  such  a good sister! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I have this kick-ass friend also named Kate who lives in NYC. Luckily for me she was in town Wednesday so I went to see her and we ate fabulous food as you always do when you go out to dinner with Kate. I have this friend, Travis, who didn't realize I actually had a  friend  named Kate and for the longest time actually thought I was just talking about myself in third-person when I would talk about her. Needless to say, he thought I was very odd until it dawned on him she actually exists. Anyway, so Kate and I end up at this brewery (yummmmm) and are enjoying great conversation. Well, you can imagine the topics that are discussed when two single girls get together....So we're in the middle of very animated conversation about sex, and more specifically how we like it...(and I will admit that we were actually using terms like bang, pound, and nail)...when you're single and it's been a while, the concept of  making love  flies right out the window. So we were totally in our own little world having this conversation when we have a moment of clarity and realize we are, in fact, in  public . We look over to the next occupied table and it's a table of about 8 guys just staring at us, jaws on the floor. We (Kate and I) just looked at each other, started cracking up, and then decide it's time to leave (and kept looking over our shoulders when we got outside to make sure we weren't being followed!)  That night I had an absolutely incredible dream that I was at the beach and two lifeguards were fighting over me (one of whom was Paul Walker of  The Fast and the Furious , yummmm). It went further than that, but I'm going to keep that for my own enjoyment...Damn was I disappointed to wake up! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I didn't mention in my blog last night that I actually went shopping yesterday evening.&nbsp; I had these $10 off jeans offers from American Eagle that expired today, so I figured I should make good use of them.&nbsp; For a girl, I really don't shop very often, especially for pants because I'm just at that height where the petites are too short but the regulars are too long and it gets very frustrating.&nbsp; Normally, if I find something I like, I just buy it in about every color it comes in, so I don't have to go shopping again for a long time.   Anyway, I was getting particularly frustrated yesterday evening because American Eagle is one of those stores that doesn't understand that not every girl wants her jeans so low that her butt-crack is peeking out to say hello.&nbsp; American Eagle is also one of these stores that has entered into conspiracy to change all the sizes of their clothes without telling anyone, or me in particular...  I   didn't change size...it must be the label's wrong...yeah, that's it.   Anyway, so I pick up several pairs of jeans and cords and merrily head to the changing room.&nbsp; A few minutes later, the more than cheerful boy who works there is changing all my 2's for 4's.&nbsp; Nice one.&nbsp; He says to me 'You're so tiny!'&nbsp;I'm like  hmmm...yeah, what happened to my 2's? &nbsp; Anyway, he practically bangs the door down to check and make sure I'm liking everything.&nbsp; I'm just getting more and more frustrated.&nbsp; I find the  perfect  pair of khaki's but the petites are like capris and the regulars are dragging on the floor even with my big shoes on.&nbsp; He says things to me like 'I   will   get you in a pair of jeans tonight.'&nbsp; I'm thinking  I'd rather get you  out    of yours .&nbsp; Ha.&nbsp; Then I tell him how shopping is  so  frustrating, and he says 'Shopping is my sport.'&nbsp; Yup, gay.&nbsp; Anyway, he did manage to get me into not only a pair of jeans, but a pair of khakis (I went for the regulars),  and  a pair of cords.&nbsp; So, well done him.   Well, I had to find something in the store to purchase to push me over the minimum limit to reap the rewards of my offers, so I chose a purple thong.&nbsp; Yes, I know that there's no one to see it, but a girl can dream.&nbsp;  Ah yes, a girl can dream.     &nbsp;  If we can get a man on the moon, then surely we can get a man on me.   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I got an email from one of my favorite people today reminding me about drunken dialling in college (please reference previous post  Making up for lost time... )&nbsp; She reminded of me of some of my finer DD moments (let's discuss racking up $80 phone bills...)   Anyway, speaking of phones...Saturday night whilst on my date, two (yes TWO) guys I had gone on date(s) with semi-recently called my phone.&nbsp; I was a little perplexed as I hadn't spoken to either in quite a while, and late-night Saturday is an odd time to call someone you haven't spoken to in a while,   I   think anyway.&nbsp; (And no, before any of you pervies suggest it, they were not booty calls, nothing untoward ever happened with either thank you very much).&nbsp; Anyway, I honestly thought my phone was in fact possessed.&nbsp; But as it turns out they both really did call me.&nbsp; I'm telling you, it's drought forever and then monsoon season.&nbsp; Why is that always the case?   So my roommate is psycho.&nbsp; She knows I think she's psycho, so I can write about it in my blog.&nbsp; She is absolutely obsessed with her boyfriend and it's a wee bit scary.&nbsp; I'm talking Norman Bates in the shower with a kitchen knife psycho.&nbsp; When they are broken up she does drive by his house on at least a daily basis, and even now that they are together she's checking our AdultFriendFinder.com account convinced he's on there trying to meet people.&nbsp; (She searches for what his profile would be).&nbsp; Anyway, the rest of the story isn't even that psycho, just annoying.&nbsp; The guy lives maybe 5 minutes down the road and owns his own house.&nbsp; She shares a house with myself and our other roommate Chris who owns the house.&nbsp; They (my roommate, her boyfriend,&nbsp;AND HIS 9-YEAR-OLD KID) split time staying at his house and our house.&nbsp; They shower here, do laundry here, cook here, keep toiletries here, etc.&nbsp; Now usually, they split it 50/50, one night here, one night there.&nbsp; This week, however, they are here every night.&nbsp; Why you ask?&nbsp; Well, because the kid is spending days this week at someone's house who lives on the next road over and it's just that much more convenient for them to travel from our house in the morning.&nbsp; Ok, does anyone else find this reason even a tad bit ridiculous???&nbsp; Please, if you need to, take a second and skim back a few sentences when I said the boyfriend&nbsp;lives 5 MINUTES AWAY.&nbsp; I could understand this reason of  convenience  if they lived an hour or&nbsp;I'd even let it slide with&nbsp;30 minutes away, but 5&nbsp;MINUTES!&nbsp; They are either the laziest people I've ever met or they're a few muffins short of a baker's dozen.&nbsp; (I'll let you decide).&nbsp; I'll just stress the point again HE OWNS HIS OWN HOUSE...5 MINUTES AWAY.&nbsp; Now, I will bring up, just to be fair, the time that I&nbsp;DEMANDED (as a freshman in college)&nbsp;a drawer in my boyfriend's dresser to keep clothes and stuff in.&nbsp; Why is this a relevant point?&nbsp; He lived   two doors   down   from me.&nbsp; Ok, so maybe I was a psycho girl at one point too, but the point is...live and learn.&nbsp; Some people forget the learning part...   So speaking of psycho girls...I mentioned that I went to a party with my friend on Friday night and how we left, then went back and crashed over.&nbsp; Not sure if I made this clear, but completely platonic friend, great guy.&nbsp; I think he was even the one who put a little blanket over me and took my glasses off me when I totally passed out on this chair (probably mouth-wide open and drooling), then even treated me to breakfast the next day (Mmmmm-mmmm yummy).&nbsp; He is unfortunately going through a divorce at the moment.&nbsp; I say unfortunately because divorce must always be a painful experience (I imagine).&nbsp; However, he will be much better off when he gets this psycho out of his life.&nbsp; Apparently,  somehow ,  SOMEHOW , she discovered he was at Poor Boys Diner with  some  girl on Saturday morning (I'm thinking she slipped him some sort of GPS tracking system), so she calls him up  at work  demanding to know who he was with and why and then hangs up on him.&nbsp; Now I fear that friendly breakfast is going to cost him thousands in the settlement.&nbsp; Like the caption in the previous picture I posted reads, 'Hell hath no fury...'   I&nbsp;implied that my date on Saturday went well enough that I wouldn't mind seeing the guy again.&nbsp; So I called him up Sunday evening just to say hi.&nbsp; Conversation was going well...towards the end of the convo he asks me to go to a party with him the next weekend...just to be coy I say maybe...then he explains that it's actually his aunt's 60th birthday party.&nbsp; This is the point where K8 slowly starts freaking out in her head...uh, um, uh, um...meeting the family??....uh, gotta go (click).&nbsp; So yeah, we'll see if he talks to  me  ever again...   Ok, I'm off to bedfordshire.&nbsp; Goodnight.     
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So you probably want to hear about my date.&nbsp; But I'm a respectable girl... (some of you are like 'yeah, right').  I have this policy on dating I live by.&nbsp; I actually don't date all that often, but when I do I follow this policy.&nbsp; If he doesn't pay, no action.&nbsp;&nbsp; Totally kidding! &nbsp; No, with regards to who pays, I personally think it should be 50/50 for the most part.&nbsp; Obviously there are exceptions to the rule, but it's not like I whip out my trusty abacus or anything.&nbsp; I live by 'it all goes around.'&nbsp; You know, you pay this time, I get next time, and it pretty much all evens out.&nbsp; Now, I know some guys get touchy about a girl offering to pay and some get touchy when a girl  expects  for him to pay.&nbsp; So my philosophy, which I think is pretty fair is...you can generally tell  before  the check comes if you ever want to see the guy again and if this is the case I let him pay, because I know that I'll pay  next  time.&nbsp; If I know that I  don't  want to see him again, I'll grab the check before he gets a chance.  So to change the subject (and leave you totally hanging), I had a pretty chill day today.&nbsp; Drank some imported cream ale from England.&nbsp; Chatted to a pretty chill friend for a hell of a long time.&nbsp; Got to ride on the back of some dude's Harley.&nbsp; That was fucking awesome.&nbsp; I'm so getting one.&nbsp; By next summer, mark my words.&nbsp; God I love my life.  And as for the date...he paid. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yup, that's me. I've always got two whiskey's and two bitches...  Official photo by K8  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    To my friend...Sound familiar??  Official photo by K8 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh how sad I can't comment on my blog during the day like before.&nbsp; Damn the man.&nbsp; Now I feel like I have to actually have something worthwhile to talk about to write in my blog.&nbsp; And let's face it, how often does that happen??&nbsp; I'm going to make up for lost time now though.&nbsp; So get comfortable...  It's mid-day Saturday and I just got home from last night a couple hours ago.&nbsp; I fucking love being single.&nbsp; Nobody pissed off I didn't call that I wasn't coming home; Nobody not speaking to me today because I didn't hang out with them.&nbsp; And no, I didn't hook up or anything before that idea gets out of hand.&nbsp; Two of the golden rules where still adhered to...so what I didn't wake up in my own bed, that's just a bonus.&nbsp; I did wake up with all clothes on, alone, and sans contacts.&nbsp; Yippee!&nbsp;   The best thing about living my life with the 'go with the flow' attitude is that things can turn 180 degrees in a matter of seconds.&nbsp; Yesterday I was going to go see The Hives in Boston, but as the day wore on I was just so exhausted I didn't feel like driving all the way there, maneuvering pedestrians, parking, etc. etc. etc.&nbsp; Anyway, so I'd resigned myself to a pathetic night in alone with&nbsp;a six-pack of Sam Adam's Summer Ale and a 4-pack of Boddington's (an English fav) only to sign onto instant messenger at one point and within a couple seconds get invited to some party by a friend of a friend (who I now consider MY friend, ahem, if  you're  reading this) and thought 'why the scooby dooby not?'&nbsp; And I'm in HKWT mode (Have Koozie Will Travel).&nbsp; I then proceed to kick my friend's ass in foosball AND darts, but that's a whole different kettle of fish.  So we were at this party and the company was good, everyone was friendly, had some laughs drank some beer and then decided it was time to go home.&nbsp; Got home, intoxicated, did the falling over taking off clothes putting sleeping attire on thing (wife beater and American flag boxer shorts ala Old Navy).&nbsp; Then my phone starts vibrating like crazy dancing all over the top of my dresser and it's my friend.&nbsp; 'Hey, let's go back to the party'&nbsp; drunk me: 'Wa-heyyyyyyyy'&nbsp; Ok, so wife beater and boxers crumpled up like used tissues on the bed now, clothes back on.&nbsp; Head downstairs to wait for my friend to come pick me back up when I proceed to drunk email.&nbsp; This is like drunk dialling, but completely one-sided and you at least have on record what was actually said (and you don't wake up the person on the receiving end, so everyone's happy, wa-hey!)&nbsp; a drunk girl, an open connection with the internet, and a computer are a BAD combination.&nbsp; Actually to be honest, I think it was all pretty tame, phew!&nbsp; I once had this phone with a mind of it's own.&nbsp; You know how if you don't have a flip-phone and you forget to lock the keypad sometimes your phone calls people by accident?&nbsp; Well, I had this phone once that insisted on always calling my ex-boyfriend.&nbsp; That was the only number it 'accidentally' dialled.&nbsp; Riiiiiight, well needless to say, me and that phone aren't friends anymore.&nbsp; My friend pulls into the driveway and I then have to wipe the drool from all over the desk because I realize at that moment I'd just been passed out hunched over my desk mouth wide open.&nbsp; Nice one.  Anyway, go back to the party and ATTEMPT to stay awake.&nbsp; Have an in-depth conversation with my friend and this guy with cool tattoos.&nbsp; Both have been married before, one has kids.&nbsp; We discuss how it's virtually impossible nowadays for a girl to meet a guy who doesn't have some sort of permanent baggage.&nbsp; I have had to drop my standards in recent months.&nbsp; I used to say I would never date a guy who is divorced.&nbsp; Now it's just I would never date a guy with kids.&nbsp; People in this area seem to get married YOUNG and then divorced still young.  ANYWAY, wake up in the morning all cramped in this chair (yes, by myself) and need to find my shoes.&nbsp; People are passed out in various chairs and couches all over the house.&nbsp; I finally spot my shoes, conveniently left RIGHT NEXT TO this couch with the cool tattoos guy sleeping on it, pants on floor, sporting the most impressive morning wood ever witnessed.&nbsp; So impressive in fact that it has to be seen by others.&nbsp; I then proceed to make my friend look at it and he makes everyone in the room get up and have a sneeky peek.&nbsp; I then have to accomplish the near impossible feat of opening the door, tip-toeing to my shoes, and snatching them without dude waking up so he doesn't get embarrassed everyone was just spying on his incredible fireman's pole.  So it's now Saturday afternoon.&nbsp; I'm home alone...no roommates...that means...naked time!!&nbsp; woo-hoo!&nbsp; I have nothing to do, I started on the wine as soon as I got back a couple hours ago.&nbsp; Tried posting pictures to my blog (wanted it in my profile, think it's posted somewhere as a separate post, oh well).&nbsp; Chatted on instant messenger to a complete stranger who reads my blog, or used to anyway, so here's a shout out to you.&nbsp; And I have a date tonight.&nbsp; Nothing  that  special, not gonna marry the dude, but he seems fun enough I suppose.  I think it's time for a little Gamecube...and a little more wine!&nbsp; I love being me.  Peace out! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Yup, that's me.  Official photo by K8 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I fucking love being single.&nbsp; No one to bitch at you, no one pissing you off.&nbsp; It's friggin great.&nbsp; All day Sunday I did nothing but scratch my ass and drink copious amounts of wine.&nbsp; No one nagging that shit had to get done, nothing.&nbsp; I had so much fun doing that, I did it all again tonight!&nbsp;   Plus I just read on MSN that Jake Gyllenhaal and Kirsten Dunst broke up.&nbsp; Sweeeeeeet, he's all mine!   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday my roommate (girl) and I were watching TV and she announced that she knew of this website people use to meet people with similar sexual fetishes or married people looking for 'discrete' fun, AdultFriendFinder.com.&nbsp; She turned to me and was like 'you wanna go on it?'&nbsp; I was like 'hell yeah!'&nbsp; So we created this whole fake profile (we're a 35-year-old Medical Sales Professional, blonde hair, blue eyes, &nbsp;5' 5"with athletic build looking for a guy with a pantyhose fetish - don't ask).&nbsp; Anyway, we did a search in our zip code, and let me tell ya, there are some real FREAKS in the 03087 area, holy cow!&nbsp; So yeah, our screen name is Krazy8_69 if anyone's interested... &nbsp; Riiiiiiiiiiiiight. &nbsp; And Jason, in order to contact people, you have to pay like $40 or something ridiculous before you get excited.&nbsp; I bet you didn't even make it to the bottom of this post before you were already on that site.&nbsp; You dirty little perv! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The man has struck.&nbsp; No more blogging at work.&nbsp; Blog has been blocked.&nbsp; But fear not faithful readers, I vow to keep you updated and informed.&nbsp; Perhaps not as often unfortunately.&nbsp; I know there are some of you who can't get through the day without their K8 fix.&nbsp; There's a therapy group starting for those who will suffer from withdrawals.&nbsp; Please contact my publicist for the dates and locations of the meetings.&nbsp; There will be a rotating coffee and donuts responsibility.  &nbsp;  Kicked Mount Monadnock's ass yesterday.&nbsp; And even mustered up enough energy to go out last night in Manch Vegas.&nbsp; My roommate (girl) is recently single, so HAD to celebrate.&nbsp; Had a pretty good time actually.&nbsp; Even ended up in some athletic club in Nashua at about 3am, not sure how that happened.&nbsp; All I know is there was a bar and no one was manning it.&nbsp; THIS girl definitely made the most of  that  opportunity!&nbsp; Needless to say I'm feeling the effects of a serious hangover.&nbsp; My goal for the day is to be the biggest lazy piece of shit known to man.&nbsp; I never miss a goal!  &nbsp;  Alright, dear readers, the remote is definitely calling my name right now.&nbsp; I may be back later.&nbsp; Peace out yo.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Went to Martha's Exchange in Nashua with Jason again last night.&nbsp; Gave it a second try, but drank bottled beer this time because I wasn't making  that  mistake again.&nbsp; (Please&nbsp;reference previous post  Thank F@&amp;$ It's Friday!!!! )&nbsp; I don't know if it was a full moon or what, but there were some serious freaks out last night.&nbsp; I mean, this  is  New Hampshire, but come on.&nbsp; I really think that the whole 'No Shirt, No Shoes, No Service' rule should be extended to include 'No teeth'&nbsp;because that would certainly help keep out some of the riff-raff (and at least one of my ex-boyfriends).&nbsp; Of course, in Nashua, this would probably cut down on their clientele by at least half.  &nbsp;  We were hoping to bump into our kickboxing instructor again, but after last time, I wouldn't be surprised if he never goes back to Martha's worried he'll be accosted by his two psycho students.  &nbsp;  The highlight of the night though was just at the end when&nbsp;this guy&nbsp;said to me 'You're Kate is great (k8isgr8)!&nbsp; I've been enthralled with your blog for about a week and a half now!'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Seriously, this kind of thing should happen far more often as far as I'm concerned.&nbsp; And more people should be around when it does.&nbsp; Then he bent down and started kissing my toes.&nbsp; I'm just kidding, that part didn't happen...but it should have.   And just in general news, to the rest of my fanbase, I'll be making a public&nbsp;appearance at the Rockingham Mall in Salem, NH today at about 5:30 p.m.&nbsp;for autographs and pictures.&nbsp; Please contact Jason Palmer, my publicist, for further details.   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dreams: Just before bed last night I was reading my celebrity bible (People) and catching up on the happenings of my two favorite cuties, Mary-Kate and Ashley (come on MK, you can pull through!)  So of course I have a dream that I have twins.  Actually it was more like a nightmare.  I continue to have this recurring dream that I have a baby (in this case twins) and I am the most horrible mother ever known.  Now this would probably not surprise Jason as he thinks I don't have a maternal bone in my body.  But in my dream I can't seem to get anything right.  I forget to strap the car seat in, baby goes flying.  I forget to keep an eye on it in the bath, baby goes under.  I forget to feed it all day, baby starves.  Honestly, it makes me wake up with a horrible feeling.  I do want kids some day, but maybe this is a sign I should just have a lot of cats.  They don't require nearly as much work.  I bet Jason feels pretty damn confident right about now that I'm babysitting for him Monday.  Accomplishments: So last night my roommates are both extremely selfish and never come home to cook me dinner.  Bastards.  So I look in the fridge and find the easiest thing possible, hot dogs.  But K8 can't have just any hotdogs, they need to be cooked on the grill.  Well, I'm 26-years old, and I have literally never lit a grill in my life, but I watched my roommate's boyfriend light the grill last week.  Piece of cake, right?  So I turn the valve on the gas, turn the knobs on the grill, grab the big, long lighter thingy and shove it in the hole on the side and press the trigger to get a flame.....then BOOM!  20 ft. flames everywhere.  So I immediately hit the deck to Stop, Drop, and Roll like we learned in 2nd grade.  I've never been so scared in my life I almost shit my pants.  I had visions of the house as smoldering ashes so I didn't even dare to look.  Luckily though, no harm no foul.  I picked myself up and turned the gas down a smidge, everything is hunky dorey.  And now I am a grill master.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's Hump Day once again.  It's grey and rainy and I have a cold.  Who gets a cold in July?  What the frick?  I have a really sore throat and I couldn't even belt out any songs from the radio on my way home from work.  Boo.  I get 1 radio station.  At least it's a good one (The River for those of you in the Boston area), maybe not my first choice (that would be FNX), but good nonetheless.  I like the River, they say 'Independent Radio for Independent Thinkers' or something to that effect, It makes you feel cool like  yeah, I'm an independent thinker. Damn the man and damn his corporate radio . My roommate (the girl) is really bothered by the fact that I don't have a CD player in my car, or that I haven't cared to fix my antenna.  I'm not sure why this bothers her so much because it's not like she rides in my car ever.  (Ok, maybe once in a GREAT while).  But I just don't care.  My car gets me where I need to go, and I do get a decent radio station (most of the time).  I also don't change the channel when the commercials come on when I'm watching TV.  She's one of those people.  I don't mind commercials.  I'm like a marketing execs wet dream.  Give me a cool commercial and I'm down to the store the next day buying whatever it is.  Yup, that's me, just another mindless consumer sheep following the mass-produced loving herd. I definitely deserve to listen to independent radio.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I must have thought that I'd already mentioned the reference to the Backstreet Boys in my last post.  To my faithful readers who check my blog every 30 seconds (you know who you are), I do apologize for any confusion.  When I Googled frick & frack this is what I learned:  From www.worldwidewords.org:  [Q] From Kevin Mcgrath: “Do you know where the phrase Frick and Frack originated? I’m sure it wasn’t because of the Back Street Boys.”  [A] The phrase has become a fairly common one in North America for any two people who are closely connected in some way. The Random House Historical Dictionary of American Slang cites it as being Black English, but it certainly has a wider circulation than that.  For example, this appeared in Newsday in September 1999: “Msgr James Lisante is quite correct in referring to Rudolph Giuliani and Hillary Rodham Clinton as ‘Frick and Frack’ on the abortion issue”. Or this one from the Toronto Star in June the same year: “He and Samaranch were like Frick and Frack”. So it’s reasonable enough that Brian and Nick of the Back Street Boys should use the nicknames Frick and Frack for each other.  The origin is ultimately in a famous partnership of Swiss comedy ice skaters, Werner Groebli and Hans Mauch, whose stage names these were. They came to public fame in the later years of a series of skating spectaculars called Ice Follies, promoted by Eddie Shipstad and his brother Roy, which began in 1936 and ran for almost 50 years. Their association lasted so long, and they were at one time so well known, that their names have gone into the language.   Some care may be needed in using the phrase, as it is said also to be a Black American English slang term for the testicles.   Ok, so the first time I didn't read it through all the way, and now I realize that we could have been being compared to a pair of testicles.  So which one am I?  The one that hangs a little lower?  Surely Jason has to be the hairy one... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      About the whole Backstreet Boys thing... I guess I don't really mind the possible reference as I do try to live my life like an international pop star.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday the receptionist at work said that me and Jason were like Frick & Frack.  I had to look it up on the internet to find out what the frick she was talking about.  This morning Jason wouldn't walk to Heav'nly Donuts with me to get coffee because the selfish bastard stopped on his way into work.  The receptionist even said something when I left by myself.  He's so not my Frack anymore.  And then the selfish bastard drank my last pink lemonade.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm pretty sure the woman at Heav'nly Donuts substituted my requested Splenda with one of those other lesser quality sweeteners today.  This is the same woman who makes up her own prices for everything, so you never pay the same amount twice for your coffee.  She's always the friendliest one at the counter, she calls everyone 'honey,' and remembers your order from day to day, so you always feel a little bit special when you get to order from her.  Then you walk back to your office and you realize she just charged you $10.32 for a medium coffee and an english muffin.  But what disturbs me most is how someone can be so callous about switching sweeteners!  Coffee is a very personal experience, and when you ask for Splenda you expect Splenda goddamnit!  Let this be a warning to you donut lady...I've got my eye on you!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so continuing with the theme of my blog (or at least what seems to be the theme) let's talk about sex.  So there's the whole idea about how when girls and guys reveal the 'number' that guys always inflate theirs 3 times and girls deflate theirs 3 times.  So this leads to the whole double standard of guys being studs if they sleep with a lot of people and girls being sluts.  But my question is, if these guys want lots of sex with lots of different people, who the hell do they think they're gonna get it from if girls aren't more liberated with their sexuality????    I will admit that I have lied about my number on occasion.  The ones I have left out in past: Mr. premature ejaculation, Mr. so drunk couldn't keep it up, and Mr. so big it wouldn't fit (and for the record guys, bigger does NOT necessarily mean better).  But technically, by all definitions of intercourse, it was sex.  But anyway, to continue with the debate...what does knowing someone's number really gain you about their experience???  Someone could have been with 20+ people (so you expect them to be a very skilled lover), but if they were all one-night stands then the person probably hasn't learned anything (other than being an expert smooth-talker).  And someone else could have been with only 1 person ever, but if it was a long-term relationship...they most likely have experimented, have explored the other person's body at length, have had raw animal sex AND made love, have taken the time to learn how to please someone besides themselves, etc. etc. etc.  I used to be obsessed with knowing how many people my boyfriends had been with before me.  But all that fills me with is questions rather than answers and I no longer care about history because of it.  Besides, all too often, the number of people they've been with before you isn't always the same number plus just 1 at the end of your relationship anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was brought to my attention by a friend that it's actually only been 1 week since I kissed someone (that friend).  Stupid alcohol and stupid blackouts!  I don't even remember it to have enjoyed it.  Bummer.  Snogging is so fun.  I love the word snogging.  It's so cool.  I have a new blog topic, but I don't want to write it in this posting.  I'll start a new one.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was just on the MSN webpage and there was a link that caught my eye.  'Ten reasons to be single.'  So of course I clicked on it to read why MSN thinks I should relish in being single.  In actuality it was a list of 'excuses' to use as to why you're still single.  For example, it's summer and everyone is on vacation, so there's no one around to date.  Ok, when I have to start using excuses like 'everyone is on vacation,' I should just give up!  Besides, at my age, everyone's already taken anyway (as Jason is so happy to point out), so that's all the excuse I need!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I've decided to keep count how long it's been, regarding sexual exploits.  When you live in Singles Land, sex really IS all you think about.  (I've mentioned this before, that really isn't just me, is it?)  So, for the record....it's been 2 weeks since my last kiss, and 6 weeks since I last got laid.  (Actually, I probably know a few married people for whom it's been longer...)  But, one thing you won't see in this blog, faithful readers, are names.  Because it's not polite to kiss and blog.  Plus then, who would buy my Heidi Fleiss-esque tell-all book?? (Ok, probably not best to compare myself to Hollywood's most notorious Madame/hooker)  *SIGH* if only.... (just kidding)
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My car wouldn't start this morning.  I've decided rather than it being a dead battery, that a witch has put some voodoo hex on my car.  I almost took it as just a sign that I wasn't supposed to go into work today, but I didn't think my boss would accept "practicing my religious beliefs" (my religion being fatalism) as a good enough excuse not to come in today.  Especially since Jason lives right down the road, and he's such a slacker, I KNEW he wouldn't have left his house yet when I called him to give me ride.  We're going to try to jump my car after work.  If that's not a success, I guess I'll have to go to the market for bat's tails and lizard legs and try to reverse the voodoo.  oh the trials and tribulations....
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So it was my first 4th of July back in the U.S. in 5 years.  For the past 4 years I'd been living in England for the 4th.  You can imagine how excited they get over it.  The first year I made a cake with white frosting for all my friends.  In red and blue icing I wrote 'We kicked your ass and loved it' on the top.  (They get a bit touchy about the whole thing over there).  Anyway, so I experienced my first Indepence Day fireworks in 5 years and actually got to light some myself (and I'm still here to talk about it) so that's pretty cool.  I was at Jason's house for a big bash and was the only single person at the party.  Being around all married couples for a whole day really makes you never want to get married, it also makes you want to get really really drunk.  Despite my best efforts, somehow I failed at that (getting drunk, not staying unmarried, just for clarification).  Normally on a night out I have 3 goals: 1) wake up in my own bed 2) wake up alone 3) wake up without my contacts in (but preferrably in their containers, not on my pillow).  I adjusted my goals specifically for this night: number 2 became wake up without any married men.  And for god's sake, don't wake up married! ha.  Needless to say, no action this weekend.  I do have my 'annual exam' at the gynecologist after work today...but that's not exactly the action I was hoping for...ho hum...so is the life of a single girl...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, it's Friday night around 20 minutes to 8:00, and I've got BIG plans tonight, BIG BIG plans.  The anticipation is probably going to kill me before it actually happens, but I'm now sitting here waiting and figured I'd spend the time wisely, by updating my blog which I haven't done since last weekend.  I can't talk about, I do apologize faithful readers, but I don't want to jinx anything.  It IS Friday the 13th after all.  Oh god, I probably shouldn't have even written that.  Oh well too late now.  So what can I talk about in the meantime?  What's going on right now.  Well, I turn 27 in 3 days, and I actually completely forgot until a couple days ago.  I have nothing planned, and I'm really not that bothered about it.  I've been focusing too much on my sister's birthday next month.  She's turning 21 and I absolutely cannot wait!!  I've been waiting sooooo long for us to be able to go out together and now it's almost here.  So, I'm not sure what the plans are for her birthday, but if anyone is in the Boston area on September 18th please get in touch!!  Ok, no more waiting.  Gotta go.  Will update soon, I promise!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so it's been like 6 days - I think officially the longest I've gone without an update. And now I've probably lost even the like 2 people who read this thing. So apologies for keeping you (two) in suspense, but I'm back, and I've got some updating to do!  So this weekend I took an NRA certified gun course, and even got this cool certificate that I'm so framing and showing to everyone I know. It reads 'The National Rifle Association of America Awards this certificate to [me] for successful completion of the NRA Personal Protection In The Home Course.' No clue why I think it's so cool, I'm not even Republican, but anyway. I would just like to point out, however, that on the website for the firing range where the course was located a special offer is explained that if you mention that you listen to Rock 101 you'll get a 25% discount off a machine gun rental. Right, like Rock music isn't already in the shit enough as it is, being blamed for violence and whatnot...now they're gonna put machine guns in the hands of the listeners (at a savings of $8.75!). Nice one.  So the course was about like what to do and how to react and position yourself with your gun and everything if someone attacks you. Then when we were shooting something unexpected happened, my  own  gun was what actually attacked me. I was shooting a 9mm semi-automatic and one of the shells, when ejecting from the chamber, actually jumped down my shirt and got wedged between my boob and my underwire bra. In case there is anyone who doesn't understand the simple chain of events when the trigger is pulled...long story short...the gun powder inside the shell casing explodes sending the bullet flying at ridiculous velocity...ok, keyword =  explosion  which means intense heat which means brass shell casing is scorching hot which means K8 now has the most attractive blister right on the crease of the underside of my left boob. Niiiiiiiiiice. And let me tell ya, Leftie is none too happy about it either. Also to explain, it was policy that we had to fire all our shots before we could set our gun down again. So I had to sit there with scorched boobie trying to fire the rest of the bullets from the magazine as quickly as possible! Ouch!!! And also of course I had about 20 guys offering assistance and suggesting they hold cold compresses against it to make it all better. Riiiiiiiight. Like  that's  gonna happen. Needless to say, I much preferred shooting my .38 special revolver. Although, the .357 magnum fucking kicks ass and how cool is it to shoot a gun that actually has flames come out the side! But that was the bodyguard's personal firearm, he let me shoot it special. He also offered me his services for personal use. I told him my entourage isn't big enough yet.  I would also just like to mention that pretty much the coolest thing ever was watching this 80-year old biddy with a portable oxygen tank strapped to her body shooting alongside everyone else. It reminded me of that song/game on Sesame Street 'One of these things is not like the others...one of these things just doesn't belong.'  Oh yes, I can see Big Bird now... 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Awwwwwww.  My roommate feels poo.  I cooked him eggs.  (That's not why he feels poo, just for the record).
     

    
</post>


</Blog>