<Blog>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          This is my first post, as indicated by the title. I began this as a way to spend my many wasted hours doing no more than before. That may not make much sense, I am aware, but I really can't think of any other reason to publish thoughts on the world wide web for so many to read and subsequently use against me, as is the custom. I just want to try something new and not have to leave the house. Perhaps I shall meet someone I can get along with. I've been on message boards before and usually end up with a new friend. Oooh I have so many, my oh my! Actually I have 3 good friends and that's enough. The rest can just fuck off. I don't care what anybody does as long as they leave me out of it. Seriously, go ahead and kill someone, go ahead and kill yourself, just don't involve me. I'm already a fuck-up and an outcast. God, I feel like Sonny. "No, they're not gonna shoot you!" I love movies. Did you know that? No? Ah yes, you have no real idea of what I am because this is most likely our first introduction. In that case, I better shut up before you decide the best thing to do is to hurt me.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know why I'm posting anything at all. I'm bored out of my mind and feel like shit but that's nothing new so why post? Seriously, what am I doing here?! I'm not contributing to anything, I have no significance in this world. I'm  fucking  nothing, so why am I here? Sometimes I feel like I just woke up and where am I, what am I doing, just who am I is something I can't comprehend. I feel like I'm watching myself and I'm not real or it's all just feeling, not reality. When I get like that I scare myself. I'm so weirded out I feel horrible. It is not enlightening, if anything it's frightening that I can acknowledge my being and yet, well, somehow be someone else when I realize it. No, I'm not on drugs and have not been drinking. I'm just in a ranting mood. I feel sick to my stomach now and even more afraid. I'm going to go now. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm God's lonely man  I'm God's lonely man  Trapped in this unholy land  Roaming it undetected, unprotected  I have no one to turn to  I'll burn in hell, you'll burn, too  You're just like them all  You'll stumble and fall  Into this pit of flames  Into my endless pain  Try to end it  Try to help it  If I work hard enough  Wash away all the scum  I can better myself  Climb right out of this hell  Damn the angel, fuck that cunt  Sharpened razor, loaded guns  Free her from her misery  Shred her chains of slavery  I was sent to take her away  From night into day  I can see better in the darkness  But she has to go back to her world  For I'm God's lonely man  I'm God's lonely man    This loneliness is everywhere  And I can't escape it  But I'll help you make it through  Kill them all just for you  You've seen what I can do  Now the one I left wants to reach me  She thinks I'll pull her out that easily  But I still have to live  I'm God's lonely man  Have to clean up that shit  For I'm God's lonely man  Can't sleep, have so much to fix  I'm God's lonely man  I'm still half in that pit  I'm God's lonely man...     8-23-03     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The thought of suicide has occured to me on several occasions. It would be almost impossible to pinpoint the first of these instances but only because I remember acknowledging the fact at a very young age. I once stated so matter-of-factly to my elder brother that it was something I had considered. Looking back, I was almost proud. I don't know why. It seems like such a cowardly thing to do at times and sometimes like a task only the bravest of the brave can undertake. I never think of Kurt Cobain as a coward. Never have I hated him for going away like so many fans seem to have. The reacton to a self-imposed death is always queer. An ever-changing perspective on the how and why of it all. Is it really so horrible to end it all? Is it really so mean to take yourself away and leave your loved ones with a simple memory of you and not the troubles you had and would bring? I always hear others remember the deceased with such pride and love and everlasting respect that why would it seem so taboo to consider going out on top? Like a comedian who's told a joke that has the audience errupting into laughs and floating on the sounds of joy and humor, why would he try to top himself when it's as good as it gets? I don't know. Maybe because you never  want  to die when it's so good. If things can be this great why not shoot for the stars and try and be this happy all the time? Yeah, that makes sense but we all know that sometimes it has to stop. It can't be built upon, it can't get better. At some point you have to admit there's nothing more for you to do. And when you admit it to yourself, admit you can never be as great as you want to be, you get down. You fall down, land on your head and your dreams and are left with nothing more than a fleeting instant in which you were king. That one second when you could do it all and had it all. Everything was perfect. But it's all down hill from ther, kiddo. There's no more. It stops and you have to go back to where you came from, be it the cement of sidewalks or the cold you feel in an empty apartment that's never been anybody's 'home'.  Yeah, life sucks, you get your highs and then you don't and then you die. 
    
</post>


</Blog>