<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Terrorists want...what? Eradication of Wester civilization, supremacy of Islam.  OK, why? Will their lives be better, will they have access to better medical care, education, wealth, better schools, freedom and justice for all?  The right to live their lives as they see fit, and all within their range of terror have to do the same.  I just don't seem able to fully grasp their reasoning. Perhaps there isn't any. 

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Working on a test pass in english and french, made easier by altavista and side by side comparisions of text.  

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Test.  

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So all these nations send help to rebuild the nation of Iraq and create prosperity, democracy, improve health, food supplies, education, etc.  The terrorists realize that if those helping succeed the support for terrorist will evaporate.  The Iraq civilians are stuck in the worst possible situation, accept the help of others and be victimized by terrorists, spurn the help of others and be victimized by the terrorist when they take power.    urlLink My Way News  

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Office&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The Office. &nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Outsourcing: Can you blame companies for doing it?  To hire an employee in America is expensive, there are government regulations, insurance, health insurance, vacations, facilities, etc to pay for.  The companies didn't make the situation expensive, they're trying to survive in an environment that makes it attractive to outsource.  The answer is to make keeping jobs in country attractive.  A good idea might be to, I don't know, LOWER TAXES!! My job is in danger of outsourcing, if it happens I won't blame the company I work for, I'll blame those that made it so damn expensive to pay me, and we all know who that is.  

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I watched some of the presentation that Kerry did last night.  If you knew nothing else about the guy you'd think his entire career has been about being a Vietnam vet!        His senatorial career was briefly mentioned, which is strange because he's been a senator a lot longer than he was a soldier.  When Clinton was running for office Kerry said that what some one was doing during that period has no bearing on their fitness for presidential office.  Now it's his main point for running for the office.        The truth is that he's seen the mood and direction of the country and customized his presentation to fit it. Strong on military, tax cuts, defending the borders are the focal points of this election, he realizes that his senatorial voting record is the opposite of that.        No problem, just ignore that record and direct all attention to the military aspects of his career.  Ignore his anti-war position after getting out of the military, ignore the accusations against his fellow soldiers of atrocities, ignore the voting against increased spending for military and intelligence, ignore the record that other Democrats describe as reliably liberal.  Repeat the three Purple Hearts story ad nausem.       I really don't think this will work for him.  

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We reserved a room with a view of Elliot Bay 6 months ago to view the fireworks show Ivars Acres of Clams does each year.  I'll spare you the build up and just say there was a building in the way and so all we could see was the fireworks reflected on the water.  But who cares!!  Julian discovered he likes calamari, really he does!  He ate a whole appetizer of squid and octopus and wanted more the next day. He also spent 15 minutes making Laura and I struggle not to cry.  We sat down for dinner and the waiter brought Julian a colouring place mat and crayons.  Instead of colouring things in he writes a letter, it's all just scribbles of course but he narrates out what he's writing. He "writes" that his Mummy is very sweet and he loves her so much, that Justin is his brother and he loves him very much too and that he's also very sweet. Stimpy the cat gets the same treatment and I even get mentioned, "Daddy gets angry at me sometimes when I'm naughty but it's OK because I love him and he loves me." That few minutes redeemed several months of naughty. I love my kids.  

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There is some concern that terrorist will try to f*ck up the celebrations and Seattle may be a target.  Bollocks to them!! We're not going to give the life hating, inhumane bastards have the satisfaction of seeing my family cower in fear.  

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   First day of vacation and it's drizzling!  I must be in Washington. I'm taking the family  to a hotel in Seattle for the 4th of July and we'll watch the fireworks from Ivars show from the hotel.  Laura had little to no fun last year due to being on bed rest so in December we planned out some fun things to do and reserved the hotel room with a view 6 months in advance.  Get a good rate that way.  

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Saddam gets a trial?  They have to build a case against him?  Did any of his victims get that? A public hanging done by someone with little experience at hangings so the job has to be done more than once sounds like the right thing to do.  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Kerry has put a lot of effort since spending four whole months in Vietnam bad mouthing the war, his fellow soldiers and any one that wanted to increase military or intelligence budgets.  Now he wants to be President based on his time in Vietnam.  This is a contradiction to everything he's done since getting out of the Navy.  This contradiction is why he will fail in November.   

						
</post>


</Blog>