<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i just wish it was monday and this stupid weekend was over. oh and by the way, welcome to my secret journal. i wont update it that often but i'll use it when i cant write publicly.  so last night i went online and i was getting harassed by bobs new boyfriend. like really harassed. it had me upset for a while. i'm going to tell my mom about it, and have her drive me over to bobs so i can give him his stuff back. if that means throwing it at his house and driving away, so be it. somehow i really dont think bob was there like his bf said he was. because the other night when we were arguing and i told him i wanted him out of my life (with good reason, trust me) he was actually good about it and said if  i ever needed someone to talk to he'd always be there. whcih made me feel bad, along with all the other guilt trips he gave me. but honestly, my friends hate him, i hate his friends. he does drugs, he's always been a little sketchy, and it just wouldnt work with us as friends. but still, he was nice about it and stuff.  and then his bf was talking all this shit thats NOT TRUE and he was like i'll tell all your friends. but even if bob was in on that, he only has a few screen names. if bob tells you anything about me it probably isnt true. that kid made up so much stuff and he just kept swearing and threatening me.  i really wanted this whole bob thing to go away. i want to forget it ever happened, but its so god damn hard. bob really hurt me and i still dont think he's got that through his thick skull. in one of our earlier arguments he said he "never stayed friends with his ex's usually" but now he's like i miss you i want you to stay and talk to you. but who knows- maybe he was just saying that so i would trust him and he could do something bad to me? i dont trust him one bit right now. but it IS possible that his bf got drunk or whatever and started saying all that last night, being overly protective and stuff. i mean yea, maybe i did hurt bobs feelings telling him i wanted him out of my life. but you really cant blame me, he was scaring me and i just wanted it to end.  so i'm going to tell my mom all about it, even though thats like the pussy thing to do or whatever. i always tell my mom everything and i dont care what anyone else says.  from the way i was being threatened, had i saved the IM, i could have gotten that kid in loads of trouble. but i didnt savei t, i just wanted it to stop. so i signed on my secret sn (which will now become my normal one, and i'll make a new secret one) because i dont want bob or anyone of his friends talkign to me on astarael anymore. as much as i love that sn...i have to let it go.  people have been so mean lately. that, and someone had left a nasty comment on my journal, and that whole thing that happened with vanessa. i just want stupid people to die. just make them all go away.  i mean seriously, i'm the injured party here, and i'm the one being threatened. its not fair, i didnt do anything that bad that would warrant that.  my weekend has sucked too. after that, i had to work all day today and it was really boring. i finished hp 2 and 3, and i just wanted to go home and read them instead. it was freezing at work, that damn blower...  it was nathans birthday, and dad & diane took him matthew and katie out to the rainforest cafe (like my fave restaraunt ever) at the burlington mall but didnt take me. because i was at work. then they picked me up (45 minutes late) and my dad ordered me that grilled chicken sandwich i usually get at tonys. and i ate, alone.  we watched some old home movies and that was fun, but diane always seems to love when she can make fun of katie and i in an evil way. its not very nice but whatever.  i ended up falling asleep, and dad woke me up and we all went to bed. so i finished the last chapter of HP and came out here. i really wanted to talk to like lyd or vanessa but neither was on, and i didnt want to risk calling lyd, since sometimes she calls me back and if that happened here it owuld be bad...i wish i could call though :/  its almost 11:11  so todays songs were "broken" by seether & amy lee and "my happy ending" by avril.  my happy ending is the epitome of me and bob. it is THE me and bob song. blah, blah bob and i, i know.  lemme paste the lyrics in here.   ===============  oh oh, oh oh, So much for my happy ending, oh oh, oh oh, So much for my happy ending, Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh  Let's talk this over It's not like we're dead Was it something I did? Was it something You said? Don't leave me hanging In a city so dead Held up so high On such a breakable thread  You were all the things I thought I knew And I thought we could be  CHORUS: You were everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending oh oh, oh oh, so much for my happy ending Oh oh, oh oh  You've got your dumb friends I know what they say (they say) They tell you I'm difficult But so are they (so are they) But they don't know me Do they even know you? (even know you) All the things you hide from me All the shit that you do (all the shit that you do) You were all the things I thought I knew And I thought we could be  [CHORUS]  It's nice to know that you were there Thanks for acting like you cared And making me feel like I was the only one It's nice to know we had it all Thanks for watching as I fall And letting me know we were done  He was everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending   You were everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending oh oh, oh oh, so much for my happy ending Oh oh, oh oh, so much for my happy ending  oh oh, oh oh, oh oh, oh oh oh oh,...   ================  nothing better works too but not as good. im the girl and he is the guy in that song.  "i feel i must interject here, you're getting carried away feeling sorry for yourself with these revisions, and gaps in history..." such a good song i   so diane gave me a card with $60 in it from them for my bday, which is good. my party is tommorow over here. its more nathans party, since nathan...never mind. but its like i'm always pushed off to the side, which is ok since he lives here and i dont really. i'm going in to work at 11:30 and im getting picked up at 1. how RETARDED is that? i wanted to get picked up later but it looks like i cant. jamie's not going to be too pleased about that, but he probly wont even find out. i'll just make loads of extra cookies and make sure the place is brimming with cups and juice and popcorn and shit before i leave. it'll last a few hours.  then i'll come here, party it up, and sleep over AGAIN. i really want to go home, that'd be a great birthday present. but of coures the parents are out and dad wants to watch us. whatever. i can stay here longer i just wanna be alone and thats impossible here. it really really is. if i'm alone for 2 seconds i'm being "antisocial" and its like jesus maybe i'm sick of being social. i'm constantly social, i just need some time to myself. i've been like miserable lately.  so i talked to vanessa about that person and i feel really stupid about it now. i'm sick of obsessing over guys and getting convinced that i have a chance with them. you all remember the last time that happened. and this time i really had no facts. i just saw the kid hanging around with a bunch of girls. god i'm pathetic. but vanessa didnt seem to care and thats good. she doesnt think im a loser. lol. its actually not loserly..i just feel like it is.  i just wish i could FIND SOMEONE GOOD who's not a freakin psycho. this andrew kid i've been talking to is awesome, but i feel like i dont reall know him that well and he does live in gardner which is a big problem.  and i still have other things to worry aobut. though proactiv has cleared alot off my face, it basically showed me that i have ALOT OF SCARRING. and that takes a few months, not just a few weeks, to treat. i have stuff for that but its just so annoying. i wish i wasnt such an idiot when i was younger. i really do hate myself sometimes, i look horrible now and everyone keeps telling me i dont but i really do look horrible. however, i didnt take it so badly until someone mentioned that in that nasty comment they made. nobody has made fun of me for this before. its not fucking fair.  i'm so sick of karl being at home all the time. it seems like he's always off from work or something. he's always hanging around, its so annoying. michelle's always watching tv downstairs and has to stare at me as i pass. its like get up off your fat ass and find something better to do. besides molesting your brothers friends.  ugh. so i'm sorry to dump all my misery on you all, but you dont have to read this journal. this is mostly for me, and for anyone i trust enough to read it. i'm thinking em, lyd, nate, and vanessa. i tell them like everything.  i just signed off AIM. i was on for a half hour and nobody was really on so whats the use. sigh.  you know, i feel like i've totally lost nicole. we havent talked like all summer, and she iddnt invite me to her party. and thats like a major blow. i defended her all year when people made fun of her and this is the thanks i get. i thought she was my friend. it wouldnt be as bad if she still talked to me, but its like i'm not her friend anymore. blerg.  i'm scared of the whole bob thing, to be honest. i mean he does know where i live, and my friends screen names, my adress, my phone number, like anything he would need. his bf just needs to get him drunk and who knows what could happen. i dont trust them at all. i just want him out of my life. i wish i could rewind and make it all go away.  listening to come clean today, the whole lets go back, back to the beginning thing. i pictured that night. forward to time past played (however unexpectedly and appropriately) and i pictured myself blocking his sn before he IMed me. the date was may 11th. we would have never met, i would have never told mary alice i was going for a walk, came back all sweaty from running, never would have taken that shower, would have just watched more of harry potter and the chamber of secrets with them and played pictionary like we did that night. it wouldn't have been as exciting as it was as it happened, but all this shit wouldnt have happeend. who knows? maybe he would have stayed with meg, and things would have been different with him. sure, i'd lose all the good times i had with him..but i think the bad times outweigh the good. and he was sketchy and i hated his friends except meg. and meg probably hates me now.  i pictured myself erasing the past and starting over clean and smiled.  if only that were possible...
    
</post>



</Blog>