<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday - End of the week  -First lesson, British History.  -Funnily enough not doing British History. -That would be common sense. -Instead doing a project on fucking Oxted. -Why? Because teachers feel the need to waste time and complain later that they have no time to teach us. -WASTE OF LESSON NUMBER 1  -Second lesson, Politics -Funnily enough didn't do politics. -That would also be common sense -Instead watched a Nazi Propaganda video and some boring old documentary with a presenter that did nothing but stutter -Why? Well - I doubt it's going to get me through my American Politics exam.  School is a fucking waste of time at the moment.   Other stuff  -I get the joys of serving drink to the new year 6's coming to school on Wednesday because I am House Captain. Woo hoo. They can dehydrate as far as I'm concerned. Lets hope it's raining heavy. They can then drink the rain water. If not I'll direct them to the water fountain - Lot easier!  -I also get the joys of going to Year 8 camp on Thursday for a BBQ. No doubt Wednesday will be my last post before I'm trapped in bed with food poisoning!   VANESSA OUT OF THE BIG BROTHER HOUSE. Note to myself - When I next see Davina running up Kirsties house. Give her a slap and telling her to stop doing poor Marco impressions. They ARE SO TERRIBLE :-P  Anyway - Got to go. All the complaining is out of my system.  Ge0rge
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         How does it go again ... "I'm lovin it" wasn't it!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok - Sixth Form has wasted half of my week!   Monday - Back to school for a fucking UCAS day. UCAS is the system you use to apply for university. Anyway - I went to the assembly and was embarassed because I brought back 5 bags of prospectuses from an open day. I was then embarassed again when my politics teacher read out my personal statement to the whole of Detillens. What a WANKER!  So therefore I decided I had heard all of this before and went to the park for the rest of the day.  Tuesday - University trip to Sussex. What a fucking SHIT HOLE that was. Went on some tour around the "campus" and looked at Law. The teacher was a nerd and the tour guide was a twat. Anyway - Got bored of that after a while and sat on the grass with mates for another 2 and a half hours. Although - I have now decided I want to spend SIX bloody years at university to become a Lawyer.  Wednesday - We had RELIGIOUS EDUCATION morning. WOOOOOOOOO! Not. Some Xian guys came in and made us "President for the day". We had to take control of an African country and decide what to do with the economy. Naturally, we fucked it up and the citizens rebelled and shot him. However, We did eventually do it with the moral that loans taken my LEDC's are going on forever due to the high interest rates. BOOOORIIINGG. Missed the last hour of that. I respect religion but I do NOT like it thrown in my face.  So that was my boring waste of a week!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Good old Rhea   Just to inform myself what happened last night at Rheas party. Anyway - It was wicked ... We had party food like Sausage Roll and those yummy party rings.   Anyway - Me and Sarah gave Rhea our joint present of a .... wait for it ... fairy outfit! and you can tell it was cheap because it either didn't fit or broke. But anyway - You get what you pay for ... utter crap!  We watched Scary Movie 3 and the only part I found REALLY hilarious was the bit where a man says "What have you done to my Daughter" to this person with a blanket over them. And when he pulls off the blanket it's Michael Jackson! HEHEHE. It's not as good as the others because they are running out of ideas but hey - it was ok overall.  Anyway - I'm going to go now and poo out all of those party rings I ate ... PAINFUL!  Bye
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok ... now I'm pissed off   After going to see my tutor today for my progress meeting, which happened to be 15 minutes late and last 25 minutes too long, I met up with Kirstie and went down to the park.  We were having lunch blah blah blah and Kirstie, who sadly bought Harry Potter stickers and has a crush on Alan Rickman (who plays Snape) was looking through her stickers and got all excited when she found one of Snape. Ok - It's not cool to blag it. But these Pikeys/Townies/Chavs/Kevs (whatever you want to call them) told her to shut up.   I, quite frankly, thinks it's none of their business what we do in a public park. The two boys looked like they were going to pass out, probably too much information from school. (How do you spell A-N-D again!?) and the girls hair was so bleached it looked like she permanantley has her hair in a bucked of bleach!  So - I have now come to decision ... eventually ... that these sort of people need to be taken care of!  There are a number of options  1) We shoot them all - The "Bang Bang ... all gone" strategy would give me so much pleasure. Without them we wouldn't have hooligans, pay less benefits and all be safe knowing that when we go to get our wallet it's still there. Marks out of 10?    I give it 7. I don't want to be sent to jail!  2) We leave them alone - What a stupid idea! Less said the better.    I give it 3 marks. I won't give it a high mark as I suspect pikeys can't count past 4.   3) We start beating them up - Now this sounds like fun! The "Squish Squish" method sounds very tempting. However, I am not a bully so I give this one 5.  So it looks like I've found a strategy - Let the shooting begin!!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          JUST THOUGHT I'D SAY HELLO .... IN SHIT!    urlLink Rate My Poo 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Oh what an extremely fun day today was   Firstly my sister decided to use the computer, which is in my room, at about 7 o'clock today which meant waking me up and I swear I nearly bashed our modem in two because that noise it makes is not good in the morning.  Anyway, It's Rheas birthday (HAPPY BIRTHDAY) and I gave her the CD I brought her (Hits 58) and she seemed to like it :-D. Anyway ... Me, Rhiannon, Kareema, Rhea, Daniel and Sarah went to the park and sat down doing fuck all so that was well ... eh ... lazy.   Daniel kept nagging on about the Conservatives doing so well in the fucking elections. I'm telling you he's got to be the most sarcastic person I know, apart from my boss. He'd blah on about something and blah on about something else speaking absolute utter shite. I'm a labourite and Daniels a conservative so we clash politically.   However, I am excited about Big Brother tonight. Apparantely there was some sort of punch up in the house last night and I can't wait to see Marco being punched by Jason, GO ON - GIVE HIM A REASON TO SCREAM!!   Plan for the rest of the night: SLEEP and watch BB Plan for tommorow: Go to school to have interview and go to Rheas B-Day thingy at 6:30  GTG. Bye!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>