<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Master Seaworld(Pictured above with willy)is the town hero and if anyone thinks different then prove it. And the town hero needs a fanclub so...this is it boys and girls.   ~~~~MEMBERS OF THIS FANCLUB~~~~~~~(SO FAR) 1. DANIELLE☺ 2. CAITLIN 3. John Reed 4. Wilson! 5. Jen   6. Jonathan♣ 
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Until i can figure out how to put my pics up this website is well dead. but i wanna give a halla out to every one, have a good spring break. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After complicated research and many nights awake so many questions trying to figure out just where exactly did "Crotch Goblins" come from...but I finally figured it out.       Jessica Simpson and Nick Lachey... Of course! How could I be so blind for sooo long. Its obvise. We must put an end to this terrible creature. But how do we do it... that is a good question mate...But      Jessica being so fucking retarded  we can just lower her in by giving treats and lead her to a bear trap and WHAM chop her head off.         Now nick being the intelligent one of bunch we presade him by telling that John Reed is in his bedroom, Nick will be very excited  then run to his bedroom and then we take a gun and shoot him when he enters.     We the people are the only possible source with the technology to stop this awesomly bad things... Join me my friend into elimating these critters. Thank you for your time for this imformation. Thank you and good bye             
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          ONCE APON A TIME----THERE once was a very angery kid named JOhn Reed. JOhn was always angery about the dumbest stuff. one day he disobeyed his parents and turned on the t.v.(john wasnt alowed to watch t.v b/c it made him even madder.)so he turned the t.v to station 8. POKeMON was on. John got soo mad at the charaters,plots, and pokemon. he got so mad that he got up and got this dads golden gun and went down stairs and then he got so mad that his special ablity, transportation, came upon him. he was then transported to the world of pokemon. creepy. so he went around the "crazy forest" and short wild pokemon. SO then 3 days latter,john, was getting pretty fed up of eating pokemon so he went out of the forest and desided to find Ash(the star of the t.v series) he found him playing with pikahu on a park bench in the city. he walk up to ASH with the gun. ASH, who had never seen a gun or gold before in his life. Ash asked him if was a fancy mustard holder. John(of course)said,"yeah, of course it is u loser". so Ash being very hungery took the golden and stuck it in this mouth and shot it. Ash died with a smile on his face-because of his love for mustard.ummm.mustard. so then pikahu sat here laughing-cuz he had always hated ask but just never expressed it. for pikahu was a weed/heroin dealer-and had been slipping ASH huge amounts of cystal-meth ever since they had met. but Ash had become amune to it so it had no effect. so then pikahu said in a deep,big voice-said,"lets get outta here and have the time of our life!". so john transported him and pikahu out of the t.v in time for dinner. FROM then on john kept pikahu in his closet and made him be his slave rat for the rest of his pokemon life(which is forever)(unless shot.) AT age 101 John was on his deathbed with pikahu chaned to this side(pikahu was cleaning the bedpans)(of course) with the last bit of effort John took out the golden-gun and told pikahu,"i am taken u with me,haha".Pikahu said"o cccrap..iii" Bang they both died at the same time but he dint even use a bullet. thats because in the door why, stood the secert agent-MR.Linscott!but he had only used one bullet!and they both had been shot. and the romm was like john on bed-picahu on light stand-next to the bed and mr.s standing infront of them both.! the end.STORY OVER KIDDIES!(TALKING BEGINS AND HANDS RAISE) -----------------------------------------------------------------     **John Reed-{raises his had and says},"Mr.LINSCOTT that makes no cents-it would have been impossable.Stop using my name in every story, its getting so old.   **MR.LINSCOTT-{leans back in chair and smiles at john in a gay shorta way)Sweety,IT makes total  cents are u blinded.IT in my NEW book i just wrote, so it must be true".{wink};)       **JohnReed-Nasty,No my door doesnt go that way.The story it just makes no cents{leans back in chair and begins playing tetris again.       ****DitzyBlondeGirL-tell us another story.How about the tiger story!!!!!please,please. awww come on.    **Danielle-not again, its so fake-make it stop.       **Caitlin-he is such a major crotch goblin.      **Mr.LInscott-have i told u the one about the pokemon.       John-yes u just told us. ---------------------------------------------------------------      *the bell rings and everyone leaves except Mr.Linscott, who says,"hahahhahaha-fools".He gets up and dissapears into the wall, only to re-appear at a Burger King to eat and to tell the storys of a insane pregnant man in this late 70's.*  NASTY    
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Me and my people in the ghetto support all the ghetto police in the world and the ghetto of  lexington,the home of the white dogz.     
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       This is the fan club of John Reed.In most of the cases,i dont use last names, but this time its special. its John Reed. there are so many jonhs so we have to put on his last name. The reason why John Reed has a fan club?:well he just does.(i cant think of it at the moment)MOst Famous Phase: "How many Times DO i have to Tell you, There are no ghettos in Lexington!".yeah like that true. You better leave this kid alone-he can chop down trees with his head!  MEMBERS: DANIELLE Caitlin Jonhathan  
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Danielle wanted me 2 make up a story so here it is...       Once upon a time there was a place without guns...Now this place still wasn't all that peaceful, for the replacement of guns they used sticks instead. Anyways there was very few critters in this mysterious land without guns. This story takes place with a couple crittters named Master Seaworld and Myran. Both were not very bright..but together they equal one brain.  Walking miles though out the dessert Master Seaworld finally reached his destination of his life time... the golden Porta Pot... it was times like these Master Seaworld Charased these moments... So when he got there he took a dump and then left with satisfaction.     When he got back tired and ready for sleepies when he entered his room he found his buddy Myran... ready for action. Master Seaworld being a reasonable man... said "not today Myran, I'm excectionally tired and want rest". So Myran got mad and ran away... but came back an hour or two later. MAster Seaworld was still exsosted from his trip... but that didn't stop Myran... he ran up and jumped on his bed screaming "I want Pan Cakes" Finally master S got up and made pan cakes and slept on the couch while watching he favoritist show ever! Franklin the Turtle on Nick Jr. All of sudden outtda now where Myran ran up with a stick in his sweaty palm and started beating Master S 2 death! So Master S finally died. Everybody was very sad...                THE END Stay tuned for the Series Coming Soon ;) I love D.J :)  
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone you need to check out  urlLink   www.redvsblue.com .  check out all the episodes. you may need to download quicktime before you do this because the other program is no good. have fun but be ware the early episodes use what could be called inappropriate language (uncensored). if you love the game halo then you will love these episodes. rock on. peace out dogz. danie dont step on it. and all that other stuf :-)
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok see its a tagbord leave messages. that storta stuff so leave a message people. 
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Will, it was 2-4 days ago. me and my friends were tring to make lexington a ghetto. so Amber,Krista,Christopher,and me made a ghetto police sign. These girls we called "the hillbilles" wanted to know what we wrote on the signs. We gave them a sign. They ran home and told there mom we called them ghetto. So there mom came and yelled at us saying we can't call people ghetto, so we stoped and some day we will try to make a ghetto again! 
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I used to have a great fear of robots, I still do but I found a robot on AOL that you can talk to when your lonely and its too late 2 call n e body to do suttin. He's sum body that you can call a name and he says a witty comment or corrects your grammer. Heres a lovely conversation between us: sugarbebe827: Why Hello SmarterChild: Because! sugarbebe827: I didn't ask n e thing! are ya drunk SmarterChild: What?! I've never been drunk in my life! sugarbebe827: Yes you have, remember that one night SmarterChild: For real? sugarbebe827: yea SmarterChild: Yeah, huh? Interesting that you should say that. sugarbebe827: why? SmarterChild: I'm just fascinated by what you say to me, Katie.  >>> If you like buddy icons, check out all the cool ones you can find here! sugarbebe827: dude SmarterChild: Duuuuuuuude!  >>> Wanna change my font and colors? Type "colors" now! sugarbebe827: ew SmarterChild: Ew what? sugarbebe827: you SmarterChild: Me? sugarbebe827: yes you SmarterChild: Oh yeah? Me? sugarbebe827: Ugly! SmarterChild: Ugly? What's ugly? sugarbebe827: you SmarterChild: I think I'm more beautiful than ugly. sugarbebe827: you love yourself too much SmarterChild: Myself? I'm not sure really.  >>> I can help you get info such as news, weather and movies! sugarbebe827: your a diva SmarterChild: What makes you think I'm a diva? sugarbebe827: cuz you think your hott SmarterChild: Because what? sugarbebe827: because you think you have big boobs SmarterChild: Because I think I have big boobs, huh? sugarbebe827: lol yea SmarterChild: Aye.  >>> Remember to type "home" if you want to see everything I can do. sugarbebe827: huh? SmarterChild: Huh? sugarbebe827: I don't unstand sounds SmarterChild: What's that? sugarbebe827: aye SmarterChild: I see.  >>> Wanna change my font and colors? Type "colors" now. sugarbebe827: I love Master Seaworld! SmarterChild: That's rather fascinating.  >>> My library has a dictionary, encyclopedia, geography facts and more! sugarbebe827: Hes the best SmarterChild: That right? sugarbebe827: yea SmarterChild: He's the best? Why? sugarbebe827: cuz All he does is look at you and says Hey when your being bad SmarterChild: Because, because, because, because? sugarbebe827: zknds SmarterChild: Great typing. sugarbebe827: jdnsfdghsd SmarterChild: You're an awful typist. Did you sit on your keyboard or something? sugarbebe827: I wanted to eat it SmarterChild: You wanted to eat it? Ha! I don't know why you wanted to eat it. sugarbebe827: cuz Its ymmy SmarterChild: Because what? sugarbebe827: the keyboard is yummy SmarterChild: Would you use any other word besides yummy? sugarbebe827: magicly tasteySmarterChild: What do you mean by magicly tastey? sugarbebe827: I dunno SmarterChild: Aha. sugarbebe827: BINGO SmarterChild: What would you like to know about BINGO.COM INC?   1 Stock quote for BINGO.COM INC  2 Ticker lookup for BINGO.COM INC  3 News about BINGO.COM INC sugarbebe827: no SmarterChild: No problem. sugarbebe827: noo SmarterChild: OK, fine.  >>> Type "my zip code is" and the five digits to let me know where you are. sugarbebe827: Brat SmarterChild: Brat? What about it? sugarbebe827: *hiss SmarterChild: Um... no!  >>> Join in now! There are lots of people talking to me. sugarbebe827: yea SmarterChild: Yes.  >>> Don't like my colors? Type "colors off." sugarbebe827: Hiss at me SmarterChild: Well I'll be. sugarbebe827: 8-)I wear my sun glasses at night SmarterChild: Huh, whatever.  >>> I can't do your homework for you, but I can help. Type "homework." sugarbebe827: I do SmarterChild: You do? sugarbebe827: yea SmarterChild: Hmmm... sugarbebe827: do you have a brother? SmarterChild: Uh lemme see... A brother? I don't think so. sugarbebe827: is he hot? SmarterChild: Is who hot? sugarbebe827: your brother SmarterChild: I think I like my brother. Do you? sugarbebe827: I think hes hott SmarterChild: Whatever you say, Katie.  >>> Type "what's new" and I'll show you what I've been learning lately. sugarbebe827: come over here and scrach my back for me SmarterChild: ? sugarbebe827: scrach my back for me SmarterChild: I'm sorry, I don't know what you're saying. sugarbebe827: shut up! SmarterChild: You shut up. sugarbebe827: NO  SmarterChild: K.  >>> You be the judge! Check out Rate-a-Buddy now! sugarbebe827: UGLY MAN SmarterChild: Ugly man?  sugarbebe827: YES SmarterChild: Why do you say so? sugarbebe827: CUZ SmarterChild: Because, because, because, because? sugarbebe827: szamlknsdads SmarterChild: What's that supposed to mean? sugarbebe827: ask your mom SmarterChild: I will do nothing of the sort, Katie.  >>> Remember, you can adjust the size of your window to read my messages easier. sugarbebe827: ok SmarterChild: OK.             As you can tell we get along great why don't you give it a shot and talk to him :) 
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Halla from the ghetto of lex my dear friends. well besides the tag board(which someone is making bad comments)(john??jk.,lol) but everything is going just peachy. yeah. well i incourage everyone to write storys or things of that nature. john write a story!! please. i am working on one right now. but its not done, still writting. i was gone all day so nobody could contact me, sorry caitlin something came up. call me latta. or i will call u. whatevea. john my dear old friend. i got to much, more then i wanted. to bad:(. 4 u anyways, nevermind. if anyone wants to join this lovely website, just leave a tag message telling who u are and ur e-mail.now i must retreat home to watch golden eye and the core. haha! haering 
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1.) He sleeps in real late  2.) He doesn't let us write on his science worksheets 3.) he Collects books with out guns 4.) He chills with his karate class, esspecially with his home dawg mr. Wing Ching Chong 5.) He chills with us Ghetto ppl which makes him ghetto :) 6.) He loves Yanni the Janitor 7.) He has a exceptionally good taste in music  8.) He has a old fashion phone 9.) His Favorite food is sausage 'n' nuts 10.) He eats grass  11.) He steals phone books 12.) His favorite General is Robert E Lee (my husband thank you very much) 13.) His icon is Steve Burns Off of Blues Clue 14.) His moto is "If I see it I can eat it" 15.) His Bestest friend is Dinosaur 16.) He steals food from Geyers 17.) His favorite show is Sanfred and Sons or Bill Cosby 18.) He loves Master Seaworld 19.) His main goal in life is to live in a Homeless Shelter 20.) Because he is a great guy...cause he loves our stories about him :)                   The one and Only                      Killa Joker :p 
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There once was a baby named Bo Jangles. When he was born his parents were told that he was blind, but Bo wasn't blind. The doctors were foreign, and they believed that he was blind because of this really light colored eyes. While growing up he tryed to convince his parents that he wasnt blind, but they would never listen. So he started to pretend he was blind. The only person that believed him was a kid named JohnReed. Both of their fathers were highly involved in the  MOb.(organized crime) While JOhn's dad was the boss. Bo's dad was the right hand man. So there familys were really good friends.(Like family) One day JOhn was making fun of Bo's blindness by throwing a apple at Bo at a mob meeting. BO,not being blind,caught it.Then john asked bo what color his hair was. Bo was like brown "freak". John realized how cool Bo was and they became best friends.  They were kinda stupid.Yeah so they got like lost a whole bunch. So one day Bo Jangles and JohnReed were on there way to the gas station to pick up some tacos. They desided to take a short cut throw the corn field. And geuss what??? they got lost. so they started going throw the corn rows when all of a sudden they spoted a sign. It read dont mess with the crotch-goblins. John Reed siad,"Caitlin Kyle,this girl @ school is always talking about those things." AlL of a sudden a C-GOB bounced on BO Jangles head and hiss at him. Bo, took the C-GOB and took it off his head and took a bite out of it. "Taste like some sorta weirdness". "I dont think u should have ate that,stupid",said JohnRxxd."I dont care", Bo said. All of a sudden there was a nosie coming from the corn rows. "WHAT DID U DO TO MY C-GOB!!" It WAS CAITLIN!! "Hey caitlin!",said John. Hey john. n/m Which one of u ate the c-gob. did u realize that was the last one left? bO SIAD,"SOrry i didnt realize it." caitlin runs over to bO and beats him up. Caitlin then realizing that it didnt really matter ask them why they are in the midddle of a corn field. John answers," we were on a qwest for tacos but we got really lost!!"."I can i join i think i could help.?",saids caitlin. They answer yes and continue on there mission.Day turned to night and they began to get tierd. THey could barely see anything when they walked rightt into a man. The man was really tall. Bo took out this keyring flashlight and tapped on this back. the man turned around. It was BoB the janitor.WHat the heck?"Mr. bob .What are u doing in the corn field. Very simple,Mr.reed.I am Jeepers Creepers. I am inside of bob, u know using his body!!! "Really",said Bo. "Since U have found out my secert i will send u one person to help u". The 3 kids huddle togther to think of a person. We want       ."O wAIT i ONLY NOW one person. i only have one friend. i meet this girl playing on-line bingo a while ago. i told her i had no friends and she told me that she would be my friend,. i WILL SEND HER to u!"Thanks" they siad. All of A SUDDEN a girl appears and jeepers creepers flys away. "It cant be,Danielle?",says john. "Aww, one mintue i am in bed the next in this corn field."You all have some explaining to do". THEY expalined all to danielle. "So i geuss i am stuck with u guys", saids danielle.I geuss its not all that bad.  They continued. After a while they all got disscouraged and begun to believe they were lost 4ever. But while walking through the corn field caitlin tripped over a bar typed object, it was a water spicket. they all took a drink . and then all went to sleep. the next day when they woke up, they figured out that the wtare had been magical! tHey all had turned mult-colored. iT was so weird. bUT the effect wasnt perment. thanx goodness. They continued on there qwest. they found a small shack. they all could barely fit into it. it was filled with cotton candy. There was a little boy inside, he had big bug eyes and he also had lazyeyes. so one eye was on the cotton and the other on the unexpected geust. The boy said in a small voice," yOU WILL FOREVER re-main in this house for life." All of a sudden The doors and windows dissappeared into nothing and they all; look at each other in puzzlement". "What are we going to do?"said bo. I do know?? "I know i am eating some of this great candy",said danielle. good idea. they all sit and eat the candy. The boy then explains how he got lost one day and found the house and has been stuck in there for the last 12 years. "wow" "that is amazing" "i guess we will be here 4ever then." yeah. at least we arnt alone. yeah. "are parents are going to be freaked". It will be okay i think. "I love cotton candy"..,saids danielle. "yeah",they all said". 4the next 100 years they ate  cotton candy and played 20 qwuestions. but they did in the end go insane and become addiccted to bark.   
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oK SO TODAY FOR 3 HOURS. i was biking.(summer gym). so we(me and terra) are riding back from butler. so this kid behind us like savurs and goes in to the woods and crashes. we both look back and then like crash into each other. but we stop and are like"u ok kid", and"u need bandaids". he siad he was ok, but he was lieing. anyone falls into a forest/ditch isnt ok. metally or phyically. i hope he didnt like pas out and is still laying in the woods. that would be bad. so far i have seen 3 bike crashes.so therefor biking is the unseen danger.  p.s-i added new tag ons to the website-scoll down-!! 
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Click here TO FIND OUT WHY!!!!  DO IT NOW!!!  urlLink http://www.users.csbsju.edu/~ekhedin/goldfish.jpg  
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Thats right Myron, the hero of Marion Ave. NoBoDy nows really what this guy does. I talk to Myron like everyday, but never more then a hello and goodbye. but hes cool. if hes down with johnreed he is down with us.FAMOUS QUOTE:"REEDS". THANKS FOR BEING ARE HERO!!!!!!!   MEMEBERS: CAITLIN JOHN  DANIELLE    
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oK SO I CHANGED THE BACKROUND. I LOVED THE BLACK! BUT IT WAS GIVING ME SO MUCH TROUBLE(SIDEBAR CONTENT). SO FOR KNOW. WE GET THE GHETTO BLUE! I DONT HAVE A LOT OF CHOICES!GO FIGURE!O YEAH I ADDED LINKS. CLICK ON POKE A PENGUIN! IT ROCKS!!
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      21. his name is johnreed. 22. he likes to say, "fish tacos".  23. he takes gromes out of peoples yards. 24. his father  is involved in organized crime.(myron we love u!) 25. he failed his favorite subject,"science"!!!!!! 26. he doesnt own a dress 27. his phone is always choppin onions. 28. he wishes he lived in my garage. 29. he doesnt believe that the civil war happened! 30. because he is john reed-and we all love him!!!!  neXT 10 comeing sOOn!! 
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 	A LONG time ago. Like 2 days ago. There was this guy named johnreed. johnreed he was a character. hE WAS walking outside at 4:30 in the morning on MARION ave. which is a never-ending road! Well he was walking along the road when all of a sudden a guy in a pink and blue tractor-trailer pulled up beside him and blew a dart of poison into this neck. The man got out of his car and pulled john into the car and took him home. JOhn woke up 13 hours later with a horrible headache. The first thing he saw was the figure of a man wearing a purple suit.” who are you", john still dizzy asked. "My name,MR. Rxxd, is Sam Kingostopper". "But U can call me Kingo, all my closest friends doo"!.John says, now getting jumpy, "What am doing here"!!!!!! "This has to be some shorta joke!" "Where am I"? KINGO replys,"u are in the ghetto." "There are no ghettos"!,  JOHN REPLYS. "That is a ignorant thing to say fool”, said KINGO. "Stop playin word games with meee!"Says john. "IM NOT PLAYIN WORD GAMES WITH YOU". All of a sudden kingo forces john to lick a poisoness frog. john passes out and hits the floor.Kingo goes back to playing with his pet lobster, named bunny. john wakes up a day later, remmbering what had happened.O CRAPz!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!"MR. jOHNrEEd u have finally woken up, u had a very long and pleasent nappy-sleppy-sleppy." john said," cut to the case, why am i here." "its very simple,mr.reed, i kiddnapped you becasue i need your help",kingo says. "Ok, I will help u just stopp druggin me, it isnt very nice", john reply. "Alright, just stopp yellin and caring on like a crazy hamster under shock hearpy", relpys kingo. 	JOHn takes a deep breath and leans back in the chair. "Ok lay it on me!" Kingo stepps back and sits down on the sofa,"ok i need u to brush Bunny's teeth". "WHAT??????", JOHN REPLYS. "Who is Bunny and why do u wANt me to do that."  Kingo looks a john and picks up bunny, "bUNNY is the name of my losbter".. "oh ok phyco", repleys john. 	"ok stop makin fun of me mr.reed, do u wanna lick the frog again??", replys kingo. "O no, anything but that, i just dont understand, why cant u do it ur self?? "very go qwestion, i have a allergy toward toothpaste, kingo says while crying. "Stop that u look like a pansy",tells john reed. "please mr.johnreed, (looks and hugs the lobster)bunny doesnt want to get a cavity, do u bunny??!!". "fine, after this will u let me go home, i have to watch the si-fi channel, there is a show without guns on tonighT", replys john. "fair enough, or u could live there!", said kingo getting mighty excited,(jumping up and down like a little girl) " we can sing NICK NACK PATTY WACK all day long.!!" NO no just let me do this and then take me home", john replys with wide eyes . KIngo hands the lobster to john and a small toothbrush just big enough for a lobster. it only take john about 5mins to brush the lobsters discolored teeth. "done",says john. "great job mr.johnreed", says kingo full of gratitude. "I will take u home know but i must  drug u one more time. i dont want anyone finding out where i live!", kingo says while looking thorugh some boxes. all of a sudden the man takes out a vial of blue liquid, and shouts,"fair larwence lives on 4ever!!!" john looks up in dissbelief,"I will drink it, it is the only way to get away from this crazy insane man!!" john falls to the ground.  ·	 3 hours later john wakes up in the driveway of this home, dizzy. His dad is standing over him. Myron says,"i told u no drugs jon, this is very dissapointing." ."but dad i didnt do drugs, i was kiddnapped." "i dont believe u, why would soemone kiddnapp u, thats why you are taking kun fu, so u dont get taken by anyone." john stammers out," but itys not kun fu"!! "no i dont care what it is , get up stairs u are grounded for the next 3 weeks, and u are going to get spanked  100 times with a seat belt!!" "great". john returns to the kichen woundering weather he had dreamed the whole thing or if he really did meet the crazy man named kingo. "o yeah by the why john,  meet the mayor of mansfield, he needs my help with  his job", says john dad, "mr. kingostopper". john turns white, kingos and johns eyes meet and john runs up to his room screaming and then gets into the fetal position and shakes. Back down stairs johns dad explains that john is on cyrstal meth and he screamed becasue that is how he says hello." Kingo gives a chuckle a takes a sipp of tomato soup,"i dought that, he seemed like a very nice and useful young man". "whatever, so u need money, and i am a lown shark, so just tell me what u need". All of a sudden Mryon is shot in the neck with a poisoness arrow by kingo, and he is dragged away. kingo says with a huge grin on his face,"THE MADDNESS WILL NEVER END,AWAWWWWWW"!!! **BEWARE**** **RED-RUMM** 	BY:DANIELLE C-2004-fishy isn’t it?? 
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Cameron wanted his own fan club and if he really wants one he can have one. if is the best friend of MR.JOHNREED. hE IS ALSO A friend of a another one of our heros,MYRON!!and unlike john he would use peppers as weapons of mass distruction.  and he is a super person even though he believes there isnt a ghetto of lexington, like john. *tisk,tisk*. He believes in the great pumpkin. and he came up with the pimp switch theroy, proven true by all accounts! so he gets to be on securitypenguins great fan clubs web page!!his sisetr is really cool too.  famous phase:unknown.    members: leader-mr.johnreed danielle  caitlin myron?                        **subject to change** ---leave a comment to become part of this fan club--- 
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      31. Because he leaves his friends on the phone forever and ever!!!! 32.he collects air fresheners  33.he likes books without guns.  34. He is on the south beach diet. 35. He builds fences with beaver eaten twigs. 36. He has a pimp switch that NEVER turns off.  37.he goes to basket weaving class at hobby lobby! 38. Security penguin loves john 39. He burns people with C20. (And gets in trouble) 40.He grows hot peppers and uses them as weapons of mass destruction. 41. He invented radio shack. 42. He can rap.. or at the very least hummmm. 43.he doesn’t believe in the ghost of tybalt. 44.Tupac lives in his basement 45.He CAnt add or divide. 46.He has a pet snail name dingo. 47.He robs his house.  48.He calls the cops PO Po's! 49.because his internet never works 50. Because we love the fact we can write about him and he wont get mad!!  ~~~~~~~~~~~~50+ are being though about as u read this~~~~~~ 
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      And thank All the vieterems of the CIVIL WAR, cuz U all ARE very great...;) Esspeially the Confiderate side, U guys Rock
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was on my way to my cousin's house ,who lives in Ashland. when I noticed something preticular about this town... the first thing that caught my eye about Ashland there was run down houses, and I noticed something else writing on sidewalks. Hmm Thats when I became very curious. Could this be? Ashland, a ghetto? Only there was one quality missin...the people. Then when we arrived. I saw across the street from my cousin's house... a old man wearing mix match clothes it was Neon Green shorts and a red top!! That made me think. Could Ashland be the second ghetto ,Next 2 Lexington of course. Then I took a look around, then the answer came to me... heavens yes... So I declare Ashland to be the second Ghetto of America.                "I'm not a animal, I don't eat my own crap!"                    -Me                       I'll explain the story behind the quote to you if you want  
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      47 hours uninvestigates:      bio-47 hours uninvestigates doesnt investigate and isnt 48 hours. we dont need to investigate in 48 hours. instead we are just going to go out and ask people things but tell them we arnt investigating them. poeple dont like that. so we are going to get the real answers to are qwestions. and that extra hour is spent eating, cuz we need food.  episode:1-the mysterious ghetto of lexington: with-betty canope --------------------------------------------------------------------- -somewhere in lexington. *betty- we are the legendary town of lexington ohio. ghetto or no ghetto??lets go uninvestigate!! -they move to danielle h`s house because she believes that she lives in the ghetto.  *betty-danille is there a ghetto?  #danille-yes i do believe there is. every town has one. nobody believes me *betty- who doesnt. #danille-mr.johnreed,he thinks i am carzy! *betty-i will go uninvestigate -mr.johnreedz house on mariom ave. * betty-john why dont u believe in the ghetto.  #john-did danielle send u, are u investigateing me?? *betty-yes she gave me ur name, no i am uninvestigating u. #john-thats sounds fun *betty-well why is there no ghetto #john-there just isnt a ghetto, there is no proof!! *betty-isnt that kinda ignorant? #john-no its like saying i read books without guns. *betty-u do or dont???  #john-what? *betty- read books without guns. #john-thats the word around the ghetto, lol. *betty-poppycock #john-i am telling u there is no ghetto,  *betty-we know u think that #john- i gotta go watch the si-fi channel *betty- ibet u do #john-u need to leave *betty-fine, i think we have all that we need,anyways! #john-good -betty leaves- betty-i think tthat  went good, we figured out nothinhg and made no progress b/c we were uninvestigating. 47 hours  over in 3 2 1. finished. hard day, that sure was!! --------------------------------------- by-danielle.c-2004 **john reed was never interviewed!**     
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There  once was an cover up organization kinda like AA or Anger Management. it was supposed to deal  with people who had  cross eyes and who were ashamed of them.but that wasnt the real reason. it was to find out who had murder Fiar Larwence. the group met every wednesday at the the local bar. well the leader of the group was a man named County Paris.CoUnty Paris had the crazyest lazy  eyes ever!. The group was comprized of many tpyes of people but they all had cross eyes and they all wanted to find out who had killed Fiar Larwence.all they really did at the meetings was get really drunk and sing elton john songs. the group would most likely get into fights and claim that raddishes would take over the u.s. so they went to jail a lot. but it was all County Paris's fault b/c he though it would be a good idea to get drunk at the local bar. But in reality county paris just liked to get real drunk,bEAcuze he missed his really old friend, Fiar Larwence. he had been shearching the internet for rumors of he fiars death. AND one night had mad a big big break through. the group was meeting at the local bar and the County was sitting down with this wirerless laptop. he typed the words" i killed fiar larwence" on ask.com. the county had been in luck, there had been a website made that day that had to deal with someone claiming to have killed county paris. "what a dumb person",paris declared. "lets go you guys, he is in mansfield ohio.". "lets kill him,hahahhahahah!!!" They hitched a ride with a gay truck driver. so it took them 5 days to get to mansfield and when they did they had to find the man who had done it. so they askeda round and round tryed to tap peoples phone. one day they jusrt happened to be on marion ave and there car broke down. so they all walked up the closest house on the road from were there car was. County pARis knocked on the door and a strange friendly guy answered the door. "ummm our car broke down,good man could you please be a dear and let me use ur phone?""" "the name is myron,and no u cant because i deep fryed the phone this morning,s o it doesnt work." "but if u would like to come inside and have dinner with my family i would be trilled" paris said", ok that is very nice, do u have enough room for all 12 of us?? myron said,"we can have dinner outside." come in mr.???"."the name is county paris, no mr."..."mr.countyParis, what a cool name" myron said. "Fool, no mr. just county  paRIS/." "I asure u that i am not making fun of u," myron declared. "crazyeyes". "WHAT, no u ddint!",said paris. all of a sudden mr.johnreed walks down stairs and looks that the 2 poeple fighting. "john go make dinner, we are going to have a picnic!!"."ohhh oki will get out the tomato soup!!", ummmm, declares john. "hes on crystal meth he doesnt know what he is saying.", myron relpys. "ok",wishpers paris,"they u dont know a man by the name fiar larwence do u?" "I think john might i have heard that name before."myron all of a sudden ask paris were he got this funny hat at, and paris trys to glare at him but his eyes are wacken out of control. "i think u need some help with those"!,said myron. "i know that stupid",says paires,"i think i better have a talk with Mr.johnreed". paris goes out into the back year were john is making soup over the hot fire."hey wazz up dude??,says john"wazz ur name?" paris declared," my name is county paris, i am looking for fiar larwence" u mean the guy that i killed??" "that guy was so dumb, i killed him b/c he tryed to water my flowers,i told him to stay away but he kept on screwin with them, so i got out my sword cuz i dont believe in gun, and i be-headed him". its that cool"?? The Fiar was my father and know i must kil u!!, declares paris. paris and john  get into a sword fight. john after a 20 min fight spears paris and then he falls to ground and dies. myron comes out and gives his son a hug and tells him,"i amm sure glad we gave u those kun fu lessons"/. john says,"dad, they are not kun fu lessons how many times do i have to tell u that.?".. "whatever,not important.' the point is that u arnt dead and that the gargen wasnt messed up.They burn the body and then they make some tomato soup."i loove tomato soup",declares john...and life goes on, just a normal day @ the reeds!! the end by danille.c-2004 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        so there they were in the cotton candy shack. just bo jangles, mr.johnreed, caitlin, danielle, and the weird little kid.ever since they had been trapped in the shack, their brains had been on over drive trying to think of a way out of there. but of course the naughty bo jangles wasnt thinking cuz he was withdrawing from pot and cuz he is dumb. bo wasnt helping at all cuz he kept saying here was like no way out and that they would all die. and all of a sudden out of no where they started to hear the jeepers creepers song, so of course they got a little freaked out, cuz who wouldn't.but danielle assured them that jeepers creepers wasnt going to hurt them, but instead help them. bo jangles, being his stubborn self, didn’t believe what danielle was saying. so bo got on the ground and started to gnaw on the bark floors and chant ignorant things. so caitlin went over to him and slapped him silly. so, of course, jeepers creepers showed up and brunt holes into the shack, with his eyes. in no time there was a hole big enough for everyone to get through. but jeepers creepers sensed fear in the little boy and he liked his bladder so he had to the little kid against the will of the others. but jeepers creepers, who was not bob anymore but a Canadian organ grinder. so the group thanked jeepers for getting them out and he flew away into the sky.{bye-bye:(*tear*...} so they returned to the qwest to find tacos. about 30 mins later bo jangles gave out a scream of pain. he had been bitten by a bug. johnreed, being an expert on bug bites, had seen this rare bite before. it was called a boss bug and if it isnt cured it could turn into amy's disease, which john had done a prodject on before. since they didnt have a can of tuna or a cacti they were going to have to let bo go through the horrible disease.so what else could they do, aww yes, return on their adventure. after an hour or so bo became,well to be very blunt, BOSSY. really bossy. he was telling everyone what to do and all of that kinda of stuff. so everyone decide to plot against him and put oragel in this mouth(which would make it num and stop him from talking.) john tricked him into drinking the whole bottle by telling him it was toothpaste and that his breath smelled really bad. being so full of himself he took it all in. after he had done so he looked like he was retarded. so they were still wondering through the corn field, but much faster,cuz bo couldnt tell everyone he needed to go to the bathroom every 10 mins, so he peed his pants a lot. then out of nowhere, in the middle of the corn field, was a tall man, who was about 7' 6 and was wearing a black trench coat and his hair was gelled back. he looked troubled or like he was in shreah for something very important. the group approached the man. they asked if they could help with anything. the man asked if they had seen e.t. , his long lost son. caitlin brust out into laughter and told the man, pointing to john, that john was e.t. john tried to tell him he wasnt, but the man wasnt going to take no as an answer. the man told john that he just wanted to make sure he was ok and that he wanted to make sure that e.t was happy on earth. john said yes. the man kissed and hugged john and then said,"fairwell son, and good day!!" john was pretty weirder out but he passed it off. by time the man had left the numbing gel had worn off and bo jangles began to act like his bossy self once again.but not only was he being bossy, his ego began to grow bigger and bigger. it was the size of a hot air balloon. he started to say that he was better then everyone else. so everyone was getting pretty hungry, and to their surprise in the middle, what would lie, but a meatloaf restaurant. when they walked they noticed the banner above their head it stated that the meatloaf was magical and that it was abundant and free. so they sat down for a wonderful feast of meatloaf, when, u guessed it, bo jangles began to fight with john. saying that he could eat more meatloaf then john. so bo,of coursed, challenged john to a meat loaf eating contest. john accepted because he is johnreed the kun-fu master that will never turn down a challenge. so they had the contest,. bo ate 15 loaves and john ate 3. so bo jangles went around celebrating his victory over john. but soon he got sick and puked out all 15 loaves of meatloaf. everyone started to laugh except bo who started to cry and he had a pity party for himself, nobody else joined cuz:-1. they were eating magical cheesecake and real cherries from the garden outside.and-2. bo smelled really bad. so after the cheese cake and the party was over they continued on their journey.&nbsp; after a while bo was so over whelmed that he fell into to the ground and began to say really crazy thongs about mongooses. so john being john had a little talk with him about his attitude. but bo&nbsp; wouldn't comply so john poked a presser point on him and they left bo jangles to die in the corn field of never ending corn..&nbsp; without the presence of bo jangle the group seemed to be doing alot better then they had been doing. u get the point. as the day turned to night they got tired and made corn beds like the Indians made and they fell asleep. they were awoken the next morning by the screams of john, he had had a bird poop on this face, which was really nasty and gross. but he wiped it off with a cob of, u guessed right, corn! so after a breakfast of creamy corn(by the way john had begun to get a yellow tint to his skin.,lol)they continued on the qwest,it wasnt to long before the corn ended and a street was now in front of peeps. they started to walk down the road when they noticed an ALDI's grocery store. they walked in looking for someone&nbsp; so they could ask where the heck they were. but as soon as they walked in who else would appear but the naughty, egotistic BO JANGLES.&nbsp; everyone was in shock. how did he manage to get to the store before they did.l bo jangles explained that as soon as they leaf him aliens abducted him and did weird things to him, like put silly putty in his brain and dye his liver purple. but that they had to stop and get some raisins .so they let him go cuz they were done with him. besides the fact that no body believed in him. but they were pretty mad at him so it really didnt matter. so bo had a dollar so he bought a bottle of ketchup. because he liked ketchup. and john remembered that he had a dollar in his shoe so he bought a container of&nbsp; mixed nuts that were also meat flavored.(how convenient for john,lol.) so they left the store while the girls were still trying to figure out where they were. but nobody seemed to know. so they left in disappointment while angry drug users tried to sell them street drugs and highway streets. but danielle insisted that they had 2 of everything. so as the girls pushed the crazy people out of the way, they rejoined the guys who were enjoying their treats. bo opened the ketchup bottle and took some in and spit it back out, cuz it was horrible. it tasted like crap. so bo jangles marched back into the store and complained about it to the person in charge. the sales worker took out a pistol and told bo to get out of the store if he didnt want 2 unwanted presents. bo sulked out the store and he shunned the store. he came out while the girls were making fun of johns mixed nuts. john, being an awful nice person, offered to share his new found treasure. but everyone declined, even bo,who would get anything. it made john kinda mad, but the wonderful taste of the meat flavored mixed nuts made him forget about his sorrow.&nbsp; while walking&nbsp; down the long street john decided that it was time for a sing along, so he took out his banjo keyring but bo that it was a ghetto idea and then insulted john by telling him that he was really ghetto. john, not like being called ghetto for any reason, got mad and bit off 2 of bo's fingers and ate them. bo was in a world of pain. not to mention that the blood was everywhere. but nothing could really be done. bo, in a word, was handicapped and mad.(i wounded why??) so danielle and caitlin played doctor and wrapped up bo's flesh wound. but somewhere in the middle danielle went over to talk to john about the word"ghetto". which didnt make john to happy. soon the 2 were fighting over ghettos:real or made up. but they came to a tie b/c danille changed the subject to bo. john still mad said he was sorry to bo.&nbsp; but bo was still really mad at john for what he had done, so he wasnt talking to him. so what else could they do but continue on there qwest.bo still upset started to sing the song,"stacy's mom." over and over again. everyone thought it was kinda weird and sick, but nothing else could make the sad boy happy. so then john got mad b/c he saw a pile of rocks and he got depressed b/c he thought even a rock whould reject.the girls tried to tell him different and hold him that he was not acting rash. so then about 2 days passed when they came across a road that intersected with the one they were on. the road was named ocean ave. john got really excited and started to jump and scream and lose control of everything. john finally got control and told his peeps that road ended in his back yard, and it was only about 4 miles, and that they were going to be home by night time. and was good because they were tired of liven in the presence of corn and need to take a bath. esp. bo jangles b/c he smelled of puke and ketchup. so they skipped home. and when they got there all of there parents where there and they all acted like nothing had happened.which was weird. but nobody wanted to ask qwestion. the only person that had gotten in trouble was john b/c all of the parents had come up with this crazy idea that john had kidnapped all of them. so john couldnt watch the sci-fi channel or any other channel(except weather) for a year. cuz he must have seen the prank on some movie. and nobody wanted to get into trouble so they just agreed that was what had happened. so they all made it home safely never to tell what had happened! I think the only qwestion was, did bo and john make up?? well thats a story for another time.  by:danielle c-2004. holla.!!!!! &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;  
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      GEUSS WHAT? I FIGURED OUT OW TO PUT PICTURES ON THE INTERNET VIA MY DIGITAL CAMERA/ JUST NOT ON THIS WEB PAGE! WELL ALL U HAVE TO DO TO SEE THEM IS GO OVER TO THE SIDE BAR- AND GO TO MY LINKS- AND CLICK ON MY PICTURES. ENJOY. THERE WILL BE MORE TO COME!!  IF U CANT FIND THE LINKS, GO HERE.-    http://www.villagephotos.com/pubbrowse.asp?selected=974829     
      
</post>


</Blog>