<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, work is heating up, putting me in untenable positions. I can't go into details. I woke up with a stained black tongue, I can't go into details, and I'll see a doctor about it next week. I can't get to my email, and I can't go into details about it. I NEED a  urlLink vacation. 
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, it turned out to be phlebitis. Not a serious case: the exact Dx was "Superficial phlebital thrombosis". In other words, the vein was damaged, it will go away (well, at least wither). I'm going to try to get along at work a bit more today. I'm hoping to actually make it for a week without the urge to bolt.  Anyway, So "Power" has been handed over in Iraq. The fact that it happened early, with no ceremony tells me that no real power transferred. If real autonomy was the case, you couldn't arbitrarily just say "Yeah, right now. Here ya go". It's a sham. I don't care who believes me, or doesn't, I'm declaring it a sham. Personally, much bigger news to me is the introduction of religion to the workplace. Evidently certain banks are employing "corporate chaplains". I don't know, but didn't Jesus chase the usurers out of the Temple? Personally, I think a lot of "religion" and "spirituality" in America is nothing but people acting exactly like the Pharisees: trumpets before they pray, fanfare when they give alms, and nothing really "spiritual" in the "spirituality". If I were of the apocalyptic stripe, I'd be looking for God's wrath about now. I mean, isn't it a sin to do stuff like Enron, and S&L scandals, and whatnot, then, call upon the name of Jesus to make you look like you're better than you are?  Seems to me a more "religious" a more "spiritual" response would be to sell the bank to the people who use it, and charge no interest on loans, but instead, make your profits on agreed upon fees? Wouldn't it be more pleasant in God's eyes if those who could afford it forgave the debts of those who can not afford them? Wouldn't it make more sense to have a "religious Jail" than a religious bank?
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, a few weeks back I had a tooth pulled. In order to put me out the gave me an IV. Now, three weeks later I still have a bruise running along my vein, a ropy feel to the vein, and pain. So I look on the web for what it could be, and it sounds like Phlebitis. I've never heard of this, but from what I've read, it's something that can happen, and evidentally happens often enough that they gave "set answers" in Nursing texts in the event you are sued for it. Lovely. So, I'm going to urgent care tomorrow to deal with it, as it's evidentally a form of thrombosis and could kill me. It's very hard to trust anyone. Every time I go to the doctor I get some new problem. So, maybe I'm whining but jeez, all I wanted was the tooth which crumbled out of my jaw a year and a half ago to be taken care of. I spent a year with a temporary filling, because Dentists were incompetant.  All I can say is I don't think I'll ever fully trust anyone, but a white coat is a good step in the wrong direction. I've had everything from Doctors middiagnose me to Dentists lie to me to rip me off to you name it. Seriously. Take this for example: I had a kidney stone. The doctor who "treated" me kept me an invalid for a month by failing to properly attempt to get it out, and further cause a hernia by his treatment methods, and then, over-charged me, to boot. So, I limp away, and eventually get the hernias repaired. Guess what? I still have problems with pain in that area. Because of damage done by the catheter. Nice huh? Try this one: I had an ulcer misdiagnosed as lung cancer. Not enough? How about back to the tooth: the reason why it had to be removed was because they hollowed it out too much when they were preparing for a root canal. Rather than deal with that, I had a dentist send me off for a completely unneccessary surgery on ANOTHER TOOTH.  Get the idea?  
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looks like the experiment was a success (well, it was a very easy experiment) So look forward to more links from me.   I can't even begin today with all the things I want to rant about. Really, I can't begin.  So, instead, I hope that those who can see the sun, do.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got no skills. But  urlLink These people  do. Hmmm. Another experiment: I'm trying the most elementary move in Link fu
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I keep on saying I’m strange, odd, a mutant, etc. To better explain this, I’m publishing my notes, written between calls, this morning. This is literally how I think, without editing:  So, I’ve decided to visit Carson Street and Mt Washington in Pittsburgh. In order to have money to make it worth my while, I’m trying to stay in the cheapest place possible, without violating health codes. So, I’m thinking everything above a Motel 6 is fair game. I’m going for within 30 miles north and west of Pittsburgh, and I’d prefer a major chain. My upper price limit is $50/night. Next, I’m going to check on Gas. My OCD tendencies are going off on this trip, probably to mask my fears, anxieties and trepidation. So, I’ve got a route: Holland to Lansing, to Ann Arbor, to toledo,to between Cleveland and Akron to Pittsburgh to Home.  Figure I’ve got a 9-gallon tank, getting 27 mpg. That means a gas stop every 243 miles. (Yeah, I’m undershooting, but that seems safer.) Figure, it’s probably a 650 mile trip, that’s 3 stops for fill up, since fractions don’t count, and since I’m going in 1 direction, I can’t just go past, and back. But, there will be some variance in there. Since the car is listed at 30 mpg, and it could have a 12-gallon tank, that means we’ve got a range of 243-360. So, realistically, I should be looking at a first stop after 240 miles, and then, a range of not less than 240 miles and not more than 360, followed up by a range of 240- finish. If I read the map correctly that means a first stop just after Toledo, followed up by a stop on the OH-PA border, followed up by the PA/MD border. So, most likely: gas first in MI, gas twice in OH, once in PA. Lowest price I can expect for Gas is $1.80, Highest is $2.15. That means $1.98 average (having checked on Gas Buddy: current prices would appear to be roughly the same as here. That means $1.80. I think it’s safer to stick with the higher figure as prices will likely jump for the holiday). That means $48 for gas. So, we’re at $98 for the trip expenses. Then, food. Figure on about a fast food diet. Figure in food times2 for the first day, times 1 for day 2,  at 6.50 per meal, and we’re at $19.50 for food, for $117.5 total. Then, figure $10 for film, so that I can make some momentos, and $10 for Tchotckes, and we’re at $137.50 for trip expenses. If I’m correct I’ve got $XXXX in the bank, as of tomorrow. Minus $300 for bills, we’re at $XXX. Then, $350 added next pay, minus $80 for expenses and we’re at $XXXX. I figure it’s safe to spend ¼ of that on this trip. Assuming, everything is correct, I should be pretty good for this. I think I genuinely need a zero stress couple of hours spent in a different city than what I’m used to. So, having enough cash for it is a good thing. I mean, I’m at max stress here, when I’m swigging my usual heroic doses of anti-acid stomache stuff and I can still literally feel the bile constricting my chest. It’s like a form of torture. If I get just these few hours without it, I think I’ll be ok. In the meantime: kinda cool that I know there some other left-leaning folks in the building. Just had a great lunch extending conversation with a guy in the Computer room who actually appears to be left-leaning and at least semi-intelligent. Probably smarter than me, but what can I say? “He’s a Geeeniyus!” I don’t know that, either. It’s sucks so badly that I’m stuck in the most awful industry, feeling the way I do, thinking the way I do. It’s like being drowned in gibbering hamsters. Makes it a relief to hear just one say something in decipherable language. But all that makes me sound so elitist. Maybe I am, but I also know I’m an idiot. Just a different stripe of idiot. It’s ok swimming with the star-bellied sneeches, but every once in awhile I’d like to be around a few without stars upon thars. It makes it doubly hard in that I know us plain bellied sneeches are defensive after being attacked by the star bellies, so we don’t even have the ability to fully trust each other. Add to that how embittered this job makes me. I mean, I deal every minute of every day with people who are fully invested in this evil empire, and that’s why they’re calling me: to be more invested in this garbage. They get mad because they think I’m trying to rip them off, when they rip themselves off constantly, and if I wanted to rip them off, I could with saying a word to them, and if I did want I wanted, I wouldn’t rip them off, I’d burn their houses, but I don’t burn down houses, or rip anyone off I just seethe. Yeah, happy camper, here.  But I’m able to make it because of the other good stuff. Like a little 10-minute conversation. Seems to me if I can put up with such a system that I find so abhorrent over such small amelioration no one should ever feel hopeless. But there is that thing. Like me still obsessively worrying about that hard little vein in my upper arm. I know it’s probably nothing, but it just keeps on nagging at me. All I want is to get by, and getting by seems like the biggest gift….  Enough whining like a little kitten. On this trip I want at least a little sunshine, but I hope it’s warm the whole way. I want to pack light. To me, that’d make it seem more carefree. Like a safari or camping. I guess I just want some freedom, some autonomy, and I guess not having to carry stuff does that. Odd, when you consider how much I like to get stuff. I guess that part is about options. It’s not that I want to keep the stuff, I just want the option to use it. Typical spoiled brat American, I think.. Ye gads, I hate having all the little tugs on my attention: it’s like being interrupted all the time. “Enforced ADD” is what I think of my job. 
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know it: I'm stressed out, you're stressed out, we're all stressed out. Had an odd thought: I wonder if Stress could be classified as a "sin". My logic goes like this: Stress is produced by anxiety over an outcome. That anxiety indicates a lack of faith, in something. If I lack faith in God to resolve something, is that a sinful thought? It could be. The counter would be that Lack of "enough" faith indicates that "grace" is diminished. God's good graces would be "earned" by having "enough" faith. If the love of god must be earned, then yes, Stress is a sin. Otherwise, in and of itself, it's merely a factor of too little faith for the situation. Yes, my brain revolves around wierd orbits. Anyway, back to assuming the position. Hope it's not this bad for everyone.
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Going to have to think about ways to advertise.... This is primarily a diary, but, I also wouldn't mind friends and family seeing it....
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, how many Blogs do you think are titled that, today?  Anyway, So they made it to space. They also made it illegal to see photos of soldiers coming home (if they're dead). It's all about trying to re-shape the world. Government, Big Business, The "media": it's all the same goal: they're trying to shape how we think. The guys who shot the rocket up, want us to think of them as "Pioneers" and as some kind of swashbucklers, full of romantic idealism. The truth is, it's a business venture. They want to be Pan Am. See it before when it was called "The concorde". The Government wants us to think of them as heroes as well. They want us to think of them as philosopher-kings, full of lofty ambitions, and compassionate concern for our well being. The truth is they're hacks and hucksters trying to buy their way through. They want to remain on the job, and that means pushing through only that legislation that suitsv their corporate masters. The "Media"? Well, I put the quotes around it because the actual media is the means of communication. What we call "The Media" is actually a cartel of corporate conglomerates that are allowed control of the flow of information. They want us to think of them as the means of communication, so that we won't notice that real communication is two way, and all they provide is their way. Told you I'm a crank. Well, here's a shocker: I don't think it's a matter of left V. Right or Capital V. Social. Both sides do it because as the Tears for fears song went "Everybody wants to rule the world". So, a left leaning government still wants to been as heroes, and a socialist will use marketing just like a capitalist. I think it's a matter of power. Who has it, who wants it, and how much they'll do for a percieved sense of power. I'm not trying to suggest a solution, other than to think on your feet. I'm just pointing it out.  As for me personally, I've got a sore throat, which is occupying all the attention not directed at work.   Hope all is well.....for everybody.  Y'know this is starting to look like my old 'zines. Maybe I'll title after them. We'll see. 
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I just did a google search for "Welcome Matt" Aieee! I knew it was a bad joke, but I didn't know it was a cliche!  Oh, well, I might re-name in a few days or weeks.  Anyway, so, I gotta thank God & my Dad. Happy Father's day, indeed. As I mentioned below, I've been looking for a new car. Out of the blue, my Dad offered me a car. Amazing! So, though I feel a bit strange accepting such a gift, I said yes, and worked out the details. And the details are a blessing as well! I've been itching to take a trip: go somewhere, anywhere. Plus, I'll get to see my Dad, and I'll get to travel some highways I've never done before! All in all, just wonderful. So, the details are this: I fly up to chicago, meet my Dad, we drive up to Holland, Michegan, and then, I drive the car down here. Sounds so luxurious to me, so wonderful....  Also, my wife (I'm not sure if I'll refer to people by their name, here, I guess I'll decide that later) is going to Finland on the 2nd, so this will give me an exciting trip while she's gone.  On yet another topic (I think this will be a diary post, or is that Dairy, hehe) I think it’s great that my wife is going to Finland. She’ll get to see her family, and in a (hopefully) positive way. I feel so badly for people who don’t have a “family”. I’m not just talking about orphans. I mean those people whom, for whatever reason, don’t feel like they have relatives to count on.  Absolutely, Families can be restrictive. Sometimes, in order to be a person, you have to leave behind certain family structures. I can see that. Further, I can see how you might have a desire to strike out on your own.  That makes sense. So I don’t blame you if you do not have a sense of family. But, I feel badly for you that things have gone this way for you. Ideally, your family would be such that they would support you not restrict you or make you dependent upon them. I know that few live up to “ideally” but I certainly wish that more were closer. I wish that I could go with her. It’d be really great to see her family, her culture, and her country, but life intervenes. Actually, wait! Hold up. A JOB intervened. Not life. Life is just there or it is not. A job, a contract between a corporation and myself is keeping me from going. That contract is necessary for me to continue to live, but my life is not a job. Further, the job is with a corporation, and corporations have no feelings, no heartbeat, and no soul. They are abstract things. Corporations are not good nor are they evil. They are simply abstract constructs, like contracts.  Lots of things are abstract constructs but we place so much into them. Things like countries. Countries have no life. They are an invention, and are things, nothing more. We place so much faith in them. You know, it could be argued that we have become modern polytheists. We have faith in so many things, but they are just things. Faith in Country, in Church, the economy, our cars, and in our cause is just faith in things. Abstract concepts and objects are only things. I suppose I could get all Old Testament on this and claim it’s all idolatry, but I think I want to just stick with the notion of bad faith. If you have to have faith in something other than a God, have it in other people. Of course, it could be argued that faith in God is faith in an abstract concept, and that faith in a contract is faith in other people, but I’m not so sure about that. It seems to me that God can be a very personal, very physical experience, and that faith is better demonstrated in your fellow man when you don’t need a contract. For example, in a family.  
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The whole consumerism thing has me so very well.  On the one hand, I know what a sweat shop looks like. I worked at one. Seriously. I was a "fufillment center". What's that? It's a factory where they make stuff for thrid parties to "fulfill" their orders. So, what we made was insert packages: you know, you order such and such product, and there's this instructional booklet and tape packaged in there? That's your insert package. So, for 9 hours a day, I'd stand in a warehouse, with no climate control at all, and I'd fold cardboard and shrink wrap. Granted not quite as bad as working a sewing machine in Manila for 16 hours a day, but about as close as a white American can get. There were no chairs, so you'd stand all day. The temperature would be about 100-110, with 75-90% humidity, and you'd fold and heat until your hands literally bled. Not particularly fun. I only lasted a month, but I still got a taste.  So, I know what goes into my stuff. I know that everything I own comes with a price. Of course there's the dollar price on the tag, representing the hours worked at some job which doesn't exactly support the planet required to obtain the product, but then, there's the price of making the product. Someone had to work to make it, and somebody had to ship it. The way that's worked out in our current system is that usually, somebody far away works 12-18 hour days for less than a dollar an hour, because they've quite literally been oppressed into the job. Maybe a revolution in their country a decade ago, or maybe somebody with a gun forcing them away from school, or maybe a government who would rather have a percentage of the population die than have a deal with Sony go bad. The way that it's shipped isn't much better, and again, we're talking overworked people forced into situations that endanger them, just to survive for a little longer. Fun, fun, fun. All that's part of the price. Then there's price of all this non-biodegradable crap clogging up landfills, and the price of all the resources just burned away to make trinkets. And so on. Everything comes with a price, and it's much more hefty that the price on the tag. But, there I am, buying way, way too much crap. I've got three pair of jeans (nowhere near my total collection, mind you) that are made by a company that calls itself "Indigo Star". All three are bought because it's one of the few brands of jean that I think look halfway decent on me, and are a bit comfortable. But right there on the label is "Made in Russia". So are they commie jeans? Nope. See, so much attention got put on the sweatshops of honduras and the Phillipines, that they moved such operations to China. Well, China started to get wise, and so they had to move the most exploitative operations to places like Russia, where the economy is so ruined, and the workers so alienated that they'll take sweat shop jobs, because there's no other game left. It's like Gogol's "Dead souls". It's so strangely evil, like some disease borne by the wind, opportunistically landing wherever the hope of men has been crushed by economics. Except that makes it sound almost natural. The fact is, it's intentional. This is done, actively, by people who know what they're doing, and supprted by people, like me, who know what it costs. So, yeah, I've got to find a way to scratch that consumerist itch without put more quarters in the death machine, you know? I hope I find a way to either stop buying so much, or somehow get off this treadmill. I'll let you know if I find a way. 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So,  Madonna changed her name to “esther”. Seems somehow appropriate. Why not? After all she’s got a lot of money. I don’t so can I just change my name to “M”? Still, it reminds me of an old Hippie room-mate of mine who changed her name to “gimmel” (Absurdity is best combatted with absurdity) I’m trying to improve things. Painting rooms in the house, eating better, trying to save money for (cue game show announcer voice) A NEW CAR. Really, I’d like to get a Moped, but it’s just not practical: Passengers, groceries,  cold weather, speed, I just can’t justify it, right now. If I can get the car cheaply enough, maybe I could still buy a cheap, used moped, sometime. But, for the meantime, I gotta be a gas hawg.  So much for environmentally improving.. I wonder if that’s the case for many? If so, how many? Is the reason we still live the way we do, in the face of everything, because we’re stuck between rocks and hard places? Obviously, we can’t weasel out of all responsibility, because we’re still buying SUV’s as opposed to compact cars, and we’re still not enacting leglislation to change things, and we’re still not putting money into public transportation, but do we deserve all of it? Is some of this because we’re stuck in a system? I’d like to think so. At the same time, I know I see things differently than most. I’m unafraid of  socialism, and major re-structuring of our government. I think of solutions that other might consider problems 
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No sense in trying to hide it: I'm a crank. I'm somewhat anti-social, and I espouse beliefs that aren't in the mainstream, and I'm vocal in my opposition to things. For one: This whole Ronald Reagan thing. The man was clearly asleep at the wheel when steering the country, did his best to bankrupt us, and "acted" his way through. Yet, this is the guy we want to carve on Mt. Rushmore? Put on the $10? Name Airports after? I've heard the response: but he made us feel good. So does Crack, for a little while. But maybe we should plaster his pruned face everywhere. Maybe we should announce to the world that not only do we represent style over substance, we want the style to be as comforting as the substance is disheartening. We want to smile, then stab you in the back, then smile again. Maybe Reagan should be our flag. Then, there's Iraq. I'm fully convinced that this time in history will be judged based around the events of that invasion. I think that   Not   announcing that you're against that thing will condemn you in the eyes of history. From there, the torture, the lies, and the death are just dressing on the disease. Once you sign up to a war of aggression, you can't very well expect civility, can you? Sure there are a lot of issues. I could go down the line and list  them all but just from those two, I think I'm pretty clearly on the left. We can leave it there, for now. But, I am a crank in other ways. Here's some of a letter I just composed:  "I have called your customer service line to register my complaint.  They have assured me that measures have been taken; yet I have not seen any results.  Quite frankly, I don’t see how having a manager call me is going to solve anything. Consider the consequences to me of your employees’ action: I don’t have access to my medication until I can see my doctor. I can see my doctor, at the earliest on Monday. I have to sacrifice a day at work to see my doctor to get a new prescription. So, I’m facing several days of pain, increased risk to my health, and expenses in seeing my doctor, both in the opportunity cost for missing work, and in the co-pay to see the doctor; all so I can rectify the error of your employees. Add to this the negative experience of going to your store, and I don’t think a phone called “I’m sorry” will be of much consequence to me. That’s even assuming that such a call will take place. I have no real assurance that it will. As I stated earlier, I’ve come to expect poor behavior, and a lack of service and/or goods in exchange for my money. I’m not expecting that to change, because mine cannot be the only complaint, and I’ve been using this pharmacy for two years, without the service level changing. I see no real call for a lawyer, though I have been slandered, and my health endangered. I know that you have access to far more financial resources than I have, and thus, will most likely ignore this letter altogether. But, I do have friends, and family, and access to other means of communication, all of which I will inform of the experience I have had with your company"  Yup, true Crank fashion: I'm the guy who writes letters of complaint! I'm the guy who holds up the line to complain about some petty injustice. I'm the guy you're wishing dead in the line at the DMV. Howdy. Nice Day?
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, so I read blogs. And This is free. And I get bored. Perhaps I'll even learn something. Who knows? But, it's an experiment. An attempt at putting some content out there, of some description. We'll see if it goes anywhere at all. Eventually, maybe this will be deleted bytes, and maybe it'll be a running account of something. For right now? It's just an experiment, that would have been named "Lame Attempt" except that seems like an ironic comment on my own greatness. Far from my intent which is just do a blog for its own sake.
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I got up this morning and listened to the radio (WTOP) whilst reading a super cheap book ($1) about Zines. The thing about Zines is that I still think of them as fantastic. Sure, they’ve fallen out of hipster favor, and, instead, all the "cool kids" prefer lame comic books, but Zines are a form of real communication, like low power radio, and Blogs, and Cable access TV shows. It’s not some scripted, processed set of thoughts in a Zine, like you’ll get on TV. Instead you get the thoughts, ideas, passions, and personality of people as they are. They might really want to be slick essayists writing for the New Yorker but, usually they’re more interesting than all that. Anyway, then, I took a shower, got dressed, and got my son up, and awake. We fed the kitties, and he watered the front yard (using recycled water from the dehumidifier in our basement) while I tried to set up the new controller for his Nintendo 64 (yes, I do like outmoded technology. With things like video games, the differences are often cosmetic, and you can get the older stuff readily, and cheaply. I got the 64 for $30 at a national chain, complete with warranty. My son can play games that entertain him, and I don’t have to invest a small car into some video game) and then, I let him take over on the video gaming. I drove to work, and listened to WSAC, which is a College Station somewhere near to here. I really like college radio for finding new music. It’s better than magazines because you can hear it, and better than mp3’s because you don’t have to put out any info on yourself. Then, at work, I did the rounds of Blogs and Meta Blogs, and started taking calls. The less said about my job, the better, but I’m somewhat at peace with it, so long as I can convince myself that I won’t be here long. I probably wouldn’t be around very long as a hunter-gatherer. I’m not good at conflict. Not that I avoid conflict. I can’t. It follows me around like my shadow. I just mean that I tend to either not get involved when it could be easily solved, or get over-involved, and make things more complex than they need to be. Maybe I didn’t play enough video games as a kid. Maybe I drank too much, when I could drink. Maybe, I’m just crazy. I don’t know. But I’m more like a squirrel: I’d hoard like crazy for a month, and then, do nothing for two. Then, again, with my physical health just about mirroring my mental health, I probably am an example of the limitations of science: I’m not meant to live, and natural selection clearly has been overcome in my case. I think it could also be argued that if our society stands, it is in defiance of science. There’s no way that people were meant to live this way. There’s no better explanation of how we can continue to follow a self-destructive path, yet thrive than that our understanding is incomplete. Either the data is wrong, or the science is. I leave it up to the reader to decide which is correct, if either. As we took calls, my co-workers and I talked about language (in between the usual gossip and slander that goes on in an office) and it seems to me that the distinction between "country" and "city" is more pronounced than any dialect in our country. Maybe we are a nation of slickers and hicks? 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A correction might be needed. Yes, I know that the very notion of a “Conservative Punk” seems like an intriguing freak show notion, so, of course, people want to talk about it. But, I feel like they’ve gotten enough press. Everybody from CNN to Boing Boing has mentioned them, by now. Every single time it’s mentioned that they are a minority. Well, why are we ignoring the majority? Punkvoter is a success, which probably is why ConservativePunk was started. Think about this: we’re giving more attention to a loathsome minority when we have a genuine grassroots youth political movement success story. Punkvoter stands a chance to make a real difference, but we’d prefer to gawk at the goofiness.  Don’t get me wrong: I do it, too. But, I’m scared out of my mind that Bush could have a second term. I sincerely believe that this would be like electing Hitler. I feel that we’re at the same kind of crossroads as Germany was at in the early 1930’s. If we pursue this power mad ego trip brutality course that we’ve been on any further, I’m fully expecting us to be cursed and damned by our poor, and sick great-grandchildren as the generation who destroyed what was left. There are a few rays of hope, and Punkvoter is one, whether you agree with them or not, in that they are galvanizing young people into political action. If you agree with them, then, there’s even more reason why they are a good thing.  I really feel that the time for wallowing in despair over world events, and the actions of the few is drawing to a close: at this point, it’s decadence to just watch Nero playing his fiddle. People need to start working on some ways of putting out fires.  So, I might just be one Chicken Little, but if I’m wrong, what’s the harm in supporting the righteous? If I’m right, however, can’t we see the harm in letting something like Punk voter wither on the vine?   On the other hand, I think we need to take the enemy seriously. Saying that the Rednecks of the world are just silly, Ironic jokes virtually guarantees their acceptance. Ignoring Nazis has never stopped anyone from being a Nazi.  I lived in Arizona for close to 15 years. In that time I saw the rise of quasi-military citizen groups. At first, they called themselves “Patriots”. Then, they called themselves a “Posse”. Then, they called themselves “Militias”. All the while, they gained membership. All the while, they got progressively more ugly. It was no surprise to me at all when a few of their number bombed a federal building in Oklahoma. The shocking part was how easily they were digested: many of them were open about their racism and about their desire to start a war and no one cared. I can remember getting into screaming matches with William Cooper, one of the founding members, because he was preaching hate, and being told to drop it by generally good people because “He’ll hang himself with all of his crazy talk”. The truth was, the freak show aspect entertained people. Put a Neo-Nazi on the panel, we want this to be inclusive. The Arizona republic would Report on the Posse Comitatus, and on The Order, in the Style section, because it wasn’t considered newsworthy. Just a diversion. And meanwhile, these bastards were networking. (They still are. People from Bo Gritz to Aryan Nation are still networking) At the same time, you had racist literature being pumped out of West Virginia, virtually unmolested, because everybody expects Hillbillies to be that way. What are you worried about, son? West Virginny is Klan country, always has been…  It wasn’t that a home grown fascist movement was unthinkable. It’s that it was unmentionable.  So, I think I’ll mention it. Again, and again. Until every last one of these are gone, I’m going to maintain that it can happen here, it has happened here, and it is happening still. There are Nazis, Neo Nazis, Racists, Paramilitary survivalists, Crypto Fascists, and other assorted scum out there in America, and they mean us all harm.  “Great” you say, “But ConservativePunk and George Bush aren’t any of those”. To this, I reply “They are”  They might not espouse it publicly, but what makes them the type of republican that dominates that party at this time is a belief in a so-called free Market that is indiscriminate of whom it hurts, and uncaring of long term ill. The type of Republican currently dominating the party espouses near theocratic levels of government involvement with religion (or rather, A religion, that being Fundamentalist Protestant Evangelical Christianity, and no other)     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I went by B,B and B, to see the Shag stuff, but alas, there was none. I did pick up what I suppose to be a knockoff, however. A $5 beachtowel. Then nailed down that Ric Flair's book will be $26 and the signing is at Noon. Might still go. But then I get home, and whilst surveying my back yard note something moving by the shed. Figuring it to be a bunny (we get rabbits) I thought to ignore when I saw "No, it's three adorable Kittens!". Well, I'm not the "Cat whisperer" that my wife is, so I have to admit failure in securing Kitty contact, but I did leave out some "kitty milk" for the kittens. I'm not looking to adopt, merely to wrangle. I'd like to get the Kittens into a home: whether the one they came from (doubtful that there is one) or a new one. Just a home. So, I'll write more when I know.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things to look forward to: 1. Anna Liisa comes back from Finland on Friday! 2. Alex flies out on Saturday, the 17th! 3.We go to see the  urlLink WWE  on Sunday! There’s a RAW event at  urlLink Harry Grove Stadium  with folks like Chris Benoit and Ric Flair (who’ll be doing a  urlLink book signing  earlier that day: maybe I’ll go. I’d like to get the book) 4. The next weekend we go to Hershey Park! Things to get done: 1. Gotta stop by Borders, or Barnes And Noble (whichever it is) to check up on the aforementioned Ric Flair book. 2. Gotta stop by Bed, Bath and Beyond for the  urlLink Shag print goodies . 3. Gotta do some laundry. 4. Gotta get the resume updated! 5. Gotta go over the kitchen, bathroom, and backyard at least one more time before Alex gets here! 6. Gotta bring the photos in. 7. Gotta relax! 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really don't have much to say. I've got some observations but they're pretty half-baked, so they'll have to wait. And my "real" life has been mostly boring stuff like cleaning and working. Maybe something will inspire me, tomorrow.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got Bad luck. Not "Cancer at age 7" terrible luck, but Charlie-Brown, "Augh" murphy's law type luck. Take this evening: I get off work at 6, and try to dash over to Target to pick up a few necessities. When I get back to the car, it won't start. Not engine trouble or battery type, I mean the key will not turn in the ignition. So, I spend the next three hours trying to call every lock smith, friend or mechanic I can think of. Meanwhile, it starts to pour rain. I mean by the bucket. I'm soaked, and still can't get any help. Finally, a guy who's soon to get off work takes pity on me: he'll stop by to help. finally, at 9:40, he gets the key to turn. My evening is shot, I'm soaked, and I've not even had breakfast. Yup, that's the kind of luck I have. The kind where I'll be the guy showing up 1 minute after they lock up. I'm the guy who gets the slice of cake with mold on it. I'm not the guy for whom there is no cake, nor am I the guy who always gets an extra slice.  I know where I stand. I'm firmly on the "bad luck" side, but more on the Charlie Brown end than on the Charles Dickens end.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I just got back, and thought maybe a trip review would be good. First, thanks to Lisa and Jonah for the ride. It was fun, and I hope they like the  urlLink monkey wine . Next, the flight: Southwest is doing some kind of  urlLink reality  show, so by flying Southwest, I consented to be filmed. Huh? I didn't see that when I signed on for the tickets over the internet... Next, Midway still sucks as an Airport. Dad was cool, I really enjoyed seeing him.  urlLink Holland  is just as Cute as I remember, and if there's any economy there, looks like a great place to be. The  urlLink Dutch Village  was especially kitschy. The car is good, despite some nervousness. The Best Fueling stop? The Flying J just south of Toledo, No Contest! The Best Radio? Around Youngstown OH,  urlLink honestly ! Detroit was really bad '70's Classic rock, there was a little college radio around Ann Arbor, and more Classic Rock around Cleveland ( nice serendipity: right as I went by Cleveland, they played Neil Young warbling "Ohio".)  Pittsburgh? First the number one impression: Traffic SUCKS! I mean aggressively awful. The roads are re-named randomly (seriously, this became a huge problem, as my Hotel was on a street that was on the map, but no longer exists, and my route into the city was dependant upon roads that have been re-named, but are not listed anywhere else) Also, you can't maneuver: everything is 1 lane with no alternates, and no turns. I ended up driving for 1.5 hours trying to find my hotel, and 3.5 trying to find a Jiffy Lube, and 2 hours trying to get to Carson Street. Really, really bad traffic. I ended up missing the  urlLink inclines  altogether, as I couldn't get there! A word to the wise: Hire a Cab when in Pittsburgh, you'll never get anywhere otherwise! So how was  urlLink Carson ? Well, OK. Three places were really cool: 1. Slacker (Best collection of T shirts and Belt Buckles I've seen. Beware the porno rear of the store, though!) 2. Luxx (ultra hipster Ben Sherman store) 3. the Tiki Lounge: like dropping a store from Melrose ave in Hollywood on a Victorian street: Tres Chic! Two places SUCKED very badly: Fat Head (a restaurant that honestly assailed me as I walked by with the smell of vomit!) and the Exchange (used CD place: the selection was terrible, and the product was all kept behind locked glass plates! I know they call 'em Jewel cases, but this was like they were jewelry!: Gimme the Tower over that mess!) A lot of places don't open when they say they open, so I missed a lot of the rest.  So, the trip? Worth it. Pittsburgh? Maybe if I had a tour guide, and a cab driver, and two days to get around. As for other events: Yes, the trip was affected by Kerry announcing Edwards as his Veep. Made traffic in Pitt burg especially nasty in the downtown area, as that's where the great stone face made his proclamation! 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, the old “Ball and Chain” went off to Finland, so I watched a bad movie,  bought explosives, liquor, fried foods, and meat. Soon, I’m going to buy tickets to wrestling. Ah, yes, the Bachelor life! The truth? Yes. But, here’s another way to put it: My lovely wife flew off to Finland to see her family, I watched “Lost in Translation” because the TV was boring, but I thought “Lost in Translation” was an awful bore. I went out and bought fireworks (for when my son gets here) a bottle of wine { for friends as a thank you ( they’re taking me to the airport, tomorrow, and my wife, who has tons more class than me, suggested buying them the wine since they’re going to a party after dropping me off, as a way to avoid the “let me pay for Gas” argument)} Cat food and tuna steaks (for  grilling when my family is here). The wrestling tickets are for when my son gets here, as a family outing. I’m actually a bit melancholy, missing so many people. That is something: hang on to your friends, and family, instead of your youth. You’ll enjoy things more deeply. Well, to make me seem ever so vaguely cool, I am listening to loud rock music, and I am going to get a sports car tomorrow. Another positive thing, I spent awhile playing my guitar. My Dad used to push playing an instrument to me when I was a kid, to try to get me to take piano lessons, or saxophone, or trumpet. Instead, I ended up picking up guitar. I’m just a hack, not a great player, but I do enjoy it. So, the essence of what Dad said is right. Playing an instrument is a good thing. But, I think you need to play the instrument that calls your name. Guitar always has called mine, ever since I was a kid, making elaborate fake guitars to imitate Kiss. 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, at least today I've got a reason to whine: my wife is off to finland for two weeks. I don't begrudge her that. She completely deserves it, and needs to go, but jeez, it sucks for us left behind. I really am trying, though, to remain cheerful. It's just that I hate my job, and my government, and my health is just not that great, and then, there's the "normal" stresses. It's very hard to then be cheerful, at least for me.  Maybe after I get back from my trip, I'll try to add it something more peppy.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I'm getting some ants in my pants to get out of dodge (enough mixed metaphors, there?). Hopefully it'll be nice. I think I've got a ride to the Airport, then, I know I've got a ride out, and then, I get in the car and Drive to the   urlLink Flying J  at Perrysburg, OH. Then, I drive to the  urlLink Red Roof Inn  at Coraopolis. Then, I drive to Mt. Washington in Pittsburgh, then, to Carson street in South Pittsburgh, then I drive home. After that, I see the Doctor (again) and unwind.  I hope I get good  urlLink weather. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I must admit, I've not been blogging as much as I should be. I think that's mostly due to over-ambition. The last post was supposed to have all these links, etc. But, I think it might be more important to me to just get something down.  No one reads this but me, anyway, so why not? So I dreamt a movie last night. I don't do that too often, but when I do, it's fairly complete. Actors, sets, plot, sub-plot the whole bit. This one was called "the War of the Ants". Basically, An Alien virus is introduced to an Ant colony on Earth, which alters their genetics to evolve selectively to be competition with Humans in the space of a single generation. Language, size, etc. But they retain the instinct of an Ant colony. Very rigid and orderly. But, all that is essentially back drop to the movie. The movie primarily concerns two men. One a shaggy Liberationist: think hippie-meets-Che Guevera. The other is a button down desk Jockey in the military. The course of the movie follows them, as the interact training seperate groups of soldiers engaged in guerilla war against the Ants. As they progress, the Hippie discovers that his methods are too scattershot, and too undisciplined. He reacts by growing more and more codified, crystallized, and stiff: in short he becomes very rigid, very strict, and very concerned with order. Meanwhile, the desk Jockey starts out as insecure. He's unsure of what, if any training ability he has. But, he is a soldier, and, as such, has the background of duty that he feels he must do what he can. So, he starts out training very much (literally) by the book. He follows the training manual to the letter. But, as situations arise that the manual doesn't cover (we are talking, after all about "GIANT ANTS") he starts to "wing it" more and more. Soon, he's thrown out the manual, and is instructing his trainees to go with instinct, to disrupt order, and to fight "dirty". By movie's end, both men feel they are better than as they started, but both are horrified at how much people are ruled by their instincts as much as the dreaded ants. Probably, that's a movie that will never exist outside of my skull, but if anybody reads this and wants to steal the idea, feel free.... 
    
</post>


</Blog>