<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Elections Canada released the final tally, and Martine lost by 427 votes.   Too bad.   She still got 16366 votes, though. Mighty impressive. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Guess who's back?  urlLink Ed's back !     edit - fixed fux0rd link 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, there was Election Night in Canada.   The Liberals won. Well, better them than Harper's Bizarre. (terribly sorry for the pun)  I was working until 11:30PM, and I was following 4 things:     Obviously, the nationwide results (Liberal, minority, good)     Also obviously, the Quebec results (Bloc, 54 seats, very good)     Less obviously, the Outremont results (I wanted Lapierre to lose, he didn't, the bastard)     Also not very obvious, the Papineau results    Let me tell you why. The candidate for the Liberals was Pierre Pettigrew. The Bloc had  urlLink Martine Carrière . Who is  urlLink Martine Carrière ? She was in my politics class, at the Uni. She's been with the Bloc for 2 years, and had the guts to go against a big name in the Liberal machine, and try to be the youngest female MP ever elected. She was 'dreaming' of forcing Pettigrew into a recount, and 'hoping' that she'd lose by about 5000 votes.   Last election, the Libs won by 12000 votes or so. This time, I was watching closely. Early in the evening, Pettigrew was winning by 300 votes. Then, by 40. Then he started losing. By 10 votes. Then by 200. Then by 800. Then by 1200. (I thouroughly apologize to the lady who had problems installing her USB drivers for her modem at this time - I  really  wasn't paying attention.) Then I left work.   Fuck this, I'm going to Martine's office. It's at Jarry metro. Luckily, I had  urlLink a friend  with me.   We get there, she's losing by 150 votes. Then by 1400. Then, by 200 again.   Then the votes stop coming out.   No one knows which polls are still to come. It's 50-50.   Drama ensues: it seems one of the poll-persons was pregnant, and was rushed to the hospital to, of all things, have a baby, on election night. Couldn't it wait? Then, another person, in the same office, got  a fucking heart attack . Right before opening the damned box.   At this point, she's losing by 334 votes.   Turns out there are two possibilities. Either all boxes have actually been opened, and the result stands, even though Elections Canada's web site says 180/182 boxes open (that's according to the  directeur du scrutin , from what I heard). Or, there are 2 boxes still uncounted, and they won't be until tomorrow morning.   Whichever it is, I spent a great evening. Tension, drama (and yes, Jon, even  one  beer)...   I'm really pround of Martine, and I'm proud of all 16270 people who voted for her. She's a great girl, and she really worked her ass off during the last month. And to think only a few months ago  I  was helping her with our Canada-Québec Politics class...  Now, to bed. I'm working tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All you Canadians here...     GO VOTE!    It takes 2 minutes, and it's the one time in 4-5 years that you actually have your say in governing your country.   Think Paul Martin's a dumb fuck? Throw him out! Think Stephen Harper is worse than Bush? Vote against him! Think there's not enough mustaches in Ottawa? Vote Layton!   I don't care who you vote for. Just go. Do it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There is something ridiculous in this country. The second question in Elections Canada's FAQ about the vote is this:    urlLink   Is someone allowed to eat a ballot?     What. The. Hell.   If  that  is frequently asked, I take back what I said. Canada's stupider than the US. No contest. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the spirit of Wonko The Sane, here's a quote I have found in my 'Cubicle Hell' desktop calendar:   An actual tip from page 16 of the HP "Environmental Health Safety Handbook for Employees":  Blink your eyelids periodically to lubricate your eyes.  For more information on Wonko The Sane and where The Asylum is, I suggest reading The Hitch Hiker's Guide to the Galaxy's fifth book in the trilogy, Mostly Harmless, or you can also read the instructions on a packet of toothpicks. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For those who didn't know, Xenoman is one of my old ex-coworkers, from back in the good ol' days when we used to get paid to play Worms and listen to music.   He's always (well, since I knew him, at least) held a very specific and, frankly a bit unsettling, view of what he refers to as "substances": alcohol, tobacco, and drugs in general.   He doesn't approve of them. Not only does he not use them, but he honestly disapproves of anyone getting drunk, smoking or doing drugs.   Which, to me, is odd, because he was genuinely set back by all this "substance-taking" that was going on. Why would anyone want to do that to himself?! Doesn't the smoker care about his body, about his health?! But, you know, at the same time, why not eat McDonalds for breakfast and lunch 4 days a week... No biggie.   But that's neither here nor there. He's entitled to his opinions, and I'll be damned if I'm going to take them away from him. We are, after all, not in America.   What really irks me about all this is, how does he fucking know? How do you get that God Damned opinion in there, if you have  absolutely  no clue what you're up against?   Maybe alcohol, I understand, he had a traumatic experience, with all that's entailed by being the only sober person in a gigantic gathering of young piss-ass-drunk high school partiers. Seeing people puke over each other is not quite what they put in beer ads, you know?   Smoking, I guess. I mean, it's easy to be anti-smoking these days. No one's making it hard for anyone to hate smokers, and no one seems to mind that they're confined to -40C temperatures, outside in the winter. It's become like that. So be it.   Drugs? Well, they're illegal, aren't they? I'm sure that's for a reason, right?   Well, you know what? I call bullshit.   There is no way you can lead a full life, in my opinion, if you deny yourself such pleasures. Of course, you're not going to find me saying that smoking's actually  good  for you, or that the Breakfast of Champions includes Mushrooms and Budweiser. But, come on.   All that "high on life" shit - how about a nice glass of wine with a big juicy steak? Or a glass of beer, once in a while? That's certainly not going to kill you,  (and in fact wine is actually good for you)  but, really, must you deny yourself that? Are you trying to make a point? Set an example?    Let me tell you who that reminds me of.   I know a girl. Let's call her, oh, I don't know, Diane.   Diane is now, I believe, 26 or so. Maybe 27. Anyways. Not important.   What's important is this: she's a virgin. Not a born-again virgin or anything like that. No. She's a true, real-life, hardcore, virgin. And you know what? She very well intends to stay that way. Forever. She has said, on a few occasions, "I really want to die a virgin". Now, never mind the reasons.   What's your take? You've probably already had sex, or else you should really go, it's past your bedtime. Is it bad? Would you give it up, forever? Remember before you had sex, the first time. Before you were even interested in girls. You didn't care, it wasn't important... If you were inclined to be very introspective, you might have even thought you could go all your life without ever having any sexual relations with any member of the opposite (or same, whichever) sex. But now - would you still do it? How do you picture it, being 40 years without sex?   Now - you can feel a few different ways about Diane. You can laugh and ask why she's not joining a convent. You can wonder why she chooses that. You can pity her because she doesn't know what she's missing. But the core of the business is this: she's forgoing something quite good, that she has absolutely no interest in, most probably because she  does not know  how good it is.     Now I know you're all expecting me to try to bridge together the concepts of "having sex" and "smoking a joint". Well, it's not going to happen. I'm sure you can draw your own conclusions. And if I'm being unclear, just ask me.   I promise I won't be drunk nor high when I answer. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Penny Arcade!   I don't even think this is necessary, but if you don't read PA, I'm not talking to you.  Ever again.    Though tempting that might sound, read it anyway. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Awful Forums - Goldmine - A Safety Message From Your USPS Letter Carrier  Some of the funniest photoshopping EVER. Go! Now!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
                                  I&#8217;m trying to see whether I can actually update my blog via e-mail. That would rock.        
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yep.   Yersterday's St-Jean party was fun. We almost ran out of hot dogs, but in the end all was good.   Except for the stupid rain.   Well, that really wouldn't have been a problem if it hadn't been for the thunderstorm. You see, pool + lightning != fun. Pool + lightning = everybody get the fuck out and get inside.   Some of us actually went back in the pool afterwards, and it was good. There is not much cooler than drinking a beer in a pool while it's pouring rain.   It was one of those parties where even though it's not memorable in any way*, it really was fun and if I could've made it last for much longer than it did, I would've. But people have to work, and that's fine. I was super-tired too.   But I was happy.    * When I say it wasn't memorable, I mean that it's not the kind of party we'll remember fondly, or at all, in a few years or whatever. It doesn't take away the fun of it all. I just don't seem to know how to throw real parties, ones that stay in your head for years, that no one wants to leave and all that. I don't know, I always feel like it's lacking  something .  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to try and make this interesting.   Not sure it's going to work, though. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This Land is your land.    One of the funniest flash films ever. Great job, and good funny all around. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink GEORGE W. BUSH NOSE JOB?   Yup - good ol' GWB got his nose replaced. Maybe it was too brown from sucking up to his Halliburton buddies?   Sorry if it's old news. Just thought it'd be fun to share. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNN.com - Cheesy, nude Monn arrested - Jul 20, 2004   Updated for your pleasure. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well it's been a few days now that I've switched over to  urlLink L.L.Lozeau  as far as money-making is concerned. And I love it.     Consider this - Mrs. Lozeau (Daughter of  urlLink Léo Laurent Lozeau , founder) is still at the helm, with her husband. She actually came down and met us (all 7 of us in training) and spoke with us, being all nice and friendly, and said that  she hoped we had fun there . And she really meant it, too. She asked each of us where we worked before, and when I said "C.A. Barbier Photo, in Lachine" she instantly said "Oh, with Mr. Giroux! Then you must know Francis (he's the guy who worked there after I left) - he's at the Camera counter..." She actually remembered, 2 days later, when she introduced our bunch to her husband, and said "this is Eric, he used to work at Barbier with Giroux." And her husband answered "Oh, Pierre! How is he, I haven't seen him in a while! Surely you know Francis! He worked there, too."    I've never seen more hands-on management, from up-high. And it looks like it works, too. You can clearly see that they care, that they show up every single day and walk around on the floor, and actually  help you out when there's a lineup .  Even better - we have specifically been instructed to  take our time with customers . If one guy talks to you for 2 hours about his cat pictures, and wants to know how he could perhaps make them better, or even if he just wants to talk about his cat,  take the God Damned Two Hours it takes . The customer'll be happy. We have been officially  promised  by the Photofinish Manager that he will never, ever ask us to "move it" or "clear the customer, we've got a line-up". Ever. And if another customer bitches that he waited in line for an hour while we were explaining things to another customer, we have been told to say that "if you ever need to have us spend two hours with you to make sure your order is correct and you're happy, we'll take all the time we need, and then some". And that's  official Lozeau policy .    It also feels nice to work in the largest photo store in Canada. You see, everywhere I used to work, anytime we didn't do some  thing  we'd just go and say "Oh, we don't do this, go to Lozeau". Well, guess what - I'm gonna have to get used to saying  yes  quite a bit.    And being the largest means also that I'll be handling  only  the photofinish counter. That's right, we're going to be  eight  behind the mother fucking counter, taking films and handing people their pictures. All day, non-stop. I swear to God, there's always a line-up. Sometimes, it stretches to the entrance of the store. And it's a big store.    I'm also getting cost+10% (same old, same old) on pretty much all products in the store - including  urlLink my next baby . Oh yeah.    It's nice to work some place I actually  like  again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink WESH.com - News - Police Arrest Cheese-Covered Naked Man : "Maryville police say they arrested a 23-year-old man wearing nothing but cheese early Sunday."  Um, yeah. Cheese. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Dihydrogen Monoxide Conspiracy   There's a major government coverup concerning this dangerous chemical. Read up, find out about it, and you'll know what's up.      If you really wanna find out what it is and are too lazy to figure it out yourself, you can just click    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been ages, but I'd ordered new shirts on  urlLink ThinkGeek , and they've arrived.   (For the curious,  urlLink I got   urlLink myself   urlLink one of   urlLink these shirts .)  Yay me. I also got my girlfriend one of the  urlLink the Common Cold  Plush Microbes. It's actually quite big, I'm surprised. I was expecting something tennis-ball size, while it's actually about softball-ball size (if my recollections of what a softball-ball look like are correct).   All in all, I'm happy. I've been waiting for a PA shirt for ages, and now I actually got 2. Yay. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow. Just watched the new Rammstein video ( urlLink ed2k link ). Whoa. That is  messed-up , but it kicks the usual ass that Rammstein kick whenever they show up.   If you have the opportunity to see them live, I strongly suggest you show up. They don't charge much (by big-ticket-band standards) and put on what is most certainly one of my top-3 shows ever. (The other two, if you're interested, are Pink Floyd's 1994 'Division Bell' tour, and Cowboys Fringants' Bell Center show.)   New single = new album = new tour. I'm giddy already. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Crap I Drew on My Lunch Break   This one's a nice one!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I start at  urlLink Lozeau  tomorrow morning.   Good news all around.  urlLink Téléperformance  can suck it.   I'm going to get paid $9,50 to stand behind the photo counter, have people bring me their films to get developped, and give them their pictures back once it's done.   Keep in mind, $9,50 is what I was getting paid LAST at Compucentre, after 4 years and being Assistant-Manager. So, same pay, none of the responsibilities. Schweet.   But I always feel awkward saying 'I quit'. I always feel bad about it, even if I'm working for a big corporation that really couldn't care less about me. Today isn't going to be fun. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You will notice two new links in the 'Links' section.   One has replaced Blogspot's own Atom XML feed, Feedburner's being much more standard-friendly.   The one right below that says 'Add this blog to My Yahoo!' and means just that. Click on it, and Shazam! Not quite exactly is now part of your My Yahoo page.   Ain't it nice?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My new email address is as follows:  redlion (at) gmail dot com  Please update accordingly.   Yes, I will probably soon have invites. Yes, I'll let you guys know. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I gots da mad G-mail skillz, yo.   Or, I will just as soon as Mr. Joshua Turner, from Kansas, MO, send me the invite.   All that e-mailly goodness for what? A Halo figurine. Master Chief. Red.   The one I tried to sell on eBay a while back, got $10 for it, and the guy  a) never got around to actually sending me money, and  b) Left me bad feedback on eBay about the whole mess.  I'm quite happy to get rid of it, and I'm also quite happy about getting Gmail.   All in all, I'm quite happy about things. Except now is the time I should be going to work. That, I'm not ecstatic about. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've always said this.   Now it's true.   How do I know? Quizilla told me.    You are a  GRAMMAR GOD !   If your mission in life is not already to preserve the English tongue, it should be. Congratulations and thank you!    urlLink   How grammatically sound are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    And when Quizilla tells you something:  a) it stays told, and  b) it's true.   So there.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      From Yahoo News: 'The Department of Homeland Security's U.S. Computer Emergency Readiness Team touched off a storm this week when it recommended for security reasons using browsers other than Microsoft's Internet Explorer.'  US-CERT actually released a  urlLink Vulnerability Note :  There are a number of significant vulnerabilities in technologies relating to the IE domain/zone security model, the DHTML object model, MIME type determination, and ActiveX. It is possible to reduce exposure to these vulnerabilities by using a different web browser, especially when browsing untrusted sites. Such a decision may, however, reduce the functionality of sites that require IE-specific features such as DHTML, VBScript, and ActiveX. Note that using a different web browser will not remove IE from a Windows system, and other programs may invoke IE, the WebBrowser ActiveX control, or the HTML rendering engine (MSHTML).    All in all, you really should use  urlLink Firefox . 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just started reading  urlLink Goats  (a comic strip, in case you didn't know).   It's actually pretty funny, and I'm only up to February 1998 in the archives. But I know what I like, and I like this quote: " There's a fine line between excessive sarcasm and permanent bitterness. "   I guess you've got to read the strip to get it, maybe.   Anyways, off to work I go in about an hour. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Athena    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   The text is unreadable, I know. It's because the image breaks my blog under IE - it makes it look all screwy. What it says is this:  You are like the Greek God Athena, of Education. You're seen as sophisticated, smart and a really down to earth person. easy to get along with, Easy to understand - and with great prospects. You do well in what you enjoy, and often excel in most things academix  (sic)   Weapons are not your thing. You would prefer to pummel your opponent to death with your fists and feet. You show a lot of Honor but some power still eludes you. I can give you this power, I can make you stronger, join me.      urlLink   How would you Murder?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Back to  urlLink work  tomorrow.   It feels weird - I have Wednesdays and Thursdays off. Plus, last Saturday I was, well, um...  what was it already? Oh yeah!  sick! &lt;wink wink nudge nudge&gt; So that means we had St-Jean Baptiste, then I worked last Friday, got a day "off", worked 3 days (one of which we finished early, because the whole company moved to a new building - I ended up working 5-9h30), get two more days off, and now it's over. 5 days a week.   I feel like I was out on bail, and I'm thrown back in.   It's not that it's a bad job. I don't mind it that much. It's the schedule.   Working 5PM to 11:30PM is a killer. You never get to eat dinner with people. You get home, everyone's asleep. You can't "do stuff" after work. And I'm still in the mindset that doing stuff before going to work means getting up crazy-early. Plus, I seem to be the only one of my "team" (read: the-people-I-was-in-training-with) on that schedule, so I always have my breaks alone.   Add to that the propension to stay up until ungodly hours in the morning, and you have a lifestyle completely at odds with everyone elses', including, but not limited to, my girlfriend's. You see, she's of the school of 'at midnight, it's time to start going to bed' - and I fully understand that, seeing as how she used to stay up super-late and wake up at noon, and when she quit doing that, she lost like 20 pounds and didn't feel so sick all the time anymore. I really don't want to pull her back into that schedule.   The only good part of starting work at 5PM is that you never, ever, have to worry about getting up late, setting your alarm, etc. In fact, you can basically stay in bed late  every single day .   But that's it, really. Anyone know of a non-telemarketing job that pays semi-well (read: above minimum wage) and that is on a more "regular" schedule?
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
           IMDB's Top 100 Best Movies of All Time  generate this HTML for your own page at  urlLink ObeytheFist.com               Rank    Movie    Didn't See It/ Started It/ Finished It/ Hated It!      1     Godfather, The (1972)     Started It      2     Shawshank Redemption, The (1994)             3     Godfather: Part II, The (1974)             4     Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King, The (2003)             5     Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers, The (2002)             6     Casablanca (1942)     Finished It      7     Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring, The (2001)     Finished It      8     Schindler's List (1993)     Hated It!      9     Shichinin no samurai (1954)             10     Star Wars (1977)     Finished It      11     Citizen Kane (1941)     Finished It      12     One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (1975)     Started It      13     Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb (1964)     Finished It      14     Rear Window (1954)             15     Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back (1980)     Finished It      16     Raiders of the Lost Ark (1981)     Finished It      17     Memento (2000)             18     Usual Suspects, The (1995)             19     Pulp Fiction (1994)     Hated It!      20     North by Northwest (1959)             21     12 Angry Men (1957)             22     Fabuleux destin d'Amélie Poulain, Le (2001)             23     Psycho (1960)     Started It      24     Lawrence of Arabia (1962)             25     Buono, il brutto, il cattivo, Il (1966)             26     Silence of the Lambs, The (1991)     Started It      27     It's a Wonderful Life (1946)             28     Goodfellas (1990)             29     American Beauty (1999)             30     Vertigo (1958)     Started It      31     Sunset Blvd. (1950)             32     Matrix, The (1999)     Finished It      33     Apocalypse Now (1979)     Started It      34     Pianist, The (2002)             35     To Kill a Mockingbird (1962)             36     C'era una volta il West (1968)     Started It      37     Some Like It Hot (1959)     Started It      38     Third Man, The (1949)             39     Taxi Driver (1976)     Started It      40     Paths of Glory (1957)             41     Sen to Chihiro no kamikakushi (2001)             42     Fight Club (1999)     Finished It      43     Boot, Das (1981)     Started It      44     Double Indemnity (1944)             45     L.A. Confidential (1997)             46     Chinatown (1974)             47     Singin' in the Rain (1952)     Started It      48     Maltese Falcon, The (1941)             49     M (1931)     Finished It      50     Requiem for a Dream (2000)             51     Bridge on the River Kwai, The (1957)     Started It      52     All About Eve (1950)             53     Se7en (1995)     Finished It      54     Monty Python and the Holy Grail (1975)     Finished It      55     Saving Private Ryan (1998)             56     Cidade de Deus (2002)             57     Raging Bull (1980)             58     Rashômon (1950)             59     Wizard of Oz, The (1939)     Finished It      60     Sting, The (1973)             61     Alien (1979)     Finished It      62     American History X (1998)             63     Mr. Smith Goes to Washington (1939)             64     Léon (1994)             65     Vita è bella, La (1997)             66     Touch of Evil (1958)             67     Manchurian Candidate, The (1962)             68     2001: A Space Odyssey (1968)     Finished It      69     Treasure of the Sierra Madre, The (1948)             70     Great Escape, The (1963)     Started It      71     Wo hu cang long (2000)             72     Reservoir Dogs (1992)             73     Clockwork Orange, A (1971)     Finished It      74     Amadeus (1984)     Finished It      75     Modern Times (1936)     Finished It      76     Ran (1985)             77     Annie Hall (1977)             78     Jaws (1975)     Finished It      79     On the Waterfront (1954)             80     Braveheart (1995)     Started It      81     High Noon (1952)             82     Apartment, The (1960)             83     Fargo (1996)             84     Sixth Sense, The (1999)     Finished It      85     Aliens (1986)     Finished It      86     Shining, The (1980)     Finished It      87     Strangers on a Train (1951)             88     Blade Runner (1982)             89     Metropolis (1927)     Finished It      90     Duck Soup (1933)             91     Finding Nemo (2003)     Finished It      92     Donnie Darko (2001)             93     General, The (1927)             94     City Lights (1931)             95     Princess Bride, The (1987)             96     Toy Story 2 (1999)     Finished It      97     Kill Bill: Vol. 1 (2003)             98     Great Dictator, The (1940)     Finished It      99     Sjunde inseglet, Det (1957)             100     Lola rennt (1998)     Finished It            urlLink Which  movies have you seen?        I've written as 'started it' the ones I saw part of in one of my Cinema classes.    (edit: moved down - took too much space up there)   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink askthetechgirl.com  AAAAAARGH!!!! This is so, so, so wrong on so many levels.   It's actually one of the saddest things I've seen, bar none.   It's basically the bastard child of a phone-sex service and a tech-support line.   Select quotes:   I'm not your average computer geek - I'm also a professional wrestler and actress. (Maria)   Some things that really make me hot are Macromedia Dreamweaver, Homesite, various FTP apps, Windows, Microsoft Office, Outlook, Outlook Express, JASC Paint Shop Pro, Microsoft Image Composer, HTML and Java Scripting."  If none of that grabs you (and you want to be grabbed, don't you?), we can talk about the upcoming 3rd movie in the Star Wars trilogy, Sandman comics, Simpson's trivia or the new Cure album, among other, less G-rated things. (Tara)  Uggghh...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Although my long-assed rant might have been seen as 'pestering' or 'pressuring' to you, that was certainly not my intention, and if it appeared so, I apologize muchly.   This is going to sound harsh, but although I consider you a very nice person (perhaps 'friend' would be too strong a word, but bear with me here), I most emphatically do not think that "sticking to your guns" or however you want to call what you're doing (conviction, ...) is "strenght of character". I pride my character on having an open mind, and leaving my options open.   You know me, I've got some very strong opinions. The thing is, I'm always open to discussing them, and you can actually end up convincing me.   I certainly wouldn't want you doing something you don't like just to "shut everyone up". That would be wrong.   I'm just trying to put forward ideas, and exchange views.   I understand if you're tired of it, and I'll stop. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Seriously.   Even though enough people have been told that SUVs were probably the worst kind of car you could buy, they still get them. Why? So they can be assholes on the road?   And second, to quote a  urlLink BlogWars  guy - " This is evolution in action. Those who choose not to wear a simple safety device can't complain when their carcass slides across the freeway, or worse. "  Amen.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you're going to be getting pictures taken, why the  fuck  do you walk around looking   urlLink confused by an ear of corn  ?  I swear to God. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink A nice take on the elections in the US . I've always enjoyed Something Positive's outlook on life: offend as many people as possible, in the shortest amount of time. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>