<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today is sunday and i woke up about an hour ago. today is gonna be a good day, bc i only have like 3 days left in prison!! yay! :D so anyways, im goin to youth at like 5 and then church at 6 30, so i get to see friends for a little bit tonite, and that is SO exciting! but yeah, i know this one is really short, but its basically just to say that if anyone wants to leave a comment you can! that would make me smile!! oh, and you dont have to be a member, or have an account or anything like that, cuz i changed the settings!! so, if your ever bored and readin this...feel free to leave one for me! ;D love ya'll, -me-  p.s. mel, i got your email!!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      		 	I cant explain what u do to me, 	the way you make me feel, 	its unlike anything else I've felt before, 	yet it appears to be so real. 	maybe it’s the way you talk, 	the way you utter every word, 	or maybe it’s the way you move, 	the way your body curves. 	It could be the way you touch me, 	just a soft brush of your hand on my shoulder, 	or the way you wrap your arms around me, 	the way you pull me closer and closer. 	I cant explain what you do to me, 	the way you've touched my soul, 	its like I have a light inside, 	it feels like forever it will glow. 	maybe its your gentle touch,	 	or the softness of your lips, 	or maybe it’s the way you smile, 	the way you put your hands on my hips. 	the only thing I know is, 	I don’t know how to explain a feeling like this.  p.s. i wish there were actually perfect guys out there like in this poem! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      	Fake Your life consists of one big lie, It wont go away, You don’t know why. Your not yourself, Your hiding, I know, You think its hidden, But it's not, it shows. You don’t live you life the way it really is, You lie about that, And hide behind this. People know your not being yourself, Putting your feelings upon a high shelf. Your pain isn’t hidden, Your face is well -read, Tear-stained and angry, You wish you were dead. I pray for you daily, That you would come to learn, Not being yourself, Isn’t something to yearn. When at school with your friends, You act different that at home, With friends a fake person, At home, you are abandoned and alone. Your life will get worse, Than it already is, So turn to the Lord, True strength comes from Him.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’ve finally won you over, 		Body, Soul, and mind, 		I finally won you over, 		I finally made you mine. 		I finally won you over,  		I can’t wait to taste your kiss, 		I finally won you over, 		I didn’t know my heart could feel like this. 		I finally won you over, 		everyday is a brand new day, 		I finally won you over, 		when im w/you, I know that everything’s gonna be ok. 		I finally won you over, 		This is much better than I thought, 		You’ve given me so many gifts, 		So many lessons you have taught. 		I finally won you over, 		It’s just so hard to think,  		I finally won you over, 		I don’t want to wake up from this dream. 		I know that I cant have you, 		Its just part of reality, 		I should of known I don’t deserve you, 		Things aren’t always what they seem.  p.s. just in case anyone was wondering, a lot of times the poems i write have nothing to do with my own life, they just come into my head and i gotta get them out. other times they do have a resemblence to me...i'll let you decide which ones are which
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i think about u randomly, thoughts of us together, i think of when u asked me out, promising we’d love each other forever. i think of when we used to kiss, our eyes shut, ur lips and mine, ur hand was always in my hair, it gave me goose bumps every time. I think of when you’d hold my hand, our fingers interlocked, we always found the perfect fit, we thought our love could never stop. But then i think about the day, u asked me to sit down, i asked if everything was ok, and why u were wearing a frown?  i remember when u told me, that you thought we should just be friends, what happened to the love?  i asked,u said it would never end.  and then i remember, the look on ur face, ur smile wasn’t apologetic,  "my life is just to busy right now, i think we should just forget it".  I remember that day perfectly, my feelings and thoughts about u, we were no longer together, our love wasn’t forever, and apparently our love was neither perfect or true.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll! im so happy to say that im in a much better mood today! last nite really sucked, but i talked to melanie after her awesome show and she told me that she loved it and had so much fun. hearing that made me so happy and im so glad that everyone did an amazing job. ( guys, you know that if there was any way i could have gone, i most definetly would have...i love you! ).  i am happy to say that i am going to finally be ungrounded in 4 days ( not that im counting, hehe!) ) i dont think you understand how exciting this is for me!! i have only been grounded for like one or two nights in a row, so dealing with this whole "sarah you are grounded for a week and five days" thing really sucks. but hey, its almost over now!!! yay!!!! so, so far today ive watched tv and movies...the secret window is sooooo good! i also watched drumline, but it wasnt for the first time..it was still really good tho! ( mel, remember how we said that that movie almost made us want to join band? lol! )alright, its about 4 and im gonna go take a nap..i am so sleepy! sweet dreams guys, i love you! -me-
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok wow... i am so pissed at my parents right now it is UNBELIEVABLE!! im not even kidding, this has to be the worst nite of my life. so, bc i am STILL grounded ( the main reason for this blog ), im gonna explain why im so mad. alright...it all started with me getting grounded for several reasons, which you already know ( hopefully ). well, bc my mom is being a total biatch, she isnt letting me go to the vivace show, even tho she gave me permission like 3 weeks before i even got grounded. i am SO mad bc my best friend ( i love you mel! ) is in it and i promised her i could go, also my other good buddies tj, travis, sterling, etc. but bc my mom is GAY she isnt letting me go...yeah so life sucks right now and i am in SUCH a bad mood. i would SO much rather be at the show with my signs ( hehe! ) and then chillin with my friends afterwards, instead of what im doing right now and probly all nite ....NOTHING.   for those of you reading this for the first time.. im really sorry that i sound so bad!! i dont want you to think im always like this, bc im not. im usually cheerful and happy ( i promise! ), but bc of this whole freaking thing, my mood had most def been changed. so i love you all, but i gotta go. -me-  p.s. whoever wants a shoutout..give me the word :D
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys!  today was pretty cool i guess...being grounded is starting to suck worse and worse as my punishment gets longer. the funny thing is....i dont even know how much longer im gonna have to do this!!! gah! ( props to mel :D ) ok but anyways, today i skipped work cuz i didnt get much sleep last nite cuz of my finger ( yuck! ) and so i slept in till like 12 30!!! woot! and then i watched some tv and then ran errands with my mom. shes bein really cool...so cool that i want to ask her about my grounding situation... its just that everytime it comes up she gets a lil mad and wont stop talking about it. so i have decided to just wait this whole stupid thing out. :( anyway...after the errand thing i went to these ppls house that we are housesitting  ( they are on vaca ) and swam and layed out. then my mom and i watched this movie with beyonce in it...so good! well, thats it so far! love you guys!! -me-
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so this is a blog all about my favorite of my brothers friends..brogan!! hey bud whats up? hows your summer goin? i hope its awesome, between all that hockey and job stuff you must be pretty busy!!  also, i think you are such a sweet guy...and you and my bro most def need to chill soon, cuz hes back from baylor! :D yay! but anyways, sorry this is so short, but i promised to give you a major shoutout so here it is...I LOVE YOU BROGAN!!!!!!! -me-
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll!!! wow today was really crazie!! :P    love ya'll, me
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! :) other than the fact that im grounded till eternity...todays been good!! my family went to hurricane harbor and we were there since about 11 and left at 3 30. so im nice and sunburned ( as always ) but what can ya do? and right now we are all just hanging out...kinda boring, but seeing as im grounded, i cant go anywhere anyways. alrighty, phones ringin! gotta run! love ya'll! -me-  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so today is saturday and i owe some ppl an apology. :( first, i really need to apologize to drew and joe for acting like a total bitch yesterday...im really sorry. i love ya'll! second, i am really sorry to travis and tj for leaving early and not saying bye..i yelled out bye guys and waved but i guess you didnt see me...im really sorry and i love you!! and by the way, travis, i need to talk to you.  ok other than that...today is saturday and i went to baylor to pick up my bro..i missed that kid! and then we went shopping at hilsborogh. alright, thats all...im sorry agian you guys, i love you!! -me
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll! ok well, its only 12, so nothing interesting has happened yet...oh wait! i woke up...i guess thats exciting? i dunno. anyways, today im gonna chill with my buddies! the usual crew ( you know who you are ) is gonna chill somewhere tonite and im excited bc last nite was "family nite" and as eventfull as that was....this is going to be SO much more fun!! ok well im out! love ya! me  p.s. shoutout to brogan bc i LOVE him! p.p.s. shoutout to autumn for teachin me how to do this cool thing! o, and for looking at my panties! (lol )
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll, its me! wow this is so tite...i've always wondered how ppl do this, and now i know how! ok, my day went something like this: i woke up at 7am and took a shower and then went to work where i spent about 9 hours being bored out of my mind and wishing i was hanging out with friends...so when i came home it was about 6 45pm and i was so tired, so i watched the rest of chasing liberty with my mommy. (yay!) then, mel and kels call me and want to know if i can chill with them tonite...my mom ends up sayin no bc my dad wants us to have a "family nite" and watch big fish. well, here it is 10 30 and i have nothing to do and both my parents are asleep...i cant go anywhere bc they would wake up and get pissed, and so that makes me sad :(  but the sugar cookies i made are done so i gotta go eat 'em! (yummy!) sweet dreams! love always, me
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll, today is thursday and i had work all day...it was&nbsp; alright i guess..it went by quicker than normal ( which is always good!) !! :)&nbsp; then, after work melanie called me and i went to spensers to chill with him , mel, mary, kels, courtney, and wesley. after i got there we went to 711 so kelsey could get gas and so spenser and court could get slurpees ( yummy!!). after that, we went to melanies hows and chilled for a bit, and waited for scottie and decker to come over. mel danced in the street while we waited....good times, love ya babe!! :D&nbsp; when scottie and adam came, we all drove to steak n shake to visit lindsay and to get shakes ( slash fries for spenser). then everyone headed to mels but it started POURING down rain, and no one wanted to run out of their cars and climb all of her steps so we decided to go to marys. so we're following spensers truck and kelsey and i are wondering why hes takin us around the block and down the alley..and then he pulls into the driveway of a house and we realize... WE WERE FOLLOWING THE WRONG TRUCK!!! ahahahahaha, it was SO funny, wow :D!!! so then kelsey heads over to my house (i gotta work in the morning so i had to come home a little early), and spenser calls while we're on our way and asks whats takin so long. after i told him the story i had gotten to my house ( thanks kels! :D ) , and couldnt stop laughing about the fact that kelsey and i were so confused and thought spenser was takin us through some shortcut...and then its not even his car!!! lol! alright, tonite was fun, thanks for helpin me get through another day of work guys...you rock! *wink*!! ok, im gonna go take a shower and then watch head of state...talk to ya'll later! much love!! *wink*!! -sare 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys... today is a really sad day. and i dont mean that just bc it rained, or bc there are only 17 days left of summer, but bc one of our schoolmates died this morning at 4 30 from alcohol poisoning.&nbsp; i dont know what happened exactly, bc there are so many diferent stories flyin around...but the fact that kebra died is terrible, and im in complete shock.&nbsp; pray for her family that they will be there for eachother, bc this has got to be the hardest thing they have ever had to face in their lives, and i know that even tho they arent aware of all&nbsp;of our&nbsp;prayers, but the fact that we would take time out of our lives to do that is one of the only things we can do in this situation. -sare 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! today was probly one of the longest days ive ever had. it all started out with an early work day not ending until like 7 30. then i had to go to this bible study thing my family does with another family during summer....(its alright), and now im here. im pretty upset that i had to work today bc i have this thing about always wanting to play mudfootball in the rain...and then maybe more ( lol drew ). but considering i had to work......i couldnt do it!! ahhh!! well, im tired and there isnt realy anything else to write, so ttyl!! love ya'll!&nbsp;&nbsp; *wInK* -sare 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so things are begining to look up at home. yay! thank you so much melanie, i couldnt ask for a better friend. -me 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *editors note* before you read this...im just warning you that its kinda long. i also dont know if its any good...so feedback would be awesome  &nbsp; ANYTHING BUT REAL: i am so tempted,  to say just how i feel it seems the courage i have mustered, is anything but real, i know that&nbsp;if i told you,  what went on in my mind, you'd be so frustrated, you'd leave me farther behind. i am so tempted, just to say how i feel, it seems the courage i've mustered, is anything but real, i know if i ever mentioned, the things that i&nbsp; think, you'd dismiss them so readily, as quick a wink. theres so much to say, that i've been keeping from you, you deserve to know everything, the time has come, and its way overdue. i am so tempted, to say just how i feel, it seems the courage i have mustered, is anything but real. i've been feeling this way, for quite a long time, my body will always want yours to be mine, jelousy is something, ive become a victim too, i have such strong feelings, whenever it comes to you. theres this thought in my head, and it wont go away, its telling me that you arent here to forever&nbsp;stay, so no matter what i've done no matter what i've ever said, you'll never understand, how i've felt about you, even in the end. i was just so tempted, to say how i feel, it seems the courage i had mustered, has just disapeared, and you will never know, just how i feel, and that, my friend, is a fact i've always feared.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  :(   &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everyone! i hope ya'll are enjoying your summer, cuz UNFORTUNATLY its almost all gone!  :( &nbsp; theres only 20 days of summer left!! omg!! thats like, ten days less than a month...ahh!!  so this morning i woke up at around 11 and my mom said we were goin to see raising helen at the dollar theater, and i was alll for it, so i made some calls, and at around 12 20 melanie and kelsey came to pick me up ( my mom picked up a friend of hers, who didnt have room in the car for all of us ) !! kelsey and mel hadnt eaten luch yet, so they swung into mcdonalds where kelsey got a kiddie meal with mandarine oranges, and mel got a burger and fries. it was SO funny bc after they got theyr food, we were sittin in the car while they ate and all of the sudden we all realized that kelsey didnt get her mandarine oranges!! * i guess you had to be there or somethin, but we thought it was pretty dang funny!* so anyway, we went to the movie, which was SO cute!, and then mel and kels went home and my mom took me to voice lessons wich i had at like 4 ish. that went alright...the time really drags on in there...but anyway! i get home and call mel and we make plans to chill at her house and watch friends/IM/ do whatever other things girls do when they hang out...and i ask my mom to take me over there but i have to wait till shes done with dinner. so my brother leaves the house to go chill with his buds, and all of the sudden my mom starts crying. and this kinda freaks me out bc i have no idea whats wrong, but then i remember that her and my dad have been fighting A WHOLE FREAKING LOT lately, and i also recall that my dads famous silent treatment (usually reserved for me ) has been effecting our house , bc he just isnt talking to my mom. omg, hes SUCH a selfish a**hole...he really pisses me off when he does this. so back to my mom...shes in the kitchen bawling and i ask her if shes ok and whats the matter....and she cant talk bc shes crying so hard. i am really scared right now bc i have no idea whats going on..ive only seen my mom cry like 3 times in my whole life. so, as we speak...shes in her room with the door locked, and im really worried.&nbsp; now that i think about it, i probly shouldnt be putting any of that on blog for everyone to read, but i dont have a journal or anything, and i have to get this outta my head and on something solid, ( the computer works, in this case ). so, i guess i better go check on her. god, this is so wierd. love you guys *wink* -sare  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so the song popular from wicked....SOOOOO good autumn...YOUR THE GREATEST!!! :) *wink* -sare 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll! today was grand and i had so much fun ( so far )!! i had madrigal practice from one till like 3 something ( good stuf!)...and afterwards me, autumn, sterling, liz, and michael went to wendys and had lunch. it was so fun, we stayed there for about 2 hours!! we were all just sittin there tellin story's and laughing about autumns book/sterlings dead pets/my stupidness/ just about everything else!!&nbsp; its so scary, autumns book told her to write a letter to a man on death row and she wrote to the scariest person ever and put "helter skelter"...that girl is so brave! lol ! so thats about all ive done today...but later on tonite i have to go eat dinner with my aunt uncle and cousin cuz her birthday was the 23d and theyr in town today!! im excited....but i really wish that i was playin poker with tyler and drew, and chillin with mel, kels, adam and scottie. sorry guys, you know i love you!! well, i gotta go take a shower! later ! *wink* -sare  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll! whats happenin? not a lot here...just chilled all day, it was good!! i woke up at about 11...i havent gotten to sleep in in a loooong time! i hung out at my house, and then my mom and i went to animias ( ahh brenna! ) and had luch. these satellite guys came over at around 12 30 to fix something that has been broken for a while ( exciting, i know ), so we couldnt go anywhere while they were here. after they left, my mom, bro, and i went to verizon wirelesse to check out phones, bc my bro is gettin a new one for his bday and my mom is gonna let me get one 2!! yay!!! so we decided on which ones we were gonna get, and then left bc it was too crowded and we had to go home to get ready for church.&nbsp; but the phone im gettin is waaayy cute! its a flip phone, and its pretty small, and it has text messaging!!!! yay!!!! and it has a camera, which is really exciting! * smiles!*&nbsp; my mom and bro are gonna go buy the phones tomorrow when its less crowded, while im at madrigal practice! now im waitin for my family to finish gettin ready for church, and now they are, so i better go!! love you guys!! *wink* love ya! -sare 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey guys! ok so since the 12 quite a lot has happened! i went to baylor from the 13-17 which was cool...but i was so tired! my mom drove me,&nbsp;tj, jess, travis, adrienne, and melanie there, and we introduced my mom to allen jackson ( wow it was funny..she hates country music! ) and then we watched school of&nbsp;rock..classic!) the ride there was cool i guess..we stopped at burger king before we got to baylor ( mels first time! ) and it was alright. then we got there and checked in and such.&nbsp;it was so crazy bc it was SO hottt outside (we had to walk everywhere) but once we finally got to the singing place it was freeeeezing!! ( crazie!! ) anyway, we basically learned all this music that will&nbsp;be the required try out songs later on this year, so that was cool...but i was thinkin after it was over that i wanted to go to tcu next year and melanie (love you babyguuuurl), jessica, meesh, and adrienne all agreed. after baylor i went to austin for a few days with my family, and that was pretty cool, we went shopping and chilled out..good times!  : )    then, i came back to my house ( the 19th ) and on monday i had madrigal rehersal which was pretty good, jessica came to pick me up, thanks babe i really owe you! then she took me and travis home and i chilled for the rest of the day. on tuesday i got really sick and thought i had strep but luckily it was just an earache/seriously bad sinus infection *yuck!*. wednesday i had to go back to work so that was kinda sucky, and i did the same thing thursday and friday. thursday was travis' birthday!! sweet 16...your finally caught up with everyone buddy!! and he also got a cell phone, which he is very excited about.  : )&nbsp;  friday after work i chilled with drew, tyler, meesh, brenna, and scottie at the movies...wow bourne supremacy is really good, except we sat sooo close ( bc the theater was packed!) that it kinda seemed blurry sometimes lol. meesh and i ate dinner with tyler and drew before the movie and then went to tylers house to play poker ( im not very good...only played like 2 times  :(&nbsp;&nbsp;  ) today is saturday and so far, meesh and mel and i went to tcu to hear the concert of the ppl that went to that choir camp this past week...we decided on goin to baylor next year after all. we also went to buy cds so we can practice..cuz for some reason, baylor didnt feel like sellin them! ( hmm!) before we got to tcu we went to starbucks, and after the concert we went to on the border ( yummy!! ).&nbsp; since then ive been doin the list of chores that my mom so nicely gave to me ( ugh!! ). im waitin to do stuff...so call my cell! alrighty, thats enough catchin up! im out! love ya'll!! *dont forget to smile!* -sare 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys! hows it goin? today was alright...for some reason i was tired allllll day long ( wierd! )! i woke up this morning and had to go to the doctor bc my mom thought i had pink eye, and guess what?! i do!! :O !! can you believe it?! i got some medicine from the really nice ladies at the pharmacy and my eye doesnt look like ive been smokin the reefer anymore! i could SO use this medicine as a disguise for when i actually have been smoking....hehe jk! after i went to the doctor my dad took me to ihop and we chilled and ate breakfast and made fun of this goofy waiter there...good times! hehe! anyways! after that, i came home and started to look for stuff to pack for baylor...mucho exciting! then, jess came to pick me up for madrigal rehersal ( woot! ) and we were at rachel tuckness's house from about 1-3. when i got home i had to babysit my neighbor...(so cute!) and when she left i started actually packing. then mel called and we chatted for a while about what all we should bring and stuff. by the way, melanie, i love you babygurrl!! lol! aight guys, thats about it! im gonna be packin and chillin here all night, cuz my favorite aunt from austin is spendin the nite! ( :D  yay!! ) so gimme a ring on the house phone, cuz my cell is packed! love ya'll! ;D -me-  p.s. oh, i almost forgot! melanie, jessica, adrienne, travis, and tj....if ur readin this....im gonna come get ya'll between 10-10 30, so be ready! dont forget to bring money for lunch, cuz my moms gonna take us out before we get to baylor! travis, im callin you at 9 for a wakeup call...have the phone by you so you get up, goofball!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys...wow its been so long i almost forgot what to do!! ( uh oh! ) i havent put anything new on here since the 5th....phew! not much has happened...just basically chilled, but i'll fill you guys in anyway! the 6th -10 : my aunt and grandparents were in town, so my brother and i were forced to spend some MAJOR bonding time with them....talk about boring and sucking all at the same time! but anyways..while they were in town we went to see some movies, got pedicures ( not my brother tho! ), and went to burgers lake! the 10 ( after my family left )- i spent the nite at my babygurrrls house! I LOVE YOU MELANIE!! we went to scotts house and chilled with adam, tj, scott, and julianna. then we went back to mels house and watched friends ( sooo good! ).  the 11- we went to church and i started packing ( sorta ) for baylor!! woot woot for choir camp!!that sounds so nerdy, but we're gonna have a lot of fun!  ok well, enough for now...dad needs the comp!! love ya'll so much! -me-
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey ya'll! wow today was SO much fun! me, mel, bren, and kelsey went to burgers lake for the whole day...and let me tell you, all you boys missed out on seein 4 fine girls in bathin suits!! ( hehe! ) we swam, grilled, played volleyball, swam somemore, ate again, more volleyball....and thats about it. we also went on this trapeze thing and not only had a blast doing it, but we also had such a fun time laughing at all the retarded ppl who dont know how to work it. seriuosly, melanie and i were cracking up everytime, and then brenna and kelsey were bein sweet and they started saying "aww" afterwards. wow so fun! but now that im home and i am SO RED! like, my body is on fire!! ( and no brenna, not that way) i am just so sunburned it is amazing. (ouch!) alright, well im gonna go aloe myself up..talk to ya'll later! -me-
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow! its been forever since i put somethin in here! well..here it is now!  hey ya'll!    omg i cant believe it! im ungrounded!!! ahhh!! this is so exciting you have no idea!! ok so today so far was alright, i slept in and chilled around the house with the fam..then i went to chick fil a with my mom ( yummy! ) and had a really good time ( surprisingly)! and now, im gettin ready to go see the notebook with mel, bren, kels, mary, and scott..i am so excited! this is the first time im gettin w/ friends out since like, 2 weeks ago...and trust me, that is a LONG LONG time. sorry this is so short, but my rides here so i gotta go! love ya'll! -me-
     

    
</post>


</Blog>