<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know what disgust me? All this shit going on in Iraq. Acting like animals and killing the innocent lives of American soldiers, and other people mostly related to the Caucasion assent. I was visiting my brother *Squeeky* in San Diego last weekend where he showed me a video of an American Soldier actually being be-headed! I was speechless.I never knew of any of this happening-anywhere! ok, I know the soldiers are willing to put their life up for their country, thats what war is all about. But all this just makes me sick? How the fuck could this happen? To anyone? I don't care if u were fuckin' Hitler's son-whatever, nobody should be treated that way, at all! It almost makes me sick to my stomach in disgust. What resolves from this, huh? A world more full of violence and hate? Takes me back to the scripture in Genesis where God talks about wanting to wipe out the face of the Earth because of so much violence caused in it, while Adam persuaded him otherwise. Sometimes, I wish he would have. To live in a world like this almost makes you wish you were never born. But to live and be alive is like a gift from God. We are like dirt in his presence, but he loved us so much to give us a chance to be one with the world. I highly doubt he intended for it to end up this way. Like anyone else, just let it go. We were born so different from everyone else around I'm sure its going to cause conficts. God gave us the gift to learn to get along and learn from one another. Sadly, I don't see that much of it at this point....  Now, these are all just my opinions.   Judge them as you like. Thank you...and remember, judge wisely.  
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the last year I've been friends to one of the most caring, sweet, and compationate girls I have ever met. Except the thing is, we haven't actually met. She actually lives all the way in Ohio. I know, sounds crazy to like someone who lives 3,000 mi. away. But your not gonna find the right person just in your own city. Heck, your soul- mate may be living in fuckin China for all you know. Now, I'm not jumping to conclusions here. I never said she was my soul-mate, even though I can't help but think it. We talk almost every day, she calls alot too cause I'm too poor to call all the way to Ohio, just kidding.But if my Dad ever found out, you know he would kill me.  Not liteally people.  I've gone through my times of hard break-ups, even at 16. I don't really think you need an age to fall in love. Parents always say "your too young to fall in love." My parents are one of the smartest people I know. But I have to disagree in this case. Love can either ruin you, or make the best of you. I fell in love for the first time at 15. Last year,I dated this girl my cousin set me up with.Even though it was for a short period time, she was nothing like any girl I had been with before. Wild and crazy..maybe sometimes a little to much. But all in all, it was more than a fantasy, but somewhat like a dream.They say good things can't last forever. I was wrong in doubting it and like what was expected, she left me and tore out the biggest part of my heart. Guess that's how love is sometimes. But anyways, sorry to get off-track. About this girl, she makes me feel like someone. Not just anyone, but someone special. Now I know this might sound corny but...Adrienne, if your reading this, you had a big effect on me. Through hard times and great times, you were there for me, and I wont ever forget it.  Now, these are all just my opinions.   Judge them as you like. Thank you...and remember, judge wisely.  
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can anyone tell me what the heck is up with relationships these days? "I love you"...and 5 seconds later... "I hate you!" A never-ending, ongoing battle that seems to occur frequently with most couples through out America. More than 50% of marriages end in divorce. I mean, c'mon people, lets grab some diagram and anti-PMS pills and put this battle to rest. Now, even more common among young adults, is the trend of un-loyal acts of "orgies, friends with benefits, cheating,cyber-sex, etc, and the common "lucky guy who scores and makes out with two hot chicks!" I know this may seem fun and popular among young adults as myself, but ask yourself...where does LOVE fall into this, or any part of it? Is this what love these days is suppose to be? If so, I don't want anything to do with it! I want a relationship built on honesty, love, respect, and faithfullness,..not with some cheesy slut at school looking for a fun time. With what, getting AIDS? You may laugh now, but look at the facts. AIDS is more common these days than it has ever been before. People losing lovers, friends, family, cause someone didn't slap on the ol' Jimmy, and thought it would be fun to take the pony for a ride. Well kids, that pony's probably dead by now. So people, I leave you with this, find the right person and learn to get along for crying out loud, cause that may well be the only pussy you'll be getting for the rest of your life.  Now, these are all just my opinions. Judge them as you like. Thank you...and remember, judge wisely. 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    D12...can it get any dumber than this?...&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now, I don't get it...what is the whole deal with "rap" these days? I mean, in the early 80's, it came out as a sort of "new form of music." MUSIC? What music? I don't get the whole *girls parading around in thongs, bling-(whatever), flashing lots of money-this, to "I'm gonna go cap that mo' fo'"-that.* Now believe me, I like girls in thongs as much as the next guy does. But to have women being vandalized and treated as objects in these "vide-ho's," as they are endowed with liquor and climbing all over some rapper flashing cash, just seems degrading to me. Do you need to have cash these days for hot girls to be crawling all over you? In some cases yes, but what for? For the mere satisfaction that they need to have MONEY for girls to like them? Kinda sad don't you think? Not only is it the stupid, ignorant, and pointless videos, the lyrics are just as bad. Do we really need to hear about how many girls one guy fucked or how he smacked that b*tch last night? It's disgusting and immorally wrong! On top of it all, they are just as bad as rappers as they are as a person in real life! Gee, what a surprise. Now, If you have ever seen the show " Punk'd ," I think you know what I mean. Showing rappers set up in some situation to make it look like they got busted for-whatever, while they use some bull sh*t excuse about everything they are questioned for. My personal favorite would have to be the episode where Brandy and this other rapper/boyfriend guy, I don't know, are pulled over for a supposed jewelry bust, and she says to the cop "don't you know who I am?" and "but I'm black!" Now, I'm  not  one to be a racist person, and I'm not, but I don't give a sh*t if you were the color of a fuckin' "Rainbow" for all I care! Why is it that these rappers think they can get away with so much stuff? I think they can come up with something a little better to explain to the cop than "Pity me, I'm black and have money." Now I'm sure we have all seen or heard about the R. Kelly scandal, and then some other rappers occasionally getting imprisoned because "THE'RE BLACK!" No, I'm just kidding everyone...."BECAUSE THEY'RE STUPID!" Now, these are all just my opinions. Judge them as you like. Thank you...and remember, judge wisely. 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so yeah. Sometimes, I can't stand my parents. But I guess we all can sometimes. Not my real Mom though, I love her to death. But ok, it's my Dad and Step Mom. My Dad always fucking yells at me for no reason. He is a dick about everything and i swear he hates me. I found out he does, when a couple of days ago he told me, straight to my face "I'd rather you leave then my wife." Ok, I know you haven't been around in my life for all 17 years, but what the fuck? Found out from my Mom yesterday that he never even wanted kids, only cause his Parents pressured him into it. No wonder he has had so many exwives. He is going on his 4th now, and each and every time he puts them before me and my little brother. Take this. His last wife, Allison, total bitch from hell who had 3 rotten step daughters. They lived with him in this big ass fucking manchine. My brother moves up to live with them. The nasty bitch doesn't want my brother to live in their guest bedroom so they build a bull-shit room in the garage with a bad, a tv, put up with fucking plastered wooden walls. Is that not the biggest hunk of crap you ever heard? Now he is with this girl Gayle. She started off in the beginning being really sweet. But then, she turned out like the rest of them. She's used to living by herself and doesn't like to hear my music or having me around. So then, she bitches to my Dad who then blames it on me, whcih really pisses me of cause she doesn't have the balls to say it to me herself. Then, when she calls a family meeting, she cries about it and becomes all emotional. Well guess what bitch, your not the only one living here!! Even my Dad, who I now hate very much, agrees with me. I woudl move but I have nowhere else to live. I live in a big nice house which has its set backs, but it's better than nowhere. I'll be moving out in 2 years after completing highschool. Thank God! and i'll never have to see them again. I know we all get mad at them every once in a awhile. But do they love or care about me? NO! She told my Dad even that she wants me out, and that it is either me or her! Sorry if I'm swearing do much, but you can see why.  Now, these are all my opinions, just them as you like. Thank you, and remember...judge wisely. 
    
</post>


</Blog>