<Blog>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A girl asked a guy if he thought she was   pretty,   he said...no...   She asked him if he would want to be with her   forever....and he said no...  She then asked him if she were to leave would he   cry, and once again he replied with a no...   She had heard enough.   As she walked away, tears streaming down her   face the boy grabbed her arm, and said....  You're not pretty...you're beautiful...  I don't want to be with you forever...i need to   be with you forever... 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      name: ice hobbies: surfing the net gender: female age: 22 date of birth: august 6, 1981 horoscope: leo school: AMA School of Medicine address: cainta rizal email add: ice08_tazcal@yahoo.com hair: natural eye colour: dark brown.. hair colour: black right or left handed: right marital status: single siblings: 2 last 4 digits of ur no:  ... when's ur bedtime: around 10-11 pm do u hav a car: none..  what type of car do you want: civic??? brand of cars : volvo & honda tried smoking: yes, until now drink alc0h0l: sometimes.. been hurt emotionally: yah.. a lot of times kept a secret from anyone: yah.. everybody does, right??? been on stage?: yup.. lot of times  *favourites*   color : blue food:  chopseuy drinks: red iced tea, lemonade and mango juice number: 08 looney toons: tazmanian devil sports: biliards (slight) song : depends on my mood.. movie: naughty and suspense friend: evelyn nucup (hahaha!!!)  *right now*  wearing now: scrub suit hairstyle: layered looking at: monitor & my boyfriends pic thinking of: my boyfriend & my prob listening to: toxic by britney spears ------------------------------------------  *do u believe in*  love?: yes fate?  yup urself: there are times that i don't  to those close to me, i see things in a brand new  perspective.. ghost: a bit.. haven't seen one pa eh.. angel: yeah.. -------------------------------------------------  *in the last 24hrs*  worn jeans: yup cleaned ur room: always cried: yah last person i talk to on the phone: my mom   *love life*  do u hav a gf/bf: yes hav a secret admirer: i dunno  do u wanna get married? yes. in time  do u plan on having kids?: yup. 3 kids he.. he.. hw old u wanna be when u get married: 26-27  how old u wanna be when u hav ur first child: 26-27 how many kids do u want: 3  do u hav a crush: hmm.. yeah   *either 1*  pink or black: black kiss or hug: kiss summer or winter: winter sunny or rainy: sunny.. chocolate or vanilla: chocolate hanging out or chilling: hanging out music or tv: music night or day: night guys or girls: guys sleepin or eatin: eating!!! love or lust: love.. silver or gold: silver sunrise or sunsets: sunsets phone or in person: in person diamond or pearl: pearl  ------------------------------------------------  *The person u know who are...*   most caring: my boyfriend most understanding: my mom      
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the skeleton & the pretty pig!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      10th grade  As I sat there in English class, I stared at the girl next to me. She was my so called "best friend". I stared at her long, silky hair, and wished she was mine. But she didn't notice me like that, and I knew it. After class, she walked up to me and asked me for the notes she had missed the day before and handed them to her. She said "thanks" and gave me a kiss on the cheek. I wanted to tell her, I want her to know that I don't want to be just friends, I love her but I'm just too shy, and I don't know why.  11th grade  The phone rang. On the other end, it was her. She was in tears, mumbling on and on about how her love had broke her heart. She asked me to come over because she didn't want to be alone, so I did. As I sat next to her on the sofa, I stared at her soft eyes, wishing she was mine. After 2 hours, one Drew Barrymore movie, and three bags of chips, she decided to go to sleep. She looked at me, said "thanks" and gave me a kiss on the cheek. I want to tell her, I want her to know that I don't want to be just friends, I love her but I'm just too shy, and I don't know why.  Senior year  The day before prom she walked to my locker. "My date is sick" she said; he's not going to go well, I didn't have a date, and in 7th grade, we made a promise that if neither of us had dates, we would go together just as "best friends". So we did. Prom night, after everything was over, I was standing at her front door step! I stared at her as she smiled at me and stared at me with her crystal eyes. I want her to be mine, but she isn't think of me like that, and I know it. Then she said "I had the best time, thanks!" and gave me a kiss on the cheek. I want to tell her, I want her to know that I don't want to be just friends, I love her but I'm just too shy, and I don't know why.  Graduation Day  A day passed, then a week, then a month. Before I could blink, it was graduation day. I watched as her perfect body floated like an angel up on stage to get her diploma. I wanted her to be mine, but she didn't notice me like that, and I knew it. Before everyone went home, she came to me in her smock and hat, and cried as I hugged her. Then she lifted her head from my shoulder and said, "you're my best friend, thanks" and gave me a kiss on the cheek. I want to tell her, I want her to know that I don't want to be just friends, I love her but I'm just too shy, and I don't know why.  A Few Years Later  Now I sit in the pews of the church. That girl is getting married now. I watched her say "I do" and drive off to her new life, married to another man. I wanted her to be mine, but she didn`t see me like that, and I knew it. But before she drove away, she came to me and said "you came!". She said "thanks" and kissed me on the cheek. I want to tell her, I want her to know that I don't want to be just friends, I love her but I'm just too shy, and I don't know why.  Funeral  Years passed, I looked down at the coffin of a girl who used to be my "best friend". At the service, they read a diary entry she had wrote in her high school years. This is what it read:I stare at him wishing he was mine, but he doesn't notice me like that, and I know it. I want to tell him, I want him to know that I don't want to be just friends, I love him but I'm just too shy, and I don't know why. I wish he would tell me he loved me!   I wish I did too... I thought to my self, and I cried. i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..i love u..   >================================= These are the moments, I know heaven must exist. These are the moments, I know all I need is this. I have all I've waited for ... And I could not ask for more..   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tess was a precocious eight-year-old when she heard her Mom and Dad talking about her little brother, Andrew. All she knew was that he was very sick and they were completely out of money. They were moving to an apartment complex next month because Daddy didn't have the money for the doctor’s bills and our house Only a very costly surgery could save him now and it was looking like there was no-one to loan them the money. She heard Daddy say to her tearful Mother with whispered desperation, "Only a miracle can save him now."   Tess went to her bedroom and pulled a glass jelly jar from its hiding place in the closet. She poured all the change out on the floor and counted it carefully. Three times, even. The total had to be exactly perfect. No chance here for mistakes. Carefully placing the coins back in the jar and twisting on the cap, she slipped out the back door and made her way 6 blocks to Rexall's Drug Store with the big red Indian Chief sign above the door. She waited patiently for the pharmacist to give her some attention but he was too busy at this moment. Tess twisted her feet to make a scuffing noise. Nothing. She cleared her throat with the most disgusting sound she could muster. No good. Finally she took a quarter from her jar and banged it on the glass counter. That did it! "And what do you want?" the pharmacist asked in an annoyed tone of voice. "I'm talking to my brother from Chicago whom I haven't seen in ages", he said without waiting for a reply to his question. "Well, I want to talk to you about my brother, "Tess answered back in the same annoyed tone. "He's really, really sick... and I want to buy a miracle." "I beg your pardon?" said the pharmacist. "His name is Andrew and he has something bad growing inside his head and my Daddy says only a miracle can "We don't sell miracles here, little girl. I'm sorry but I can't help you," the pharmacist said, softening a little. "Listen, I have the money to pay for it. If it isn't enough, I will get the rest. Just tell me how much it costs." The pharmacist's brother was a well dressed man. He stooped down and asked the little girl, "What kind of a miracle does your brother need?" "I don't know," Tess replied with her eyes welling up. "I just know he's really sick and Mommy says he needs an operation. But my Daddy can't pay for it, so I want to use my money". "How much do you have?" asked the man from Chicago. "One dollar and eleven cents," Tess answered barely audibly. "And it's all the money I have, but I can get some more if I need to. "Well, what a coincidence," smiled the man. "A dollar and eleven cents is the exact price of a miracle for a little brother." He took her money in one hand and with the other hand he grasped her mitten and said "Take me to where you live. I want to see your brother and meet your parents. Let's see if I have the kind of miracle you need." That well dressed man was Dr. Carlton Armstrong, a surgeon, specializing in neuro-surgery. The operation was completed without charge and it wasn't long until Andrew was home again and doing well. Mom and Dad were happily talking about the chain of events that had led them to this place. "That surgery," her Mom whispered. "was a real miracle. I wonder how much it would have cost?" Tess smiled. She knew exactly how much a miracle cost... one dollar and eleven cents ..... plus the faith of a little child. A miracle is not the suspension of natural law, but the operation of a higher law...... (A TRUE STORY) I know you'll keep the ball moving! Here it goes. Throw it back to someone else who means something to you! The Friendship Ball A ball is a circle, no beginning, no end. It keeps us together like our Circle of Friends.But the treasure inside for you to see is the treasure of friendship you've granted to me. Today I pass the friendship ball to you. Pass it on to someone who is a friend to  you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    pretty me!!! *wink*&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Do not fall in love every time you fall in bed. Learn to detach emotionally. 2. Sex does not equal commitment. 3. Do not revolve your entire life around him/her. Addiction is bad for your health! 4. Do not cling, act needy or demand. Doormats are for your feet, not your heart. 5. It's OK to say NO! 6. Stop talking so much. NEVER reveal everything. 7. Do not grill them or their friends for information. 8. Master the art of LISTENING. 9. Treat him/her as you would your best friend. 10. Friendship creates long term love and comes before sex. 11. FORGET about fixing your partner. IT WILL NEVER HAPPEN. 12. Your choice of partner is a reflection of who you are and who you are not! 13. Enjoy the moment first. Live in the present. 14. Don't worry about the ex's or start naming your future children. 15. NEVER read their journal or go through their paperwork. 16. If you have no trust, you have no relationship. 17. Allow space and freedom between you. 18. DO NOT always be available. 19. Calling frequently is a turn off and signals insecurity, neediness and control. 20. Open your eyes to lies and cheating, OR... close them...justify the bad behaviour, and live with the consequences. 21. Little or no eye contact? Start walking. They won't even notice your gone. 22. Anyone preoccupied with their physical appearance and dress, usually have very little or nothing to offer from within. Look beyond the physical! 23. Never compromise your values. 24. If you OVER give, you will lose your lover and her/his respect. 25. DO NOT LOSE YOUR IDENTITY. 26. If someone REALLY wants to be with you, they will be. 27. State your personal rules in the very beginning or expect them to be broken. 28. If they ask to be just friends, be just that and look elsewhere for a love partner. 29. If someone wants to really be with you, they will. If they keep giving reasons for not calling or say they are extremely busy, GET THE HINT, leave them alone. 30. Don't ever give up your friends for him/her. 31. If your partner one day leaves you, be sure you have friends, money, a career and a life of your own which you never gave up. If you do not, who do you have to blame but yourself!  All of us will only pass this lifetime once...we owe it to ourselves to make the most out of it... Its nice to see when we look back that WE LIVED WELL & LOVED BEST!!!   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>