<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh well...still not much to report.  Did 1 Hour of Step Aerobics...did not do any strength training as I had planned.  Pretty disappointed with myself overall.   Cardio:  Step Aerobics (1 Hour)  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, not much today...Just Yoga.   Flexibility: YOGA (90 Minutes)  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Be sure to tune in for our first official weigh-in this Sunday.  Veronica & I will be posting our current weight & measurements, and posting new pics showing off our progress (minimal as it will be) for the first week.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok...I ran my three miles this morning..then I did my regular crunch routine. My meals include...Grilled Tuna, steamed brocolli, Chicken, and protien Drinks..I am allowing myself to cheat when I crave to with cereal.I lost 60 pds doing this exact meal plan, and i know it works. Their are really no carbs involved except the cereal. Though I am eating more protein than anything. Im not taking any supplements, though I might try the flaxseed, and the omega 3 fish oils. All a daily vitamin. I read that what burns fat are acid fruits..like apples, grapefruit, citrus oranges. Also soybeans..but i heard that they dont tast all that great.. but then again..what does when your trying to burn fat? Nothing does. Anyhow. My weight goal for my height it 13-140. I will be happy with 140-145. I have alot of muscle on me, and as we all know muscle weighs more than fat. Just want to get rid of the stomach! So if anyonw has any more ideas..please tell me. Then again what woman doesnt want to get rid of her stomach =-0).  Ok..So this evening I found myself, once again on the treadmill.. though this time.. i walked three miles. I worked on my lats, and ended up talking to a friend at the gym for about an hour, so by then i did two more sets of pulldowns, this time i did three sets @40 pds. Then came home and worked on Legs and Calves. Im doing 4 sets of 20 with 15 pds on each end.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay...so here's what I actually did today:   Strength Training: Body For Life/Upper Body  Cardio: 20 Minutes on Treadmill, 15 Minutes on Bike, 15 Minutes on Elliptical Trainer, 25 Minutes Step (Teaching)  Flexibility:  Not Yet   I feel fantastic & can't wait for tomorrow.  Hopefully, I will do YOGA in a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Just me.Simplicity, Outgoing, fun, spontaneous and Creative!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay...maybe not that popular...but anywho.  Click on the thumbnails below for larger pics.    urlLink   &nbsp; &nbsp; urlLink   
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, so Monday is our start date.  Let's see how many days we can each go without missing a workout.  I know we can do this, if we just stick with it.!!!    Here's what I have planned for Monday (let's just see if I can stick to it).     Strength Training- Body For Life: Upper Body (45 Minutes)  Cardio- Intermediate Step (5:30-6:30 PM at Bally's Katy Location)  Flexibility- YOGA (90 Minutes)   Total Workout Time: 3.25 Hours (A Little Long...but we'll see)  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I have to say that Dog Food doesnt sound to pleasant..so you got me there Erica!I'm in the roll once again..did 1 hour and 30 minutes on cardio yesterday..then worked on legs by doing 4 sets of 15 pds. For abs i did crunches to salsa =-0), and it only gets better. =-0)...I know I DONT WANT to eat any dog food anytime soon =-0)..lets melt off this fat! Burn baby burnnnnnnn.!!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Starting Monday June 28th, Veronica & I will commit to 100 days of exercise.  But, like any great motivation program...there is a catch.  If one of us misses a day...we have to start back at day 1.  The first one to complete the 100 days wins...so let the competition begin.   Rules (afterall...can't have a competition without rules :)     All workouts must be logged daily...if it is not logged, it is null & void   All workouts should last at least 45 minutes (although 1 to 2 hrs is preferable)   A weigh-in will take place each Sunday.  If a participant gains 8lbs or more, they have to eat a can of dog food (Yup...Good ole Alpo...How's that for motivation?)      
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CARDIO. STAIRCLIMBER AND TREADMILL. 1HR 30 MIN. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CARDIO STAIRCLIMBER 45 MINS.&nbsp; LAT PULL DOWN 3 SETS 20 30 AND 40 POUNDS. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well today i ran 30 min on the treadmill, and worked on my shoulders. I gave myself a challenge and went for a 1 mile run on the outskirts of my complex, i was amazed to see that by the third time around I was still going, and I still had energy, my calves were cramping up a bit, but other than that it was a great challenge, and will probably start running out doors again instead of on the treadmill, especially as it gets cooler.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      45 TREADMILL, 20 STAIRCLIMBER, 3 SET 30 PDS LET PULL DOWNS, 3 SETS OF 50 CRUNCHES.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Today I ran once again, and I am finding that my body is too comfortable so I am going to change my routine around a little bit, I did my cardio and shoulder extentions with 10 pound weights 2 sets&nbsp; 20 10 5  i feel great. I feel like I am getting leaner, and that i have aot more energy than I have had in a good while. My eating habits are very disciplined. I eat alot of protein and greens, and sirloin steak grilled. Keep this up through december and Ill be quite content.    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      cardio 45 minutes. Tricep pull downs- 3 sets 20&nbsp;@&nbsp; 35 pds 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      stairclimber 55 mintues. freeweights at home.Squats.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CARDIO CARDIO CARDIO. 45 MINUTES.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today  I joggged 3 miles. I worked on shoulders and calves. For Dinner I made a beef stew. Heah Erica where are you??? =-0)Hope all is well.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well, after being Glued to the Copa America game after I got home I watched bolivia and venzuela tie, man what a game! Then or course Colombia and Peru, and they too tied, so..i got up in the middle of the game and went for my 45 minute run, man did i sweat! i increased the treadmill on incline, but damn i feel good! anyhow. Thats pretty much it, i was eager to get back home to see who won the game, and it turns out that peru is eliminated, Yes go colombia! However...I have to go for my home team Brazil! their games on wednesday night at 8:30pm. But ill be sure to get my run in before then. =-0)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok so today i did the usual, 45 minutes cardio, this time i did the stair climber. I worked on Lats 2 sets of 30, and 3 sets of 20. Ill be running three miles later this evening and workingout my calves..Like i need to workout my calves =-0)...i just hope they dont get any bigger.Just want to cut em up even more.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today i worked on shoulders and back, and did 45 minutes of jogging on the treadmill.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK HAD A FAMILY EMERGENCY THESE PAST FEW DAYS. NOW GETTING BACK ON TRACK. WORKED ON LEGS AND ABS TONIGHT. =-0)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I got home last from work, after hanging out for a while, So I didnt workout today, so I am a little disappointed at myself, however, i wont be hard on myself, because i have been working out pretty hard every day for the past few weeks. Ill just use this as my rest day, and have to workout sunday. =-0)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well, today i started a new routine. Given by my friend eric. Today I did HITT for 20 minutes. Man does that stuff work! and three sets of 30 on Abs, incline. New pics coming soon. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I havent logged in a while, but Im still working out last night, I did cardio for about 3 hours, i walked outside after the gym, it was nice out. Today, the 11th...I ran the treadmill and worked on back. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I havent been posting, but the majority of the days i have been doing cardio cardio cardio. Tonight I'll work legs. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>