<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh!!! We had a blackout here...
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being some time since I blogged...  Haha...someone didn't believe me when I said that I am blogging...well I told them I got verbal diarrhoea!  Let me see...what to write?  Quite a few things, let's start with soccer, ok?  Well, well, there have been a number of upsets in Euro 2004. Traditional favourites like Spain, Germany, Italy got knocked out in the group stages. England was pipped in the penalty shoot-out by host Portugal, defending champion France was dumped by unfancied Greece, then Holland survived against Sweden and then finallly the Czech Republic won with a convincing 3-0 win over Denmark.  The semi-finals will see Portugal pitted against Holland, while Greece will face the Czech Republic...  I will be betting for a Portugal vs Czech Republic final...  Attended my previous company's barbeque function on Saturday night...hmm, I was kinda surprised that I was about the only ex-employee there...you see, I left that company 8 months ago, so I was not really expecting it...initially I had thought that this was a gathering of some of my ex-colleagues and good friends...  Well, there were quite a number of new faces there...I think my previous company is now getting back on track in its business...cheers...  Back to more mundane stuff, with my new school term approaching, I guess it's time o pull up my socks and fight hard this year. The time is soon coming when I must decide whether to stay on with my present institution or to change. I am just very uncomfortable with the way things are done over there...sigh...  My friends will know that I tend to understate things or be "diplomatic" when I talk...so I let you venture on that thought.  Till the next blog...
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hear...hear...   The Spanish Armada failed to beat the Portugese Navigators...actually talking about Euro 2004...Portugal defeated Spain 1-0.  Figo and company goes to 2nd round.  Greece 1 Russia 2 Despite this defeat, this could happen to be the year of the Greeks...they got two movies ("Troy" and "Alexander the Great" coming up and keeping people interested in the Greek mythologies...think men in skirts wearing sandals...)     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha, did a little bit of rock-climbing today...SAFRA was holding the last day of their rock-climbing competition today.  Anyway, the competitive bit was over on Sat. So today's event was open to the kids and the public...  so funny to see the kids hanging for dear life as they struggle to reach for each handhold. Crowd support was fantastic, they cheered as the child passed an extremely tough obstacle or completed the climb...  I joined the queue and then found myself alone for this climb...gulps...  I got height phobia!!!  Yeah, it's true. I admit it, people. I got this height phobia...maybe due to the fact that I wear spectacles.  Always afraid that my glasses will fall off and that I will be left hanging in mid-air helplessly...  Anyway, with the legendary speed and agility of the Kai...you climb the wall effortlessly and complete it...  Yeah...there I go again, imagining myself as some kind of character...  But the truth is for a first-timer, it's quite alright, not too tough...just like the feeling when I reached the top...it's exhilarating!!!  Yippee...Markus 1 Height Phobia 0    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is to help save some space on my Friendster...  ~~~  A self-composed poem: "the timing seems all wrong... the mind is not what it seems... the spirit of the soul is flagging... the body is itching yet aching...  Things come but at the wrong time... Yet not to do will make a dodo... To do means hard to balance... Yet a necessary evil to stay afloat..."  ~~~  "What is my destiny? That is a question that only Time can tell..."  ~~~  Translated from a Chinese saying..."There is no feast in the wide world that does not finish...all good things must draw to an end..."  ~~~  They say a star has fallen in the east. Its tail a trail of fading light in the dark. I went there to seek it. And found engraved in it my prophecy of doom.  ~~~  The hand of Fate can be rather unfair at times, doesn't it? *sneers* 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Ash nazg durbatuluk, ash nazg gimbatul, ash nazg thrakatuluk, agh burzum-ishi krimpatul."...  "One Ring to rule them all, One Ring to find them, One Ring to bring them all and in the Darkness bind them."...  LOTR freak...one day I might be a Ranger...another day, I might be an Elf princess, and then I could turn to the side of evil and become a dark lord or a snivelling misshapen creature struggling for survival... 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amazing, just as I lament on not watching enough soccer...there I go, not being able to sleep and I managed to catch the incredible comeback of the Czech Republic as they came from 2 goals down to beat Holland 3-2. Simply superb...
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Try standing for two days while on exhibition duty...tires you out...wonder if I am getting old...sigh...  There's a Rock Climbing Competition organised by SAFRA at Suntec City yesterday and today. Many kids took part in this. So thrilling to see the relays that took place. If you are not careful, you miss your footing and that means precious time lost.  The "business" is not good lah!!! Wrong place, wrong crowd...  So far only managed to watch only one Euro 2004 game so far...that's the Italy vs Denmark game...and I watched one half of it. Punters and fans, you know that game ended in a nil-nil draw...yawnz...first time I missed so many football games worth watching...maybe I should fly to Portugal...*grinz*  That's it...till the next time... 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hallo, ladies and gentlemen,  this is my first blog post...let me explore a bit more before I unleash the power of my thoughts...hehe... 
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe you may wonder why I have been away for so long.  Try juggling work and part-time studies. Sometimes, you just feel so tired *mentally* that when you reach home after a long day's work and pursuit of a degree/diploma course, you just want to drop on your bed and sleep. I am sure that many working adults in Singapore share my sentiments.  Right now, my stories are still stuck in limbo...I guess it will be some time before I can proceed on to finish it. *sigh*  Talk of which, i better be doing some writing soon...I am supposed to be doing an essay on world trade organizations and about the challenges and issues facing the WTO.  Sucks...  By the way, if the quality of my posts drop, can somebody shoot me in the head please?  Oops, what am I saying? I should be saying "...can somebody tell me to buck up and be more creative?"  Haha, till the next blog...  
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was Food Fiesta 2004 at Suntec City this weekend...  I was helping out my uncle at his booth, selling the Hainanese delicacy - Chicken Rice Balls.  What's that? Well, to put it briefly, this consists of chicken rice rolled up into a round shape, about the size of a tennis ball. According to my uncle, this helps to keep the fragrance of the chicken rice and prevents the smell of the chicken from dissipating.  The making of Chicken Rice Balls is a dying art in Singapore and of the many Hainanese hawkers who used to make Chicken Rice Balls years ago, my uncle's business is the only one left still standing.  Well, many people think selling Chicken Rice is good business in food-mad Singapore. True, it may be good and the fact that we hear TALES of hawkers who drive luxury cars, add to the allure of that business.  But they may not know of the back-breaking hard work and long hours put in by the hawkers and their assistants to give you that prefect mouth-watering and simply delicious plate of food, be it Chicken Rice, Nasi Lemak, Roti Prata, Wan Ton Noodles or "Tzi Cha", etc.  (For my foreign friends, these are some of the more famous local food in Singapore.)  Ok, to be fair, all people in the food industry deserve plaudits for their efforts. (This applies to chefs, cooks, the food manufacturers and many other people as well.)  As I am typing this, I am resting now at home from all the serving, carrying, packing and cashiering work at the food fair. Heavens! You should see the crowd and queues!  More on these tomorrow... 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phew! Sometimes I wish that there are 48 hours in a day instead of 24 hours. There are so many things to do that we really wish that there is more time to do everything there is to do.  But then again, having more time may not be a blessing. It's just like if we are mortal and then suddenly given immortality, can we really stand the thought of seeing so many things over so many years, centuries and millenia? The human mind, although mysteriously unique and with many latent secrets yet unlocked, can get tired of this unchanging march of time.  Take "Bruce Almighty" for example, in the end, Jim Carrey's character went out of control and there was one point when he couldn't handle everything.  The moral of the story? I leave it to you, the reader, to decide.  
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One fear...that I have is that I will never live to see myself in a convocation robe and a degree...given the subjects that I am studying, my infamous lack of patience to sit down and really do some work, and my current temperament, which is basically anger and frustration...
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Instead of the usual blog and post-your-thoughts, style, I think I might also put up extracts from my writings.  I have already tried to make things different by writing "dark" poems...but I guess a lot work is needed to make this a truly unique blog site...  More on these some other time...
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate work whereby there is no reward (intangible in terms of experience gained or tangible in terms of money)...  Just before you, the reader, and any of my friends start labelling me as "materialistic"...let me inform you beforehand that I am a Taurus and the Taurus guy does put material possessions in a high priority. Understand?  So where does this bring us? The progress of one's life.  Ok, maybe you are right, I am materialistic. But to be realistic, face it, you just have to work like hell just to get a simple thing done...  Sure? Why is it sometimes it seems so easy for people to do things and for me in the same position, I find it so difficult?  Why?  What is the meaning of this?  Slog...slog...slog.   I am sure that my life means more than that. Let me argue more on that when my mind is clearer from rest and exhaustion.  Zzzzzz....
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They spoke of the Greek gods, mighty deities who overthrew the Titans and became the pantheon of the Greek peoples.  Zeus, king of Olympus and wielder of the all-conquering lightning bolt, Poseidon who rules the oceans, Hades the lord of the underworld, Hera, queen of the gods, Aphrodite, goddess of love, Athena, goddess of wisdom  Then there are the Greek heroes, who performed great deeds of valour and heroism.  Heracles (Hercules) and his 12 Labours, Perseus who killed the Medusa, Theseus who defeated the Minotaur, Jason who led the Argonauts in search of the Golden Fleece, Achilles who was the greatest of all warriors in the Trojan war, Hector who fought for the Trojans.  The modern-day Greeks may not be able to yoke a fire-breathing bull or slay ferocious dragons, but what they have done is still a feat of greatness.  Stunning Portugal in the opener of Euro 2004 and beating them in the final again, dumping champions France out, edging out the Czech Republic, these Greeks have shown what a force they can be.  Although I won't call their soccer attractive, but it has been brutally efficient. Defend tightly and don't concede space to the opponents. Harass them and break out whenever there's a chance...  Defensive and counter-attacking football, which relies on teamwork and high concentration. Some people may call it negative football. Well, my football vocabulary isn't that great, so perhaps that is what it really is.  I won't fancy Greece to win World Cup 2006, taking into consideration the effects of aging players, retirements and new additions, but they will be a team to watch out for.  Maybe I should change my name to something Greek. Markolos ---> me? 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Foul mood today...  When I am angry and frustrated, I post evil poems...  Brood...thunder in the distance And the sky grows darker Beware, the time of shadows approaches And all will face its perils or survive.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe it is the impending release of my UOL exam results, maybe it is due to the frustration I feel about my life, work, studies and everything in general.  I know that I feel this distinct unease within me for days now.  I sense that everything is building up to a point whereby I must make a big decision. Perhaps I can pinpoint this to the release of the results, whereby the decisions that I make will affect me for the next few months or even possibly the next few years.  To stay or to go? That will be a big question that I will attempt to answer.  To be true, I am gradually getting fed-up with the education system at UOL. I wonder if the 100% theory-based syllabus over there really prepares one for the thrills and knocks of working life.  Theory is one thing, but actual experience is another matter entirely.  As I have always maintained to my friends and anyone who would care to listen to me for the past one year, in the future, there will be so many people holding degrees such that if you throw a stone, you will hit a university graduate (be it from Singapore, UK, USA, Australia or whatever country)  When it comes to the job hunt (pedigree of the university not included), the only factor that will distinguish one job-seeker from another is the work experience that he/she has, and the quality of that experience.   So what does it mean? It means that people nowadays have become more discerning. A paper qualification means little or nothing. What they care about is whether you have the experience and ability to do the job, and what can you bring to the organisation.  I don't propose being an "organisation" man, but I think we should all take charge of our lives. You decide your own career, not your company.  Live your own life and be free.  Till the next  blog.   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy National Day! Singapore!  It is our 39th National Day! Yippee! 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You may wonder why the title of this post is so named...  As I sit here, typing this post, there is this one speaker blasting out the latest pop music at full volume above my head.  Why is that so?  I am at this carnvial for HardwareZone's Reality Challenge event, held outside the ever-popular Orchard Cineleisure.  It happens that my company's booth is located in such a way that my sitting position is just next to the overhead speakers.  Oh well, one could get nuts with all the loud music blasting over my head. Well, after going through it for more than 2 days, I have been sitting there thinking and thinking.  Think what? Ouch the music is too loud...  More on that the other time...till the next blog.      
    
</post>


</Blog>