<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, its almost the end of day 2 of my blog :) ther's a lotta text for 2 days, but ya know how it is, when I get a new toy I wanna play with it :)  My hay fever has been bugging me all day long... and I just found out that danique also has it... today was a really weird day... normally I'm cheering when I got a free day, I'll go do stuff I like all day long... but today I didnt really feel like doing anything... I felt really weird. Tomorrow is probabley the same deal, and I can sorta guess what's causing it too... It feels like butterflies in my stomach, only its not the same...  Today turned out to be a little fun anyway... I chatted for a while with Danique, but I could sense she was somewhere else with her thought... with vince, maybe? just before she went offline, vince came offline, and he was all lame and stuff... luckely those 2 dont got eachother's emailadresses... vince doesnt understand the word subtile though... when I told him I was chatting with Danique he was all like: "Dude, I'm not going to do anything with it, and this is just a normal thing, can ya please gimme danique's email adress??" wich offcourse, I didnt.. If he wants her email adress, then he should goto her and ask... Like I did(n't).  Tomorrow will definitley suck.. the entire day noone was online, except danique for 30 minutes, and vince for 15 mins... and I spent the afternoon at vince's house, playing James Bond ;) so probabley sunday will suck as bad too.. luckely there is fathers day, so we also must goto my grandpa (like in, my dads father ;)) so I would be gone pretty much all day... keeps my mind of stuff... wich is good, cause I keep on daydreaming about everything thats happened the last 2 days... and ofcourse about danique (and it pretty much keeps me awake too, so it may seem very nice and all, but at times it aint so nice...)  And after 2morrow, there will be.... monday... yesterday I looked up to it, but now I kinda feel like I wanna goto school again... wich is weird, at least for me it is ;)  well, I would love to make this post longer and longer, but I need my sleep (yesterday I almost didnt sleep, for no apperant reason...) well, bye :)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just confronted him with the truth, and highly ashamed, and reallly really lame, he admitted he sended a mail... but he thought she would never see it anyway, cus its on her old email adress... Now, I actually dont want to, but still, I feel sorry for the guy... After all, being in love with someone is the nicest compliment ya can give that person... or so I think ;) OMG, the guy was actually mad I knew about the email, but I haven't reavealed anything. Luckely I changed my msn name, just before he could see it, so he didnt read this page yet... about reading this page.. OMG, the first few comments on my sick sick posts are there... thats like..... really weird :) but its still nice anyway (in case ya didnt know... I do have a nice side ya know... its just so hard to regonise it under the layers of pain and misserey, and self pity and such)  I find it strange that Danique hasnt replied to vince's email just yet, or maybe vince doesnt want to say sumting about that too... Danique didnt revealed anything either when I was chatting with her 10 minutes ago. I dunno, maybe she just doesnt want to hurt vince? or maybe she really likes him =| OMG, if so be the case, please shoot me...  ... what? why I havent exactley declared her my love and such? well, I'm too much of a shyguy for that, plus I have to draw a number for that... there's a long waiting list... her list of boys who like her is bigger then the list of people who need organ transplants... also, I can allready predict the answer with my magical 8th sense (XP) ... "NO! NO WAY! GET AWAY FROM ME, YA PERV! ARGH! How disgusting!" yeah, well, I'm getting weird and emotional again, so I better leave, maybe I'll post something again 2night ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whoops, I forgot one little thing... vince isn't supposed to sse the text from 2/3/4 blogs back... =| I'm in deep shit... but at the other hand, like I care, Danique just should've told him sooner, I'm not responsible for that shit...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Vince, I gotta ask ya this: WHY ARE YA FUCKING LYING TO ME, GODDAMNIT? I fucking know what ya sended to Danique in a email... about that u liked her and ya where to shy to tell her face to face... so what? what do ya think I will do to ya? kill you? goddamnit, I really can't trust ya, can I?  for the people who cant follow the series of events:  well, I just came home from being at vince's house... I could resist screaming and shouting to him, but I just couldnt resist asking what he sended in the email to Danique... damn, how can he say that he doesnt remember it... does he actually think I belive that? dream on... I feel pretty damaged... and pathetic too, the only persons I can trust and talk to, are inside my computer! (well, not exactley, but ya get my point) well, vince can come online any minute now, so then he will see the adress to this blog... so vince, this is to you: STOP LYING OR GET THE FUCK OUTTA MY SIGHT! DAMNIT... if I could do my life over again, I would do it in a heartbeat... ow well, cant do that so I'm screwed with this fucking life... gotta eat now, I'll be back
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lol, yeah, in an hour I'm going to vince.. He doesnt know Danique doesnt like him, yet... Well, I cant tell him, that would be way too lame, let Danique do that part herself, but I'm afraid I cant keep my big mouth shut... I really hate vince @ tha moment... not for falling in love with Danique or anything, but the fact that he is way too lame to even just notify me about it... u know, that just sucks, he's my best friend, and he doesnt even seem to trust me? weird... I dunno how I will react when I see him, but I think (cause I'm just a shy person, I dont like conflicts) that I'm just gonna put on a happy face... But god, please, please, let him shut up.. cus I'm not going to be responsible for what happens elseway...  He also persuaded me to come to a school party (the last school party) but I dont think I'm going anymore... damn ticket cost me €4,- but I dont really care about da frigging money... I just dont like getting stabbed in da back...  gotta go get my medicine now... I got eyedrops, nosespray, and inhaler (all of the sudden I'm having hay fever, and I hate it) and now I also got stuff for my muscles... (bwahahaha, if ya can call it muscles) damn, I wrecked a few of them. I also bruced a couple of bones while banging my head against the wall yesterday, but I'll live (sorry people, hate to dissapoint ya'all, but I will live...)  well, my plan was to keep this little frigging post a little small, but as ya can see I'm just to hopeless to do that ;) gotta go now, wish me luck
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn, I can't seem to shut my subconciousness up... I try to tell myself I dont give a fuck about anything, or anyone, but it seems like I do... I'm depressed now... Sitting in my chair, just staring at a computerscreen. I don't feel like moving, but very soon I'll just have too :( Well, maybe I'll just stay home on monday till wednesday.. I mean, its not like anyone at school even cares about me coming or not, so why bother going right? On wednesday our entire class will go do sumting together... great isn't it? I thought we would go swimming or sumting, but instead we goto some weird place...  My dad's calling me now, I gotta eat. Time to put on my happy mask, and to forget about all my problems for a little while... bah, well, I just felt like typing again. Have a nice day...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yes, my 4rth post tonight... I mean, I'm busy now anyway, right?  I really really hate the fucking block option in msn, I believ I'm just being blocked by the only 3 people in my contact list: vince, danique and esther. Well, I dont blame them offcourse, but still, its so not cool :( at first I decided to keep this blog a secret, but now it feels like everyone has left me, I'm like: "Fuck ya'all!" and just putted my blog adress in my msn name... I'm quite sure they'll get curious, and going to read the blog, and then their gonna be upset, and pissed, and very very mad, but I dont care... I want to make a clean ship.. its not like I'm gonna see them ever again anyway... I'm off too another class then them... They all get high grades, perform good at school, and got like all those things, while I need to study for hours, just to get another F... wheeh! Well, I can say for one thing, it feels great to write all the shit down that happened in my life... Everyone will hate me for it, but fuck everyone... the only ones I got left that dont move away from me are my fucking fishes... but then again, they cant wlak or anything... well, I'm gonna nap, its 23:15 now, and I'm sleepy.. Peace out.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah, well, I bet you are all like, OMFG, there is yet another fucking post on the same day as the rest, thats fucking number three allready! but I'm walking with all this shit for like 14 1/2 year, so excuse me :)  Love is a strange thing, it can make you feel warm inside, it makes ya thing of noone lese but that one girl.. and then... all ya daydreams get squashed as ya best friend goes and asks her on a dat without even telling me... WHAT IS THIS FOR A GODDAMN WORLD? AT LEAST I WAS POLITE ENOUGH TO TELL HIM I LOVED THE SAME GIRL AS HIM.... damn, thanks to him, I made a complete fool of myself... after getting the email adress of Danique, I was like yay! chatting, w00t, ow yeah! so I got on, and added her, and like then seconds later I was added... After chatting a while here and there she went offline again, and her best friend added me too so we could chat too ^_^ well, she just asked me tonight, all of the sudden, like, if vince likes danique... not knowing that son of a bitch emailed her about his love, I didnt know what to say, so I was like I dunno... then she was like "Hell yeah ya do know, he send her an email about it and all..." well, that, suprisingly, shocked me... how could taht be else? I instantley felt the urge to kill him on the spot, to bad he lives to far from me... One w00t for me though, I dont know if she likes me or not (but I'm quite sure that's a big fat NOT), but at least she doenst like him either... that was one thing that made me cheer a bit more...  well, vince and I would go shopping for a gift for our fathers 2morrow, but as ya might understand, I'm not really in the mood for that... I'm not even in the mood to go but a fucking present.. but its fathers day, so I have too... damn...  2 days, and one hour away is monday... I'm gonna hate monday, without a doubt, it will become the worst day of my life... I dunno how to go face vince... should I kick his ass, or feel sorry for him? I think I'm just gonna ignore him... A little childish, but what the hell, I'm still a kid anyway, right? And then there is also Danique offcourse... I dunno how she is gonna react. I bet her best friend allready told her that I like her... so I'm going in, prepared for the worst...   wish me luck...    Wesley
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      excuse me grammar, I'm not english ;) if u are reading this blog, and are not mentally ill, I suggest not to look at any other posts that may be displayed here, it can be bad for ya health... just do what I don't, get a life!  So well, anyway, erhm... I got myself a blog, but I dunno anything funny to actually post on it... lemme just post a few thing in my life that are not so incredible funny...  me family:  I got one little brother of 8 years old, and a little sis of 12, and sometimes (most of the time) I hate them very much. There only goal in live seems to be to annoy me, and make my life as miserable as possible.. My mom decided after 17 years of happily marriage that she doesnt like my dad, she gets a divorce, and then turns lesbian and runs off with her best friend.. yay... well, the only normal person in my family is my dad. He's the kinda guy that doesnt punish ya for every little thing, and he tries to understand people and stuff, and he's really cool and all, but he is still one of the people I rarther not talk to about complicated stuff in my life...  me friends:  woah, I dont really got much friends. actually, I just have one good friend, and the others are just a bunch of loser hanging around us... Vince is my best friend, he's just a weird dude, like me, we have the same interests, we act the same, and we both dont give shit about life (at least, not @ school) only stupid thing with liking the same things is, also liking the same girls... Offcourse then there is sander. Just ya regular jerk-off wannabee computer-nerd, 300% gay, noone likes him really, but he hangs around us, and pretend we follow him instead of he following us... so that basicly the typical guy ya rather want to ditch, but a well... And there is this that dude, polo... man, I belive in tolerance and that stuff, but fuck him, let him die and burn in hell! this guy is a real prankster, he thinks he's pretty funny, doing stuff like stealing books, trowing pencils outta the window, call you sick at school, stuff like that. He hangs around sander a lot, so he's basicly stuck to us.. See, I dont like the last two guys, but vince is a friend of Sander, so they always just tag along with him.. well, those are my "friends" in a nutshell.. O wait, I would almost forget the few, very few nice girls in our class that say hi to us when we see them (just to me and vince ;) ) those girls are nice, they are one of the few reasons I wanna goto school  me lovelife:  I thought this was gonna be empty sheet for a long time, but I guess there still are a few women that dig weirdo's... a few... a very slim number...  at first there where these few girls, (not gonna say names, they dont like that ;) ) that liked me, but once they got to know me, that love was soon over... well, at least they showed me what women actually care about.. the outside (and even that suprised me, and still does) Then I got this crush on a girl in the first year on junior high (at least I think its called junior high, the schools and shit are different here in holland) well, anyway, I THOUGHT I had a crush on her, but soon I realised that I didnt, I was just lonely. And then the final bomb, the drop that really did it, a girl in my class (the 3th year now) I really really like this girl, she is like the first love of my life.. But as I said sooner, my best friend also likes her, and so do like 10 other people... Slim change for me there, so I allready dealt on big loss, and cried my eyeballs out (sorta). Well, that kinda maked me not going to love a girl anymore till I'm like 16 or 18, just I'm just not in a mood to fall in love after this list of dissasters...  my school:  My school just sucks, and I mean that like major sucks... my class is filled with nerd's, and a few sluts too (no offence) you can see my grades really sticking out, like A++, A++, A++, and wesley, you got a... F. great... I hate teachers, especially my french teacher, Gaufau or something, he's a real son of a bitch. He goes around calling students stupid, telling them their dead shrimps (dont ask...) and generally putting students down... especially me, he seems to hate me.. well, I just hate him right back, I even stopped making homework for French lessons, cause I'm not learning something anyway... People at school keep calling me stupid, but people outside school seem to think about me as a potential great scientist, or sumting that style... I don't get it, can ya really measure how smart someone is by there school grades?  my life:   Well, I hope for you you really didnt actually read all of that, but I needed to get that all of my chest... feels good ;) well, now ya know how basicly my life is... I just spend my days in a deadly boring routine of sleep, school, computers, music, msn, eating and sleeping... yeah... I thought of suicide more then just once, 'cause I really didnt saw the point in life anymore... I also been at a soul shrink for a few weeks.. Man I hate such people... Nothing personal offcourse, I mean, she was really nice and all, but I hate it how ya can just talk about anything with those people.. sounds stupid, but then again, I am stupid... bah, I'm going to quit typing now, cause I'm losing the feeling in my fingertops, cya all sometime, somewhere :)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay! after long time wathing millions of people I know getting a blog, I decided to get my own one to post my weird thoughts and problems and such on... so here it is, suprise! yeah, yawn, I'm wondering, why the hell are ya even reading this?
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got the cat-blues :D listening to music, it rocks... boo-yeah! sorry for not updating much, but I'm trying to do stuff :) I tried to skate, but for now I can only stand on a board :) and right now I'm trying to dance... chatting with 'nique (hope she doesnt mind me giving her that name XP) she's dancing too :) dancing together.. hay, dont get ideas, ya perv. damn its hot in here... the neighbors from across the streets must think I'm nuts, dancing and waving infront of the window ;) but 2morrow will be booring, cause I gotta go 2 my mom :( o well, I'm still happy :) dunno why, but I am... maybe because people are daing on my tv-screen :) had a computercrash a few hours ago, I lost everything, luckely I'm back online :D well, gotta go again, to happy to post... oegaboegaboega!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont feel like posting, I dont feel like getting to bed, I dont feel like waking up every day again, I dont feel like living, I dont...  Well, ya get da drill, I'm boored as hell (yes, still) and all I can still think of is danique, wich is actually bothering me,cause it reminds me every second of the day that she doesnt like me... yeah, still haven't asked her yet, I haven't seen her yet... maybe I'll just write her an email, just like vince, maybe thats better... thinking of it, I'm gonna send the email right after I finished this blog entry :)  Today brought my books back to school, so I just putted on my happy face, and went, said goodbye (and hi) to a few people (guess who) the tagged along with vince to go play some video games... I also ate at vince's stack, and after that we played video games till this time ;) my dad was very angry, cause I called him to late... I was hoping to see danique online tonight, but its very late, so I guess not...  well, erhm.. yeah... then I'm gonna send the love letter of doom now... sigh... yeah, bye :)
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, for my self to do something and keep my thoughts away from other things I've decided to jump back into the computer things again... I'm gonna study how binary works, how to do boolean equatations, as well as logic equatations... yeah, like that means anything to you ;) anyway, I've decided that the first time I'll see danique again (on msn or face to face) I'm gonna say what I feel for her... I'm sure to get a big fat NO, also cause I heard she fancy's a guy from her neighborhood, but anyway, it would make me feel a whole damn lot better to hear it from her mouth (or her fingers ;)) anyway, this is a short blog, since I'm not in the mood of writing down everything thats bugging, just wanted to show I'm still alive (pitty, huh?) bye again, I'm gonna sleep
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      why would someone (a girl *hint, hint*) want put herself down? when yesterday I was chatting with Danique, she was really putting herself down, saying she sucked etc.. that really made me feel sad, I tried to say lots of nice things, but she still putted herself down =( what do I need to do now? I told her, if she would ever say such things about herself again, I would come to her house to tell her face to face thats she's one of the nicest and cutest girls that I know... she responded by giving her adress XP cool... well, u know the rest (read post below ;)) anyway... erhm... yeah, bye =D
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello peoplez, srry for not posting yesterday, but I went on a motorride with my dad. Yesterday I chatted with danique, and she gave her adress to me ;) well, my dad saw the adress and asked me if I went along for a ride... Offcourse I didnt knew where we would goto, so all of the sudden I was in her neighborhood... =| I saw her too, and I was with my head in da clouds again... But now I'm a little ashamed... She must think I'm some kinda stalker or something =) this was the last day of my school BTW :D tomorrow we have a little trip with the entire class and then.. VACATION! w00t! but at the other end, I dont like vacation any more (all of the sudden ;) ) Maybe I just need to ask her to do something in the vacation together... yeah, maybe...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I got oceans of time, but I cant swim" -  That is the best way to describe what I feel like... I always knew so well what to do with my time, but lately, lots of stuff has changed. Its like my life isn't my life anymore. At least not the way I expected my life to be... O well, today was father's day, but I didnt had a present :( he'll get it when I buy it for him someday ;) we where gone to my grandparents all day and I just came home... It was a nice day... I drunk beer for the first time in my life today... I had lots of breezers and stuff before, but never a beer, it tasted funny. My dad didnt think I would really do it, and called me a bluffer, but I drank it till the last little drop :D felt kinda sick afterwards though, cause I hadnt eaten anything before it (I have a weird day, I'm not hungry, all I ate was a cracker and a lolly ;))  I'm afraid of tomorrow, I thought I could like, handle it, but I dont think I can... I'm in a dillemma: "To go, or not to go, thats the question" But I'll just have to go :(  "Evanesence -  Everybody's fool" is like my favorite song right now. I gotta try getting it on mp3 ;) although I like "addicted" of "simple plan" a lot too... I dunno what it is, the last year, my interest for music has grown... I never liked music, now I cant live without. All off the sudden I don't like the vacation no more.. Please, please let me goto school in tha vacation! may sound stupid, but I just dunno what to do... maybe I'm just gonna learen myself how to skateboard, or I'm gonna buy me a pair of rollerblades or sumting.... I heard they are quite popular again, and it gives me sumting to do too :) well, I dont like wasting ur time any more, so I'm gonna stop typing. Bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just right now, when vacation has just truly begun, I hear that danique has a boyfriend... I dont feel like posting, I'm going to bed...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello peoplez, itsa me again! yesterday and today I was @ my grandparents's so I wasn't online... Haven't chatted with peoplez for like 4 dayz now, except for a brief moment with vince and a guy called tarik. Anywayz, its been great fun the last 2 dayz, but sadn @ tha same time. I had a really weird dream about Danique last night. We where doing all kinds of stuff together, but something everytime went wrong and just before I woke up, she walked off with vince... ok, I know that doesnt make any sence whatsoever, but it still made me feel very sad. What made me happy again was my grandpa trying to computer XP it just so rules to see him trieing and trieing over again :) ok, enough happy things.. gonna wait till my dad leaves the house, then I'm gonna cry my eyeballs out cause of tha stupid dream (I didn't had the time to do that yet XP)  peace out
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wheeh! I'm still alive :) allthough it was close, I was almost drivven over by a car :0 I got a photo of myself on my comp, my dad was really happy and made a photo of me with a borrowed digital camera, but the photo is really screwed, XP I dont dare putting it online ;) dont really have much to say, I'm just such a booring person, I hate myself XP I'm really gonna find me a hobby or something, maybe I can play gitar again, or trumpet or sumting... but thats such a long time ago, I'm pwetty sure I cant do it anymore... maybe I need to go and learn like skateboarding or sumting XD but I'm acting obsessive again, so I need to go punish myself for that XP bye-bye :)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      itsa.. me... yeah, well, I decided to stop blogging, cuz I really dont feel like writing no more these days.. I'm still happy on the outside, but on the inside I feel just terrible.. well, I hope someone liked this short blogspot XP yeah, well... byebyez :)
     

    
</post>


</Blog>