<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man, that was a great weekend. Just came back from a nice weekend trip to east coast. Met few old friends.. just kick back and relax. Had a great time in short. Now off to bed, gotta get up early in the morning for the work. Big week ahead!
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 3 am on the morning and I am still awake (but sleepy) in front of my sand box. Need to go to sleep now. Nothing better life, just same ol' same ol'. I really need to sleep now, as need to get up early for a presentation tomorrow. Over and out.
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well no luck so far with gmail :) Filled up my week's quota for sleep last night. That dr. from GMA will be happy that I am getting rest of my life :) Had pretty wierd dreams thought, so wierd that I don't even wanna think about them forget about bloggin them! Well, it's new day and fine morning. Life goes on. Oh and found my favorite item I thought was lost forever.. life after all doesn't suck that all!
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A little pigeon told me that this is the happening place if you want to get into gMail brotherhood. Well I have tried everything, why not this? Let's see how it works out.
    
</post>


<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently, I started looking to starting my own e-commerce website, to put in simple words, a site selling services.  Trying to understand the mechanics of e-commerce has been very interesting so far. It's amazing to see how you can break all the geo-political boundaries and start wondering about what's legal and what's not. For example, if I want to sell services (deliver gifts etc.) in India, it's quite easy to set-up a website any where in the world and start selling and accepting money via credit card. There are millions of Indians across the world, who shop on similar websites and send the gifts to friends and family in India. Not to mention, now-a-days, there are quite a few folks from India who have started to spends some bucks on the net. The funny part comes in where you start looking for ways to get that money into your Indian bank account. Usually, the cheapest gateways to accept credit cards online is though services like PayPal etc. But most of these service can't talk to your Indian bank account like they can to the US counter-part. So, unless you have a US bank acount, it get's difficult, not to mention possibly illegal, to get money from you PayPal account into India. It's almost scary when you start thinking about it, that you might unknowningly get into trouble. It all looks like you can do most parts of the process straight forward, but it's hard to find the resources on the net that tell you what part of it is not violating any laws of the land or for that matter international trade.
    
</post>


</Blog>