<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so I work at this local supermarket right? Where they have this system set up that you can save this "Bonus Discount" in a special savings account, but you can allso just get the bonus discount taken off the amount you pay.  So I'm sitting behind my cash register thisafternoon, and I spot my mom at a different thing. She looks like she's been having a load of hassle. I come home from work and ask the full story, here's the deal:   Shukufa (real name no alias shes this f****n dumb b**ch) does the routine of passing my moms stuff past the scanner and then asks for her bonus card. Mom searches but can't find it, and figures she'll just pay the whole thing. When shukufa makes   Mistake number1: she askes another customer to lend a bonuscard. She gets one, which has the savings thing set up on it. BING! not allowed. Mistake number2: She does not tell my mom to press the stop button for the savings thing untill my mom accidentally has pressed yes. Mistake number3: She doesn't know theres this huge button on the cash register that reads: CANCEL SAVING. Mistake number4: She says its my moms fault.  Argh shes such a dumb girl. Someone should really tell her that sometime. Of course, theres allso 2 faults on my moms behalf. She doesn't tell the staff that it was shukufa who asked for the bonus card. And she doesn't file a complaint. People the reason of filing complaints is that the supermarket staff get notified of their mistakes and don't make them again. This was a perfectly justified reason to file a complaint. And there have been many others but because no one bothers to file any, shukufa is not notified of her mistakes (or if every single customer had filed a (JUSTIFIED!) complaint, she'd have been fired)  You know in all the months I've worked there, I've only had one complaint. And that was not a justifyable reason: I had been working there for like 3 or 4 days, and wasn't very fast yet and got stuck on a few things. When this guy who thought it took to long just took off leaving all his shoppings standing there. He filed a complaint but it wasn't taken very seriously. And at least all the other customers in my line helped clear up the groceries and were very sympathetic...  yup. I like my job, just not all my collegues...  So if anyone happens to pop by the "Albert Heijn" in the dutch town of "Wassenaar" file a complaint on Shukufa for me :-P 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay on request from Viper I shall not steal his avatar. Allso, Viper and the american are not the same. The american doesn't have a thing for megaman for instance O.o  Oh and allso, just to annoy her: Bek, you teh hot saix babe :)
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay so the reason I got a blog, is cuz of Viper. This dude I know, he's got thos huge thing for megaman, it's sick. He's said megaman so often I'm inclined to be suprised that he hasn't been sued for copyright infringement or something. I'm not quite sure how far his thing for megaman goes. Frankly, I'm quite scared to find out.  Wow, he's been quiet for like 5 minutes now, oh no wait forget it he started typing again. Well at least the american isn't talking. He can be annoying, all he thinks about is girls, music and that drinking and stuff is evil. Damn kid musta been brainwashed.  Yeah so, I think I'm going to steal Vipers msn avatar. It's this picture of megaman... Dammit he must have me brainwashed. I oh so hope he gets over his crush soon. It's starting to freak me out, and I'm supposed to be going over there next summer.   	   Goodnight all,    Lone Wolf   
    
</post>


</Blog>