<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        IT'S HALEYS BIRTHDAY!!!!!!!! AWWWWWW YEAH!!!!!! lol (wow im kool huh?) WE ARE GONNA PAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARTAAAAYY HARD!!!! the actual partys tomorrow but me and hur and ev are goin out to dinna tonite and then tomorrow we are gonna party like izz 1999!!!!  fur now ima go watc tele-v wit ev . tawk to yall layta!!!!!! asta lavista yall
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        i am veeeeeery bord.........i luv this song  "You Oughta Know"  I want you to know, that I'm happy for you I wish nothing but the best for you both An older version of me Is she perverted like me Would she go down on you in a theatre Does she speak eloquently And would she have your baby I'm sure she'd make a really excellent mother  Cause the love that you gave that we made wasn't able To make it enough for you to be open wide, no And every time you speak her name Does she know how you told me you'd hold me Until you died, till you died But you're still alive  And I'm here to remind you Of the mess you left when you went away It's not fair to deny me Of the cross I bear that you gave to me You, you, you oughta know  You seem very well, things look peaceful I'm not quite as well, I thought you should know Did you forget about me Mr. Duplicity I hate to bug you in the middle of dinner It was a slap in the face how quickly I was replaced Are you thinking of me when you fuck her  Cause the love that you gave that we made wasn't able To make it enough for you to be open wide, no And every time you speak her name Does she know how you told me you'd hold me Until you died, til you died But you're still alive  And I'm here to remind you Of the mess you left when you went away It's not fair to deny me Of the cross I bear that you gave to me You, you, you oughta know  Cause the joke that you laid on the bed that was me And I'm not gonna fade As soon as you close your eyes and you know it And every time I scratch my nails down someone else's back I hope you feel it...well can you feel it  And I'm here to remind you Of the mess you left when you went away It's not fair to deny me Of the cross I bear that you gave to me You, you, you oughta know   
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Thank yall so much for comin to my site! i dont really no wut to say. this is the furst time i've eva dun a website by myself so if you ave any  suggestions for me puh-leeez lemme no!asat lavista yall!
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         ok so here im spozza tell you about myself, umm ok here we go- im like 5'7. i have blonde hair and most of the time blue eyes. but they change depending on my mood.i love dancing.i've been doin it since i wuz four.its awesome,and anyone who thinx dancing isnt a sport can kiss my ass.I LOVE MY FIRNEDS!!!they are the best people in the world!they have helped me thru alooooot of shit- which brings me to my next topic, im a recovered pot head,cutter,slut,and drinker, alll because of a few people-this one guy in particular. he's amazing!you would love him.there is no reason in hell not to.hes hott and sweet and funny and original and classic and sexy and fun to be with and kool and he makes me feel important.he makes me feel like i matter. and i love him for it! HE ROX MY SOX!!!!!! i'll tell you guys SHITLOADS more about him as this site gets bigger.but fur now im gonna go. much luv yall!
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        im at haleys hizz-ouse.lol. we are having bunches and bunches of fun! we were playing harry potter!!!! but then i started making up stupid spells that dont even exzist and then i broke the chair!!!! yahoo! lol............yeah we're really lame... GOTHIKA IS SUUUUUUUCH A GOOOOOOD MOVIE!!!!! YAHOOOO!!!!!!! you can not trust someone who thinks you are crazy.   MS.HINSON IS THE BEST AND I LOVE HER LOVE HER LOVE HER!!!         &nbsp;   tah-tah for now!!     luv-sarah   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        THE HYPERNESS WILL EAT YOU!!!! RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!!! YAHHH!!!!!! rashaad is very very very very very very very very very very very sexxx-aaaaayyyy!!!!! yaaaaahhh!!!   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ok! so yesterday i woke up at 8:45 am and called rashaad and mary. we were all up and ready by 9:45. we went to get mary and then me and mary went to publix. then me and mary were sitting in the car at the gas station and i put the steering wheele cover on my head! and then the mexican was looking at me!! lol (mary- look at that silly mexican tryna look at the strawberry!lolo)  then the casheir woman called us silly! lol.  then we went to pick up rashaad and all wuz good! so we had the doughnuts, we had the water gun, we had our slippers, we had rashaad, and we had the  bottle rocket   so we were on our way to michaels to give him his big soup-rise!!! we got to michaels and his mom wuz like "whats going on?" but it wuz all kool. so we went in to michaels room while he wuz sleeping and we sprayed him with the water guns and made him eat doughnuts! horaayy!!! we were all chillin out and then we brought out the fire works..  now the night befor we had been tawkin bout setting it off in his room and scarin the shit oudda him....me bein the blonde that i am, i didnt know it was a joke. so then rashaad took them out from under the covers and wuz givin me this "go ahead! go ahead!" look and he wuz like "do it!" so i got a match and lit it...well it turned out to be a much bigger explosion then i thot it wuz gonna be.that bee-otch wuz loud as a muther fucker!!! lol. it wuz like making theses high pitched whistles and these high&nbsp;pitched screamy things.&nbsp;his cat started spazzin out all over the place! his dog had a fit! mary started screaming and covering her ears. i wuz just like "oh shit! oh shit! oh shit!" michaels runnin around in 50 billion directions all over his room tryna catch the damn cat. or maybey he wuz juz tryna run away from the fire cracker which wuz flyin all over his room!rashaads just sittin there lookin like&nbsp;"damn it sarah! you've really dun it this time!"so finally the ting stopped and there wuz so much smoke in that room you couldnt see more that 6 inches in frunna you! and michael goze "wich wunna you DUMBASSES just set that off!!!!!"  then came the downfall.........we thot we were at home alone...we thot rong, in walks michaels dad (even tho we were at his moms house and his rents are divorced!)an he goze "what in the hell is goin on here!?!"then he makes us all go sit on the couch outside! lol! of all places! outside! on the couch!        so then his dad leaves and his mom comes home bout 20 minutes later. she didnt know about it  yet   so then we all hurried outof there to get to my house and we sucseeded! so me and mike and rashaad were back here and we started havin&nbsp;a dance party wahoo! then w ehad a cocoa butter fight in my room! then my dad came home and yelled at us for bein in my room. then my mom came home and wuz bein kool for a lil while..but then she started bein reeeeeeel mean to rashaad....:o( that made me sad.   then last night i was walkin down the stairs and i kicked a piece of cat food of the side of the porch and my foot got stuck in the railing and i fell down the stairs and i swung around and hit my head on the railing then the step then tried to catch myself with my hand and i couldnt hold myself up and i hurt my wrist! ouch!  ok well im gonna go see if i can find evan and we're gonna watch gothica! yahoo! good movie!         &nbsp;   buh bye!     luv-sarah       &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        michael is mad at me..that makes me very sad.i dont know what i did wrong.im am sad. if this is michael reading this - i love you so much . it makes me sad that you are mad at me and im very sorry for whatever it is i did rong. i did not mean to make you mad.if you feel like i took your best friend im sorry.i wood prolly be mad at some one who took haley and so i'll try and respect that and back off a lil bit. im gonna let you and rashaad have yalls space. im sorry if i messed anything up. please accept my apology. it wood really hurt if you werent my friend anymore. please come talk to me when ever you're ready. i love you man!!!!     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        i am in love with rashaad. he is the best guy! kool kool kool kool kool kool kool kool guy!!!!! i am soooooo in love wit this guy!!!he came over and it wuz aawwwwwwwwesome!!!!!!!! i love him love him love him.i have so much fun with him! today wuz great! my mom and dad are oudda town and so he came over and we got to just- chill. and it wuz good. we ate pizza and talked online and beat each other up and wrestled and danced in the rain and layed down and had a good time! we jumped in the puddles and slid down the hill on our asses! it wuz rainin and we were all wet so we ran and then jumped and lifeted our feet and slid down the hill&nbsp; and it wuz great. i love him. he left his shoes here! that nerd! i love him. i made a new frined! her names is michelle. i like her. she a nice lil gurl. HEY MICHELLE! i learned how to download music today! yahoooo! i am crazy bout downloadin now!! agh! i think im havin an addiction problem recently. im gettin addicted to everything!!!!!i have to go now!!!!  p o  w!!!  bang!  b  o  o  m!!!!     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        life isnt worth going through. 
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        today wuz actually pretty fun for a change.*laugh* laz night rashaad came over for the furst time in FOREVER! and we got to umm "hang out" lol. kidding. we watched gothika after deciding on how to dispose of my gross kooking. lol. yeah nad so then he went home and i watched movies wit the gurlz all night. rashaad wuz spozza call me this mornin but he didnt so i ended up goin to the pool and met up with chelsea ! yay! i havent tawked to that chick in fo eva! im so happy. i met the nicest prettiest girl today. her name wuz merrelise, i think. but shezza kool gurl and me and amelia hung out wich wuz kool.me and chelsea&nbsp; are gonna tryn make plans for tomorrow so we'll see how that goze. lol.&nbsp; i luv chels tho. shezza sweetie.ok well rashaad is bout to come over. so i'll tawk layta. asta lavista yall.!  &nbsp; :o)   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       rashaad- and then i will take the knife and i will slit your throat and then you will faaaaaaaaalll on the ground and then i will stand over your bleeding corpse and i will laugh and evil laugh and then i will turn around and STAAAAAB you in the boooooooob!!!!!! mwwwuah hahahahahha..    &nbsp;  lololololol thaz my boy!!!  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        canadian film minister-the united states has graphic violence on t.v all the time! we cant believe a movie with a little foul language would piss you off so much!       &nbsp;   stan's mom-BECAUSE IT'S EVIL!!!       &nbsp;   canadian film minister-CAN I FINISH!?!?!?! PLEASE CAN I JUST FINISH!?!?!?!..............uhh...um...ok im finished       &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;   stan-YOU KILLED KENNY! OH MY GOD!!       &nbsp;   kyle-you bastard!!!       &nbsp;   cartman-wow!i guess you CAN light a fart on fire, huh?       &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;   mr.garrison-well, your moms are all just upset, they're probly all on thier periods or somthing       &nbsp;   gregory-mr.garrison, wendy and i&nbsp;think that was a sexist statement.       &nbsp;   mr.garrison-well im sorry gregory but i just dont trust anything that bleeds for five days and doesnt die       &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;   stan- chef, how do you make a woman like you more than she likes any other guy?       &nbsp;   chef-oh, that's easy! you just have to find the clitoris!       &nbsp;   stan-huh?       &nbsp;   chef-opps..uhhh.....       &nbsp;   stan-what does that mean? find the clitoris?       &nbsp;   chef-uhh....umm forget i said anything!!!!       &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        1-i hate when guys wear orange     2-i love flo-joe flip flops      3-justin timberlake is my husband-to-be      4-im really fair-skinned      5-i hate being fair-skinned      6-i hate soccer      7-i have only met one person ever that hasent gotten on my nerves  yet       8-im the oldest of 3 girls      9-we are all seperated by 4 years      10-i want to learn to sky-dive      11-i have started a list of things i wanna do befor i croak      12-i never wanna "croak"      13-i have a potty mouth      14-people call me a dum-blonde      15-im trying hard to ruin that reputation      16-i love power rangers      17-i have dressed up as the yellow one 3 times for halloween      18-halloween is my favorite holiday      19-chores suck      20-i was on honer role from 1rst grade to 5th grade      21-in 6th grade i failed 3 classes and didnt get any a's      22-in 7th i had to go to summer school      23-i love&nbsp;the name joseph soo much, but i wood never name my kid that      24-i always get along with justin's really well      25-i  haaaaaaate  math      26-im a cosmetic fuh-reeeek      27-my mom thinks you can cure anything with natural stuff      28-i hate camping      29-i love alanis moorsette      30-i love cherry coke      31-i hate pepsi      32-i cud live on pizza hut      33-i want a big family      34-i cant wait to get married      35-i think it will be soo fun getting married      36-i love laughing but i think i have a dorky laugh      37-im a really big dork      38-i have been dancing &nbsp;since i wuz four      39-i love tap dancing but im not good enough to satisfy myself yet      40-its really really hard to satisfy me      41-im messy- very very messy      42-but im a huge perfectionist      43-i have always HATED sunday school      44-i looooove youth group      45-im NOT a christian      46-my mom always said i wuz very couragus      47-my best friend izza huuuuge chicken      48-i am NOT a chicken and i never ever have been      49-i have a reeeely bad memory      50-my new years resolution was to walk my dog once a day      51-i realized that wuz very unrealistic and so i changed it to twice a week      52-i have kept up widdit very well      53-i love the color black      54-i think pastel yellow is really pretty but i wood neva wear it      55-im a very real person      56-some people call me pessimistic because of that      57-i CANNOT stand     it when kids dont respect old people     58-i have a list of qualities that the guy   i marry MUST have      59-i loooved to dress up when i wuz little      60-i still love wearin extreme outfits      61-if i want sumthin, i go for it, i dont hold back      62- i can be very very stubborn      63-im not petty, i try real hard to let things go and not get pissed at every lil thing      64-im bi-polar      65-I HATE BEING BI-POLAR!!      66-it sux when people think your crazy      67-life will be much better when you learn not to kare wut other people&nbsp;think      68-&nbsp;i have always made better friends with guys      69-heh heh 69      70-i have a nasty mind      71-mary thinks im silly      72-i am im love with rashaad hinson      73-antonio banderas is hot      74-i love searching for things on google- alot      75-my favorite drink is a french vanilla frappuccino from starbux      76- i love salt and vinager chips       77-limp bizkit rooooox!! rox rox rox!!!      78-the best concert i've ever seen is a tie between limp bizkit in florida or janet jackson at phillip's arena      79-my eyes change color depending on my mood      80-i hate wasting time      81-i love cranberry juice     82-rashaad's mom rox.     83-i think it sux to fight with parents     84-i have the best bestfriend in the world     85-i have 20 pairs of jeans!     86- i love being in a tank top and jeans     87-shopping rox rox rox!     88-i have a problem with spending money     89-i have a problem with loosing money     90-i want to be in a horror movie really really really bad!     91- i think rashaad should make a horror movie     92-i think it would be a fun job to dance in the shows at six flags     93-i love saying rox     94- i was a baddass untill 4th grade     95-theni turned into a big preppy bitch     96- and now im finally getting to     the point where i like the way i am     97-i love snakes     98-im not like alot of other people     99-i love lotion     100-my mantra is "dont start nuthin there wont be nuthin but if you wunna start sumthin theres gonna be sumthin"   
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ugh! life is suckin pretty damn bad at the time.ok i think the laz time i rote wuz when i wuz bout to go to bredas b-day- which turned out as an absolute disaster! my mom got reaaaaaaalllllly pissed off! she wuz like "agh!" and the managment told me that they were callin the cops in 30 minz if we din leave. and at the moment im on probation for trespassing. so i had to leave.i felt bad fur fuckin up her party but life goes on. they had an awesome time anyways and it turnz out the police din come anyways!so wuteva.so we got home and my mom decided she wanted to go look at houses in north carolina. so we all had to go look at houses and it sucked! the ppl are awful. i hate them all. alot. i love my friends here and i dont want any new ppl. i hate the smell. i hate the trees. there's no pollution and it drives me crazy! there's no traffic! there is nuthin and i hate it more than anything! it depresses me. alot. a whoooooooole lot. but if the world din suck we wood all fall off..............but i still hate it.&nbsp;rashaad wont answer his fone...........i'll tawk to yall layta   
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ugh how the hell do you even spell that wurd? god! well how eva it is i am bord.  very very very bord. bredas party is tomorrow. yay! that meenz i get to say hay to everybody at least once befor i leave. :o( i HATE moving! you have to like - move and you have to pack and you have to leave all yur friends and go to this new place and ugh! i hate it! i wuz feeling so mischevious last nite. lol. i wuz like "ooooooooooo i wanna do sumthin baaaaaaaad!! bad bad bad bad!!!!!" i am feeling lie a juvinile delinquent- i want to pull a practical joke on sum one............RASHIID! i wannna do sumthin bad to rashiid. i cant wait. im going to form a plan. muwahhhhhhhh hahahahahahahahahahaha...........tawk to yall layta
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love friends sooooooo much more than anyone else. if you dont believe me go ask chris who wuz sitting with me when i wuz cryin my head off durin the finaaly. take the test.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow i deffinetly did not no i put that so many times. it's really not even that kool of a site.i just like faries........yeah. rashaad is the koolest guy eva!!!!!!!!! wahooooo!!!!! asta lavista for now yall. (haley- I THOT IT WUZ YUR SHOLDUR I SWEAR!!!!!!!) lolololooololool i luv ya lil gurl!
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i luuuuuuuuuuuv this site- if you're a guy, dont go- you juz gonna think izz dum. but izz not.  http://www.fairiesworld.com/
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        this site is kooooool. if yur a guy- dont go. but if yur a chick you deffinetly shud- its kool  http://www.fairiesworld.com/
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        this site is kooooool. if yur a guy- dont go. but if yur a chick you deffinetly shud- its kool  http://www.fairiesworld.com/
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yall. goodness im so sorry i havent written in so long! sooo much haz gone on! ugh. ok so lemme start off wid the 4th of july- my rents took us out to this biiiiig feild to see fireworks and when we got there my dad told us we r moving! he got a kick ass job in north carolina and so now we r movin up too charrolett by he end of the summa- :o( we have to have a huuuuuuuuuuuuuuge goin away party, the thing is my house will be empty so we cant have it here- if any one can think of a place lemme no.im pissed off about havin to move. i neva thot i cud care so much for a   boy     especially   a northern boy. but ima miss ras so much i dont even no wut to do. so now he is in north carolina on vacation for a couple days (i wuz spozza be wit him but now i have to be here gettin ready for this stupid move)but he'll be home tomorrow. haleys old best friend fara is intown and so now im not gonna see haley for two weeks- and it sux cuz im only here for anotha month.ugh so wuteva. i just got back from the pool. i went to lindmoore and hung out wid like - jonathan and chris and spencer and errbody.it wuz fun! i din do    i wood regret and im really happy! the most action i got wuz georgia (wunna my chix) throwin me into the pool! yay! i got grounded but i dnt think izz gonna stick so izz all gravey.RAS COMES HOME TOMORROW!!!!!i cant fuckin wait!! georgia is my new friend and im super super happy! breda- caaaaaaaaal me!!! mary- i miss you!! joseph-"yeah you no sporty spice, sexy spice,old spice...."lolol! luv ya mann!
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey yall. i dont really no where i left off........umm......my internet hasent been wurkin. i havent really been doin anything....i went to see the village with mike and geofrey and   rashaad   and it wuz   soooooooooooooooo good!!! (oooo wudda pretty color!)   anyways so me and breda have been chillin out. my mom is oudda town. me and breda have been chillin alot now that i think about it. im havin tonza fun but now im really tired so im gonna go. i miss rashaaad.   im going to go talk to him on the fone  good bye!       -sarah  
    
</post>


</Blog>