<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, tomorrow is the big day.  Canada Day....Canada's birthday.  Irrelevant to some...Actually, I'd go as far as to say that it's irrelevant to most people. But it's one of those days that you can sit back and actually reflect on what this country means to you.  I personally think we take this country for granted.  A big part of that opinion has come from living in Chicago for school last year (and going back in a few months).  But even before I had set of for my 4 years in the US, I always appreciated this country and was proud of being able to call myself Canadian.    This country has such multiculturalism in it, especially in cities like Toronto.  But beyond that, it's an actual peaceful country.  We look towards mediating our differences rather than just picking up a gun an blowing apart anyone that decides to disagree with us.  We put our money into things that hold importance to the growth of a society such as health care, education, and national services.  I like the fact that more than our army, we are known for our deployment of peacekeepers.  I also like the fact that no matter where I am in the world, I can bust out a Canadian flag on my bag, and know that I'll be treated with some respect for it.  In our community, although it seems violent sometimes, when compared to others, it is fairly peaceful and very good natured.  People actually smile at each other, and I'm not scared to walk downtown or through neighbourhoods.  People wonder why I am so proud to be Canadian.  Part of it has to do with my parents.  I mean, my dad came to this country in 1970 and was barely even able to speak English and had like $100 CAN in his pocket.  And look at him now...He speaks near perfect English, and has accomplished so much in life.  We're no where close to rich or well off, but he owns his house, he's put one kid through university, gotten her married, and then supported her for a few years.  He put his second kid through university and is now putting him through professional school.  (To be completely fair, this second kid is me, and I've gone on loans ever since I got out of highschool, but the fact remains that my parents got me to this point).  And he's still going...Putting a 3rd kid through school.  Do I honestly believe that he could have done this in just any country?  Being a foreigner from India?  I honestly think that there are slim chances that any other country would have given him so much opportunity and treated him so well.  Then again, that is just my opinion.  Regardless of the fact though, my father came here with almost nothing.  And now he's got so much more.  He went from bachelor, to husband, to father, to newly appointed grandfather.  He may be the type to complain about the state of the country or the state of the government, but internally, I know he would never move anywhere else.  He asked me plenty of times if I have any intentions of staying in America after I'm done school (Oh hell no).  And even though he says it very nonchalantly, I can tell that underneath that all, he doesn't want to leave Canada at all.  So for everything you've given my father, my family, me, my friends, everyone...Here's to you Canada.  Lift your glasses one time and bow your heads and remember the reasons why you enjoy calling yourself "Canadian".  Cheers to you Canada..  Thank you for everything.  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am again.  Stuck at work.  Talking on MSN to people in order to keep myself from completely going insane.  I seriously cannot stand this place.  I first started working here when I was what...16 yrs old?...No, I think it was 17.  Anyways, a LONG time ago.  It's been a good 7 years or so.  The only good thing is that the pay is good, the work is easy, and they pretty much give me shifts whenever I come back for even a week or two.  Now for most people this sounds like the ideal job.  But it isn't.  It is the complete opposite.  This is the worst job a person could find.  Firstly, it is completely indian run.  Now, let me just clarify that a bit.  The company is one of those limo companies that run too and from the airport.  Not the stretches, but not the beat up crap-cars that are city taxis.    So each driver basically owns a share in the company.  Each year, they elect 5 Board of Directors who end up running the company for that year.  Now of course, all these drivers are indians, and most of them can barely speak english and don't know the first thing about running a company.  But of course, they all think they do.  So they come in, make changes in the company that best suit them and their friends, and in the end, the customer suffers.  They hire people that are their friends or relatives, but who don't do any work, and then they bitch at the rest of us cuz mistakes are being made and business is going down.    It really annoys me as well because they set up all these rules in the office, but then they only selectively inforce them.  Like there's this rule about not having cell phones on in the office.  And if someone they don't like breaks the rule even for an emergency, they nail that person and give them a warning letter in their employee file.  But then this other girl comes in to work at 8pm-6am, and I swear, she doesn't get off her cell phone.  She'll even ignore the lines ringing while she's talking to one of her friends on her cell.  And they NEVER say a word to her.  And it pisses me off because she gets annoyed if the phones start getting busy and she has to get off her cell.  Like it's some big chore to come to work and ACTUALLY work.  And if it isn't her cell, it'll be MSN. She'll ignore her job to sit there and talk on MSN for hours and hours.  What we need is just one set of Board of Directors to set everyone straight.  I'll admit, I'm not the model employee either.  I sit and read, or sit on MSN, but I don't put that stuff before the job.  I answer the phones first.  I'll leave friends on MSN hanging and not even say "brb" if the phones get busy or something.  I think that at least is a good sign.  I mean, I think it's ok to give employees certain leeway, such as the internet, or music, or the ability to read material.  But if the employee starts to ignore the work over their "activities", then by all means, it should be taken away.  The people here don't put their work as the priority, and then they bitch when the extra "fun" items get taken away because of degrading business.  Honestly, what did you expect?  A reward for ignoring your job?  A raise?....*Sigh*....  Anyways, I have like a little under 2hrs left today.  I can't wait to leave.  I never want to work here again.  But like always, I know I'm going to end up here come winter.  They'll ask for a few hours covered, and I'll initially say "no".  Then I'll look at my credit card statement and revise my answer.  Then they'll offer me another shift, and another....And I'll just keep doing more and more.  It's just one big destructive cycle.  (You were right Vee).  :-s.  Damn this capitalism.    Other than that, not a whole lot is new.  The Liberals won the election with a minority government. This is possibly the best thing we could have hoped for.  I didn't want Harper winning, that was for sure.  He pretty much is the US government's bitch.  His policies mirror those of the US so much it's not even funny.  Yeah, sure, the US is a prosperous country...But Canada is my country.  I have no desire to have our country named "America Jr" anymore.  But with the minority government, it'll force the different parties to work together much more.  I think it'll be interesting to see what they accomplish.    Alright, I think that's enough for now.  Maybe I'll write more when I get home tonight...Maybe not.  :)....We'll see.    Time...9:20pm...T-minus 1hr40min until freedom.
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so this is the first actual entry into this thing.  I can't believe I'm actually writing one of these, but almost all psychologists say that writing down one's thoughts is an excellent method to relieve stress and relax.  It also helps one put their thoughts on paper (somewhat) and kind of reflect on them I guess.  Either way, things have been getting to me more and more recently, and one of my close friends suggested that I do this, that it helped him out.  And since I respect his opinion greatly, here I am.  Well, what has happened recently?...The big things would probably be the party we held for my nephew Arjun, and the trip up to Vee's cottage.    Lets start with the party.  Will someone please tell me why we find it a necessity to clean a house COMPLETELY before anyone comes over?...Like, ok, I understand if just one or two families are coming, you want the house to look nice.  But honestly, we had over 100 people invited, by the 30th or 40th person, the house is not gonna be the main focus!...So why break your back mopping up EVERY single corner of the house??  Why not just clean it so it looks respectable, and then clean it properly AFTER the party (which you're gonna have todo anyways since the people are gonna mess up your house).  I mean, I don't mind the cleaning, but I got into so much trouble over it.  I'd be asked to do like 5 things at once, finish 4 of them, and then get a little lecture because I forgot to do the 5th.  I know my parents are just stressed out with the amount of work they have to do as well, but still.      But the party went off ok.  Everyone seemed to have a good time.  I, as usual, wasn't the life of the party, but I think I did alright.  I mean, the one thing about me is that I like simplicity.  I don't like to complicate things at all.  So when it comes to a group of mostly uncles and auntie's, I don't really like to be the one in the middle.  They've never really understood that.  I can't really relate to them...Can't get 100% comfortable around them because they still have that "respect" level that they deserve.  With friends, we can sit and tell stories without any kind of need to censor ourselves.  Beyond that, even when I'm with friends, if the group gets larger than 5 people or so, I don't really like to be the "loud" one or anything.  Again, I like simplicity...Too many people just becomes too complicated for me.  Ah well, not much I can do about that really.  No one has ever put a whole lot of pressure on it, just more like soemthing they would like.  The party was on Saturday, and me, Vee, and Pete left for the cottage on Sunday morning.  Well....Afternoon.  :-)  The time at Vee's cottage was awesome.  It was just so relaxing and such.  No ciy errands to run...Just sit, relax, and chill out.  It's by far one of the best times we have is when we go to Vee's cottage.  We just chilled out..Watched tv...Sat around.  :-D  Most work we did was help put the dock back together and help clean the boat.  Gotta give Vee props...That was a great time.  I always have a lot of fun with Vee.  The guy is just too hilarious.  Me and him get along really well, which is probably one of the reasons we stayed roommates for our entire undergrad.  We just have the same sense of humour.  It's too bad that our other roommate (Gib) couldn't make it out.  But then again, that isn't anything new.  He's usually too busy in Delhi.    Other than that, the return to the city and the city life was ok too.  Came back feeling pretty refreshed and relaxed.  Only bad thing is that at the cottage, I missed two days of working out.  :-S...Gonna have to catch up on that.   Ok, that's enough of my journal now.  Maybe more some other time.  
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so I got an online journal.  Call me a geek.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, this post has no insight, no commentary, no personal analysis, nothing of that sort.&nbsp; This post is a pure and complete rant about the things that have been annoying me about people or subjects for the past little while.&nbsp; I warn you now, this will be a lot more crude than normal.   1) THE GYM     What the fuck is wrong with people at the gym?&nbsp; Can they not read?&nbsp; Are they so absorbed in flexing those muscles and injecting those steroids that they forget about any kind of common decency?&nbsp; If you take a weight out, put it the fuck back!...I don't even care if you put it in the right spot again, but at least don't leave it on the fucking floor.&nbsp; If you're some kind of genetic freak and want to use the 120lb weight to do butterfly curls, then go right ahead...But put it back!...The rest of us aren't hyped up on steroids like yourself and aren't about to lug around 24olbs worth of weights just cuz your dumb ass couldn't take them back.&nbsp;&nbsp; Or going around collecting EVERY 45lb weight to put on the leg press machine (you know this is just for you Superman), just so you can wrap your legs in 6 metres of bandages and do a 1 inch press 3x???  Then if&nbsp;they people aren't injecting themselves with steroids and rolling their weights all over the gym, they're sitting there doing nothing.&nbsp; What the fuck&nbsp;do you come to the gym for?&nbsp;&nbsp;Why are there people who stand around at the same machine TALKING for about 20 minutes, then quickly pull off one or two sets, and then go home as if they've done some huge workout?&nbsp; If that's the only workout you wanna do, then fine...But get the fuck away from the&nbsp;machine!...Other people want to use it too and they don't need you standing there&nbsp;holding up the&nbsp;machine while you talk about how you're going to put a wing on your car once your mommy and daddy buy it for you.&nbsp; Fag.  2) DRIVERS    Have people completely forgotten how to drive?&nbsp; Or are we just handing out driver's licenses to anyone that can dish out the testing fee nowadays?&nbsp; I saw a man at least 75 yrs old swerving all over the fuckin highway this past weekend, and when I was about to pass him (for my own safety), I look over and see the guy squinting over the steering wheel with glasses that could have been used in the fuckin Hubble telescope.&nbsp; Then I get another person going 75km/h on the 401 around the airport. Like honestly!...75!&nbsp; Does he WANT to get rammed from behind?&nbsp; And then when someone behind him gave him a polite little honk of the horn, the driver had the audacity to actually give the honker the finger.&nbsp; As if he's not doing anything wrong!....If your car is incapable of going more than 90-95km/hr, then STAY OFF THE FUCKIN 400 series highways!    3) TELEMARKETERS     Ok, this is somewhat of a touchy area, because I used to telemarket.&nbsp; And I have a bit of patience for them.&nbsp; But calling me at 9 am on a SUNDAY fucking morning?...You seriously must need your head fuck-started because that is just a death wish!&nbsp; What is wrong with these companies who think "Hmmm...I know!&nbsp; We'll get the best response to people if we call them bright and early on one of the TWO days that they don't HAVE to get up early!...They'll thank us for waking them up."&nbsp; Do these thoughts even GO through a person's mind when they're deciding the working schedule for their team of telemarketers???&nbsp; And on top of this is the telemarketers who have the audacity to be RUDE at this time of the day.&nbsp; Let me get this straight, you're calling me...Waking me up....Disturbing my sleep...Trying to sell me something.....AND you're gonna give me attitude?&nbsp; You must be out of your fuckin mind!   *Sigh*....Alright, that's enough for this rant session (remember, it's only Episode I).&nbsp; On a side note, thanks the my boy Vee for helping us with the move on Friday night.&nbsp; Would have taken us forever if he didn't come and help out.&nbsp;  G'nite.&nbsp; And if you're one of the above listen people (Gym, Drivers, or Telemarketers).....Sleep with one eye open. =P&nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Alright, so why in the world do we as a society set up so many barriers for ourselves?&nbsp; Is it in our nature to segregate ourselves and try to make little factions so that under no uncertain terms can we ever achieve any type of harmonious happiness?&nbsp; Look at the world, we have so many ways that we have divided ourselves:   Countries  Race  Culture  Caste (for some cultures)  Religion  SES (Socio-economic status)  Etc.   It seems that no matter where you turn, there's something else that tries to keep you from relating to your fellow man/woman.&nbsp; But what's worse is that people actually  believe  that these barriers need to be upheld.&nbsp; Interracial marriages still aren't fully accepted by society, much less inter-religious marriages.&nbsp; We have countries that declare war on each other simply over the ability to either extend their own land, or to be able to say that a certain peice of land belongs to them.&nbsp; We have governments around the world that institute laws and policies and tax plans that cause the gap between the rich and the poor to widen, and then the rich start believing that they actually are better humans than the poor.&nbsp; Caste is perhaps one of the biggest barriers as some people in India and other countries will not even  talk/touch  someone who is considered to be of a lower caste than them.&nbsp; (Don't be fooled, the mass media may say that caste has been abolished, but it's much easier to claim a law that abolishes it than to go out into the cities and force everyone to stop paying attention to it).&nbsp;   Why do we keep dividing ourselves?&nbsp; What is it that we are so scared of?&nbsp; Or do we actually think that because we are born in a certain country/religion/financial household, that we automatically achieve some type of status?&nbsp; I personally find the words of Bruce Lee (yes, Bruce Lee) to be very appropriate in this case:   "You know what I want to think of myself?&nbsp; As a  human being .&nbsp; Because, and I don't want to sound like "As Confucius says...", but under the sky, under the heavens, there is but one family.&nbsp; It just so happens that people are different."  I'm seriously tired of being divided.&nbsp; I'm tired of hearing people talk about how a certain group of people are just not trustworthy because of the religion they are or where they come from.&nbsp; I'm tired of all these stereotypes and levels that we have put on ourselves.&nbsp; As a society, we've conquered so much throughout time.&nbsp; We've travelled the limits of the earth, stepped on the moon, gazed to some of the most distant points in the galaxy, and theorized about the extents that the universe reaches.&nbsp; Yet you would think that with everything we've conquered, we would have come to the point where we could at least be at peace with ourselves.&nbsp; All this external exploring and external discoveries, but we haven't yet been able to fully explore ourselves and discover our true nature as humans.  &nbsp;  Instead we put that off.&nbsp; We lift up walls and methods of breaking down society rather than mixing it together and giving harmony a shot.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Just think about it.&nbsp; Something as simple as economy [ok, for all you Econ majors, I know it's not simple, but on a relative scale here ok?&nbsp;=o)]...Throughout the world, we've even divided ourselves with our money.&nbsp; US money is better than Japanese money; British money is worth more than Canadian money; etc.&nbsp; It's all just divisions.&nbsp; I at least partially applaud the European countries for developing the Euro.&nbsp; It is at least a step towards breaking down some barriers (regardless of how small).  &nbsp;  What's funnier is that almost all religions teach us that we are all equal.&nbsp; God loves all his children equally and that we should let nothing come between us as a society.&nbsp; Yet religion is such a driving force behind some of the biggest barriers.&nbsp; In fact, I would go so far as to say that religion is THE biggest barrier between people.&nbsp; Isn't that ironic.&nbsp; Religion teaches us to love everyone equally, and we use it as a method to set up some of the highest barriers society has ever built.&nbsp;   So I start to think to myself, "Are we ever gonna stop dividing ourselves?&nbsp; Or is this just one destructive cycle; division after division?".&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I sincerely believe that the first step in elminating the divisions is to first acknowledge that they exist.&nbsp; Ignoring the problem or thinking that it will go away itself is not going to solve anything. Our generation has to stop paying attention to the segregations present in the world&nbsp;and work to educate others to do the same.  &nbsp;  Hmmm..I guess in a way, that's another sort of irony.&nbsp; Only through working together and full commitment can we start to break down the barriers that keep us apart as a society.  &nbsp;  Either way, I got some sledge hammers and I'm ready to do some barrier breaking.  &nbsp;  Smashy smashy.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't understand how this company stays afloat.  I truly and honestly do not.  When I first started working here, there was not one single person who worked in the office who was not qualified in at least some sense of their job.  New order takers always got a week of training before they were even allowed to touch the phone and interact with customers.  The accounting department had actual accountants and people with degrees; we had an office manager who kept things running in pretty good shape; and the dispatchers were experienced people who knew the city and could dispatch faster than most of us can talk.    Mind you, the job wasn't perfect back then.  People were really annoying here.  We had a lot of "workplace politics", and people would constantly be fighting and arguing because very few people genuinely liked each other.  But you couldn't really complain.  The pay was decent, they had a radio to entertain us, and the work wasn't hard.    Now that was about 7 years ago.  Fast forward to now.  We have all the phone conversations recorded, there are camera's up in every room, and the radio has been taken away (although in all fairness, most of the terminals now have the internet).  All this to "improve efficiency".  Now, obviously, to someone who is looking at this post, a lot of these changes seem logical.  I mean, phone's should be recorded for legal purposes, the office needs to be monitored, and a loud radio can be heard over the phone and will make the office environment seem less professional.    But, after making all these changes, there have also been a lot of changes made to the staff.  Firstly, the accounting department no longer has ANY real accountant.  Only people who learned the job after about 2 weeks of training.  There are so many so called "dispatchers" entering the office who are drivers for the company and they feel that they can make the easy transition between the two jobs.  The order takers are replaced by friends or family of the board of directors.  So that's where we sit now.  But here's the good part:    Dispatchers: Although they know the city, most of them can't speak enough english to make themselves understood.  Order Takers: Most of them can't speak enough english to make themselves understood; they don't know the first thing about how to use a computer (the order taking process is computer based); and they don't know the city at ALL (so can't answer any of the questions of the customter...Although this hardly matters because even if they  did  know the answer, they don't know enough english to formulate it into a proper sentence)  Accountants: Give credit where it is due, these guys can at least make themselves understood in english.  But they refuse to do anything beyond the accounting.  If the office gets busy, they're supposed to help with the order taking, but of course, they don't.      Today was the worst day.  We had one of the regular guys (full time guy who is pretty cool and is one of the rare ordertakers that can speak english, knows the city, and knows how to do his job) gone on vacation.  So the replacement came in.  And this woman didn't know the difference between Yonge St. and Hwy401.  She could seriously barely speak english (although she was trying her best).  Any time she got a customer that she didn't understand, she'd just put them on hold.  Wouldn't even tell me that the person was on hold and I needed to answer the phone.  It took her forever to get through an order (don't blame her, she didn't get any real training), and it was frustrating because today was pretty busy.  This coupled with the night dispatcher (wrote about her before, always on msn or on her phone) who doesn't answer phones meant that I was sitting there working like mad.    Now, I in NO way blame this lady for her lack of work.  I blame the management (yes, those wonderful Board of Directors).  They hire people not out of qualification, but out of the fact that they have some affiliation with them.  They hire them because, the person is their friend, the son of their friend, their cousin, etc etc.  Now, I know this is the way the world works, but honestly, those jobs are usually given when the person has at least SOME qualification that matches the job.  But no, we can't have qualified people getting these jobs...That would mean that the company would actually start working better! God forbid!  But instead, they hire tonnes of people and just throw them on the phones without any kind of training and tell them to learn on the fly.  What's the result? Customers get annoyed and end up cancelling their business and taking it elsewhere.    And of course, the blame goes back to the workers.  Can never be the management's fault.  Oh God no.  The management is perfect.  All hail the management.  They'll never steer you wrong.  Follow them blindly and the company shall prosper!  Management idiots.  Taste the sarcasm.  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sounds like a latest movie blockbuster doesn't it?  Unfortunately, it's not.  It's a signal that I am soon going to be returning to school (i.e. - hell).  I guess with this journal thing, I never really commented on my first year out in Chicago at the Illinois College of Optometry.  To be honest with everyone, I can still remember the first day out there during orientation.  It was a lot different than my first orientation day at Western.  Mostly because at Western, there were still people that I knew and my roommate was a friend from highschool.  So I still had that feeling of familiarity and recognition.  It was just a matter of making new friends and meeting new people (which I met plenty of and had a great time doing it).  Plus at Western, there were a LOT more people, so everyone was just suddenly thrown together.  You tended to have a lot easier time mixing in with each other.    At ICO, things were much different.  I was not only in a different city, but in a different country.  While at Western, most of the people came from different cities, the majority of them were still from somewhere in Ontario.  So there was this sense of community still...Everyone had something in common.  You could talk to a person and be like, "Oh, you're from 'so and so', I went there to visit a friend once."  So even then, you kind of had something to connect to and something in common.  But when it came to Chicago...Everyone was from all over the place.  And I'm seriously talking about all over.  People spanned from all across the United States and Canada.  We had people from Albert, Manitoba, Ontario, Saskatchewan, etc etc.  So you went there, and after your family left....It just hit you..."I don't know ANYONE!"  What's worse for me was that my roommate at that point hadn't arrived (and subsequently wouldn't arrive for the next 2 days).  So when going to all the meetings and such, while most people at least had their roommate to go with...I kind of had to go on my own and try to meet people.  Had to put in that extra effort and stuff.  But it all worked out.  Met some great people, made good friends and such.    School on the other hand...School taught me a new lesson in life.  No matter how hard you think you're being pushed...You can always go harder.  I used to think that university would give us too much work and too much material to cover in a term.  University was NOTHING compared to optometry school.  We have 12 weeks in our term (4 terms per year).  Each term is the same.  First 2 weeks is introductory class material and such.  Then for 8 weeks, we have classes + assignments + labs + quizzes + midterms.  This usually translates to about 2-3 midterms a week plus at least 1 lab quiz a week.  Then at the end of the 10 weeks, we have finals.  We usually have 6 finals in the course of 8 days.  And these are like huge finals covering upwards of 600 pages (damn that Dr.T).  Then, mercifully, you get the 12th week of the term off to rest and recuperate.  Then you start the new term and the cycle regenerates itself.  The first term you run through this ok.  The second term seems harder, but with thanksgiving break, christmas break, etc...You never really feel the full effects of the term.  By 3rd term..You're exhausted.  You have no fuel left in the tank, and all you want is to go home and crawl into bed, go to sleep, and not wake up till they're calling your name at the graduation ceremony.  That 3rd quarter, I started to HATE my desk.  I hated it with a passion.  I couldn't stand looking at it or sitting down in it even if I was sitting down to watch tv.    And now, with the summer coming to an end, I'll be returning to that life.  I'll probably be living on my own in a bachelor's appartment.  That means I'll have to move down my desk and some belongings. But it also means I get to put all my posters back up.   :-D  Got a new Bruce Lee one that is simply gorgeous.    On the bright side, I met a bunch of amazing people in Chicago last year, and it'll be great to go down there and be able to see them again.  God knows I'll be seeing them for the next two years straight (no more summer holidays).  After this year is over, I'll also be hitting clinic, which will really put to test if optometry is what I want to do with the rest of my life (kind of late now isn't it?  After spending close to $100,000 US).    But meeting all those people, going out, having fun...all of it definately gets weighed down by those weeks where you spend 20 out of the 24hrs in a day at your desk (2 sleeping and then 2 writing the exam).  They just completely wear you out.  They think they can break me though?  They think I'll crumble?  They think I'll just lay down and die?  Oh no.  Not I.  I will survive.  For as long as I know how to cram, I know I'll stay alive!  =o)  G'nite all.  Time to hit the gym. 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well well, I'm at work agian, so of course, that means that it is time to sit down and add another page into this journal.  Things are getting ready to make a big turn in life these days.  My sister and my brother in law are getting ready to move out next weekend.  Now this in itself is always a big deal, but it's not something that was gonna affect me a whole lot.  I mean, I've kind of been ready for this for about 2 years now (the time they first started living with  us).  It has always been a sort of inevitability that the day was going to come when Gulshan (my brother in law) would be on his feet and they'd move out of our house.  Therefore, although sad, this event isn't unexpected.  What is a bit more of a pull and strain is the fact that they're going to take my new nephew with them.  Him I will miss dearly.  He's right around that age that being around him is going to be so much fun.  He's starting to make more facial expression, starting to recognize people's faces, and starting to pick his favourites.  Seeing him go and not being able to wake up the next day and go play with him, or not seeing the way he grabs for my hat brim every time I'm wearing it....These things were not expected and they are seriously gonna take a bigger chunk out of me.  Who knew you'd get so attached to someone you've known for a little over a month.  Anyways, that was my little rant about that.  I'm not looking forward to next weekend; firstly because I hate moving days (such tiring days), and secondly because of Arjun (nephew).  Beyond that, the main thing that has gotten on my mind lately is the notion of having preconceptions about people.  This all started a few days ago.  I was actually having a conversation with a friend of mine who knows me fairly well, and she invited a friend of hers to join in.  I got no problem with that, love meeting new people.  So this new person knows basically nothing about me.  And we were talking on a subject (doesn't really matter which one), and in the midst of it, I stated an opinion that was, from my point of view, completely truthful and genuine.  This girl then proceeded to make a somewhat sarcastic remark regarding how my opinion was the typical guy opinion.  Now, when she referred to "typical guy opinion", she was referring to the idea that I only had/gave that opinion so that I could impress women, sweet talk a girl, or try and fool a girl into thinking my opinion was sincere.    This really bothers me.  She basically was stating that my opinion was fake...insincere...pretty much saying that I was lying in order to make myself look better.    Now..This all came because she believed that "all" guys do this and it's just the 'guy' thing to do.  That all guys will say anything and everything and exaggerate in order to make themselves look better and fool a girl by hiding their  real  opinions.  And of course, she stamped all these traits onto me as if I was some kind of juice carton in desperate need of a "100% fake" label.  This came after having talked to me for about 15 minutes total.  A  little premature?  I personally think so.  Why are all these kinds of preconceptions labelled onto us without even first taking the time to get to know the person?  I mean, I fully understand that it is almost impossible to NOT have a single preconception about someone, but is it so hard to push those preconceptions to the back of our mind and just give the person the benefit of the doubt before we start accusing them of certain things based on stereotypes?  Just because I'm a guy, does NOT mean that every word that spews from my mouth is forumulated for the sole purpose to execute my master plan of playing a girl.    I know this goes both ways.  It has nothing to do with gender or whatnot.  Gender is just one of the reasons for stereotypes and such.  But really, why do people always feel they know everything about a person just because they see the way they dress, hear the way they talk, know their gender/race/religion, etc.  It's one thing to have these preconceptions in your mind, but it's a completely different ordeal to allow those stereotypes to guide the way you think, act, talk, or treat the person.    This girl wants to have the preconception that all guys are players?  Fine, that's her decision.  But to treat me like one because of the fact that I fit the mold of being "a guy"?  That is where I start taking offence.  I know it's not 100% her fault either.  The stereotypes have to be created from some actual events.  But still, it isn't fair, and it shouldn't be done.  I put up with it when my elders do it because they have their reasons.  But when we've grown up in such a multicultural and educated society, how in the world do we still go around saying, "Oh man, don't ask to borrow money from that guy.  He's Jewish."  Jokes are one thing...Being serious and actually believing any of those stereotypes are totally different.  They're only gonna hurt us in the end.  Might as well let go of them now.  I might write more later...This is all I can really say on this topic.  Just annoys me so much. 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another Friday night...Another night stuck here at work.  I think this is what I will remember most from this summer.  Spending my nights at work writing posts for this journal so that random people can come here and read about whatever boredom flings into my mind.  On an actual surprising note, I have found that quite a few people have actually been reading this thing and responding to it.  Now, this is not only surprising, but also pleasing in a way.  I actually will have conversations with certain people that are ignited from something they read in this journal.  Now who knows how long people will keep reading this, but for now, it ain't half bad.  Glad to see that this is actually amusing people.  =D  So anyways, onto the topic for today.  This is actually coming from a comment that someone said earlier this week.  Well, actually it came from two comments he made.  A friend of mine down in the States had wanted desperately to get into NYC med school, but had also applied to other med schools in the US.  But believe me, he wanted nothing more than to be able to go to NYC (his long time girlfriend was there and he wanted to go there so they could live together, among other things about NYC that he loved).  So anyways, on Monday, he got a letter from a Med school out in California saying that he had been accepted for the class entering in 2004.  Of course, he was thrilled since it was his first acceptance letter.  Subsequently, I was also thrilled for him and congratulated him numerous times.  His response basically was, "Thanks a lot.  It's good to know that my hard work finally came through and that I earned this".  I felt really happy for him knowing that things had worked out so well for him.  Then on Wednesday, he got his letter from NYC, and unfortunately, he didn't get in there.  Needless to say, he was a bit upset, but was taking it really well.  When I was talking to him about it, he simply said, "Hey, it could be worse. This is just the way it was meant to be.  I guess Fate just doesn't want me in New York."    Now, this kind of got me thinking.  I hear these kinds of comments all the time.  "I earned this"...."It was fate".  But I never noticed before how many times I hear those phrases from the same person.  If both those comments represent what the person feels, then they form somewhat of a paradox.  How can one believe that they "earn" on thing, yet believe in "fate" at another point?  (Cheti, if you're reading this, you know EXACTLY where this is going) =D  So it comes to the idea of Choice vs Fate.  Which do you believe?  Now, before I go on with this post, I want to emphasize that I am in NO way trying to degrade anyone's belief's or the teachings of anyone's religions or such.  I'm simply stating my opinion and the way that I view things.  If you view them differently, then that's great.  I respect your opinion and would love to hear your take on the topic.  So yes, back to the topic at hand.  What initially intrigued me is that there are so many instances when something good happens, that we credit it to ourselves and say that we made the right decision, or we earned something, or we went about everything the right way.  But when something happens that is detrimental to our lives, we console ourselves by saying stuff like; its what was meant to be, it's the way life goes, that's just fate.  This seems interesting...Our accomplishments are of our own doing, but our failures are not due to our decisions, they're due to fate.  How does that work?  Either you are a stoic and everything that happens is due to fate, or you believe in free will and everything is a consequence of you decisions, or possibly you believe in a mix between the two (like myself).  However, what cannot happen is that you believe certain things are solely due to fate, while others are solely due to your credit.  That just doesn't work in my view.  Seems like a defence mechanism a lot of us have developed in order to help transfer and justify the pain of our failures.  You got a scholarship?  Good job!  You worked hard for it!...You got fire from your job? Don't worry, it's just not what you were meant to do in life.    Why isn't it ever the other way around?  You got a scholarship?  Well that's good, but you were fated to get it anyways.  You got fired from your job?  Well, you just made some bad choices in your career path....See the difference?  The second set seems so cold hearted.  Doesn't make you feel good about it at all.  But if you belive in fate, then in both cases, you should only believe the "meant to be" answers.  If you believe in choice, then you should only belive in the "accomplishment" answers.  Either way, you have a case when you have at least 1 cold hearted answer.  But this doesn't happen...We alter our mind to create a situation in which we always get rid of the cold hearted answer.  Interesting no?  I think so.  An extension of this, I've never understood how people who belive in "judgement after death" can believe in fate.  I mean, doesn't fate mean that everything in your life is written?  So how can you be judged (and found guilty) over doing something that you had no control over?  Example:   God:  You killed a village and set fire to houses John.  For this, you must be sent to hell and be punished. John:  Well God, if fate exists, then all this was written before I even did it.  I had no choice in it, and couldn't have stopped myself if I wanted to.  But I couldn't even  want  to stop myself, because how I was going to feel was also written by fate.  So how can I possibly be punished for something I had no control over?   Now some might say that it's not that simple, namely those people who believe in karma and in reincarnation.  Fate in this life is written by your deeds in the past life.  Well, weren't the deeds in the past life a part of fate too?  Weren't they written by the deeds in the life before that? And the deeds in that life written by the deeds in the one before that?  Etc etc?  So in reality, none of the incarnations were your fault, and you really can't be held accountable for anything that you do or have done.  On top of that, life tends to lose some meaning doesn't it?   Personally, I believe that fate plays a role in life, but not such a concrete one that most believe.  I think fate writes out certain things in life for us, but it's up to us to make decisions as opportunities and challenges are put in front of us.  So basically, fate has a plan, but we have the power to change and alter the plan.  As a comparison, it's like one big chess game.  The peices you have and the size of the board is set out for you, but how you play the game and where you end up on the board is dependent on your choices.  So go out there and play your game of chess.  Make your gambits, move your peices...That's enough writing for now.  Checkmate.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you need all 3 to figure it out...Then seriously, you haven't been paying ANY attention whatsoever.  :-)  Once again, I sit here stuck at work.  Stuck with two other people.  One woman who refuses to do anything but talk on MSN, and one guy who does do his work, but stops working the second someone calls him (which is approximately every 10 minutes).    So I get left here to just get more and more annoyed every time the phone rings because no one picks it up and I end up having to do it all the time.  And on top of that, you get really annoying customers who don't listen to what you're asking them and feel that they know the best way how you should do your job.  *Sigh*...Honestly...  But it isn't all bad.  Sometimes you just get the nicest customer alive. They're all cheery and happy and just have a great phone voice and just by talking to them, you feel that your job isn't half as bad as you think it is.  It's unfortunate that those people don't call more often, they can really make the day go a lot quicker and help you get through your day without wanting to carve your intestines out with a dull and rusted spoon.  I guess it's just that way in life though.  You meet a lot of people; some of them are absolutely the greatest people and make life worth living.  There are also just neutral people.  You don't particularly love them or have any reason to hate them either.  You treat them with proper respect, but wouldn't go out of your way for them.  And then there are those people who just rub you completely the wrong way.  Your life would be a hell of a lot easier if these people had no part in it.  The tricky part I guess is to try and maximize the number of people in column A (and possibly B), and minimize the number of people in column C.  It becomes even trickier because the older you get, the more you realize that too many people in the world have selfish personalities, and that automatically puts them in column C.  Beyond that, too many people in the world are two-faced.  They come off as a person who belongs in column A, but all too late you realize that this person is definately a C.    This really bugs me.  I'm a fairly honest man, and I have the weakness that I can't tell initially when someone is being chalaak with me.     Ok, sidenote time.  For those of you who don't know what "chalaak" is (i.e. - the non Punjabi's or the people i haven't converted yet); Chalaak basically means conniving.  Like a person who plots and plans to screw people over and make work to their own benefit. Always wanting the worst for others, but the best for themselves.  I think you get the idea.   Anyways, back to my rant.  So yeah, I've had supposed "friends" who have been completely chalaak, and I can't see it two feet from my face.  I think over the years, I've gotten better at it, but it's still no to the point where it should be.  I still remember the first time I realized that i trust people way too much and too easily.  I met a friend in highschool, leave him nameless for now, and my best friend Banh said straight up to me (another quality of his I respect), "Monnie, watch out for (blank), he's just trying to use you.  He's not your friend."  I didn't believe him at the time...I took his words into account, but didn't totally believe him.  Of course, he turned out to be 100% right.  It just took me a good 8 months to figure it out.  It's the same story now.  I meet someone, I respect them instantly and wait for them to do something that causes me to lose respect for them.  If they don't do anything, then I continue to fully respect them.  I don't want to change this about me...I like to stay optimistic about the world and think that not evryone is out there to screw me over.  I like the believe that intrinsically, we're all good people at heart.    Unfortunately, I meet more and more chalaak people.  Don't get me wrong, I still meet people who are too nice for words, but they're becoming fewer and further in between.  This is part of the reason that I have so much respect for honest people and for my friends who are still close to me.  They've shown that they are not chalaak with me and have nothing in their mind except my best.  This includes both friends and family.   To these people (you should know who you are)...I tip my hat.  You are truly extraordinary and life would not be what it is without you.    Bottom line...I just wish people would be more straight up and honest.  The world is hard enough without having to think if your "friends" are being chalaak with you or they're being sincere.  If you don't like someone, don't fake that you do.  Don't pretend like they're your best friend.  Show them the respect of an acquaintance and be on your way.  Honesty truly is the best policy.  Lets try and work it into our lives more often.  Dr.Phil...Signing off.  =-P
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, for those of you reading this who don't enjoy geeky topics, I'd suggest that you stop reading now. (For those of you who have thought this journal is nothing but geeky topics...Screw you!  :-D)  Anyways, I'm stuck at work again right now, and it seems that this it the time that I have to write a bit in my journal.  So what geeky topic do I have to discuss?  One word: Relativity.  Now, to most people, the first word that pops into their head after hearing 'relativity' is naturally "Einstein", who was the father of modern day relativity.  But I'm actually talking about Carnap.  His relativity was not the physical concept that Einstein fathomed, but was more about the relative nature between physical laws and the geometrical nature of space.  Now, Carnap basically stated that the laws of physics were relative to the nature of space that one decided to assume.  For example, we know certain laws of thermodynamics cause objects to expand when they are heated.  But what Carnap reminds us is that these laws are only relevant in the linear 2D view of space-time.  Therefore, the laws of thermodynamics that we have established only hold true if we believe space to be non curved.  This holds for other laws as well, including the laws of gravity developed by Newton.    Newton stated that objects fall towards an object of great mass because that massive object creates a "force" of gravity.  This is how we explain the earth having a pull on everything in space like meteors and such (in reality, everything exerts a pull on each other, but the masses of small objects is so low that it is practically zero).  Now Einstein came along and said that those laws are only true if space is flat, which he believed it was not.  He stated that the reason the earth causes objects to spiral down towards its centre is not because it "exerts" a force, but because the earth causes a disruption in the "flat" nature of space.    An example of this would be if you took a marble, an orange and a flat plate.  The flat plate represents space, while the orange represents the earth, and the marble represents some small object (say a small meteor).  Now, if the orange is put on the flat plate and the marble is rolled by it, nothing happens.  Einstein believed that rather than a flat plate, a better representation would be to use a large bowl with the orange at the centre.  Now if the marble is released, it quickly spirals down towards the orange.  Einstein believed that this represented the manner in which the Earth/orange 'bent' space-time rather than exerting some special force on it.  Now, Carnap goes along the same lines.  He states that rather than having a law for thermal expansion, the actual nature of space is bent in order to accomodate the expansion of the heated material.  So this raises somewhat of an interesting idea.  Do we really need all these formulas and laws and such?  It's already been proven that the nature of space is NOT flat and that in reality, space has a very complex geometrical pattern to it.  Yet our society continues to hold on to the idea that space is flat, and we continue to develop laws and investigate relationships and teach physics based on this belief.  Now of course, I don't have nearly the experience to know WHY we continue to see space as flat, as I'm sure there must be some benefit to it.  But the ideas raised by Carnap are quite intriguing.  He insists that our view of space should shift to the 3d geometric view, and we should investigate spatial relationships with respects to the geometry rather than the physical relationships.    It's an interesting idea.  Complex forumlas to explain flat space....Or no formulas and try to understand complex geometrical space.  Kind of like the lesser of two evils.  But the most interesting part, to me at least, is the duality of it all.  You can take whichever view you want.  You can believe space is geometrically linear and then use formulas to help you understand why the solar system revolves around the sun; or you can believe that these physical relationships don't exist, and look at the universe as a curved and contorted 3 dimensional structure and use that idea to explain everything that happens around you.  It's all relative to the way you think, and Carnap tries to show this to us.  Either way you go...you can't escape the physics behind it all.    Simply amazing.  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, it's been a while since I updated this. What can I say? Not going to work anymore has cut down on the number of hours I have to screw around and do nothing. Not to say that life has been hectic since work ended, but it's just that I've actually had time to sit back and relax...So I try and choose to sit back and relax away from this computer.  Not many things have happened lately. The big thing has been that I have gotten to see some old friends that I hadn't seen in a long time. Mathu, Audrey, and Tim...It's definately been WAY too long. It was good to sit down with them and just relax....Just sit back, and pretend we were all back in highschool....All back together without any of the worries of having to find work, pay bills, learn the path of the parasympathetic innervation of the iris.....Oh wait, most of you probably don't have to do that one....(damn you all). But yeah, we sat around and just talked, played cards, and caught up on old stories. All in all, it was a great time. I still can't believe Tim had that Darth Maul toy.  Ok, for all of you who don't know the story (which is probably most of you), me and Tim roomed together first year at Western. It was a good time because we had both known each other from highschool (and middle school), so there was that sense of not going into this brand new world alone. Well, we were obviously both Star Wars geeks and back then, the whole craze was the new Star Wars movie (Episode I). The ONLY good thing about this movie was Darth Maul with his double edged lightsaber. That was thie complete highlight of the movie. So anyways, back to the story. Me, Tim, and a few other people are walking through Sears at Masonville mall, and naturally, me and Tim head right to the toys section (where else would we go??!). And there it was...About a 25cm tall Darth Mall piggy bank. But not just any piggy bank. When you inserted money into it (or pressed the handy dandy button), Darth Maul would come alive and start moving and talking. And get this....His lightsaber...Oh yeah...It would ignite! (well, it's plastic right, so the plastic representation of the saber beam would roll out). We saw that lightsaber ignite and our jaws hit the floor. It was immediately concluded that both of us were gonna get this, but neither of us could justify spending $50 on it. Luckily, Christmas was just around the corner, and me and Tim both had the same thought at the same time. We turned around to each other, and said:  "Tim/Monnie....I'm getting you this for Christmas"  The deed was done....There was no stopping it. So of course, Christmas rolled around...And we got each other the Darth Maul piggy bank. I walked into Tim's basement yesterday...And BAM...there it was. That one toy pretty much embodied the entirety of first year for me. Just brought back so many memories. Some that I actually thought I had forgot.  Anyways, other than that...I have a few changes. 1) Bourne Identity and Supremacy have made it to my list of all time favourite movies. 2) Go watch Harold and Kumar go to White Castle. It is TOO funny (and refreshing to see an indian and asian guy talking in lead role WITHOUT accents). 3) I'm going back to Chicago soon....Shoot me.    "If the trace was correct, I shall find them quickly Master"....."At last, we shall have our revenge".....Hahahaha...That toy was SO cool!   
    
</post>


</Blog>