<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, let me see.  Last you knew, I had just gotten my job and was going for my drivers test in the morning.  Well, I woke up fairly early and practiced parallel parking several times.  Having never attempted it before, I was slightly nervous.  I did ok, except for the part when I hit the other Honda’s bumper while pulling out.  Both cars were ok, but I just got more nervous.  When I went to the test, I remembered that there were two instructors.  The guy was easy, while with the lady you make the smallest mistake and BANG.  So I'm sitting there, then the guy comes over.  Whew.  Went through the test and managed to pass.  I'm a pretty safe driver, unless you guarantee me that there are no cops around.  I respect their profession, but they do function as a slight deterrent.  Which is probably a good thing.  Probably.  What else happened last week?  Let me see... oh yeah.  I had the job "training" thingy on Thursday morning.  The job looks like a cakewalk, at least on the assigned dates.  See, we work on 15 specified days, then we have several other days where we are just called in.  You do a lot harder, and more interesting work on the call-in days.  At least that’s what it looks like.  Um, already mentioned about the party, but here’s some "behind-the-scenes."  I had planned to go to three parties: A guy's, a girl's, and another guy's.  The first guy's one wasn't until 2, and I (for some unexplained reason that I don't even understand) really wanted to go to the girl's.  As I said before, I went there and stayed there.  I was having fun, too.  I want to chat w/ her again, but she's going to Albany to see an old friend that she hasn't seen in two years.  So, maybe tonight, if I'm lucky.  Oh boy.  I'm going to die early now.  Bedtime is supposed to be 12 - 1 for me, but talking to her it turns into 2-4.  I am tired.  But I wake up whenever I'm doing something interesting, and talking to her certainly counts.  She had a mouse that her mom had found with her last night.  It looked like he (Nuggets, to be precise) might not last long.  He sounded so cute!  I hope he makes it, and lives out the whole of his mouse days.  Whoa, hang on a sec... It looks like I'm going to get a new bedroom.  FREEDOM!!! My mom just told me that I need to rearrange the old tv room so that we can move a bunkbed in there for my brother and me to use!  Better get to work.  Later!
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't written in awhile, but I'll update you later (as in tomorrow).  Just finished watching Insomnia, a great movie with Al Pachino and Robin Williams.  I can somewhat identify with Al (who plays the main character), who suffers from insomnia due to interesting things, because I am extremely tired.  I was up till about 3 in the morning yesterday,  talking with a new friend of mine.  I was at her graduation party on Saturday, we exchanged AIM screennames, and we were talking that night late.  Probably about 3-4 hours conversation on AIM, then throw in about 3-4 more hours spent talking to her at her party.  I have known her all year from school, but we never really talked.  She teased me all the time, though.  I came to her party because, frankly, she seemed a very interesting person and I figured this would probably be the last time I'd see her.  I was the only one from the school who showed up at her party for about 3 hours, then what seemed like everyone showed for about 20-30 minutes.  I stayed until all was said and done, helped clean up, etc.  Why?  Don't really know.  We started talking, and something just sort of clicked.  Weird, isn't it?  Both of us are people who would never start a conversation, but we are in a way forced to talk to each other and we really hit it off.  Oh, she just got on AIM.  Write more later!
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I had a great time at the six flags yesterday, but right now that's not really high in my thought pattern order thingy.  It was cool, awesome, loved the Superman ride which I waited an hour in line so I could get the front seat, but the real agenda (I love words like that) is the fact that I got back from my job interview at BOCES about an hour and a half ago.  The interview went well I thought, not really sure because this was my first one, but when I got home after making a few stops my brother told me they had called.  I called the guy back and he said "I can offer you a position if you are still interested."  Yes!  My first job!  Well, besides working for my dad.  That doesn't count.  But... got a job.  So, steps that need to be done:   1. Repay my dad for all the money that I borrowed from him over the school year.   2. Acquire a decent joystick ( Logitech Wingman Digital Extreme  rocks!) 3. I want to play Icewind Dale.  Get those games.  Oh, and Planetscape: Torment. 4. I've been GMing a SWRPG game with two of my younger brothers.  Get that rolling again. 5. Get my drivers license.  Test is tomorrow, practice... now, actually  Signing off to practice for my drivers test... 
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, got back about an hour ago from church.  Yep, I'm a Christian.  Service was... unusual today as it was more of a financial meeting then a short message for fathers afterwards.  In celebration for Fathers day, my family is going out to our cottage by a glorified pond referred to as Gerry Lake.  We're going to have pizza, soda, (Mountain Dew rocks!) and then go swimming.  Or maybe swim first then eat after.  Don’t know, don't care.  Boy, I was up to about 12 AM last night playing Max Payne.  Cool game, really.  Expect a review when I beat it.  Probably not going to play it tonight, cause I need to get some sleep.  My school is having an "end-of-the-year" trip and I gotta be at the school (1/2 hour away) by 6:00.  So.... no late night.  As I'm typing right now, I also happen to be trying to download Magic the Gathering Online so I can play it.  I like CCGs (Collectable Card Games, in case you didn't know,) and online games are cool.  Except for lag.  When you're out in the boondocks and you can only get a 56k connection that runs at about 28k on a good day, you get lag.  A card game shouldn't have too much lag... I hope.  Just finished the book "Artimis Fowl" yesterday as well.  I'm a very speedy reader, so I read quite a lot.  And it's fun too!  The book was cool, well, let me see.  In writing style, the book wasn't that great.  Too many... uh, what do you call them?  Oh yeah, sentence fragments.  Little more like a children’s book, hang on a sec... oh yeah, it  is  a children’s book.  Oops.  Well, plotwise, the characters weren’t well developed, but the overall storyline was well though out.  However, I still liked the characters.  Artimis is just a cool kid, Holly is a cool (though egotistical) fairy, and Butler is, is, Butler.  What really made me like this book was the concept of the world and devices.  I can't really go into detail about that, because my mom (whop is unaware of my blog) wants me to get off the net so she can call her father who is in Texas.  So... gotta get off.  Write later.
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello!  My real name is * (deleted by *(-deleted-)), but you out there will just know me as Roulex.  Before you start calling me "Watch-boy" or something to that effect, realize that it's spelled "ROULEX", not "ROLEX." (all punctuation marks inside the quotation marks, how could I forget thanks to my English teacher's pet peeve about the thing.)  Roulex actually comes from ancient history, in the Punic Wars (Say what?  Punic wars?  What's that?)  where he (Roulex) was a mercenary general who assisted the Carthigians (Yes, these guys did get wiped out by the Romans, which is why they aren’t exactly well known.)  Well, I live in New York (the state, not the town,) between 2 towns named Bainbridge and Guilford.  I'm the oldest in a huge family (9 kids including myself,) still in high school, and currently unemployed (looking at this point.)  I like music, virtually any kind, though my favorite bands at the moment (They change) are Skillet, Creed, Thousand Foot Krutch, Switchfoot, and U2.  Movies are cool, especially The Matrix, Star Wars, and Lord of the Rings.  I love to read, though I like computer games more.  BTW, read Shogun by James Clavell.  One of the best books of all time (IMHO.)  Computer games... where do I begin?  Baldur's Gate II is probably my all-time favorite, though it is LONG!  Recently been playing Half-Life, Diablo II, and Max Payne.  The reason I chose this layout was actually because it looks kinda like Half-Life's format with the text and all.  Expect from this blog random comments, updates on my oh-so-hated life, and reviews of various stuff I find cool or stupid. Well, until next time...  (Oh, feel free to post comments or insult me here too.)
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow.  It's been awhile since I've updated this.  Musically speaking, I've acquired an Incubus CD, the 12 Stones CD, and Under my Skin with Avril.  Yeah, I'm listening to pop now.  And, I really like some of it.  Plus the fact that I'm turning into a crybaby.  I mean, I like never cry.  And driving home from work, listening to My Immortal then switching to Nobody's Home just... man.  I'm heading for a nervous breakdown or something.  I can't think of any other possible reason.  It's like all my emotions are actually showing themselves occasionally.  Like I was closing windows and thinking about something (a couple people) and I found myself slamming the windows down I was getting so angry.  Actually, just thinking about what I was thinking about then gets me mad... CHANGE SUBJECT!!!  Well, I love my job since the cleaning thing kind of fell through.  Turns out then only needed like 2 people like twice a week to actually clean.  They hired 4 people.  So... I now can work full time in the tech shop there if I want too.  YES!!!  That's actually fun.  So, That's what I've been doing with my work.  I've figured out I have made about $1,500-$1,800 by the end of the summer, at about $200 a week.  I'm looking at this nice Dell laptop, I could get a $1,700 model or a $2,300 model.  Trying to figure out whether to get a cheaper one that I can just buy or make payments on a better one.  I'm hoping that this machine will last me the first 2 years of college, which is why I'm tempted to get the more expensive one.  Had an AWESOME time Saturday, even though I got into MAJOR TROUBLE!!!  I went over to that girls house, let's call her... hmmm.... I'm got three choices... let me see... which would be the least known... yeah.  "ae"  You'd have to know her to get that, and then you'd probably know who I was already, so I'm safe.  Ok.  So, I went to the library to run errands.  I had made it so that we'd "accidentally" bump into each other there.  I almost wasn't able to go because of my mom, but I did some wrangling so I was able to go.  They thought I was going to the video store, K-mart, and the library.  2 hours tops, is what she said she had thought after I gotten home.  I went there, and I didn't even think of getting my books after he started talking.  I got there at 12:30.  The library closed at 3:00.  The librarian told us it was time to go, so since she had left her wallet in her other car I let her use mine.  We both really didn't feel like ending the conversation, so I asked if she knew anywhere we could continue.  Her house was only like 5 minutes away, turns out we live basically just down the road from each other and never knew it.  So, I went over to her place, and stayed until about 8:45.  Had dinner, chatted for what seemed like 10 minutes or so.  Oh My Gosh.  I was in so big trouble, especially since I didn't call, and it was a girl's house.  CRAZY.  Well, I'll talk more later.  Though I really hope she'll be on tonight...
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That was interesting.  Just as I finished the title, I heard a sound behind me.  In the kitchen.  Sounded like water.  Dripping.  Dripping into a small pool, in fact.  I decided to investigate.  Turns out our ceiling is leaking again.  There's some soft of plumbing problem with the upstairs sink, which my dad will fix, but it will start leaking again later.  It varies how long the repair lasts, but the leaking is still rare enough to be unusual.  My dad's fixing it now as I type.  I'd just get in the way, probably break it more.  He won't hire a plumber because last time he did for something around here he got ripped off bad.  So, wait, I think he just got it fixed.  Okay.  Problem solved, thanks to... my dad's mad skillz, I guess.  Probably.  Just watched another movie.  It's nice having a brother who works 4-5 days out of the week at a full-time job earning $10 bucks a hour.  The lousy part is, I’m 17, and he’s 15.  I make $5.75 an hour working sporadically at BOCES.  Well, at least he doesn't know what to do with his money yet.  That's good.  Not for him, but for me.  He still won't submit to my wishes on finance completely, though.  And he still refers to my by that annoying nickname, "*B"  * for my name, B for Bankrupt.  Even though I always beat him at monopoly.  Actually, I'm pretty good at that game.  I usually win regardless.  Unless the other players gang up against me.  Especially if there girls.  Then I lose.  Badly.  Why I'm rambling about things I just talked about yesterday I don't know.  Probably because that's what on my mind, though why I don't know.  Today I tried to pull a crazy juggling act.  I was going to go to this party that the girl that I've been talking with on the net might go to with her boyfriend.  It started at 2, and went on who knows how long.  I was planning to go to that, that's all.  Then another friend of mine, who happens to be a girl, calls me that morning around 11.  She invites me to a music festival up past Oneonta "about an hour away from your place."  It's from 1-7.  I'm like, Sure!  Sound's great.  I'll be their a little later.  So, my plan is to go to the party for a hour or two, or three, however long it lasts, as long as it's not too late, then go to the music festival until it ends.  Sounds great, right?  So, at 11:30, my mom tells me that I have to be home to baby-sit by 4, 4:30 at the absolute latest.  Ohh...keyyy.  Not good.  Not good at all.  So I ask a good friend of mine who happened to be on the net at that time what he though I should do. So, I followed his idea pretty much to the letter.  His AIM is YamiArashi88, if you want to get some advice from him.  Oh, and for deep stuff advice, check out someone else.  You have to ask me to find out who they are, though.  Oh, and don't ask them what my real name is.  They won't tell you.  But if you ask, even though they won't tell you, I'll still figure out who YOU are and hunt you down and bring my Beretta and... sorry.  Got a little carried away.  I prefer to remain anonymous down here.  Unless you already know me.  Then it's your own problem.  Sorry.  Can't help you with that.  Unless you just happen to be a friend.  I have some of those.  They are nice.  Really nice to have.  Why am I rambling?  STOP!  Well, back to the topic at hand.  So, I go to the music festival first.  I leave so that I'll be there about 1.  Yeah, right.  Turns out she (the girl who told me about it) takes the back roads to get there.  And she said  about  an hour.  I get there about 1:45.  And I was going about 75 thee whole way.  In a 65 zone.  With police officers all over the place looking for drunk drivers.  Fortunally, I was a happy criminal.  So, I stayed there about 1/2 hour.  The music was ok, not my style, but good for country/gospel.  Plus I had a nice conversation with the girl who I haven't talked to since the Darien Lake thing.  So I leave there about 2:15, 2:20.  I drive at 80-85 back to Sidney, passing a car crash where a horse trailer had tipped over.  Don't worry, everyone and the horse was ok, the owner had it safely over to the side, but there was hay spilled everywhere.  Ok, just got back from being AFK a second ago.  Was making a snack.  Nachos with salsa and sour cream.  Mmm, sour cream.  Salsa is good; I just like the liquid stuff, not the chunks.  The chunks are ok, just not that good, at least to me.  STOP!  I'm rambiling yet again.  Why?  I'm nuts, no, even better, I'm ODD!  Well, I got to where the party was about 4:05.  Yeah, late.  I saw a few cars there, but not the girl who might have been there's car.  It's pretty identifiable, since the right external mirror is shorn clean off.  Nice green... something, don't really know cars.  I know what it looks like, but I can't tell you what it is.  So, since I didn't see her car, I went home, arriving at 4:18.  I probably was speeding, but by then I didn't care.  I haven’t heard from her yet, so she's probably was or is at her boyfriends apartment near Albany that he shares with some other guys.  I want to meet this guy, he sounds pretty cool from the way she describes him.  Well, she  is  probably biased.  Correction.  Not probably, IS biased.  He still sounds cool.  I'll have to see if I can "accidentally" run into them sometime in town.  I love accidents.  That kind, at least.  Not the normal kind.  Planned accidents are so much better.  SO much better.  Um... I promised content, but what you got was basically an update on my existence, which doesn't really matter unless you're me or get some soft of kick from reading someone else's ramblings.  So, here's my mini-review of Max Payne.  Max Payne:  Graphics: 8/10 Great for a third person shooter.  The particle effects are what make it all so cool.  Environments are a bit blocky and flat, though.  The graphic novel scenes are well illustrated, too.  Sound: ?/10 I am not going to rate sound, because I have no freaking clue to what to measure up against.  But, I will say, the heartbeat effect is really cool when you're in Bullet Time.  Level design: 7/10 While for the most part it seems constant (you spend WAY too much time in a hotel with the same dirty pictures and ads in EVERY FREAKING ROOM!!!), every once in awhile you'd get something really cool (the burning restaurant comes to mind, as well as the other hotel you get to go in, the one with the bombs blowing up.  Oh, and the lobby.  That is my favorite fight in the whole game.  Totally.) that makes the game memorable.  Equipment Varity: 6/10 About normal for your FPS, you have 2 melee weapons (lead pipe and baseball bad), 2 pistols (Desert eagle and Beretta), 2 shotguns (pump-action and sawed-off), 2 automatics (Colt Commando, an automatic rifle, and Ingram, a Uzi thingy that I KNOW I've seen before... in the Matrix), 1 sniper rifle, and 2 grenades (regular and Molotov Cocktails).  Nothing special, but you can dual-wield the Beretta and the Ingram, which is cool.  Bullet time using dual Ingram’s is the coolest FPS moment I think I've ever had.  Ever.  And that's saying a lot.  For me, at least.  Storyline: 9/10 This is what makes or breaks a game for me, usually.  Almost always, unless I'm in the mood for a mindless FPS.  The plot is excellent, if you like the gangster kind of stuff.  Or just the dark "film noir" style of it all.  That's what attracts me.  I feel this guy's pain as he just loses it all, then strikes back, at first aimlessly, then with purpose.  Single-minded near suicidal purpose, but that's ok.  I like it. A lot.  Gameplay: 6/10 If it wasn't for the fact that I usually hate and will refuse to play 3d person shooters, I'd give it a lot better rating.  I understand that all the cool visual and gameplay effects would be impossible without the view the way it is, but I still suck at it.  It's hard to aim, though I am getting better.  I die wayyy to easy, too.  There is a good deal of trial and error in this game until you get good at using the bullet-time feature to bail you out.  The special gameplay effects, namely, bullet-time, are what MAKE this game.  Without it, it would just be another 3d person shooter in the bargain bin.  I mean, the rest of the game is cool, but bullet-time is what sets this game apart.  I'll stop ranting now on this totally AWSOME feature.  Replayability: 7/10 Why am I giving this game such a high rating?  Because no other game is like it, and while it's decently long, it still felt a little short too me.  Plus, you unlock each difficulty level as you beat the one right below it!  Now if that isn't a shameless attempt to try to make you play this game again, I don't know what is.  Overall: 8/10 This game is awesome.  I recommend buying it.  I mean, at $10-15 buck at your local Wal-Mart, what's to lose?  Either you love it or hate it.  Try the demo first... if there is one.  Not sure.  I always try demos first... unless I can borrow a copy from a friend.  Like I'm doing with this game.  I hope he doesn’t want it back anytime soon...  OK guys.  It's late.  I need to go to bed.  Church today, then a picnic.  Must... sleep. Night!
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I promised one.  Here you go.  Bye!
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I did get my new bedroom.  Even though it looks like World War III since it's still under constant rearranging.  Nice, though.  I just got the Evanescence CD, Fallen.  It's awesome!  The singer is awesome, and the mix of rock and classical styles just, just, it's awesome.  Listen to them!!!  I know I need to keep my promise and post the review for Max Payne and Half-Life, but I'm having too much fun playing them again to do it yet.  Plus, I'm just lazy.  Oh, I have a new favorite word.  Odd.  Yep, Odd.  That's me.  If I really exist, that is.  Never mind.  Driving is fun.  Very fun.  If you are wondering why I'm acting/typing so weird, it's because I'm in a hurry.  Someone is going to be visiting this site and shaking their head, and I want to throw on some content quick.  Which is turning out to be pretty lame.  So, I'll end here and add some real content tomorrow.  I promise.  Really!
    
</post>


</Blog>