<Blog>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Penny Arcade  is the coolest online comic in the world. There i said it. they have a bunch of cool products at their  urlLink online store  btw. buy it! its good.    out 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ive been trying to bamboozle my mom into buying me a new computer, but not to any avail as of yet. She is weakening though. When i get it im gonna install gentoo as ive said be4 but slackware 10 just came out and it seems pretty nifty. ill decide later. I think im gonna goto hobby lobby today and get some model paints; i have a truck i wanna finish. its a good hobby and kills time like you wouldnt believe. Its great fun to do. I highly reccomend it too. also, i found the best wallpaper site for hotties in the world. it literally has thousands of wallpapers with girls ranging from carmen electra to nikki nova, the porn star. its  urlLink www.skins.be  . i highly reccomend it.    out.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going to get a new computer come hell or high water.  urlLink Main Pc Usa  has a build your own system thing with really cheap parts and the comp i wanna get is like 354 dollars. When it comes, im gonna put  urlLink slackware  on it. i just found out that slackware 10.0 is gonna be released really really soon. thats gonna be my new distro methinks. Ill hafta keep a watch at  urlLink distrowatch.com  and see for the official release date.   out.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey. i just thought id make another post. Ive been using mandrake linux for a while now, and its okay. I would reccommend it to a newcomer to linux, but im thinking about switching to  urlLink slackware  or maybe  urlLink gentoo.  i hear that gentoo is pretty hard to get the hang of, but i like the idea of emerge. in fact, i think that other distros should incorporate something along the lines of many packages and programs available for download on one source. Ive been looking for a  urlLink gmail  account invite for a while as well. I think that a gig of space for email is pretty cool. However, ive also heard about them scanning your mail to tailor ads to your taste, and although it would be good that you wouldnt get random ads, i dont like the idea of somebody reading my mail. Still, the `1GB sounds really tempting. i hear that  urlLink spymac  also has 1GB mailboxes, but lacks the sleek and easy to use interface of gmail. I also hear that many "active" bloggers are getting invitations.   ttyl  mako
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi. this is my first blog that ive had. I look forward to bloggin, and in the meantime, vistit http://www.slashdot.org  ttyl   Mako
     

    
</post>


</Blog>