<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      today well im counting the days katie comes home from the bday party that my mom would let me go to because i had a hyposlimck attack  wich is 1 more day mom tells me today that i have an orto apptment tomarow now she tell me man i yelled at her for that and i might have inprtions done too man i hate thoes i woke up thins morning forgitting its fathers day and i started reading in bed and my dad comes in at ten or so and he tell me to stop reading so he can open his prezents(they whernt even raped dad shesh and i was there when mom bout them) when i came out they where wahing that retared rogger rabbit movie and i come out with a bodders bag and hes gits a sctv dvd thing and a book witha a naked barby on it   ohh and my nabors had a nother party today again that the 3ed on in a roe made snot bubbles today i hate beeing sick  at dinner after i finnish my ice cream i took a napkin and put it on my head and i called my self the pope and told every one god bless you and jeasus loves you lol my mom sayes i cant be a pope becaue im not a old guy and im a athist whereing my uatarin shirt humm i soud like i hate every thing  mood- pised at my mom what im whereing jeans and my untarin shirt and a pots-it saying eat me on my forhead
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well im a 13 year old athist and invermontlist my name is emily but i call me self packman i have lots of problems like anxity problems and ADD and hyposlima i used blogger logg back before it was bout by google for fun with my friend for a jounal for are neopets it lasted a week :D im 5.1" and i am the skinnyest girl in the 8th grade 85 pounds ohh and i live in a city off the cost of the san fransico bay area uhumm thats all i can tink of right now 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i was talking to my frined katie today and asked her if she wanted staff anbd she sayed yes if it was protcted so its protected  more personal info tonight 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i had to go tho the ortho and i had exrays done and they are dumb bunnys there they thought i was gitting a retaner sheesh what are they smoking   then i yelled at my mom there so i have to go there again the 7th weee
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so any ways my sister got head gear then yesderday the people came to clean my house then we whent out and had lunch and whyent to sportsmart to get new shes my sister needed new ones more than i did so i was just looking and my mom insisted that  needed sandles I DIDNT WANT ANY DAM SANDLES WHEN WOULD I HAVE TIME TO WHERE THEM THIS SUMMER???? so she chooses some after i sayed no 6 billon times i didnt want to scream it because we where in public so i left her in the store i hid by the sports bras untill haley found me she sayed i was in deep dodo and she was with my mom who had some realy ugly sandles and i told her once more no sandles sho she like fine bu your in truble and if u dont want them put them back so i did but i didnt get in truble at all  last night was fun anna maya and kitie and i drew up dresses for tyheses boys wedding lane pactrick and victors and vivans wedding it was fun    i had x rays taken today my head still hirts they where somany stin teddy bares there   pokemon rules  dont support this  mode - 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No one to talk to today.  I'm so lonely!:( I got my passport today.  The pix is so ugly.  I found these smillys its soo cute       Or at least intertaning. i found out today that blogger is not family frendly wich buggs me     mood-   sorry for the somany smillyes
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I JUTS FOUND OUT KATIE IS AT SOME CAMP WITH ANNA AND MAYA AND NO ONE TOLD ME MAYAS FRIEND ALLISON HAD TO TELL ME GRR IM SO MAD AND REALLY UPSET I WAS A LITTLE UPSET WHEN I FOUND OUT SHE WAS "OUT OF TOWN" FROM HER MOM  then my mom bout me sandles omg i cant bleave her i told her no sandles then she gives them to haley grrrr i hate her for doing that  then the sandles are 2 sizes diff lol NOT so she has to return them now   happy gay pride week ohh and tgif  THINGS TO DO  1 KILL KATIE FOR NOT TELLING ME ANY THING ABOUT HER LITTLE TRIP 2 PACK FOR TAHOE  3 KILL KATIE  4 STOP CRYING   moode -  and      reading -princes diries II
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i found out last night that my cousen allison is going to come this summer in agust im so happy because its just her and my anut   still no contact with katie i relay need to talk too her about ysc and stuff   im doing a peper for my guild on neopets no one has applied yet if i cound contact katie she would help   things i need to do 1 get a hold of katie 2 start packing 3 get people to apply to the newspaper 4 pack stuff to do on the way to tahoe  moode-  books reading princes diriess II
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      me and katie are good now i go back form tahoe yesderday i never stoped lafing  mia is the funest girl i ever met  i started ysc today it was fun i thought i was going to be like last time with some stuped boy and i didnt know any one   ------------------   Preserve wildlife! Adopt a plushie otter today!  ohh and i am reading princess n wating
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wow i havent entered in this for a long time  well i have been verry bissy we are leaving for england weds  katie sleeped over and then i sleeped over and saw sam i havent seen her in years victora still has her little winny tone when she talks it drives me crazy grrr im curntly doing ysc and its way to tiring i sleep all day i have become ubsest with pokemon again and i found out im gitting brases in agust    what happend to the rating EC for early childhood now im finding games like dora explora that are rated E it scarry   my pokemon team (i coulnt find any more so if you know of some cute pokemon pix please leave a comment)  urlLink   border="0" alt="I adopted an Umbreon Plushie!">  urlLink   border="0" alt="I adopted a Latios Plushie!">   daly quiz      Which Band Should You Be In?  by  urlLink  couplandesque        Your Name           Band Name    Radiohead       Role    Drummer       Trademark    Punk Rock Fashion Sense      Love Interest    The Drummer              Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
           Whats does your personality rate from 1-10? by  urlLink  morning_prayer        Your first full name           Your personality rates a    nine      your best quality is    youre a sweetheart      your worst quality is    nothing! lucky you ;)      this is because    other people influenced you             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
           Who were you in a past life?  by  urlLink  Kat007        Name:           Birthdate:           Favorite Color:           Country:           You were most probably:    Edgar Allan Poe       If not then you were:    A pretty little flower               urlLink  Quiz created with MemeGen  !      soo funny 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i did so much i dont know what to say  humm lets see the tub is fun and umm well i lets just say im a little jetlagged right now i fell asleep a 5 yesderday and woke up at 2 am and im so tired and bord anna and maya are in orgen and i havent talked to katie at all
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i found out last week that i needed wisdome teeth pulled ect well i found out on wes how they pull them eww im realy nurvis becuase im getting them pulled(and 3 of my 12 year molers and 1 moler that you get after your 12 molers) tomarow at 9:50   we whent to thae beer and crap festivle i mean festivle of the arts  it realy bad freebies every where
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      change of  date he he i had my wisdom teeth pulled today and the stiches are driving mr crazy and i keep felling holes in my mouth meep! i got them pulled at 8 and my top lip is still numb and its 4 here well i gess i get to show off that i had stiches in 4 differnt plases and i hvae a cool scar where my iv was  and i got to wach bbc america all day lol;)        What Instrument SHOULD You Be Playing?  by Jazzy_K      Your Name           Your Age           What You Play Now           What You SHOULD Play    Drums              urlLink  Quiz created with MemeGen  !      yay i allways wanted to play the drums
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      got a kitty yesderday 8 weeks old she was bottle fed when she was little lucy loves her she picked her up and got in big trubble bad dog  i saw prinsess driess very disaponted because lilly didnt have a big part but it was cute  almost froze katies hamster and when  katie loged on aim i was eating pasta i was gone for an half and hour im so stuped so stuped *crys some more*  im ubsetsed with graphix now hence the link go there i tell u   - mode depresd reading-nothing realy finninshed all the prinesses books got to wait till cristmas
     

    
</post>


</Blog>