<Blog>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi and welcome to my first 'Blog' entry. I thought long and hard about my first entry, since I want to make it a good one. I debated on where to start, so I guess first off I'll give you a little insight into what to expect from my blog entries and who I am.  Some characteristics that one might choose to describe me are: sarcastic, observant, movie fanatic (esp. classics circa 30's/40's, horror and suspense), sardonic, hopeful and a 'closet optimist.'   Let me preface my entries with these helpful nuggets-o-insight: For those who may be considering reading my blogs, you might wanna brush up on your pop culture references. Mainly 70's and 80's. I love pop culture in all its' guises, so like my real-life conversations, I'll most likely be using it in my blogs as well. Also, I tend to ramble from time to time, about things that may otherwise ordinarily seem mundane. I'll be the first to admit I don't have much of a life, so no surprises there. So, if you are looking for high adventures via rock climbing expeditions, kayaking down a mighty river, or recent sexual escapades, you may want to keep on searching for that person's blog, 'cause that ain't me. I'm perfectly content renting movies, buying things I can't live without on eBay and enjoying delicious Chinese meals with the newspaper and my trusty (possibly now obsolete) journal. So, if you crave the frustrating misadventures of someone else's life, the occasional frustrating social interaction with the random idiot and rants about how I was awakened from a deep sleep by a strolling Jehovah Witness wearing a powder blue suit, then settle in! You've found your niche!  And last, but certainly not least, I'd also like to give a 'shout out' to the woman who inspired my delving into the world of blogging and made this all possible: Joy Gohring (AKA "Jane" from my new favorite TV show 'Good Girls Don't...'). I stumbled across "Jane's Blog" yesterday, read some of the entries and was hooked. She's just hilarious. I love  urlLink Jane  (but not in a creepy Single White Female kinda way). In the immortal words of Nina Simone, don't let me be misunderstood. I have no ties with Joy or the TV show "Good Girls Don't...," or the Oxygen channel for that matter. I'm just a fan who's been inspired to set aside his old spiral bound notebook/journal and blog away online, instead. So, thanks 'Jane' for making me laugh and inspiring me to finally start writing more and to never ever steal an ex-boyfriend's TiVo....unless I have a really good grasp before I pull it outta the wall. I'll never forget you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I have what I consider to be an extensive collection of books, movies and music, I've decided that my weekend blog entries will consist of book, movie and music recommendations and/or reviews. Today's blog is going to be about some of my favorite "kitsch" books. *Keep in mind that some, but not all of my books may currently be out of print. This doesn't necessarily mean you can't find them, you just may have to be a little more creative in where you look. I suggest used bookstores, thrift stores or online sites such as  urlLink Half.com , Amazon.com or even eBay.    My first book recommendation is   Roseanne Roseannadanna's "Hey, Get Back To Work!" Book , by Alan Zweibel & Gilda Radner. © 1983. Softcover.   If you are a fan of  urlLink Gilda Radner  or her Saturday night Live character, Roseanne Roseannadanna, then you will LOVE this book. The hilarious stories, articles and reminiscences are only compounded by the scrapbook-style photographs, cartoons, charts, etc. One of my favorite anecdotes is the "In Memory Of" portion, some of which I'll relay here:  General George Patton, my pet parakeet that died when I was fourteen years old, but it really wasn't my fault. Sure, I was the one who let him outta his cage 'cause he looked like he needed some exercise. And sure, I was the one that was makin' whole wheat toast in the kitchen 'cause I felt like I needed the roughage. Okay. Okay. I also gotta admit that I was the one that made the pitcher of  urlLink Kool-Aid  to help the roughage flush outta my system anythin' that mighta been lyin' aroun' in there. But I  wasn't  the one that rang the doorbell that made me leave the kitchen to go answer the door. The delivery boy did that. And I wasn't the one that told General George Patton to fly on to the toaster, or to lick one of those hot toaster coils, or to start chirpin' for help, or to stiffen his little body, or to fall dead into my pitcher of Kool-Aid. He did that all by himself.     My other book is   Philip Garner's Better Living Catalog: 62 Absolute Necessities For Contemporary Survival . © 1982. Softcover.  I can't put into words how cool I think this book is. The book consists primarily of images of wacky, surreal and dare I say  genius , inventions.  A few of my personal favorites: Shower In A Can, The Half-Suit, The TeeVee Chair, The Chevrolounge, Dashboard Desk, Tacoradio and the Pet-A-Vision. So crazy, you gotta see em' to really appreciate em'. Highly recommended!   Other books I recommend, include:  The Wonder Book of Sex. By Glen Baxter. © 1995. Hardcover Monkey vs Robot. By James Kochalka. © 2000. Softcover Greetings From This Modern World. By Tom Tomorrow. © 1992. Softcover Doc Phantom. By Jay Stephens. © 2003. Softcover. Graphic Novel Hey Skinny! By Miles Beller & Jerry Leibowitz. © 1995. Softcover
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to a "gay"  urlLink coffee house/book store  tonight. I know, you're saying to yourself "Coffee has a gender?" Sure! Why not? We live in a world where people like Ashton Kutcher are considered actors, so why can't our coffee have a "sexual preference"...at least for the purpose of this blog. And by "gay" I mean that the establishment is in a predominately gay neighborhood, thus frequently by predominantly gay cliental. Not  urlLink Gen Y 's "gay" which seems to be what they consider just about anything that they aren't familiar with. Here's by observations from last night, as transcribed from my journal:  Two very thin, but cute guys are sitting across from me signing. Very peaceful, interesting and somehow  sexy . Makes me wonder if the situation ever arose, would/could I date a  urlLink deaf  guy. I think I would. I guess, like anything else, it would depend on the individual. Seems like anytime I have seen deaf gay men in this area, they seem to travel in little groups (Mental note: Do a group of gay men have a name? You know, like a murder of crows or a gaggle of geese? Hmm. How about "pod?"....no, that's whales I think. I know! Let's refer to them as a " globe " of gay deaf men. 'g' to signify the gay aspect and 'lobe' as an ear reference. I like it!). So, anyway, this one time I saw this  globe  of guys hanging out in front of this gay bar (I call them all bars, not "clubs") and they were acting REALLY whorey, which kinda caught me by surprise. I guess I never think about there being deaf whores. I digress. The two deaf guys begin taking turns writing their conversation down on a small wirebound notepad, which they are passing back and forth to each other across the table. This is what I'm wondering: Does the owner of the pad keep the pages with the conversation on it after they're through? Or does he simply throw them away? I'm tempted to ask, but I don't want to appear insane. It's just the idea of being able to conjure up old conversation with someone, a 'hardcopy' if you will, intrigues me. I can just imagine a box at home filled with used notepads, napkins, flyers, with stuff scribbled on them, like: "Frank Bradford: July 1983" You could never really "forget" a memory because you would always be able to refer back to it. On the down side, though, I guess it could also be kinda depressing or even incriminating.  Ooh, look, W.A.S.P. Boys in Da 'Hood. Your "street cred" kinda goes out the window when you see some really fruity guy in a do-rag, who weighs 80lbs say " aight " or " peace out ." I don't get it. Reminds me of that time in college, in history class when the  urlLink sorority  chick behind me told her pal Lemon Spongecake or whatever her name was, "don't be dissin' me." That SO doesn't work. It's official. Some people are just  urlLink TOO white . *Mental note: Do NOT order the papaya tea ever again. Gag. This stuff tastes like licorice and bug repellent.  Now that's just creepy. It's around 10:30 and a little kid (9 or 10? I never know with kids.) just walked by, on his way to the bathroom. What's THAT about? I mean, he doesn't appear to be with anyone (i.e. a parent/guardian). That's just wrong. What kind of parent let's their kid wander around the neighborhood and hang out in a gay bookstore at this time of night? I mean, Sesame Street this ain't....unless Mr. Hooper was in reality a bold n' sassy pothead with a penchant for concealer. Nah.  Lol! As I was walking to my car, there's these 3 people (2 guys and a girl...I wanna say "fag hag" but the term always kinda turned me off. I guess because I never really got the whole "hag" aspect.) talking as their getting into their car and one of the guys is saying " ...you know? I mean if you're going to be my friend...be... " then the other guy and girl say in unison (as if on the same wavelength) " real! " And he's like " yeah! " (They SO 'get' him! Deep). The irony? These people "keepin' it real" all have on enough skin care products to choke a gay moose. Plus: dyed hair, strategically placed baseball caps,  urlLink Hot Topic  wardrobe and generic Celtic/barbed wire/ urlLink XXX -style bicep tattoos and misc. nose/eyebrow/tongue piercings....getting into a friggin' Jeep Cherokee. Way to go  urlLink Stepford  clones. If it gets any more "real" the cookie cutter might just burst. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, here's the situation. I live in a neighborhood that has LOTS of big, old trees. My backyard has about 5 BIG trees. I make a concerted effort to keep my yard up to par, even though my philosophy is "I'm not  urlLink Tarzan , I don't live outside. Who really cares?" But since the people on either side of me have the same yard men who take care of their yards, I keep things looking neat.   Well, apparently my leaves have become a source of contempt for the withered ol'  urlLink Sea Monkey  who lives next door. For the sake of this post, let's refer to her as "Ms. Fossil." Ms. Fossil has a history of being obsessed by the misc. leaves that enter her yard via natural causes, like wind and autumn. She's even been so kind as to inform me that she intends on planting a hedge between our two houses, in hopes of putting an end to this dark evil. "Not because of your leaves," she tells me, but because of "the neighborhood's leaves that blow into her yard." The hedge has yet to be planted, primarily because she's a tightwad.   So, about 2 weeks ago I get a phone call from her. She opens the conversation with "This is Ms. Fossil. Have you eaten yet?" So, since we have exchanged misc. food over the years, I think to myself "Oh. She made a tablespoon too much of something and wants to bring it over." (What is it with old people and portions, anyway? Just an observation.) So I tell her no, that I'm actually about to head out to go eat lunch. She then goes on to tell me she has "bad news." According to her, the  urlLink tree  in my backyard has got to be cut down. My first thought is "Oh. It's diseased." Then she chimes in with how there are life-threatening dead branches falling from my tree into her yard, near her storage house and how it's not something I will be able to take care of myself, but instead, a job for a "professional." First off, this is not the first time she's pulled this routine. I've personally removed dead branches once before, and in my defense, they were not bone-crushingly huge, nor were they plentiful. I'm prepared to accept responsibility for my tree, but let's leave the drama to the thespians, okay?. My first reaction is she's been huffing  urlLink Pledge  too long, if she thinks I am cutting down a huge tree in my yard because she has nothing better to do with her time, but keep a running tab on how many leaves/branches fall on her property. BUT I will look into getting the branches removed.   She then goes on to tell me how she was initially going to write a letter to my parents about the problem, but thought she would call me first. I told her "Well, that's good, since I'm the one who actually lives here." *She's notorious for flagging my parents down when they visit and regaling them with tales of woe. And because they are from the generation that thinks all the elderly automatically deserve our respect (I'm from the school of "Respect is earned. Not a birthright"), they fall for her frail old lady routine, and I come out looking like the irrational asshole. DJ Jazzy Jeff was right, parents just don't understand.  Anyway, I tell her that I will work on getting some estimates and get it taken care of ASAP. She then goes on to explain that the reason she asked if I'd eaten yet, was because that was some old proverb referring to "Never give a man bad news on an empty stomach." I say "neat" and she pulls a Foghorn Leghorn on me and says "It's a joke, son." I say "Okay. Was that all?," she says yes and we go on to lead separate lives, just like Phil Collins always wanted.  In the meantime, I get out the ol' phonebook and write down the names and numbers of all the tree trimming services that offer free estimates and are insured and certified. I start calling them, one by one, to make appointments. The first 3, no answer. The 4th one answers and I make an appt. Fifth and 6th are answering machines. Seventh recommends someone else (what's THAT about?) and the 8th one is booked for a month. Made appt. with the 9th one. So, even though I don't want to, I call Ms. Fossil and let her know that I am working on remedying the problem, HOWEVER it may take 3-4 weeks for some of them to come out and give me an estimate, due to extensive workloads, because of the recent storms. She's says "That's fine. I'm not in any hurry as long as it gets done." To which, I politely say "Bite me" (okay, not really), and we end the conversation.  So, the first guy comes out the same week that I called, and wants $275 for both the trimming and the carrying away (I have some piles of branches/brush). Two weeks pass. I'm on the way to my car to run some errands and what do I see out the corner of my eye, but Ms. Fossil shuffling towards me. She says "What have you heard about the tree?" I tell her I'm waiting on some estimates. She says "What?" (She has selective hearing too. Precious.) I repeat what I said and she then goes on to tell me how it's still dropping dead branches and how her yard man is getting older (yeah, 24's a real turning point in the annals of health) and can't keep bending to pick them all up and how my tree drops lots of leaves, etc. etc. I reassure her that it's being taken care of, but she won't let up, instead opting to continue repeating what she's already said. I start to make a mental check list in my head of anything I might be forgetting, before I leave: Car keys? check. Driver's License? check.  urlLink Check book ? check. Grocery list? check. Cell phone? check. Did I lock the door? check. I snap out of it when a car drives by and honks (I live near a busy street) and she's in the middle of her oral report on the life-altering effects of leaves. I shortly, but sweetly, tell her "Trees have leaves and there's lots of trees in our neighborhood. I'll have the tree trimmers pick up any and all dead branches that my tree has dropped. I'm working on getting it taken care of." She's still on autopilot, so I say "byyye."  Estimate #2 came out today, after a 20 minute phone call with someone who's first language was apparently NOT English. Five of those minutes were spent dealing with actual business, the rest were filled with me repeating, spelling and sounding out my name, address, phone number and directions. Just when I thought I was gonna have to resort to semaphore flags, he correctly repeats my information and schedules a time. He'll be here between 3:30 and 4:30. Fine.   Four o'clock rolls around and I get a phone call. He's lost, and driving with the cell phone (double yikes), supposedly nearby. He quadruple checks the address and directions and says he should be here shortly. Fast forward 30 minutes. He's still lost. I'm close to the point of not caring, when he mentions a nearby landmark (a mere 3 minutes away). Eureka! We've made contact! Jesus Christ. So now he's REALLY on his way and will be here shortly. Half an hour later, he shows up. He gives me an estimate that's roughly $200 higher than my first estimate. I smile and say "Thanks for coming out. Bye bye." He drives away. So, we have just one more estimate to go. According to him, he'll "probably" be here Friday or Saturday, or if not, Sunday. I'm on the edge of my seat! Stay tuned!   If trees could scream, would we be so cavalier about cutting them down?  We might, if they screamed all the time, for no good reason.   ~Jack Handey
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Normally, I not that big of a TV watcher. By that I mean, there's rarely a TV show that I watch on a regular basis (besides  urlLink The Daily Show  &  urlLink Nip/Tuck ). Not since  urlLink Twin Peaks  or  urlLink American Gothic  have I consistently kept up with a television show. I usually just watch movies on  urlLink DVD  or VHS. However, lately I have discovered (and rediscovered) some new and old favorites.  For example, I now get up every morning at 6, to watch Buffy The Vampire Slayer. When news of the show first started circulating, I remember joking with friends at the time about how/why in the world were they gonna make a series based on a movie that tanked to begin with? Then the show began, and I was hooked...initially. LOVED the first season: Sexy  urlLink Xander  (Nicholas Brendon..who has an identical twin brother, BTW...ROWR-rowr!), bookworm Willow (Alyson Hannigan) and of course, vampires! LOVED the second season (Hello  urlLink Spike ! ROWR!). Season 3, still diggin' it...then came Season 4 with its' bullshit underground military lair storyline. So not interested. Bye bye, sleepy now. So, anyway, the FX channel started showing back-to-back episodes at 6AM, so I started watching, initially due to insomnia. As it turned out, I got in on the beginning of the end, season 7. Thus my rekindled love affair with Buffy. Now I gotta catch up with Season 5 & 6.  So, besides Buffy, I have some NEW favorites, one of which I mentioned in my first post:  urlLink Good Girls Don't...  It's my most recent "can't miss" show. The show airs on the Oxygen channel and was created by the people who brought us That 70's Show (another favorite of mine). I love the whole cast from GGD and the situations they find themselves in. Joy Gohring and Kevin Christy are just about the sexiest, funniest (even more important than sexy) things on TV.   Since I've been watching GGD, I've started to pay more attention to some of Oxygen's other shows: Show Me Yours, Bliss and Talk Sex/The Sunday Night Sex Show. I initially shied away from Show Me Yours, because I assumed it would be a poor man's Red Shoe Diaries and because one of the main actors kinda gives me the creeps: Adam Harrington (he plays co-author Benjamin Chase Ph.D). I'd seen him before in the 80's homage slasher  Valentine . I'm sure he's a perfectly nice guy and all, but he reminds me of a  urlLink llama  with a rigorous skin care regime. I dunno why. So anyway, if you can get past that visual, the show is actually pretty well done. The synopsis (via the website) is as follows:  Sexual tension fuels this steamy, romantic comedy, about a woman researching a book on sexual practices and the two men in her life: one, her often-difficult boyfriend, and the other, her increasingly irresistible co-author.  I think that's one temptation I could resist.  Bliss is another show that I'm slowly warming up to. The format is relatively simple: A different erotic story each week, from a woman's perspective. I say "women's perspective" because all the stories have been adapted by women screenwriters and directors. To be honest, I don't get that turned on by the Zalman King-style "erotica," but the stories and characters make up for that. But hey, that's just me. Maybe if I was a straight man, it'd have more impact, it's just fun to watch.  And the last show from Oxygen, that I have fallen in love with, is Talk Sex and The Sunday Night Sex Show, both hosted by renowned sex educator Sue Johanson. I enjoy our local talk radio station as well as the online station  urlLink Mystery Play Internet Radio  (they play all those old Mystery and Thriller radio programs from the 40's and 50's), so Sue's show was a natural for me.  Since the show topic(s) are pretty much dictated by the callers, you never know where the subject matter is gonna go next. Much more interesting to me than the Gen Y version: Loveline. Sue's show has more diversity and substance.  And while we're on the subject of television shows, lots of them are being released to DVD lately: Punky Brewster, Dukes of Hazzard, Wonder Woman, and even Nip/Tuck. HOWEVER, there are plenty of shows that HAVEN'T been released to DVD, that I, personally, would LOVE to see. Such as: Square Pegs, Facts of Life, American Gothic, Duckman and  urlLink John Doe , just to name a few. I was excited to find out that the following shows are heading to DVD this year: ALF: Season 1- Aug. 10, Laverne & Shirley: Season 1-Aug. 17th and Night Gallery: Season 1- Aug. 24!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, that's right. I said it. Sure, I've been aware of the whole "low carb" fad since the bunless Whopper was introduced at Burger King. Since then we've been inundated with Subway's "Low Carb Wraps," low carb Pepsi Edge, low-carb, genetically-engineered  urlLink potatoes  (premiering in January, 2005! I know I'm on the edge of MY seat!...whatever) and the most recent induction into the retarded food hall of fame: the  urlLink "Thickburger"  over at Carl Jr.'s and Hardee's.  I just got back from the grocery store (for unfatal dairy and meat*  see previous post ) and to pick up a few items I needed to make a spaghetti dinner (My most recent love affair is with the Kraft Tangy Italian Spaghetti Dinner), and what do I see? Lite Garlic Toast. LITE! What the hell is "Lite" garlic toast, and do I care? No. No, I don't. I don't want to plan my entire life around how many friggin' carbs something has. I've seen this Atkins diet fad come and go once before (back in the 80's), and it will again. Not unlike Figurines, Jazzercise (which, let's face it, was just a  urlLink cameltoe  waiting to happen) and  urlLink Ayds . I mean, let's be realistic people, are people who eat fast food to begin with, really the target audience for some corn tortilla filled with lettuce and sawdust? I think not.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to discount grocery store today. The grocery store has all kinds of good stuff, though I have to admit, I wouldn't feel too comfortable buying anything like meat or dairy products there. Rule of thumb when buying frozen food: If the product has enough ice crystals on it to build a snowman with, don't buy it. I also passed on some weirdo  urlLink Laffy Taffy  flavor that had (understandably) been discontinued:  Chocolate Mousse . However, I was pleasantly surprised to find the type of lightbulbs that I use in my  urlLink Frostie Root Beer  clock, for just 59¢! They usually cost more, so I stocked up. I also was excited to see a scented oil-Air freshener that I learned to love, only to have it be discontinued, in stock! *And for those of you wondering if I realize how sad it sounds to have fallen in love with an air freshener, yes, yes I know.  So, anyway, I go to check out and in a huge bin near the register is stacks of various flavors of breadsticks. And you know how I love breadsticks! (if you don't, you do now) So, I snatch up a few boxes (the sesame, my favorite) for just $1 a box!! As I'm waiting in line, I notice the couple in front of me are Amish. I briefly flash on scenes from Witness, then on to darker scenes from  urlLink Deadly Blessing  (though, technically those people were, "Hittites," but I digress). Once I come back from FlashbackLand, I notice that they are paying with a credit card. I didn't know Amish people even had credit cards. After they had finished checking out and were on their way to the parking lot, I nonchalantly sauntered over to the window to see what kind of vehicle they were in. I mean, if they have a credit card, then maybe the horse & buggy stereotype is out the window too. Enquiring minds wanted to know. So, get this, I watched them load their groceries (actually she was doing most of the work, he was busy standing around looking authoritative) into a Camaro! Who knew the Amish loved Camaros? I'm always learning new things.  And speaking of learning experiences, once I got in my own car, I decide to dig into those tasty-lookin' sesame breadsticks. I'm no expert, but I don't think breadsticks are supposed to taste like gasoline. Not, that I've tasted gasoline, but this was definitely some kind of petroleum product "flavor." Blech! Now I know why they were such a bargain.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to a couple of garage sales, an estate sale and drove by a 'moving sale' (I saw their stuff and thought "keep movin'") this weekend. Normally I'm not a fan of shopping where there's no air conditioning and there's risk of possible heatstroke (I live in Texas), but I passed all these sales while on errands to places I needed to go anyway, and couldn't resist.  The first place I went to was the estate sale, since it was just 2 streets behind my house. My main reason for wanting to go wasn't really bargains, but to see what the house looked like inside. Reason 1: The houses in this neighborhood are older (think 40's/50's) and sooo cute. Imagine hardwood floors, fireplaces in the living room, built in bookshelves and those cool little counters in the kitchen that are rounded on the end, and end in tiers of shelves. TOO COOL! And Reason 2: I always come away from an estate sale feeling better about how the interior of my house looks/smells, etc.  So I pull up to the house and there are already cars lining the street. My first thought is, "It's Saturday. Who they hell is awake at 9:30 AM on a Saturday? Weirdos." Then I remember that I'M there at 9:30AM, but then exclude myself from Weirdoville, 'cause I didn't get up to specifically go to yard sales, but instead, to get my errands over with. Yeah..okay, I'm a weirdo, too. Touche. So, walking up the house, my hopes are already kinda waning. I see some boxes of pillows covered in cat hair and as I'm stepping up on the sidewalk, a box filled with used bathroom toiletries. Let me at em'!...NOT! Who the hell would buy someone's 2/3 full bottle of lotion or toothpaste? Freaks, that's who.   I'm inside now and the first thing I notice is the  urlLink eau de cat  fragrance. Apparently the owner was/is (with most estate sales the owner has passed away, but sometimes their kids are just putting them in a home) a cat owner. Judging from the smell, a MULTIPLE cat owner. Wow. I feel self conscious because I can't control my nostrils from flaring, so I keep my head down and head for the books and records, which turn out to be a letdown. The books mostly consist of those old Reader's Digest condensed books and microwave cookbooks (a cookbook collector's kryptonite). However, I do see 2 cool little wooden boxes. They look kinda old, have hinged lids with black metal clasps. Very cool. I look for a price on them and the smaller one has $4 written on the bottom, so I think "Eureka! I'll get em'. If the small ones just $4, how much could the big one be?" So I ask one of the umpteen women running the estate sale how much the other one is, telling her I see the $4 price on one, but the other isn't priced. She takes the one that's priced and says "Oh, that's what I paid for it. I'm selling it for $20. And the other is $35. I got those at Pier One." I smile as if to say "neat," but I'm really thinking "You are seriously on some industrial-strength crack if you think I'm paying $50+ on 2 Pier One clearance items, one of which has a broken latch!" I quietly set them back down where they were and head towards the dining room, all the while overhearing people saying to each other "Is this really $100? "How much?" etc. I scope the rest of the house, but find nothing, so I head outside, without bothering looking at the boxes with misc. crap in them, sitting in the front yard. Who knows? I might have passed up half a carton of Whoppers for a mere $45! Whatever.  At my next two garage sales I do find a few things: A couple of tapes (Purple Rain soundtrack/Depeche Mode 101) to listen to in the ol' Walkman when I eventually start my exercise routine, 2 CDs (Savage Garden: Affirmation and The Corrs: Talk On Corners Special Edition), a couple of cheesy old cookbooks (Searchlight Recipe Book/Toll House Cookie Cookbook), a cool old liquor decanter shaped like a circus strongman and a cool, unused scrapbook from the 70's. All for under $10! Yaye bacon!  P.s. I got an e-mail from Jane today! I can't believe she wrote me back. What a sweetie. Jane, I say keep Marjorie's designer knockoff shoes. Deep down inside, I think she really wants you to have them. Oh, and I'm working on getting my blog up to blog standards. Promise! :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been having problems with a temperamental toilet. Sometimes it flushes, sometimes it gets its' swirl on, but nothing happens.  So, I got online and searched for plumbers in my area ('cause I don't have a phone book 'cause it's the size of War & Peace). I ended up choosing "Diamond K Plumbing" 'cause my name starts with a 'K' and to me that translates into fate (it doesn't take much for me). Yeah, that's logical.   Anyway, I called because I heard dripping and it sounded as if it was dripping under the house. *Side note: I have an old house (it was built in 1940), so it has what they call a 'crawlspace' (AKA creepy flashback to  urlLink The Boogens  movie), beneath it. The crawlspace is accessible from a panel in the floor of the dining room closet.   Soooo, if the plumber had to get under the house, that means I had to remove all the misc. debris from the dining room closet (AKA deathtrap). That's always fun. I found stuff I didn't even remember having: Halloween decorations I couldn't find last Halloween, a heating pad (when did I buy that?), a Tom & Jerry board game and lots of misc. crap. It also turns out I own half a bag of Halloween candy circa 1995. Some of it had congealed in the bag. Nice. So I clear out the closet contents, move it to another room and lay down newspaper just in case it's muddy under there.  He's scheduled to be here at 9 and shows up promptly at 2:30. What punctuality! So, he goes in the bathroom and (naturally) can't hear the dripping sound that I'm hearing (great, now I'm hearing things), so he decides to go investigate the crawlspace. I give him a flashlight and read him his last rites (the Boogens) and off he goes. Turns out it's NOT dripping under the house, thank god. However the dirt under the house is slightly damp, due to all the heavy rainfall we've been having, and after he's managed to fill very nook and cranny of his workboots with mud, he proceeds to grind dirt into 3 large rugs on the way to the door to wipe his feet (why bother?).  So while he's replacing some thingamajig in the back of the toilet, I decided to stop breathing down his neck like some old lady and get online and check on the news. Turns out another American guy got beheaded in Iraq. I go back to the bathroom to make small talk and casually mention this frustrating tidbit of news. Before I can finish the sentence he finishes it for me and tells me how he heard it on the radio in the truck on his way over. His voice kinda fades away, during his sentence, then he stands up and goes BA-fuckin'-LISTIC about us being over there in Iraq and what a mistake it was and how nobody takes responsibility for their actions anymore and how Bush is just the puppetmaster for all the corporations, etc. All of which I agree with, but he's getting increasingly pissed with every octave and the more he talks about it the more I'm starting to think to myself "What can I use as a weapon if he goes completely postal? What's within reach? Soap dispenser? No good. Toothbrush? No. Air freshener? That's it! I'll mace him with Crisp Breeze and while he's temporarily blinded (yet fragrant), I'll pelt him with various toiletries until I can get safely to the front door and out into the street."  Lucky for him, he gradually begins to calm down (maybe it was due to the cornered animal-look in my eyes), and sits back down on the edge of the tub and finishes changing out the doohickey, all the while mumbling about Vietnam vets and something about a Tejano music festival he missed. I slowly backed out, smiling and nodding and went to sit quietly, far away, with a book until he was done.  As it turns out, the whole problem was easily remedied. Apparently the tiny hole in the bottom of the bowl that controls the flow of water, when you flush the toilet, get clogged with sediment from the water, over time. He cleaned it out with his pocket knife (yikes) and the toilet flushed like gangbusters! I was so excited. I couldn't believe it. I'd been putting this off for over a year, due to another plumber's $900 estimate, and it was all taken care of in a matter of minutes. And for a hell of a lot less than $900! (try $85!)  I asked for his card, for future reference and wrote him a check. He gave me a receipt and got into his truck and was on his way. In the plus column, I now have a new plumber that I can rely on for any future plumbing emergencies. One that I know won't ream me with outrageous charges and bogus advice. Thank you volatile Larry!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I stayed up to watch  urlLink  Thank God It's Friday   on television. It's such a fun movie and has so much great music in it. It got me to thinking of some of my favorite 70's and 80's movies and their soundtracks, as well as current films that take place during those prospective eras. This in turn prompted me to ransack my soundtracks and suggest these 4 musical time capsules.     THEN:      Thank God It's Friday: Motion Picture Soundtrack . © 1978    Favorite tracks include  : 1, 4, 5, 7, 9  1. Thank God It's Friday - Love And Kisses 2. After Dark - Pattie Brooks 3. With Your Love - Donna Summer 4. Last Dance - Donna Summer 5. Disco Queen - Paul Jabara 6. Find My Way - Cameo      7. Too Hot Ta Trot - The Commodores      8. Leatherman's Theme - Wright Bros. Flying Machine      9. I Wanna Dance - Marathon      10. Take It To The Zoo - Sunshine      11. Sevilla Nights - Santa Esmeralda      12. You're The Most Precious Thing In My Life - Love And Kisses 13. Do You Want The Real Thing - D.C. Larue      14. Trapped In A Stairway - Paul Jabara      15. Floyd's Theme - Natural Juices      16. Lovin', Livin' And Givin' - Diana Ross      17. Love Masterpiece - Thelma Houston      18. Last Dance (Reprise) - Donna Summer      19. Je T'Aime (Moi Non Plus) - Donna Summer     NOW:      The Last Days Of Disco: Motion Picture Soundtrack . © 1998  This soundtrack can currently be purchased at Half.com for as little as  urlLink $3.00!     Favorite tracks include  : 1, 2, 7, 8, 14, 16  01.   I Love The Nightlife (Disco 'Round) - Alicia Bridges 02.   I'm Coming Out - Diana Ross 03.   Got To Be Real - Cheryl Lynn 04.   Good Times - Chic 05.   He's The Greatest Dancer - Sister Sledge 06.   I Don't Know If It's Right - Evelyn "Champagne" King 07.   More, More, More (Pt. 1) - Andrea True Connection 08.   Doctor's Orders - Carol Douglas 09.   Everybody Dance - Chic 10.   Love I Lost, The - Harold Melvin/The Blue Notes 11.   Let's All Chant - Michael Zager Band 12.   Got To Have Loving - Don Ray 13.   Shame - Evelyn "Champagne" King 14.   Knock On Wood - Amii Stewart 15.   Oogum Boogum Song, The - Brenton Wood 16.   Love Train - The O'Jays 17.   I Love The Nightlife (Disco 'Round) - India/Nuyorican Soul    THEN:      Valley Girl: Motion Picture Soundtrack . © 1983    Favorite tracks include  : 1, 2, 3, 9, 15  01.   Million Miles Away, A - The Plimsouls 02.   Johnny, Are You Queer? - Josie Cotton 03.   Eyes Of A Stranger - Payola$ 04.   Angst In My Pants - Sparks 05.   Who Can It Be Now? - Men At Work 06.   Everywhere At Once - The Plimsouls 07.   I La La La Love You - Pat Travers'Black Pearl 08.   He Could Be The One - Josie Cotton 09.   Love My Way - The Psychedelic Furs 10.   Jukebox (Don't Put Another Dime) - Flirts 11.   Fanatic, The - Felony 12.   She Talks In Stereo - Gary Myrick &amp; The Figures 13.   Oldest Story In The World - The Plimsouls 14.   School Is In - Josie Cotton 15.   I Melt With You - Modern English    NOW:      200 Cigarettes: Motion Picture Soundtrack . © 1999  This fantastic soundtrack can currently be purchased at Half.com for a mere  urlLink $1.99!     Favorite tracks include  : 1, 3, 5, 8, 9  01.   Cruel To Be Kind - Nick Lowe 02.   In The Flesh - Blondie 03.   Just What I Needed - The Cars 04.   Save It For Later - Harvey Danger 05.   Our Lips Are Sealed - The Go-Go's 06.   I Want Candy - Bow Wow Wow 07.   I Don't Care - The Ramones 08.   Boogie Wonderland - Girls Against Boys 09.   Ladies Night - Kool &amp; The Gang 10.   It's Different For Girls - Joe Jackson 11.   Nowhere Girl - B-Movie 12.   More Than This - Roxy Music 13.   Romeo &amp; Juliet - Dire Straits 14.   Peace, Love &amp; Understanding? (What's So Funny About) - Elvis Costello &amp; The Attractions 15.   Blondie Medley (The Loud Allstar Rock Remix): Rapture / Maria / No Exit - Blondie/Coolio/The Loud Allstars
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Living in Texas all my life, you'd think I'd have come to terms with summer by now. Well, I haven't. I still dread it every year, 'cause I know it's gonna be  urlLink miserable . My friend Derik and I have an ongoing morbid joke about how it's not officially summer in Texas until somebody leaves their baby in the car. If only  urlLink George Foreman  designed cars. I know, it's sad, it's horrible, it's reality. And it happens E V E R Y single year. Last year alone, 95 such deaths happened nationwide, 530 since 1998. It's like some sort of barometer for stupidity. Derik's philosophy is that it's some sort of intentional genetic candle snuffer, since a suspiciously overwhelming majority of the children just  happen  to be mentally/physically handicapped. It's like the parents' way of ridding themselves of life's lil' speedbump. Some people just weren't meant to be parents.  Well, this year the state of Texas is instigating a new campaign that reminds people not to leave their baby in their car. It's called the "Look before you leave" campaign. Just another ridiculous waste of money and resources. I can't believe that people have to be taught how NOT to kill their child. Over the years I see more and more absentee parents. People don't discipline their children anymore.   Here's a prime example of the kind of morons passing themselves off as "parents," that I come in contact with on a regular basis. I was at the grocery store the other day, in line at the check out, 4 people deep. I rubberneck ahead to see what the holdup is: Is the checker using an abacus? Is the sacker on his cellphone again? Is another dumbass waiting until they've watched ever item scan, before they start writing their goddamn check? Or is some old coot rummaging to the bottom of their fuckin' coin purse/pockets for exact change again? What?! WHAT?! No, it's none of these things. It's a woman, holding up her 4 year old, letting her scan her goddamn groceries! 'Cause " she likes to. " This at peak shopping hours. I fucking kid you not. I'm lookin' around for the Candid Camera crew. I could not believe it. I'd like to sail lil' Hailey's spoiled ass right across that fuckin' scanner and into a brick wall, like a goddamn air hockey puck! Man! Parents are retarded!  And that's just the tip of the iceberg. From tantrums that end in "rewards" for stopping, to "time outs" that have all the effectiveness of a  urlLink Whiffle  brand diaphragm. Today's parents feel compelled to take their kids with them EVERYWHERE. Whatever happened to  urlLink baby-sitters ? Whatever happened to  urlLink discipline ? Whatever happened to parenting? Fuck this "Dr." Phil psychobabble about damaging their delicate lil' psyche. Children must have discipline, or face my wrath (Khan has nuthin' on me...and I don't mean Chaka). Come back to the five and dime,  urlLink Mabel King , Mabel King.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life is filled with what I like to call " urlLink Scooby-Doo  mysteries." You know, like:   • Why is that gorgeous man with  her ? • What  does  she see in him? • Agent Cody Banks made enough money to spawn a  sequel ?  Well, get  urlLink Nancy Drew  on the case, 'cause there's another mystery afoot at Shadow Ranch! Allow me to elaborate. There's this hot guy online, whose blog I've been ardently reading for a little over a year now. What keeps me coming back for more, you may ask? Well, I'll tell you. He's smart, funny, a great writer and not your typical bodybuilder (obnoxious/arrogant). And ... he's just  urlLink so damn cute!  His chin needs my kisses. I'll admit it, I'm smitten. He posts images in his blog entries, of himself before/during/after his workouts and I love em'. He's got the best nose and  urlLink pecs . I know it's a weird combo, but hey, it's my thing, okay? I have all kinds of fetishes, big noses and pecs, being just one of them, and this guy has em' in spades! In the immortal words of the  urlLink Kool-Aid Man  "Oh YEAH!"  So anyway, over time, he's developed this nasty habit of posting pictures of his wife, who's also a bodybuilder (Female bodybuilders gross me out) and a dead ringer for Fear Factor's host,  urlLink Joe Rogan  dressed as Chyna. Pretty. And when I say he posts pictures of her, I don't mean just every once in a while. It's become a regular thing now, and it's really cramping our make believe relationship.  I've been following the sport of bodybuilding since the early 80's and one Scooby-Doo mystery that continues to rear it's ugly head is: Why do HOT male  urlLink bodybuilders  insist on choosing these bykes ('bisexual dyke')? Manly, yes, but they like em' too! Ech. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know what you're thinking: "He just likes a healthy woman who can keep up with him and his healthy lifestyle." Yeah, you know what? There's a big difference between healthy and horsey. 'Healthy' women come in all shapes and sizes and still maintain their femininity. These women the bodybuilders are choosin' are one cough away from a prostate exam, if you know what I mean.  All I'm saying is, I guess I'll never understand why some people make the choices they do. Especially the really cute ones. There's a million reasons, from personal preference to temporary insanity. I guess some mysteries will forever remain just that. A mystery. What a sad, sad day for this  urlLink Hardy Boy .
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I just saw a very disturbing commercial...for a church. I didn't even know churches made commercials. It kinda reminded me of those old  urlLink Taco Bueno  commercials from the late 90's. You know, the ones that spoofed  Spanish  urlLink telenovelas : Over the top acting, very dramalicious.   Here's the church's commercial set up: The scene opens with an anxious man sitting in a prison cell, a collage of visuals swimming in his mind: the trial, the jury finding him guilty, his lawyer, his idictment, up to his imprisonment. Then all of a sudden, a prison guard comes to the cell, opens the door with a key and tells the man "You're off the hook, someone is taking your place." Flash forward to the  urlLink execution , via electric chair. One male witness, in the viewing room, jumps up and dramatically exclaims, while pointing to the man about to get executed behind the large payne of glass, "It's crazy!" (re: the fact that someone else took the place of the actual convicted person) and the man next to him says "No....it's love.", while pursing his lips as if to say " urlLink Oh yeah, I'm THAT smooth, baby ." You can practically smell the  urlLink Vitalis .  The screen then switches to the preacher/pastor of the church advertising and he goes on to tell you "Jesus died for your sins," and other misc. information on church times of operation.  Yikes. I found this form of propaganda, quite unsettling. If you have to resort to recruiting new parishioners via television, what does that say about the church your hawking? In the immortal words of  urlLink Charlie Brown  “Oh no! My own dog--gone commercial. I can't stand it.”
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Some friends and I were chatting online yesterday, and of all things, the subject of colonics came up. *For those who may not be familiar with the term, a "colonic" is  the irrigation of the colon for cleansing purposes . Apparently the average person has 5-10lbs of impacted feces in their colon. And in an article in USA Today, according to the autopsy, John Wayne had 40lbs of impacted fecal matter in his body at death.  urlLink Elvis  reportedly had 60. Can you believe that shit (pun intended)?! That's roughly the weight of a 5-6 year-old child! That's one helluva loaf to pinch. Why, that's an  urlLink I Love Lucy-Pioneer Women episode -sized loaf! Damn!   So, I decided to get online and learn more about colonics and how they work. In the process, I came across an informative, yet unintentionally funny site that promotes a product called  urlLink  Colonix  . With testimonials (many including photos of the author. What's THAT about?) like: “ You feel like dancing in the streets ”, “ You have given me hope and energy to really start enjoying my life again ,” and my personal favorite: “ We are having awesome adventures in the bathroom ,” I was more than a little intrigued.   As I read through the testimonials, some as long as 6 paragraphs (one's own personal ode to better living through feculence), I couldn't help but laugh at the over exuberance of some of the proclamations: “ I feel like I have so much more energy inside me just bursting to get out… ” (yeah, as long as it doesn't happen in public) and “ I experience anywhere from 14-20 bowel movements per week ” (geez, I hope you took some vacation time). But " Daniel K " from  New Jersey  had the creepiest observation of them all: “ I NOTICED some pretty neat stuff in my stool. ” Gee, I hope you took pictures. gah. Daniel might want to consider getting cable.      As I read some of the symptoms that might make one a candidate for "internal cleansing," I realized some of them applied to me! Could I be the next testimonial? Could Colonix make ME the master of my own dookie destiny?! Could I be ready for MY close-up, Mr. DeMille? I'll admit I'm tempted, but also a little creeped out by some of the artifacts some of these people are discovering. Mainly the misc. parasites and the occasional "egg sac." BLEAH! I dunno if I'm prepared to know what's cruising through my colon. On the upside, the Colonix clients claim to have experienced weight loss, shinier hair and even more energy. Not a bad trade off. I'm still not completely sold in the idea of a colonic, but I am gonna do some more research.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My 4th of July was pretty uneventful, but then it usually is. I've never been a big participant in what I refer to as the "BBQ holidays." i.e. Labor Day, 4th of July and Memorial Day. I've never had much interest in heatstroke with an audience. And you know what baffles me the most about these holiday festivities? Someone ALWAYS drowns. Around here, the parade isn't the only thing in town with floats. It's like a bad horror movie. Every single year it's the same thing. You'd think these people would invest in a lifejacket or just steer clear of the lake altogether, but nooooo.   The weekend, in general was pretty uneventful. My mom went to her 40-something class reunion this weekend. Haven't talked to her yet to see how it went. I don't foresee me ever going to a class reunion. Don't get me wrong, I loved school. It was the people I couldn't stand. I was fairly popular in  urlLink high school . I joined my fair share of clubs and was even voted "most talented," for what it's worth, but I was never really all that interested in the whole social aspect of it all. I wasn't shy or anything, I just wasn't interested. My perspective on social interaction hasn't really changed all that much. The period of time between meeting the cool people and the idiotic people is just too far apart. I'm kinda jaded, I guess.  Oh! While I was watching  urlLink The Muppet Movie  this weekend, I thought of a question and an idea. First the question: When deaf people go see a movie at the theater, I assume they read lips. So, does that mean that a movie who's entire cast is Muppets, would pretty much be outta the question? And now for my idea (they're kinda related). Okay, I know that some theaters provide devices for people who have hearing issues. BUT, what if the film companies came up with a film that had the dialogue imbedded in the film? The naked eye couldn't detect it, but when viewed with special glasses, you could. This could revolutionize the movie going experience for the deaf! Or not. It's just an idea.  Why am I always a little freaked out when I open a can of biscuits? It must be psychological. I made some of those  urlLink Pilsbury Orange Cinnamon Rolls  with icing, last night and started to laugh because I reminded myself of a friend's cat who when you approached her with a spray bottle of water (to reprimand her), she would scrunch up her face and turn away.  Also, on the subject of scary food, the new commercial for the  urlLink Skippy Peanutbutter Snack Bars , with those weirdo-lookin' CGI Rastafarian elephants, creeps me out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Nip/Tuck: TV Soundtrack . © 2004.  A CD as cool, hip and unpredictable as the show itself. An eclectic mix of what I would consider Ambient "Chill Out" music. A great grab bag of artists, whom you will most-likely want to check out, individually, after experiencing the CD.  Bebel Gilberto  (*check out   Tanto Tempo Remixes ) in particular stands out for me, though I also really like  The Engine Room 's sound.    Favorite tracks include:   1, 3, 7, 8 & 11.  01. A Perfect Lie (G&D Remix) - The Engine Room 02. So Damn Beautiful - Poloroid 03. Angels - Wax Poetic featuring Norah Jones  04. Fever - Daniel Ash 05. All The Way To The Top - Jazzupstarts 06. The Headphonist (Gil-Only Version) - Kinky 07. Falling - Chris Coco  08. Cosmopolitans (Tri-Factor Remix) - Erin McKeown 09. Price of Love - Client 10. Just Be Me - Kirsty Hawkshaw   11. Lonely - Bebel Gilberto     12. Elvis - Alpha     13. Following - Chungking     14. Pride - Syntax     15. A Perfect Lie (Original Version) - The Engine Room     Splendor: Motion Picture Soundtrack . © 1999.  This is one of my favorite  urlLink Gregg Araki  movies. God! Could  urlLink Matt Keeslar  BE any hotter?! Damn! Definitely worth checking out! If you're familiar with Gregg Araki's films, then you know how vibrant and kitschy his films can be. His music choices for his film's soundtracks are just as tasty. This affordable, yet undiscovered little gem can be found at Half.com for as low as  urlLink $3 . You can't go wrong with this CD, it's one of those rare CDs that you like from beginning to end. Great for an evening with friends.    Favorite tracks include:   2, 3, 6, 7, 9, 14.  01.   Sho' Nuff - Fatboy Slim 02.   Shine (Splendiferous Locust Mix)- Slowdive 03.   The Chemistry Between Us (Lionrock Remix)- The London Suede 04.   Before Today (Chicane Remix)- Everything But The Girl 05.   I Don't Know Why I Love You (7" Drip Of Rockman Mix)- The House Of Love 06.   Kelly Watch The Stars (Moog Cookbook Remix)- Air 07.   The Jag (Radio Edit)- The Micronauts 08.   Electrobank (Radio Edit)- The Chemical Brothers 09.   Beetlebum (Moby's Mix)- Blur 10.   Mesmerise (Mesmerising Vocal Mix)- Chapterhouse 11.   Only The Strongest Will Survive (James Lavelle Remix)- Hurricane #1 12.   Sweetness & Light (Orange Squash Mix)- Lush 13.   Floerz (Radio Edit)- Armand Van Helden/Roland Clark 14.   Bizarre Love Triangle - New Order     Permanent Midnight: Motion Picture Soundtrack  © 1998.  A surreal and underrated film, the soundtrack to Permanent Midnight features a smorgasbord of great artists and songs. This sleeper gem can be found for as low as  urlLink $1  over at Half.com and is well worth it. You'll find yourself listening to it again and again. Great when getting ready for a night on the town.   Favorite tracks include:   1, 8, 9, 11, 13.  01.  Now Is The Time (Permanent Midnight Mix) - The Crystal Method 02.   EPR - Girls Against Boys 03.   Get Miles - Gomez 04.   Horses - Black Lab 05.   Suite From Permanent Midnight - Free Radical/Paul Hepker 06.   Overwhelming - Art Alexakis 07.   Cigarette - Lael Alderman 08.   Godspeed - BT 09.   Honey - Moby 10.   A Permanent Theme - Spring Heel Jack 11.   Smack My Bitch Up - Prodigy 12.   Take Your Time - Spiritualized 13.   Tape Loop (Diabolical Brothers Mix) - Morcheeba  14.   Free Ride - Embrace      Sex And The City: TV Soundtrack  © 2000.  Wow. This is one of my favorite CDs. As hip, sophisticated and diverse as the show it represents. A great soundtrack for lounging around the house with your headphones on.   Favorite tracks include:   1, 2, 6, 13.  01.   Sexbomb (Peppermint Jam Remix) - Tom Jones/Mousse T. 02.   Taste The Tears - Amber 03.   Righteous Love - Joan Osborne 04.   Love TKO - Bette Midler 05.   Count To 10 - Imani Coppola 06.   More, More, More 07.   Hot Boyz - Missy "Misdemeanor" Elliott 08.   Got The Girl - Reiss 09.   The Time Is Now - Moloko 10.   Calling It Quits - Aimee Mann 11.   Dreams Come True - Elan Atias 12.   For Only You - Trisha Yearwood 13.   Sex And The City Theme - Groove Armada
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Are you hep to the jive,  urlLink daddy-o ? You will be if you check out any of these CDs I'm recommending today. Remember being curious as to what your parents records sounded like, when you were young? Then putting one on to play and then thinking to yourself "squaresville!" Haven't you heard? It's hip to be square, man. These CDs are lounge, hear them purr! The first 2 CDs will make you wanna cha cha over to the liquor cabinet and mix yourself a Martini, Gimlet or a Bellini. Don't forget the swizzle stick! The last CD is a little spicier. If you're a fan of  urlLink Rockabilly  and/or that jazzy  urlLink Stray Cats  sound, then you will definitely dig The Naughty Ones. You may even find yourself reaching for the pomade! The best part about all these CDs is that each of them have flown under the radar and can generally be found for under $4!      Swingin' Jazz For Hipsters: Volume 1. © 1997   This CD can currently be purchased at Half.com for a mere pittance of  urlLink $3.50!    Favorite tracks include: 1, 3, 8, 10, 12    01.   The Candy Man - Ray Brown/Monty Alexander/Sam Most 02.   Goin' Out Of My Head - Captain Jack McDuff/Herb Besson/Joe Magnarelli 03.   Walk Between The Raindrops - Mel Tormé/Marty Paich Dek-tette 04.   Isn't She Lovely - Stephane Grappelli/Martin Taylor 05.   Slidin' - Hendrik Meurkens/Dado Moroni/Peter Bernstein 06.   Honey Suckle Rose - Stefan Scaggiari Trio 07.   I Can Do It - Tania Maria/Mitch Stein 08.   Days Of Wine And Roses - Ruby Braff/Scott Hamilton/Dave McKenna 09.   Sleepwalk - Rom Eschete Trio 10.   The 59th Street Bridge Song (Feelin' Groovy) - Ernestine Anderson/Hank Jones 11.   The Lady Wants To Know - Howard Roberts/Ross Tompkins 12.   The Girl From Ipanema - Charlie Byrd Trio     Music For The Jet Set. © 1996   This CD can can be yours at Half.com for just  urlLink $3.85!    Favorite tracks include: 2, 5, 7, 11, 13, 14    01.   April In Paris - Gloria Lynne 02.   On A Little Street In Singapore - Harry Zimmerman 03.   Maori Flea - Arthur Lyman 04.   Catriburium Na Batacuda - Carnival In Rio 05.   It Happened In Monterey - Bob Florence 06.   Bermuda - Troy Walker 07.   Prelude A La Cha Cha Cha - Woody Herman/Charlie Byrd 08.   The Third Man Theme - Anton Karas And His Two Rudis 09.   Vaya Con Dios - Harry Zimmerman 10.   Mosaico Andaluz - Bernabe de Moron 11.   Bali Ha'i - Gloria Lynne 12.   Aiylong - Soubri Moulin/His African Beats 13.   China Nights Mambo - Jack "Bongo" Burger 14.   C'est Si Bon - Ray Ventura Singers     The Naughty Ones: I Dig Your Voodoo! © 1995 Favorite tracks include: 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, 14    01.   Boulevard Of Broken Dreams 02.   Voodoo Kiss 03.   Walkin' Blues, The 04.   Pretty Plaid Skirt 05.   Azure Te 06.   Tapped In A Web Of Love 07.   Charlie Parker Twist (Billie's Bounce) 08.   Skiddy-Wo 09.   I Dig Your Voodoo 10.   Ain't Gonna Cry No More 11.   What's My Name 12.   Harlem Nocturne 13.   Charade 14.   Well You Needn't
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A lot of random things have been swirling around in my head lately, so today's blog is gonna be a potluck dinner for your mind. Dig in!      Read an interesting little article in  urlLink Reader's Digest , entitled " Fight The Energy Vampires ," and thought it was so good I would share it with you:  They're everywhere--people who make themselves feel better at our expense. "But, if we're prepared, they won't have power over us," says Judith Orloff, psychiatrist and author of Positive Energy. Here's how to deflect the vampires as they strike :    •  CONSTANT TALKER-   Scenario:  Your airplane seatmate wants to talk politics--for the whole flight.  Solution:  Say, "That's interesting, but I hope you understand this is my time to relax. I need to read now." •  THE DRAMA QUEEN-   Scenario:  To your co-worker, losing $1 in the vending machine is the end of the world.  Solution:  Say, "I'm sorry that happened-I hope you can work it out-but I need to get back to work." •  KNIFE TWISTER-   Scenario:  A "friend" consoles you after a bad date, saying, "Maybe you're setting your sights too high."  Solution:  Minimize your contact with that person. At the least, tell her/him, "That was hurtful. Please don't say things like that to me." Then recognize the insults for the insecurity that they show.      One of my all-time favorite shows,  urlLink Strangers With Candy , starring one of my favorite people, Amy Sedaris, is going to be made into a movie! I'm so psyched. Here's the brief article released by the Associated Press:    David Letterman's Worldwide Pants Inc. is producing its first film, an independent feature based on Comedy Central's cockeyed cautionary tale, "Strangers With Candy."  Amy Sedaris played a middle-aged dropout who returns to highs choolin the TV series, which ran from 1998-2000. The film also stars "Strangers With Candy" co-creators, writers and stars Steven Colbertand Paul Dinello.     The film, which has the working title, "Strangers With Candy: The Movie," is being directed by Dinello.    Believe it or not, I actually had some money yesterday, so I went to my favorite bookstore and picked up a few books to keep me entertained for a while. They are:   The Film Noir Style   by Alain Silver &amp; James Ursini ( tons of great images ),   Going, Going, Gone: Vanishing Americana   ( items that may not be around much longer. Again, GREAT retro images ) and last but certainly not least:    urlLink Slowpoke : Cafe Pompous   by Jen Sorensen ( hilarious topical cartoons ).   Saw a great documentary on STARZ! True Stories channel, last night, called   Last of The Mississippi Jukes  . It was a close look at the disappearing venues where rural blues originated. If you like the Blues, then you will enjoy it. The music was great, and fortunately there's a  urlLink soundtrack  available. You can also buy it on DVD. It's scheduled to play again on Friday, July 23, and twice on Tuesday, July 27. Check your local listings for time and channel. Not to be missed!      Heard this REALLY queer commercial on the radio the other day. It was SO sappy, I originally thought it was a joke and was anxiously awaiting the punchline, only to find out it was a REAL commercial. Here's the synopsis: The announcer starts the ad by saying "Expressions of love" (Is that bile I taste, welling up in my throat?), followed by some cheesy soap opera-style music. Cue a woman's voice talking about how she and her husband are arguing over what color to paint their house. He wants gray with black trim. She wants "the more traditional" yellow with white trim. They can't decide on a compromise. She goes on to say how they made a pact when first getting married that they would never go to bed with unresolved issues. But now she's concerned, because he's leaving on a business trip, early the next morning. The next afternoon she gets a delivery from Generic Florist. It's a bouquet of yellow and white flowers, from her husband. Yellow and white. The same colors she wanted to paint the house (cue me gagging).  Cue cheesy music and announcer . Gah. Guaranteed to wipeout any diabetics within earshot.   Now that summer is here, I have started using this little vintage electric fan I have. And, you know how the older fans didn't really have much in the way of protection from the fan blades. Well, last night as I was bending down to turn it off, the drawstring from my pants got caught in the fan and it started reeling in my drawstring, closer to my crotch! Yipes! I couldn't help but flash on the scene from Jumpin' Jack Flash, where Whoopi gets her dress caught in the  urlLink paper shredder . lol! Anyway, I got the fan unplugged, and my drawstring untangled from the fan. Bloodshed averted.   Don't forget to watch the new episode of  urlLink Good Girls Dont...  on Oxygen tonight.  urlLink In Touch Weekly  calls it"...the best bet to fill the 'Friend's' void." Personally, I think the show's a lot fresher and genuinely funnier than Friends. Not as WASPy. Plus, you gotta check out some of my favorite people: Joy Gohring (Jane)and Kevin Christy(Ben). My favorite scene with Jane, is where she's dressed in this red top with her hair up in pigtails, wistfully watching her make-believe boyfriend Danny Masterson (Hyde from That 70's Show) on TV. She's just too foxy! Favorite line: Jane pretends to be pregnant to get a date with a guy in the grocery store, so she expands on the charade by telling him her husband is dead, but that's a good thing, 'cause he used to beat her, and the guy says "If he weren't dead I'd wring his neck like a chicken." And Jane says hungrily, " I love chicken. " Lol! Gotta love that Jane! And then there's underdog Ben, who considers himself "Doughy and bookish," but I think he's just  so  good-lookin'. His combination of humility, self-deprecating humor and the fact that he looks  so  good in glasses, just makes me love him more. It airs tonight, and twice on Sunday, so there's no reason to miss it. Check your local listings for time and channel you'll be glad you did!   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A friend and I were discussing the subject of people we know who must be handled with kid gloves, since they are diabetic, vegetarian, lactose intolerant, have food allergies, etc. and what a drag they are to be around. Before we go any further, let me preface this by saying I'm not "anti" vegetarian, if that's your thing, that's precious, nor am I unsympathetic to those with medical conditions. However, I AM anti-drama. Things don't always have to be about YOU and/or complicated. This blog is referring to the high maintenance people whom wield their beliefs and/or condition like a hypoallergenic stainless steel sword.  I've had friends who were vegetarians and/or diabetic. I say "had" because their high maintenance nutritional needs wore me out and eventually aided in the disintegration of our friendship. Some prime examples of the drama: One friend was diabetic and whenever we went out to eat, we had to eat somewhere more expensive than I was willing to shell out. So when I offered to have pizza delivered one night (from  urlLink Pizza Inn ), "Oh, Miguel (who's a diabetic) can't eat pizza." Um, okay. So where do you want to eat? They pick Cici's Pizza. For someone who couldn't eat pizza, Miguel managed to eat his way thru the buffet of assorted pizzas, quite adeptly. I guess when she said Miguel couldn't eat pizza, I guess what she really meant was "pizza from where you want to eat."      So Halloween rolls around and I'm planning my annual  urlLink Halloween  party menu, when I get reminded by Marla that she's a "vegetarian." Marla's what I refer to as a "pseudo-vegetarian." It's hip, it's trendy, it gets attention, all the cool kids are doin' it! SIGH. When confronted about her occasional trips to carnivore town, she'll admonish it with "I don't eat anything cute." Neat. Sorry, but you can't be a vegetarian just 6 days a week. Back to the Halloween party. So, while working on a budget I have to keep in mind that Marla and Miguel have special needs. I have some assorted sugar-free candies for Miguel (not cheap), chips, cookies, cupcakes, vegetable tray, etc. And the pièce de résistance a pricey chicken nugget platter from  urlLink Chick-Fil-A . Naturally, I ordered the platter with the "carnivore's" in mind, so I didn't factor in Marla and Miguel, due to their hypersensitive dietary needs. So, who do you think scarfs down 3/4 the platter? You guessed it. Miguel The Fragile, who can't eat fast food, when it comes to what I can afford. And Marla, the "vegetarian" whose lifestyle we must forever be cognizant of.  My friend Terri regaled me with tails of wedding woes, due to guests who were either lactose intolerant, didn't eat meat and/or were allergic to shellfish and peanuts. What the fuck? If you're going to attend a wedding reception and/or the rehearsal dinner and you're that goddamn delicate, you might wanna keep your frail ass home. Like the bride doesn't have enough to deal with than to remember that Cousin Larry swells up like a microwaved marshmallow, if he gets anywhere near a peanut. Or that Helen thinks meat is murder. Here's a revolutionary idea. Why not step outside your little bubble and eat what you can (or eat before you arrive) and be a gracious GUEST. It'll be just like old times. Grab yourself a fuckin' bag of  urlLink Cheerios  and go to town, but give the rest of us a break.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Some things that make me want to scream:    Internet Sites With Audio:   Ever been poking around the Internet and stumble across a site that has audio? LOUD aidio? That shit always scares the hell outta me. You'd think I'd build up a tolerance over time, but it's so random, that I don't think about it until I've been scared witless (and shitless...but that just happened once) by the midi file version of Livin' la Vida Loca. Why do people want audio on their site anyway? Nothing makes me click the "Back" button faster than a bad Casio keyboard version of some TV show theme or some cha cha version of a TLC song. No thanks.    Lame "Antique" Stores:   I enjoy going to "thrifting" and shopping for misc. things I don't need, but I've stopped going to antique malls altogether. I pretty much gave up on them about 6 or 7 years ago, because they usually have more froo-froo NEW shit and what I call "country crock crafty" shit ( Picture wood cutouts of geese, hearts, "country folk," etc, then paint em' desert rose or periwinkle blue. Add rafia and a "cute" saying like "There's No Place Like Home" and you've got yourself some country crock crap ), than actual OLD things. My friend Derik and I discuss this from time to time. We both are the type of people who know what they like and can pretty much breeze through an antique mall and all it's stalls pretty quickly. Shopping with him has its' pros and cons.  Pros:  I don't have a "pal" under my ass the whole time slowing me down to show me everything "neat." That makes me want to pull my hair out! Plus, if he DOES see something I might like, he waits until we meet up again and points me in the right direction, thus saving me the stop-start-stop-start time.  Cons:  He's seen everything there's ever been to see, so nothing is new tohim or interesting, unless it's something he's buying. That kinda takes the wind outta your sales, when you've "discovered" a treasure. Plus, no mater what I pay for it, it was "too much." I've been with other friends before and they're like "God, did you sprint through the place?" No, my mind is kinda like a scanner. When I detect silk flowers, resin figurines, a bowl filled with potpourri, cherubs, a guest book and/or things I have no interest in, I walk on by. I'm one of those weird people that prefers the less organized, non-"themed" booths and prefers to look amongst the clutter. Those people always have more interesting things and don't have them all priced at "family heirloom" prices. Also, what the fuck is with the tea rooms in all the antique malls? You know, with some queer name like Ruffles 'N Bows Tea Room. I don't know about you, but I can't get enough lattice work with twinkle lights and fake ivy entwined amongst it, separating the $10 chicken salad sandwich from the crusty "collectibles." Let me at it! Not.    Cheap Toilet Paper:   So, my mom is always buying me  urlLink toilet paper . I dunno what she thinks goes on here at Chez Kirk, but it ain't no poopapalooza. So, she bought this shitty (no pun intended) brand called  urlLink Scott . Well, unless you WANT to wipe your ass with your hand, I wouldn't suggest buying it anytime soon. It's gotta be made out of some kind of rice paper/tracing paper/sandpaper hybrid. De-lovely! NOT.    Unexpected Internet Porn Ambush:   Since I am SUCH a graphic design nut and all-around visual person, whenever I am on the Internet, I am usually looking for images. Mostly kitschy, pop-culture-type stuff. Sometimes celebrities. It just depends. One thing leads to another and before you know it, I've inadvertently stumbled upon some random, explicit porn (Usually straight porn, 9X outta 10). Lord only knows why typing in "corndog" brings up some chick with a battered wiener on a stick, nestled between her headlights. Prime example: I was looking for images from the animated MTV show, Daria (Now showing on one of the Nick channels). Pretty tame stuff, right? WRONG. So, I typed in various characters names at random. When I typed in "Daria, Trent" I find some images from the show PLUS some really fucked up images that I guess fans came up with, of Daria, Jane, Trent and other misc. characters from the show having explicit sex. What's THAT about? I'm convinced anything can be sexual to anyone, at this point. I just find it more than a little unsettling to see a female cartoon character exposing her hamshack.     Chain Letters:   Is it just me, or do you get e-mail chain letters, too? I thought those were a thing of the past. Last time I got one (in the actual mailbox) was back in the early 80's. I find it a little amusing (and annoying) that something as ridiculous and for some people, unnerving, as a chain letter, has gone on to bug a whole new generation. Personally, I am not a superstitious person, so the new e-mail versions go in the same place the old ones used to go: In the trashcan. Who knew the chain letter would be so resilient as to go hi-tech? I guess idiocy never goes outta style.    Solicitors:   When I'm at home, I'm one of those people who doesn't go to/open the door, unless I'm expecting company or recognize the person/people at the door. I don't wanna find Jesus, subscribe to any magazines at incredible savings or get my lawn mowed by an illegal alien, okay? So, unless I know you, I'm expecting you and/or you've called ahead and made an appointment, go away. And why is it that after ringing the doorbell and knocking on the glass door, people then try to open the locked screen door? What's THAT about? I find it more than a little disturbing when I hear them pumping the handle to get it open. Weirdoes. I guess some people have a hard time accepting the fact that they're not getting a response. It's like those people who go up to an elevator and even though the button they want is already pushed, they push it again. Yeah, that'll help.    Wrong Numbers:   I have the feature "Call Block" on my home phone. Regrettably, it only holds 10 numbers at a time, and once it is full I have to delete them and start from scratch. Since I have so few friends, and since the ones I do have are too busy to pick up a phone, needless to say I don't get many calls. On the other hand, I get plenty of calls for Mona, Rae-Rae and someone who I'm guessing is Mexican, since I don't speak Spanish. I especially love the ones that start out: (long pause) "Uh...um...eh...who dis?" Wonderful. Or better yet, the endearing black woman repeating "Rae Rae? Rae Rae. Rae Rae?" Neat. So, after telling them they have the wrong number (sometimes I get out the whole sentence before they hang up on me. Dandy!), I immediately block their ignorant ass, so they do not  accidentally  call me again. SO, maybe 2 months later, the Call Block list fills up and I have to delete it. I swear to God, maybe 3-4 hours passes before I get another wrong number. Again. Same person, looking for the same people. What the FUCK? If you've ever seen the 80's movie  urlLink Murder By Phone , then you know that I can't wait for the day that you can electrocute people via the telephone. Is that burnt hair I smell? Sorry 'bout that Lakeisha.  Oh, and before I forget, I'd like to give a shout out to my friend Seth, who gave me some HTML tips to help my blog look better. Thanks Seth! :)  Now, if someone could help me with some HTML to get rid of the damn boxes around my images, so they can be flush with the background, I'd be in Heaven!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I dunno about you, but I do some pretty odd things when I'm home alone...and occasionally in public (but only when I think nobody is paying attention). Mostly talk to myself. Yeah, I can see myself in my golden years, shuffling through the grocery store parking lot, congratulating myself for remembering to actually pick up the ice I paid for (I always forget to pick it up!).   It seems like I'm always being caught talking to myself or doing something strange (to the public, but funny to me). I hate having to remind myself that "that's not acceptable behavior" or restraining myself from doing something I would get a kick out of, but which most people would probably pull their children closer, if I followed through with it. For instance, I always feel compelled to goose an old person while they're shopping for produce, reading a package of English muffins or basically preoccupied with shopping. I try to convince myself I'm really doing it for them. Keeping them alert and on their toes, which all old people should be. But in reality, I just wanna hear them yelp or see their cute lil' faces twist up into what I like to refer to as "gnarly face."  I remember this one time I was in the frozen food section and this old lady was pretty much camped out in the TV dinners section. So I waited. And waited. And waited, for her to make a decision, so I could get on with my shopping and hopefully get home before nightfall (it was 3:30). So I kinda sneaked up beside her (out of view of her and others, of course) and made what I call "monster hands." You know, like when you're a little kid and you wanna be scary, you poise your hands like claws. So anyway, I'm passing the time by making monster hands and pretending to sneak up on her, all the while going "Grrrr" under my breath. Until she looked up and caught me. I quickly pretended to be yawning and stretching my hands, while checking my watch (which I wasn't wearing). She seemed to be none the wiser. From now on, monster hands are for behind the back, only. Not within the person's peripheral vision. Duly noted.   I've noticed I pretty much stick to three basic kinds of people, when humoring myself in public: Old people, hot guys and the stupid. Here's why:   Old people  usually bring out the "BOO!" inside me. Like, when I get stuck behind them for 20 minutes, 'cause they are diggin' in their purse or making a cart maneuvering decision or reminding themselves to breath. When these stall tactics take place, I wanna tippy tippy toe up behind them and scream "BOO!" or "MOVE!" But I don't, 'cause that would not be nice. But seeing them get some use outta those Depends would be kinda funny.   Hot guys  are just fun eyecandy. I've never been one to "cruise" someone, but I'm not blind either. I'll see the occasional hot guy and make my usual (internal) cat-from-Pepe Le Pew-cartoon-sound of "Rowr rowr," or the always favorable "Me likee." Unfortunately, I sometimes unintentionally forget to keep this to an inner dialogue and have been overheard once or twice. C'est la vie.  And last, but not least, my favorite:  Stupid people . Their favorite move seems to be parking their cart in the center of the fuckin' aisle, while they choose between Chicken Noodle or Chicken With Stars. Decisions, decisions. I can practically hear the Jeopardy music playing. Not the good version, but the version played with kazoos and paper combs. Normally I wait a minute or two for them to touch down on planet Earth, notice they are blocking the flow of traffic, and move their cart accordingly. When this doesn't happen, though, I like to do one of two things: 1) Move their cart for them. The look of panic on women's faces when they see their cart, with their purse in it, being moved, is priceless. 2) Go stand next to them and pretend to be contemplating, too. And by "stand next to," I mean getting into their personal space. Not quite touching them, but close enough to smell my breath. This seems to get them moving and on their way. It also clears them from any future aisles I may find myself shopping on. Neat.  Oh yeah, and for the odd behavior at home: My kitchen window is right across from my nosey neighbor's bedroom window (Ms. Fossil). So, late the other night, I was up making a sandwich and whilst cutting it in half, yelled "Hikeebah!" (It's a Tom Servo/Japanese thing. Think Emeril's "Bam!"), before realizing I did it so loudly. I'm sure she appreciated that.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Where do you fall on the liberal - conservative political spectrum?  (United States)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       AOL posts the top news stories on the main page on a daily basis, so that, along with the news and the newspaper, is how I go about seeing what's going on in the world these days. I read yesterday how George Dubya has recently thrown in his 2¢ on the subject of gay marriage. He's against it. Wow. Alert the media.  Now before I get into the whole gay marriage "thing" let me give you a little insight into my background as well as the whole gay subculture. I'll be primarily referencing gay MEN, since that's what I know. So, don't get the impression that I am anti-women/lesbian. However, I can't say that I don't have my prejudices within the gay subculture. I hate the words "gay community," because that implies unity, and that's not necessarily the case. There are WAY too many cliques within the so-called community, not to mention the dissension (Gay Republicans. Need I say more?). At least that's what I've experienced.  Sure, recent television shows and movies portray gay men as physically fit, good-looking, funny, fruity, promiscuous, well-groomed and of course, stricken with AIDS. Well, I hope you're sitting down, but trust me when I say not all gay men are all those things. There are plenty of average guys out there that believe in monogamy, love, God, etc. I personally have never been a big fan of organized religion (can you blame me?), but then that's a whole other blog. My point is, unless you know the person, don't automatically assume that they or their mores fit the stereotype for their particular "lifestyle."  On the other hand, I don't consider myself to be anything like the typical gay men that  I  meet:   • I don't do the bar scene. • I can't stand show tunes. • I don't believe in "open relationships."  • I don't dig the drag queen scene. (Not opposed to it, just not interested.) • I'm not a whore.  • My bathroom doesn't resemble a Clinique lab or GNC.  • I wear what I like. (Don't care about labels or names.)  • I'm not pretentious or high maintenance.  • I don't like to travel. • My cologne collection doesn't belong on a lazy susan.  I've never been to a gay pride parade. Mainly because I've never been brimming with pride about being gay. I'm not ashamed, in the closet or in denial, I just never had any reason to don some leather chaps and choreograph an elaborate routine involving a flag and handfuls of confetti.  I've been busy . If someone asks if I'm gay and I don't think it's any of their business, I have no problem telling them that. But I also don't edit my conversations for the comfort of others. I just don't have the energy, and besides, why should I? Secondly, I don't like parades. Too many children. I can't stand them (just shattered that stereotype about gay men fuckin' lil' kids). I'm totally content with the televised  urlLink Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade  once a year.  I know, what your thinking. I can hear the  urlLink Adam Ant  song playing in your mind:  Don't drink, don't smoke, what do ya do?  As little as possible.  Bada bing!  Thank you! Thank you! I'm here all week! T-shirts and CDs in the lobby! But seriously, I'm just me. That's the only way I know how to say it. I'm just a guy who enjoys  urlLink Chinese food , playing  urlLink Boggle , reading my weirdo books, shopping for and watching DVDs and hanging out with friends. I don't need someone to "complete me," but if someone comes along that I click with, then that's great. If not, that's cool, too.  Now, onto the whole gay marriage thing. I don't see the big deal, or really care one way or the other, to be quite honest. The only benefit I'd like to see come out of any of it, is to be able to legally have your significant other on your insurance, taxes, etc. Just to simplify things.   Then I read the AOL message boards (where people can post their thoughts on current events) and I remember why I find the whole gay topic depressing. No matter how much you think the world is becoming more tolerant, all you have to do is read the majority of the posts on AOL, to get a bitter dose of reality. I'll be bypassing the  urlLink Bible  monkeys. You know, the 'people' who brought us the clever "Adam & Eve, not Adam &  Steve !"   Wow, the words rhyme n' stuff. That's a keeper. Now let's think of something that rhymes with tribal!  I also won't linger on the people who like to think homosexuality is a choice, preference, sickness, etc.  What sane person wouldn't choose to be hated, not based on your mores or who you are, but what you are. Goodie gumdrops!  But the ones that irk me the most are the people who use taxes as an excuse to hate. Because of the beloved  children . So they don't want gay people to be able to claim their significant other on their insurance etc., because seemingly their insurance rates will go up. BUT the people who don't have kids are supposed to be okay with paying taxes for some bigot's genetic dingleberries to go to school? Shyeah! I think not. You wanted the little troglodytes so much, YOU pay for em'. This ain't no Whitney Houston song. I  don't  believe the children are our future.  And last, but certainly not least, how could any self-respecting gay person be "director of vice presidential operations for the Bush-Cheney re-election campaign?" Yep, that's right. One of Cheney's own kids is a lesbian. According to an article issued by the Associated Press, she's been "less visible" this year, due to "travel and working at campaign headquarters in Arlington, Va." However, she's expected to conveniently be more visible as election day nears, and undoubtedly be the GOP's "voice" for the homosexual people. Yeah, I think the word for that is ' token ' Let's hope she comes to her senses and gets some self-respect. Some people never learn.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've opted to postpone the book recommendations this weekend and instead, write about a movie I watched last night: Xanadu! You know, the " ...story about a girl who makes dreams come true! " Xanadu is what I lovingly refer to as  urlLink   Flash Gordon    with choreography. I own the DVD, so naturally I'm a fan. Here's hoping you are too.  After watching Xanadu, I thought I would get online and see what kind of reviews the average person gave it. The majority were overwhelmingly positive, but there was the occasional wet blanket looking to impress the reader with his/her handful of cinematic jargon. Such whiny complaints of bad plots and acting, to the superficial dislike of the wardrobe choices. Well, I'll be the first one to say that everyone is entitled to their opinion. Especially mine. The right one. Lol! Just kidding. But seriously, I don't think I'd probably want to know, much less be friends with, someone who's train of thought and sense of fun is so stunted as to go into a campy movie like Xanadu, looking for the cure for Cancer. It ain't here, folks. Xanadu is fun eyecandy with great music. Plain and simple. If you go into it with any other preconceived ideas, then you might as well stay home and watch Masterpiece Theater. This film wasn't made for you.   There's so many things that I enjoy about Xanadu. From the opening homage to the old  urlLink Universal  logo: When you see the airplane circling the Earth...changing into a 747...changing into a rocketship, and finally into a UFO, you know fun times are ahead. I also made a few observations this time around, that I thought were fun and/or interesting, from a social and trivia standpoint.   First off, anyone who knows me, knows that I am not a big fan of the whole interworkings of corporate America. I may be getting old, or maybe I'm just nostalgic for a time when things weren't as complicated. Perhaps a foreshadowing of what was to become, the scene where Sonny goes to talk to his boss who tells him " ...before you know it, you've got a bunch of people running around doing what they want to do. That's not a company, that's chaos. " Oh no! People doing what they want to do? The horror! The horror!   On the trivia front, I noticed that the rock that Gene Kelly's character, Danny, is sitting on, playing the clarinet, is the same rock that Robert Downey, Jr.sat on when he was strung out on coke in   Less Than Zero   (another 80's favorite of mine).  My favorite chapter on the DVD, which includes the original trailer, by the way (a definite plus), is chapter 13. The scene begins with Kira and Sonny taking Danny shopping for some new threads for the opening night of club Xanadu. The shopping spree turns into an all-out dance number, that reminds me of another favorite movie scene from Girls Just Want To Have Fun. Very fun. Great music. VERY 80's. Me likee.   So, if you get the chance, go rent Xanadu, or if you already own it, pop it in the ol' VCR/DVD player and be whisked away to a place where nobody dared to go, the love that we came to know. They call it Xanadu.  Where time stops and the magic never ends! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Stars In Your Kitchen edited by Marta Brookfield Michel. © 1953    This is one of my favorite retro recipe books (not to mention rare), simply because every recipe inside was submitted by a classic Hollywood movie star or personality! From Charles Addams to Richard Widmark, there are recipes from just about any major star of the time. In addition to the interesting recipes, there are also great little illustrated characatures of the various celebrities. One of my favorite recipes was submitted by Chico Marx:   • Macaroni a La Lido •   1 pkg. elbow macaroni 1/2 lb. sliced bacon cut small 1/2 cup chopped onions 1/2 cup diced celery 1/4 cup diced green peppers 1/2 cup grated cheese salt and pepper to taste 1 No. 2 1/2 can tomatoes     Cook macaroni, drain well. In a large skillet fry the bacon until light brown. Add onion, celery and green peppers. Cook on low fire till vegetables are tender, not brown. Add the tomatoes and stir well. On top sprinkle the macaroni and cheese, place in moderate oven and cook for about 20 to 25 minutes.     The Highly Unlikely Celebrity Cookbook by Frank Jacobs. © 1964    Another celebrity-flavored "cookbook" isn't really a cookbook at all, but more of a satire. With celebrity "recipes" endorsed by Cole Porter, Ian Fleming, Jimmy Hoffa and Alfred Hitchcock, you know your in for a treat. Being a fan of his films, naturally my favorite recipe was submitted by Alfred Hitchcock:   • Stewed Chicken Alfred Hitchcock •   1 5-pound hen 1 teaspoon of salt 1 cut lemon     In the dead of night, creep up quietly on a 5-pound hen and without no warning at all -- chop off its head! Clean the body thoroughly to remove all traces of your evil work, then rub with a cut lemon. Now place the succulent flesh in the dark confines of a deep, black cauldron and pour in hot water to the light of the full moon. After you have bolted all doors and drawn all shades, bring the water to a boil. Now slowly cook the body for 1 1/2 to 2 1/2 hours until it is excruciatingly tender, making sure to add salt and a few fiendish incantations at the end of the first hour. Allow the body to cool, then pluck it from the cauldron, place it on a plate, and  devour it.  When finished, bury the bones in the cellar. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ms. Fossil called on Wednesday to ask me  again  when I thought the tree trimming guy would be coming. I told her  again  that it's still 3 weeks, just like I told her 2 weeks ago. She then goes off on a tangent about how her yard man can't park in her driveway because his truck with the attached trailer full of yard implements is too long and how he has to carry everything from two houses down the street. ? I have no idea what this has to do with me, but then I've never been much of a visionary. She goes on to tell me how she has asthma, and that it's probably due to the hazy weather, undoubtedly caused by the forest fires raging in California. I manage to balance my checkbook, rewind a video that I rented and change clothes, all while she's telling me all this. Note to self: Must resist urge to kill.   I went to get a haircut, because it was "Wacky Wednesday" at the place I get my hair cut. By the way, it's $2 off on Wacky Wednesday, so then I can afford to give whoever cuts my hair, a tip. Otherwise, it's nearly $15! Insane. This time around I get a Korean woman, whom I've noticed isn't much for small talk, since I had to wait until she was finished cutting some guy's hair who was going on and on about how he was "never much one for fair food" but "enjoyed the Texas Star" (fyi the Texas Star is a HUGE ferris wheel, which is the centerpiece of the Texas State Fairair...next to Big Tex). She speaks really bad English, and it's my guess (which is confirmed later) that her grasp of understanding the English language is probably not up to par, either. Now for the pros and cons.   Pro:   She gave me a really good haircut.   Con:   She had some major B.O.   Pro:   I caught a few Z's while she was trimming my hair (I couldn't help it. Something about the combination of the vibration of the clippers and the sound of the thinning shears, makes me drift right off).   Con:   there was still some old snips of gray hair from someone's previous haircut, on the plastic bib thing tied around my neck. I dunno what it is about gray hair that creeps me out, but it does. I think it goes all the way back to when I moved into my first apartment and was cleaning out the cabinet underneath the sink, I found clumps of gray hair along the edge of where the carpet met the cabinet. Gross. Well, at least she was better than the last person who cut my hair. Some fat black chick who kept using her stomach to turn the chair around and apparently didn't realize (or care) that cutting hair where it falls onto your face the whole time, is not a good technique.   The grocery store I got to has some cutie guy checkers who also bag groceries. One's name is "Luke" (very soap opera) and is a "babe" (both figuratively and literally) and then there's "Tommy" who I always manage to catch taking a break by the Coke machines outside. I think they're cute, but they have the kind of hair that my friend Derik hates. Lol! Kinda like my dad and "those big-ass pants" that never seem to go outta style. I guess every generation has their teen peeves. Annnnnyway... Tommy's also cute, but not so much babe-worthy, but cute just the same (I think it's the tan and the big nose, but hey, that't me). Of course, he's also 11 years old (okay, maybe I'm exaggerating a little, but he might as well be). So, Tommy was scanning my groceries and notices I bought a container of popcorn chicken from the deli, and gets all excited, telling me how good they are. I say "Yeah, they really are" and he goes on to say how those and some Mountain Dew make the perfect lunch and that he's going to go get some in a few minutes. I share my top-secret knowledge that Mountain Dew and Hawaiian Punch make a great flavor combo, he says how he's never tried that but will have to now and then I leave. Bonding accomplished.   Went to the video store and returned  Adam & Evil  and checked out  Chopping Mall ,  Calendar Girls , and  Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen . Those reviews coming up later, once I've watched them all. And while we're on the subject of entertainment, I also bought 3 CDs and 3 DVDs. More about those later. So, I go to rent my movies and while the guy is checking out my movies, some customer comes in and he says "Hi," she looks his way, says nothing and keeps on truckin'. He's like "Um, okaaaay. Whatever" and looks at me. Knowing what it's like to work with the public, I've totally been there before. I say "It's amazing how many mute people there are in the world, huh?" and he laughs and says no kidding. Rapport established. So the guy is looking at the cover of Chopping Mall and says something about it looking interesting. I tell him that "yeah, it's a fun movie" and that it's coming to DVD soon, but I couldn't wait to watch it. He's looking at the back of the box and then it dawns on him what it's about and he goes bananas. He's all "Oh my god, I've been wanting to see this movie for so long! This is the one where the robot security guards go crazy and kill everybody in the mall." I'm like "Yeaaah. Good times." He's all "Chopping Mall! Oh my god, I didn't know that was the name, I can't believe we have that. I haven't seen that since like 1989." I say "Yep. It's an old one." (hey! I graduated in 1989!) and then start heading for the door, all the while he's still freaking out about it. Bonding session 2 accomplished.  And the cherry on the cake, you may ask? I come home from running all these errands and realize I neglected to lock the front door! Brilliant, Kirk, just brilliant. So then I spend the rest of the night playing scenes in my head, from that creepy made-for-TV-movie Hider In The House, starring Gary Busey. Ew, Gary Busey...::shiver:: creepy.  P.s. Let me preface this by saying that I live in a neighborhood, near a busy road. From time to time, there will be someone walking down the street during the day or night, for whatever reason (i.e. school, work, etc.)    For some unknown (and annoying) reason, it seems like our neighborhood has an unusual amount of power surges. This in turn, causes the breaker to my A/C to flip off sometimes, calling for me to go outside, to the side of the house, and flip it back on (see? I told you it was annoying). Well, last night it happened  again , 'cause I woke up feeling muggy and gross. So, around midnight, I go open the front door, flashlight in hand, to go outside and flip the switch. At the same time, some random guy happens to be walking by across the street, in front of my house. Well, my front door has an awful squeaky creak to it, which I, personally like for two reasons: A) It sounds great at Halloween and B) I like to think that I have a built-in early warning system, should a prowler break in to kill me in my sleep (yes, I'm a little paranoid). So anyway, I swing the front door open and some random guy walking on the sidewalk across the street jumps outta his hide, spins towards me and looks over, startled. I act like I don't notice, but on the inside, I am cracking up. I'm usually the one who's leery of people walking along the street at night and here I am making him skittish. Lol! Just thought I would share that with you, because I thought it was funny.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why is it every time I like something, they quit making it? Example: Pillsbury garlic breadsticks. They go great with spaghetti and are  so  doggone good! And now they're being "discontinued." But I love, thee, oh garlicky one! Just another food product that will soon be extinct. Sigh.  The more I thought about it, the more I realized just how many things I used to really look forward to eating, that are now no longer available. Things, that conjure up childhood memories, that when I mention them to anyone under 25, I get met with a blank stare. But then I remind myself that most Gen Y'ers normally have a glazed look to them anyway, and dismiss it as more pop culture ignorance. Here's a brief list of my top faves:  •   Chef Boyardee Roller Coasters   (Delicious pasta with meatballs) •   Crazy Cow Cereal   (Strawberry was my favorite, but it also came in chocolate) •   Grape Tang   (Grape-flavored version of the drink astronauts took into space!) •   Marshal Mallow Cocoa Mix   (Cocoa mix with little star-shaped marshmallows right in the mix!) •   Butoni Instant Pizza   (Like a Pop-Tart, but filled with delicious pizza goodness) •   Doritos Original Taco Flavor Chips   (Undoubtedly better than the "Nacho" flavored ones) •   Figurines   ("Diet" snack resembled a thinner Little Debbie Nutty Bar. Vanilla was my favorite) •   Franco-American Macaroni and Cheese   (Self explanatory) •   Vanilla-Flavored Cookie Crisp Cereal   (Better than the chocolate chip-flavor...but I like that one too) •   Willy Wonka Skrunch Bar   (Kinda like a Clark Bar, but skrunchier) •   Jolly Rancher Stix   (Came in Fire, Pink Lemonade and Peach flavors and was bigger than a JR) •   Mug-o-Lunch Mixes   (Kinda like Cup-O-Noodles. Just add hot water!)   And even though some of my favorites have survived the 70's and/or 80's, some of them just don't have the same flavor that I remember. For instance, my all-time favorite cereal was always Frankenberry (I still like it, but now I think it's more for the nostalgia, than the flavor), but now it seems to lack that certain oaty, strawberry flavor that I remember loving. Now it has that annoying flavor, like those french fries from Burger King that have that stay-crisp coating. You know what I mean? It's like the cereal now has a chemical shellac taste to it. Same thing goes for Trix, which I still like occasionally, but which I used to LOVE. "Back in the day" the cereal makers kept it simple, and the cereal pieces were shaped like little spheres (think Kix cereal in rainbow colors) and had a great corn and fruit taste. Today, they pieces are shaped like various fruits, and again have that weirdo shellac on them AND are so overly fruit-flavored that I find myself wanting more milk than cereal. Plus, there's a weirdo aftertaste that wreaks of "stay-crunchy" shellac. Bleah.  On the other hand, there are those foods that know a good thing when they see it, and manage to keep the original recipe & flavor of their product. Thank goodness for:  •   Munchos Potato Crisps   (Light and airy & loaded with salt and oil. I miss the bright orange bag) •   TAB Soda   (The quintessential 70's diet soda. I'm a saccharin fiend, so I still love it) •   Quisp Cereal   (A lot like Capt N' Crunch) •   Pringles Potato Chips   (They may have lost their pull-tab top, but they still taste good to me!) •   Razzles   (A chewable candy, that turns into gum! Is it a candy or is it a gum?) •   Shrimp Flavored Chips   (They may sound gross, but boy are they shrimpalicious!) •   Jiffy Pop   (You gotta love this one. JP wreaks of nostalgia. No one can resist its' foil dome!) •   Moon Pies   (Little Debbie comes closest to the flavor I remember, more so than the orig. MP) •   Reese's Big Peanutbutter Cup   (It's new & "limited edition," but already a favorite of mine)   I have to admit, I get nostalgic for some of the old packaging as well. I recently watched  You can't Buy Me Love  and sighed during a party scene when I saw the old Doritos bag. You know, the one with the little window in the front and the giant wedge of cheese on it? If only the manufacturers would periodically bring back a "Nostalgia" line of their products, with the original recipes and packaging, I bet you anything they'd sell like crazy. I know I'd be hoarding some serious Crazy Cow, Roller Coasters and Taco-Flavored Doritos!  And you know what else I miss? The shape of fishsticks. They used to resemble rectangles with rounded corners. Now fishsticks are more cylindrical and the taste just isn't the same. I swear the shape has something to do with it. It may sound weird, but I used to love when we would have fishsticks for lunch. Especially if there was a side of macaroni and cheese! This must be what lunch is like in Heaven.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Though I usually consider the world of professional wrestling (& NASCAR) to be the realm of the mullet crowd, I must come clean. I fall in lust with the occasional wrestler from time to time. The first wrestler I remember lusting after, was way back in the late 80's:  urlLink Lex Luger  (real name Larry Pfohl), AKA "The Perfect Package." Rowr rowr! Appropriately named, I instantly fell for Lex's pex and (yes again) his nose. My interest started to wane once he got all lean and defined and took on some hokey American Gladiator-style persona. Goofy red, white and blue costume to match. Not to mention his penchant for punchin' the ladies. Classy! I guess everything has a price. Regardless, I'll always have a soft spot in my heart for his random arrogant bouts of pec bouncing and flexing. Good times.   Fast forward to 1999 or so, and my ring had a new king: Big Poppa Pump (formerly Scott Steiner). I kinda knew who he was, before his new persona, but really took notice once he cut that damn brown mullet of his, dyed his hair blonde, grew a goatee and got into some serious pharmaceuticals. He had a great bod before, it just got bigger and more streamlined. Thanks Synthol! Regardless of the how and why, Big Poppa Pump emerged from his cocoon lookin' mighty pinchable. The only thing that kinda creeped me out about him, besides his relentless pursuit of the almighty panty hamster, was his unusually small forearms. They just don't match his HUGE biceps. I dunno if it's a genetic thing or a side effect of the "vitamins" but it was noticeable.  Well, it looks like the big P has all but disappeared from sight. I no longer see or read anything new about him. Since I never really watched his matches for the wrestling, I didn't keep up with the 'storyline,' so maybe he was written out, got too big for his britches (sigh) or was irreversibly injured in some way. All I have to remind me of him is a couple of misc. magazines and the occasional action figure. I miss my Big Poppa Pump. I hope he's doing okay.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Over the weekend, there was a piece on the news about how The University of Iowa was conducting research to better understand the cause of children's bicycle injuries. Due to advances in virtual reality the researchers were able to immerse children, ages 10-12, as well as adults, in a safe virtual environment, in order to observe bicycle safety behavior. Their conclusion. The reason children have bicycle accidents with vehicles: They didn't successfully judge traffic gaps. Wow. That's money and time well spent. Who needs a cure for Cancer, when we can pool our resources to find out that the reason kids become flattened fauna is because they didn't wait long enough to cross the street. Maybe these children should stick to less tasking past times like utilizing their motor skills with a  urlLink Lemon Twist  or perhaps start a leaf collection.    I'm more than a little tired of how today's kids have to be coddled and protected from everything from swallowing cereal prizes to inadvertently gutting themselves with a Snoopy Sno-Cone Machine. I find it incredulous that generations of children before them managed to survive Stretch Armstrong, E-Z Bake Ovens and playground equipment constructed of actual metal, all without losing an eye or somehow mangling themselves. Why, we even managed to not suffocate ourselves on the Twister mat or impale ourselves on Lincoln Logs. Wowee! We musta been some kinda mavericks! And on the rare occasion we  did  get hurt, our parent's first instinct wasn't "Someone must pay!." We both just marked it up to being a dumbass and knew not to do it again. Lesson learned.    But then today's parents have so much more to contend with, what with their ever-important cellphone calls and all, to do pesky stuff like pay attention to their children. Why take responsibility for not exercising common sense when you can just blame someone else and maybe get a settlement out of it in the process? What? You say your child got injured while running in the store like a maniac? It's not your fault. There were clearly no warning signs posted. What's that you say? While you were getting yourself a latte at  urlLink Starbucks , your precious angel was buried in a landslide of ceramic coffee cups, while climbing the display case like it was Mt. Everest? This clearly wouldn't have happened if more business establishments had child care centers. It's clearly their fault. I'd sue those rat bastards, if I were you.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever get those "Value Packs" in the mail, filled with coupons for everything from the local thrift store to fast food restaurants to pest control (where were they when I had that stalker 6 years ago?)? Well, I do and I always look through them and pick out the ones I'll use and ditch the rest. One thing I've noticed is that apparently all blue collar guys are hot lovemonkeys.    For example, check out this hunky "air duct maintenance technician." Check out those biceps and that face. He's a fox! My air duct guy never looks like this. Not to mention the cable guy, exterminator, mailman, plumber, electrician, etc.? You know, that whole fantasy, where the TV repairman drops by, is super hot and then steamy encounters take place.  Whatever . Now, I'm not lookin' for a little afternoon delight, but the occasional piece of eyecandy would be a nice change of pace. Instead, I get the deodorantly-challenged. The terminally married. The English is my  second  language (and I'm not that swift at the first one) guy (AKA Queso-&-so) and/or the ever-popular buttcrack guy. Swoon! ...Not.   Here's another ad for a local tune-up place. Who's mechanic looks like THAT? Bet he smells good too. All the guys at the garage I go to are Pakistani or look like Cooter from The Dukes of Hazzard.     As I thumbed through the various coupons, I came across one for laser hair removal.  There's a woman in a bikini quoted as saying "I'd love to get rid of my excess body hair and really learn to like myself." Who knew self-worth was just an electrolysis appointment away? Yeah right, good luck Sasquatch. And while I'm thinking about it, there's also an ad for some Herpes medication that claims to regulate your Herpes break outs so you can "take back control of your life." Um, you have  Herpes . I'd say control isn't one of your strong points. And while we're on the subject, why is it that all the people we see in Herpes ads always lead such vibrant and active lifestyles? So then, can we deduce that people with cold sores have bouts with 'keeping up with the Joneses?' I don't know about you, but I sometimes find myself secretly yearning for Herpes, just so I can go to the beach and/or go bicycling through a lush forest glen, and leave this tedious existence behind once and for all. I know it sounds selfish, but I'd really love to catch up on my leisure reading.  Herpes: They're not just for 'hos anymore! Get Herpes and start living life in the fast lane!  To see just how specialized our society has become, check out the online  urlLink Herpes singles dating service!  'Cause nuthin' says romance like a raging case of Herpes!  And finally, the ad I see at my online bank website. I guess there are businesses out there that still believe in "keepin' it real":    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         The first time I saw it, was the summer of 1985, while on vacation with my parents. We saw it at a drive-in theater in Wisconsin. I remember thinking it was the best thing  ever . I remember reading the paperback and anything else 'Goonies' I could get my hands on. I also remember staying up late to watch  Friday Night Videos (network television's answer to MTV), to see the "debut" of the Cyndi Lauper music video!   Last night I went to the midnight movie at the Inwood Theater and saw The Goonies on the big screen, for the first time in 19 years! The Goonies has it all: Great cast, comedy, adventure, you name it! I was mesmerized from beginning to end, and tonight was no exception. Sure, I own the DVD, but nothing compares to seeing it on the big screen with an appreciative audience.     The theater I went to see the movie at, is a Landmark theater, in more ways than one. It's been around for 57 years and is one of the sole survivors of the 1940s movie palaces.  urlLink The Inwood Theater  has that incredible nostalgic soul, that today's theaters lack.  You get a distinct sense of participating in a piece of cinematic history, just by being in its' presence. You know, the huge marquee with lights around it, the foyer ceiling covered in lights, and the "old school" tubular ticket booth. SUCH great atmosphere. As you enter the small lobby, the first thing your eyes are drawn to is the incredible domed ceiling, which has a mural painted on it. There's is a huge red-carpeted staircase, off to the right and on the left is a cafe/coffee shop, marked off by glass bricks. There are two small theaters upstairs (I got nauseous in one of them while seeing The Blair Witch Project). Straight ahead is the small concession stand, which I am pleased to say offers tea. I know it sounds kinda square, but I prefer tea to soda, when I go to the movies, and most theaters don't offer it. After the concession stand, there are two sets of double doors which go into the foyer of the main theater, which is HUGE and originally seated 1,100 people! There is even a little stage at the base of the movie screen. Sigh. Breathtaking.  I got to the theater about 20 minutes early and found a great parking space. On the way to the theater I walked past a couple (her sitting on a bench, him kneeling on the ground in front of her) who were apparently having an argument. She looked like she was about to cry (mad) and he was desperately trying to talk his way outta whatever it was. The drama. The drama. Let's hope they get married and make it official. So, I get in line behind the Aqua Teen Younger Force and got my ticket. Then to the small bathroom (this is my movie ritual: Ticket, bathroom, concession stand, theater), which is old and small and has a cloth shower curtain separating the 1 toilet from the 2 urinals & sink. After getting to hear how "this bathroom sucks," (Gen Y, you know I love em'!) I washed my hands (you wouldn't believe how many guys don't) and went to get provisions and find a seat.   I was surprised how many teens there were. I was expecting a more mature crowd, like when I went to go see  Fast Times At Ridgemont High . Before the show begins, a theater employee comes out and there's a contest to win the DVD version of whatever movie is that night's main attraction. However, this time, in addition to the DVD giveaway, there was also a  Truffle Shuffle  contest! LMAO! He asked for volunteers and about 7 vibrant, fresh-faced teens went up (2 girls, the rest guys). The guy prefaced the contest by first making sure everyone knew what the Truffle Shuffle was. One didn't. My first reaction is "beat it, dillhole," but I kept that to myself. So the guy asks for one of them to demonstrate it to him. This one guy volunteers and kicks ass! Then the contest starts and the nonexistent (ech...what ever ) teen bellies are a shakin'! When they are done, the guy holds his hand over each person's head and the one who receives the most applause wins. The one I wanted to win, and clapped for, won (the guy who demonstrated the Truffle Shuffle for the benefit of IdiotBoy). He was the only one who had remotely any tummy and his Truffle Shuffle rendition rocked da hizouse! The prize: a pint of Rocky Road ice cream (with spoon)!! The runner-up (IdiotBoy, much to my chagrin) also got a pint. I didn't win the DVD, but some jailbait in a tubetop won it, and, get this, she doesn't even own a fuckin' DVD player. Whatever.   The movie starts and everyone claps once the skull and crossbones appear on the screen and we're off! Now, I must confide something. I LOVED the entire cast (yes, even Corey Feldman, whom I normally  despise ), but my favorite Goonie was Martha Plimpton's character (' Stef ') and my first cinematic crush: Josh Brolin (' Brand '). God, I remember thinking he was the hottest thing since  urlLink Lou Ferrigno  as  The Incredible Hulk . ROWR ROWR! Thus began my love-affair with Brand and The Goonies. Josh is still a hottie (when he opts to bathe, shave and brush his hair) and has been in some other favorite movies of mine. I just recently bought  Thrashin' , just for  him. Definitely worth the price.    While on the subject of hotties, at the time I thought Sean Astin (' Mikey ') was pretty insignificant. Wow! Who knew he would turn out to be such a babe? I could give two elf farts for those  Lord of The Rings  movies, but I think he's just  too  cute. Esp. when he has a beard. Rowr!  It was a lot of fun to be a part of something you know everyone loves. I also got a kick out of the scene where Sloth exclaims "Hey you guys!," just before he saves the day, 'cause the entire audience cheered and clapped. And during the scene where Mikey opens the hatch to the "rich stuff", you could have heard a pin drop. It was great! And naturally, there was plenty of clapping at the end, while The Goonies theme played in the background during the credits. A great audience experience, overall. Not one single cell phone ringing or dumbass in the bunch (with the exception of IdiotBoy, of course). Fun was had by all.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Stop the presses! Light the fireworks! The tree trimmers  finally  arrived (Thursday) and trimmed the tree in my backyard! As I mentioned in the July 1st post, my next door neighbor, Ms. Fossil has been losing sleep over my tree's branches hanging precariously over her storage shed in her back yard, like some dark evil. She's been relentless in calling me to check on the status of the trimming. Thank god, they came when they did. I was beginning to search online for Jim Jones' Kool-Aid recipe.  So, the guys (5) show up at 8:30 and I take the guy who seems to be in charge, to the back and we go over which branches are to be cut. I'm kinda nervous, because (again), English isn't his forte, so I end up using my hands a lot, when talking to him about what limbs need to be removed, etc. I inadvertently pick a large branch that wasn't one of the ones that was included in the original estimate, and he said it was way too big and that it would cost more, so I just told him to go ahead and cut the ones closest to her shed's roof and that that should be fine. So, before they can get to work, I have to call Ms. Fossil and let her know that they have to get into her backyard. I call and alert her and then all systems are go.    I don't want to be under the tree trimmer's ass the entire time he's working, like my mom used to do whenever we had service men out, or breathing down their neck, like when the clerk at the grocery store was ringing up the groceries (that was "quiet time" and any conversation from me was met with a "Shush!" through gritted teeth. Thanks, mom). However, I had to keep vigil on Ms. Fossil's yard, via the den window, in case she decided to waddle out there and "coach." I told the guy when he first got here, that she might try to come out and dictate which branches to cut, but reminded him that she ain't payin' for it/ So, should there be any doubts, just come get me and I'd be more than happy to help clear up any misconceptions. Well, Ms. Fossil must have realized it was in her best interest (and health) that she stay safely indoors. Afterall, we wouldn't want any of those nasty branches driving her sweet, little body into the ground, like some sort of gray-haired tent spike, now would we?  So, about an hour and a half passes (I had lots of brush piles, too), and the guy comes to the door to let me know they're finished. He goes with me to the backyard to check it out, and 'lo and behold, who do you think magically appears, like some sort of geriatric leprechaun? You guessed it. Ms. Fossil. She's already there, inspecting. First off, let me say they did an  amazing  job. It looks really great and made a world of difference. They picked up ALL the debris from trimming the tree and even got the few dead branches (all 5) that had fallen from  my  tree (the ones she's been obsessing over and repeatedly reminding me of, for the past month).    I'm really pleased, but guess who has 2¢ to contribute? Right, again. Ms. Fossil. Instead of having something positive to say about how good it looks, she points out the one branch (the one that I had originally picked out and was subsequently told was way too big and high and would cost more) and says " I don't know... don't you think that one should come down, too? It's still hanging over the roof of my shed and I'm worried what will happen if it falls. " Well, short of a 300lb squirrel deciding to use it as a trampoline or a stray bolt of lightening, it ain't coming down. It's healthy, it's at least 50ft above the roof and doesn't show any signs of being thin and/or brittle. I tell her "Not anytime soon. He just finished trimming what I can afford. That's it for today (I was tempted to add a "buy-bye now. buh -bye," but didn't)." The guy even says that he doesn't see any reason for concern. I then tell her (to deter any future phone calls or impromptu chats, on the way to my car) that "should there be any more branches fall in her yard, to just have her yard men toss them over into my yard", not unlike the little pile she had them deposit near my A/C unit. Fuckin' petty old dwarf! And she (get a load of this) looks to the tree trimmer guy and actually has the gall to say " Oh, I'm not worried about the branches that fall in the yard, just the roof of the shed. "  WTF?  I have to control myself from leaping over the fence and giving her an enema with her own lawn angel. Sideways! She's been bitching about the fucking branches from day one. Geez. She then continues repeating her concerns all over again about the roof. I whisper to him "she needs some alone time, let's go get that check I owe you," while making "she's cuckoo" eyes in her direction, and we walk away, leaving her to commune with nature. Good riddance. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay, I admit it. I'm guilty. That's right, I readily admit that I have rented and/or sat through movies I cared nothing about, just to get to the beefcake. I have no regrets. Don't look at me like that, I'm sure you've done it before too. I know for a fact some of my friends have done it. My friend, Nathan, for example, just admitted that he's actually going to pay money to go see Halle Barry's new litterbox fodder, Cat Woman. But who am I to scoff, I've sat through worse. Much worse. At least his movie will have big name stars, cutting-edge special effects and a budget that rivals The Matrix. While, the movies I've sat through were lucky if they got on set catering from the likes of Hot Pockets.   Growing up gay in a small town, surrounded by less-than-accommodating hicks, kinda limits your access to gay-themed movies, much less all-male action. I had to be creative and just a little bit sneaky. Having a muscle/bodybuilder fetish early on, I'd rent movies like: • Ator The Fighting Eagle • Hercules In New York • Deathstalker • For Ladies Only (Rented it for "my mom") • Campus Man • HUNK • IronMaster • Stay Hungry • Killer Workout   As you can see, more than a few of them were those godawful "sword and sandal"-type movies and a couple of them starred Arnold Schwarzenegger, who has masterful pecs, but whose mentality is for the birds. But then who really cares how big a hot guy's brain is? Looking back at some of them, I realize how my tastes have evolved over time and also come to the realization just how bad 80's hair really was. I still buy/rent the occasional movie for the voyeur in me, but I've noticed that more and more of the actors I like, leave me cold in the bod department, but have beautiful faces and/or aspects to their personalities: Vince Vaughn, Richard Gere, Jude Law, Antonio Banderas, Johnny Knoxville, Craig Bierko, Nicholas Brendon, Carson Daly (I  know . Everyone thinks he's a tool), Eminem, etc. Don't get me wrong, I still like the bods, but the faces & personalities seem to have moved up on the priorities list. Who knows, maybe I'm evolving.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Final Cut. Starring Jude Law. ©1998    The camera never lies...it's a pity about friends   Synopsis:  The film opens with the cast gathering after the funeral of Jude to see a film he had been working on for two years. It turns out that the film is secret videos of all those gathered together in their most despicable moments including thievery, spousal abuse, adultery, etc. The revelations remove the masks from the so-called close friends.  Comment:  Since I pretty much own all Vince Vaughn & Jude Law movies available, adding this one to my collection was a no-brainer. Initially this film wasn't available in the US in any format. I bought a bootleg version of it on VHS on eBay and was happy to finally get it on DVD.      Cruel Intentions 3. Starring Kerr Smith. © 2004    The 3rd time's a charm...   Synopsis:  Cassidy Merteuil, the distant cousin of Kathryn Merteuil, arrives in Santa Barbara, California to attend college where she meets Jason Argyle, a former friend from her high school also attending the school, while Jason gets a roommate, Patrick Bales, whom he and Jason form a mean-spirited partnership of seducing and dumping various young women on campus. When both of their latest conquests bore them, Jason bets Patrick if they can bed out a particular newcomer under the wing of Cassidy. But nothing is what it seems as a triangle of Cassidy, Jason and Patrick forms with each one scheming to outwit the other.  Comment:  I loved the original Cruel Intentions and the movie it was a remake of, Dangerous Liaisons. However, I find the concept of making straight-to-video sequels, pretty lame (i.e. Bring It On, Wild Things, etc.) and really have no interest in most of these so-called "sequels,"  until  I saw that Kerr Smith is in the 3rd one. He purty.     The Triplets of Belleville. © 2003    Synopsis:  Adopted by his grandmother Madame Souza, Champion is a lonely little boy whose only friends are his loyal puppy Bruno and his tricycle. As an adult, Champion enters the world-famous cycling race, the Tour de France. In the midst of his race, Champion is kidnapped by two mysterious men in black and when he does not cross the finish line, Madame Souza and her faithful dog Bruno set out to rescue him. Their quest takes them across the ocean to the giant megalopolis of Belleville where they encounter the renowned "Triplets of Belleville," three eccentric female music-hall stars from the '30s.  Comment:  The DVD contains the music video for the infectious theme song:  Belleville Rendez-Vous , sung by "M," whose real name happens to be Mathieu Chédid (see inset for picture). For some strange reason I find him hauntingly attractive, with his French  Flock of Seagulls  'do.     Classic TV Commercials. © 2003    Synopsis:  Those classic ads from yesterday are back once again for your ultimate viewing pleasure! This DVD is devoted entirely to commercials with more of a feminine mystique associated with them. These unintentionally hilarious ads were written by men and directed at women, in a time when male chauvinism was a way of life! So sit back, relax and enjoy loads of commercials not interrupted by that irritating regularly scheduled programming!  Comment:  Picture quality on these is TONS better than some other shit disc I bought a year earlier, though I wish there were more "fun" ones that I remember. i.e. "Ancient, Chinese secret, huh?" (Calgon), cereal commercials, etc. However, some favorites on this disc include: Bewitched: Elizabeth Montgomery for Clairol, QT Quick Tan, Pringles, etc.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I was dusting the bookshelves the other day and decided to sit down and look through some old scrapbooks and photo albums. For someone who detests having their picture taken, I sure take a lot of pictures. Anyway, as I started looking through the albums, I started thinking of how many people I've befriended and subsequently lost contact with and/or have fallen outta like with. Starting from 1990 (the year I entered Junior College), here's the list of friends of the past:  • Chad • Lacy •  Moira  •  Chris  •  Bill  • Dan • Nathan • Dennis •  Andrea  •  Elsa  •  Tonia  •  Cathy  • Kelly • Nancy • Tomm •  Kelea & John  •  Robyn & Steve  •  Frank & Steve  • Yolanda & Xander •  Sonny & Robert  • Starla & Michael •  Blake & David  •  Arnie & Jon  •  Dru & Dean  •  Vickie & Steve    I estimate that approximately  9%  of my past friendships eventually ended once that person/couple moved away.  2%  mysteriously ended with no explanation.  4%  ended after a falling out and the remaining 10% ended due to lack of communication, etc. The "etc." ranging from one friend who turned out to be a needy stalker ( Imagine 7-8 phone calls a day + if i didn't answer the door, he would go from window to window, trying to see if I was home! ) to one couple who I finally cut loose because I gave up on being the one who did all the work. i.e.- birthday remembering, phone calling, card sending, hosting, etc. After taking a good hard look at the list I realized that I still miss the friendships of exactly 3 individuals and 3 couples.  Out of all the friendships that have come and gone, the ones that bother me the most are the ones that ended with no explanation, no closure. Pretty cowardly, if you ask me, but then I've learned to roll with the punches. Now, I know what you're thinking (I've considered it, too). "Maybe you were too needy or too negative." On the contrary, I make a concerted effort not to be that gloomy gus people dread being around, nor the person whom calls so often that you start screening the caller I.D./answering machine. I've been on the receiving end of those traits and I don't like em' either. On the other hand, I'm always the one that keeps everyone laughing with my sarcasm. Maybe that's it. Maybe I was too sarcastic. Who knows. Maybe it had nothing to do with me at all.   As you get older, it becomes harder and harder to make new friends. It's like that time I was complaining to my mom, when I first moved here, about how difficult it is to meet people, especially when you don't get into the bar scene. And my mom, having grown up in the 50's, still has that 50's mentality. Her suggestion: go up to someone interesting, who was also alone, in the library, cafeteria, etc., introduce yourself and take it from there. Yeah. You know what happens when you do that? You get looked at like you just handed them a piece of paper that says "Give me all your money. This is a stick up." People today are just too suspicious, and I can't say I can really blame them, what with all the weirdness going on in the world today. It's unfortunate when something as innocent as looking to meet new people is looked upon as the realm of the spastic or the psychotic. And if you're thinking of going the whole Dear Abby route, by suggesting joining a group/club with people who have the same interests, that doesn't work either. I took tennis lessons for 3 summers in a row, joined a gay men's discussion group, volunteered and even resorted to personal ads (I'm currently working on a book about all my horrendous "dates."). I'm at a loss for ideas. I talk to a few people online who I enjoy talking to, but it'd be nice to have someone around to do stuff with from time to time. Even if it's just to play Boggle and order in Chinese food.  And on a closing note, should you find yourself feeling lonely and like nobody understands you, here is my prescription: Rent any (or all) of the movies below or better yet, make them a part of your DVD/VHS collection. Guaranteed to bring a smile to your face!   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Yesterday, I was listening to the radio and a fuckin' "slow jam" came on! LMAO! I thought the popularity of the  slow jam  was something that died a dusty death, back in the mid-late 90's. And this was no classic slow jam, this was a  NEW  slow jam.   For those who may not be familiar with the slow jam's "style," I'll explain: A slow jam is one of those songs that has an urban mid-tempo feel to it, where the singer "talks/sings" all breathless, and/or faux sexy-like. The slow jam is supposed to be the song(s) you put on when you wanna be wit yo lady. (insert sarcastic fart sound here). Some slow jam artists might include: Johnny Gill, Klymaxx, Monifah and the Tevin Campbell.   It took some investigating ('cause I'm not down with the new slow jams), but apparently the new song I heard was by Usher and called "Burn." Initially, it was kinda sexy (his voice), and reminded me a little of  urlLink Marky Mark , the Brooklyn accent thing (always sexy, BTW), but then the lyrics kicked in and the breathless sexiness and I started to crack up. With lyrics like "  Man I don't know what I'm gonna do without my booo ," (I initially thought he said "Don't know what I'm gonna do without my pooh"), can you blame me? This song epitomizes the new slow jam, especially when the singer starts talkin' real fast with lyrics like " Callin' her your name / Ladies tell me do you understand? / Now all my fellas do you feel my pain? / It's the way I feel / I know I made a mistake / Now it's too late ." The cheesiness of it all makes me think of  urlLink The Ladies Man  character from Saturday Night Live. I wanna be bustin' out the vanilla-scented candles, some ice-cold Malt Duck, sprinkle some rose petals around the room, dim the lights and light some incense, bruh. If you happen to enjoy slow jams, then you're sure to enjoy these sites:  •  urlLink New Black Music.net  •  urlLink Soul-patrol Streaming Radio  •  urlLink Sirius Radio.com- Slow Jamz 52  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's some of the things that I observed or had thoughts about on my recent trip to the grocery store.   When did cookies get to be so complicated, not to mention expensive? Sure, it's nice to have choices, but sometimes you just want a plain oatmeal cookie, ya know? But can I find a quality, plain ol' oatmeal cookie? No, but I can find Raisin Raisin Oatmeal, Chocolate Chunk Pecan, Peanut Peanutbutter, Belgian Chocolate Chunk and Chocolate Chip Macadamia. And why are Pinwheels $4? Are they that complicated to make? I can get the same flavor effect with a $1.09 box of Little Debbie Marshmallow Cream Pies. Weird.   Some guy just walked by and he smelled like grape Kool-Aid. You know, like that smell/taste you get when you pour the Kool-Aid mix into a deep pitcher and the dust from the powder floats up into the air. He smelled like that. Yum!   I just manhandled a box of crackers off the shelf and started an avalanche of flavor. I hate it when they stack shit so close to the edge, that the slightest move makes it fall off the fuckin' shelf, and in turn, starts a domino effect on everything it hits on the way down. Then I end up looking like a some goddamn third rate juggling act from Circus of The Stars.   In order to appease my hunger for cheese and crackers (look out  urlLink Wallace & Gromit !), I took a close look at all the cheeses. Decided on an offbrand, until, upon closer inspection, noticed it said " cheese product. " What the hell does that mean? Sounds like a sneaky way of saying "not cheese." I opted for the store brand, which  is  actual cheese.   Ooh,  urlLink Duncan Hines  has a new line of brownie mixes called Candy Shoppe. Apparently they come in Twix, Reese's Peanutbutter Cups, m&ms and Butterfinger falvors. Yum! But why is it nearly $4 a box? Couldn't I just buy the Duncan Hines brownie mix that's on sale for $1 and add the candy of my choice for another buck?   I swear to God, I thought I was in a Budweiser commercial from the 70's. All that was missing was jingle bells and snow. I heard CLIP CLOP! CLIP! CLOP! CLIP CLOP!, coming my direction, from behind. It was some chick in clogs. Can she not hear herself? Geez, everyone else sure can. Doesn't she realize she sounds like the fuckin Little Dutch Boy on a stickhorse? Damn.   Nobody noteworthy on the cover of any of the magazines this time. Looked at the books. Saw one called  Fields of Honor: The Pat Tillman Story . Apparently some guy who used to play professional football (the Cardinals, I think) voluntarily joined the Army. Whoopee. He's hot, though. Rowr!   Some woman just yelled at her kid because she "wants to get home before it rains." It's supposed to rain today? So? I don't get why people here in Texas get so worked up over rain. I could understand if you had no functioning windshield wipers, but goddamn, it's just water. Relax, turn on your headlights and drive like a normal person. Idjits.   On the way home I pass a church whose sign out front says: " Because we've been found, we have  a mission to find the lost. " Who exactly is "we" and how did anyone know you were missing? Maybe you were found because the lost ratted you out. Or maybe, the lost don't wanna be found, ever think of that? Maybe the found people need to get lost. Religious people freak me out.   Oh, and while I'm on the subject of freaking out, here's something I'm sure our little church friends can appreciate. My chicken. Yep, it's official. I'm going to Hell. I wonder which side dish Satanic chicken prefers:  urlLink Stove Top  or mashed potatoes? Maybe I'll make both and really raise some Hell.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Confessions of a Teenage Drama Queen. © 2004      I've grown to like Lindsay Lohan, though I must admit I was livid when I first heard news that Disney was remaking one of my favorite movies, The Parent Trap. Blasphemy! I eventually rented it, but it lacked the magic of the original. Lindsey was cute, but was no Hayley Mills. Back to CTDQ. The movie had a sense of fun and Lindsay's character was likable, as were the supporting characters. I was surprised to see that the movie was light in the comedy department. The trailer led me to believe that there would be more laughs, but the laughs seemed to be confined strictly to the trailer. On the plus side, there was Carol Kane and the male lead was mighty fine (Adam Garcia). Overall, it was a little too Hilary Duff with a severe case of girlpower, for my tastes, but tolerable.   ∑∑      Calendar Girls. © 2003      Wow, this movie  finally  came out. I remember seeing it advertise well over a year ago, and have been wanting to see it ever since. Well, I finally rented it and it wasn't half bad. It had a Saving Grace feel to it, if you've ever seen and/or enjoyed that movie. Most men and the likes of Gen Y can't seem to get over the idea that the plot involves a group of 60-something women getting "nude" (to pose for a calendar to raise money for Leukemia). I've never been one for the whole "ew" attitude, so it doesn't bother me in the least. Besides, if you're of the "ew" persuasion, then it's probably got way too much of a plot for you to bother with and you might as well go rent some "sweet-ass" (or with today's kid's spelling "sweat -ass") XXX or Torque movie. Anyway, the movie was a lot of fun, though the buzz kinda wore off towards the end, when it gets kinda preachy and self-righteous.   ∑∑  1/2     Adam & Evil. © 2004      Okay, okay. I know, what you're thinking: "He'll rent anything!" Well, it's kinda true...when it comes to slasher flicks. Growing up in the 80's, I LOVED slasher flicks and still do. However, as a rule, I pretty much know that any slasher flicks that come out these days (esp. straight-to-video) are gonna probably not be up to par. However, every once in a while, when there is a horror drought in the new release section, I'll take a chance and rent one that has a great cover, familiar premise and/or a killer with a nasty penchant for sharp things and/or a cool costume. Well, Adam & Evil was actually all right. I read some dumbasse's review on IMDB, who evidently didn't watch the movie. He also was baffled by why it was called Adam & Evil. Um, hello.  WARNING:  Spoiler: The main character's name is Adam and there's a girl named EVElyn....who's uh, well, evil. Doi. That's rocket science.  Not.  So, anyway, the movies' overall look was better than I expected. I was SO hoping I hadn't rented another one of those cheap-ass movies that looks like someone shot it on their camcorder. I am SO bad at falling for their cool cover art. In addition to the professional look, the movie also some occasional original, cool music. The killer had a cool m.o. (leaving a roman candle at the scene of the crime) and the implements of murder + the murders were pretty fun, too. Not a lot of gore, but enough to make it worth the rental. Also, the one cute guy ("Seth") was also some nice eyecandy. Now the downside: Wow, was the acting and the dialogue ever BAD. The badly delivered teen urban lingo was SOOO corny, I swear I could taste the nibblets. Also, the ending was pretty cheese-o-riffic and like I mentioned earlier, not enough gore in the murder sequences. Would have liked to see a little more Friday The 13th-style killings.   ∑∑∑      Chopping Mall. © 1986      With dialogue like "In about an hour and a half we bail this BBQ and it's good times to the max!" (said to a fellow co-worker at their fast food job at the mall), it could only be an 80's B movie. Mmmm, can you smell it's fetid goodness? Is it a plausible concept? Of course not. Is it dated? Oh yeah. Okay, so this movie isn't going to win any awards, but I still love it for the cheese-addled late 80's horror classic that it is. Plus, there's a fairly good body count/gore factor  AND  one of my many 80's dream hunks (AKA Deathstalker in Deathstalker 2-4), John Terlesky can be seen in all his  pec tacular-chiseled-jaw-glory. Who could ask for more?  ∑∑∑∑      Lord of The Rings: Return of The King. © 2003      Okay, I admit to being bored one day and renting this on PayPerView. I generally relegate this type of movie for the Renaissance Festival crowd, but in my defense, the only reason I PPV'ed it was because I was too lazy to go rent it and I heard there's some Eijah nip towards the end. Well, Elijah nip or not, he wasn't worth the 8 hours it took to get there (okay, I'm exaggerating a little. It was just 6 hours....jk). Seriously though, this was the longest nymph turd I've ever had to sit through, since I saw Willow. I just don't get these kind of movies. In it's defense, it looked and sounded beautiful (score), but 9X out of 10 I had no idea, nor did I care, what anyone was talking about. Apparently there's some evil piece of jewelry floating around and it must be destoyed. Neat. Whatever. Let's pick up the pace, people! So, the Elijah nip scene was way too dark and way too brief to have made this worth my time. I ended up forward winding through most of it out of sheer impatience. P.s. I totally don't get the whole Orlando Bloom appeal.   ∑    ∑ = I want a refund  ∑∑ = Wait and watch it on cable  ∑∑∑ = Worth the rental  ∑∑∑∑ = I'd buy it...for the right price  ∑∑∑∑∑  = I'd add it to my movie collection
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hi gang! I recently went to one of the best new/used CD stores in Dallas and bought lots of great CDs. I've hyperlinked all the titles (primarily to Half.com, 'cause they are a lot cheaper than SchmAmazon). There's a little something here for just about everyone, so be sure and check them out.   •  urlLink  Cleopatra Enchantments. © 1995   Great remixes of various Industrial artists: Spahn Ranch, Frontline Assembly & more!  My Rating:  ****  •  urlLink Blue Break Beats: Vol. 1. © 1993  This is volume 1 of a 3 volume set. The entire "Blue" series kicks ass.  My Rating:  ****  •  urlLink The Legendary Big Band Vocalists. © 1995  A must-have for fans of Big Band music and/or Jazz. Various artists, such as Ella Fitzgerald, Peggy Lee, Doris Day.  My Rating:  *****  •  urlLink Maroon 5: Songs About Jane. © 2004  I LOVE this entire CD.  My Rating:  *****  •  urlLink Big Floor Funk. © 2004  Awesome dance CD, from beginning to end! My favorite track: "Sexy." Good through and through.  My Rating:  *****  •  urlLink My Life With The Thrill Kill Kult: Dirty Little Secrets: The Remixes. © 1999  Great remixes for fans of Thrill Kill Kult, but be warned, not all are gems.  My Rating:  ***  •  urlLink Wild Cool & Swingin: Wayne Newton. © 1999  Another CD I love from beginning to end. I've been looking for a good Wayne Newton collection, and this one fit the bill!  My Rating:  *****  •  urlLink The Killers: Hot Fuss. © 2004  Love the entire CD. You can't go wrong with this one.  My Rating:  *****  •  urlLink The Stills: Logic Will Break Your Heart. ©2004  Hate to sound like a broken record, but again, I loved this entire CD.  My Rating:  *****  •  urlLink Industrial Virus: Disc 1. ©1997  Wow. This one really takes me back to the early 90's. Totally great collection of Industrial favorites! New Order, Orbital, The Shamen, Skinny Puppy, Tackhead, Meat Beat Manifesto.  My Rating:  *****
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       While listening to the radio, I noticed just how retarded the lyrics to a lot of the commercials, especially fast food, really are. And how misleading. Take Poncho's Mexican Buffet, for instance: " Raise the flag, raise the flag, you're ready for a little more Poncho's Mexican Buffet. "...and subsequently, a little more  diarrhea . McDonald's: " Tastes so good, I can't contain it. What's special sauce? I dunno, can't explain it. " Yeah, you know why you can't contain it? It's called Olean. And that "special sauce," it's called French Dressing. McDonald's, I'm not lovin' it. First it was Hip Hop. Then this Smashmouth-sounding jingle and the latest one I saw on TV was some Techno Rave version where people are coming in so late (from DJ'ing et al), that nothing but McGriddles will appease their hip, youthful cravings. Whatever. Stop the MTV madness, Ronald.   Lifetime (Television for battered wives) has been airing episodes of Laverne & Shirley, early in the mornings. They started out with the classic episodes, back when  urlLink Laverne & Shirley  still worked at the brewery. However, after only a week or so, they switched over to the super-lame older episodes, where Shirley had gotten married and moved away, leaving Laverne on her own in L.A. ( Personally, I thought the move to L.A. was the beginning of the end...but the new "cousin" was hunkalicious...rowr! ) Boy, all I can say is that I hope Penny Marshall was making these episodes because she was obligated by contract, not because she actually believed the show was still funny. Yikes.   Only AOL could label M. Night Shyamalan the "King of The Twist." Gimme a fuckin' break. I love how the entertainment industry jumps on these one-hit wonders bandwagon and instantly label them cinematic geniuses. Hardly. I admit to liking The Sixth Sense, had no interest in Unbreakable and wanted a refund after renting Signs (the inopportune "precious moments" scenes were too sappy for me). First off, the name itself is the biggest gimmick I have seen since the director "McG," whose style, I admit to liking, what with his saturated, high Pop-style, but the name is beyond pretentious. And while we're on the subject of pretentious, Shamalamadingdong's compulsion to have cameos in all his films, is a serious case of "been there, done that (much better)." Alfred Hitchcock he ain't. Strictly a director for the mall crowd.   While doing my usual sweep of the Internet for fun and/or unusual pictures, I had the misfortune of stumbling across this website for  urlLink "Cherished Friends ." Some goober named Lee Middleton makes these collectible monstrosities, which I'm sure Home Shopping Network sells out of on a regular basis. I've never been one of those people who find dolls and/or clowns  scary , so that's not what I dislike about them. I just find the fact that someone out there actually shelled out $150 for this gopher shit in a dress. I think they all look like they have Downs Syndrome, but I'm sure some "collector" out there, thinks they are just  precious . The ones shown here are called "Applelicious" and "Irish Eyes." I've renamed them "Apple Juice In My Panties" and "Ragweed Ramona." Adorable!  Also available:  "That's My Kitty," "Baby's First Organ Harvest," "Fecal Fiesta: Adventures in Toilet Training," and "Hydrocephalic Alice."   On a recent trip to the store, I was happy to be reunited with an old friend.  urlLink A&W Root Beer  barrels! I forgot how much I love the taste of these hard candies! Man, are they good! Apparently, someone finally decided to refill the Brach's candy bins, and there they were, in all their rooty glory. Viva le root beer flavor! Visit the  urlLink Nostalgic Candy  store!   Here's a recent picture of Neil Patrick Harris AKA Doogie Howser. Apparently the once boy-genius is either an avid crack smoker with a traveling circus OR the new master of ceremonies in Broadway's " Cabaret ." I'm so creeped out by this photo, I don't know where to begin. I'm sure teengirl Goth wannabe is swooning right now. I know androgyny is goth-a-licious, but I've never found androgyny "sexy." In all fairness, though, I must admit, Neil was pretty doggone funny in  urlLink Undercover Brother , and I hear he has a cameo in the new  urlLink Harold and Kumar Go to White Castle .
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *Part 4 of a 4-part series   At this point, you may be thinking "Geez, what  do  you like?", so I will be ending this, the last of the four part series of blogs, on a positive note, so be warned. Like I always say, I'm a surface pessimist, but a closet optimist.  Again, I have assigned letters A-E for each set of pictures, for easy referral throughout the various categories of men whom I, personally, find attractive. The combination of their profiles, personalities and photos have culminated into what I wouldn't mind dating should the opportunity present itself.    A:  This guy is so damn handsome, I can't stand it. I'm a sucker for a guy in glasses who's not an anorexic dandy. Great face, even greater profile. Appears to be the average Joe who, like myself, also enjoys the finer qualities of kitsch. He didn't give an age, so I'm assuming he either wants to appeal to a younger audience or has some kind of age complex. Regardless, he's #1 on the list.   B:  Again, another guy with above average good looks. He also gets points for the glasses, the beard (I used to hate facial hair, I guess things change over time) and overall personality. He seems funny and we have a lot of the same interests, and we happen to be the exact same age. The one cause for pause: He has kids (and you know how I love kids). Depending on the domestic situation, I'd still date him.   C:  Cute, cute, cute. This guy seems like a real person who likes to have fun. He's got a great nose and eyes and seems to be genuinely looking for a quality person. His profiles states that he's never been married, yet in the photo I detected a wedding band. He also loves to travel, which I normally detest, but again, with the right person, that might change. Whether or not you enjoy something in life, has so much to do with the company you keep.   D:  The cutest little face, ever. Love the short hair and the goatee. Looks really young, but is actually 1 year younger than myself. Seems like an overall good guy. The only worry I have is the shirtless photo. That's usually one of the warning signs of manwhore. He's still cute, though. I'd still date him.   E:  A cute guy with a great profile. He's new to town and seems like a levelheaded guy who claims to have a sarcastic and dry wit (sounds like my kinda guy!). The only downsides are he's a smoker and ironically prefers to date someone "Fit." I'd date him, but I don't think I'm his type.  And there you have it, folks. Just a few of the people whom I'm actually interested in. I even went so far as to send one an e-mail, but he never responded. Maybe his arms are in a cast or he's on vacation. Yeah, that's it. Well, if I've learned one thing from all my dating experience, it's that the people I like usually don't like me or vice versa. A lot of the time, it's mutual, but not always. Sometimes there's that certain click of personalities, but the physical just isn't there. Oh well, that's how it goes. As Robbie Neville, that 80's one-hit-wonder once sang "C'est la vie."  And now for the positive note, I promised at the beginning of this blog. I know nobody's perfect (neither am I) and I'm more than willing to meet the right person half way. And sure, I may have date trauma, and sure I may be what the sassy 'mos love to label "bitter," but what I've grown to consider "realistic," but this by no means means that I have given up on ever meeting Mr. Right. Deep, deep, deeeeeeep, deep down inside, I still have that glimmer of hope that one day I'll be somewhere, see someone trip and fall, laugh hysterically, and as my eyes look across the crowded room, he'll be there too...laughing. Kismet!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *Part 3 of a 4-part series   As you can see, I've assigned letters A-E for each photo, for easy referral while I try to decipher the various categories of men whom I, unfortunately, seem to appeal to. I'm sure that some of them would be just perfect for someone else out there, just not me. For some reason my sense of humor and friendliness (I  am  friendly, dammit! Stop laughing!) brings out the unsavory:     A: Trekkie:  Wow. Where do I begin with this one? Better yet, is elaboration really necessary? I think the name pretty much says it all. Friendly enough, but socially awkward. Be prepared to debate the original Star Trek series to today's Star Trek Enterprise. May not be up to date on current music and/or movies (other than sci-fi, of course). May make obscure Star Trek references and/or spontaneously speak Klingon. Avoid.  Age range:  19+.  See also:  King dweeb, Franklin Mint addict and/or Dungeons & Dragons Overlord: Level 10+ .   B: Comic Book Store Manager:  Cool by association, at first, because of his comic book surroundings. Culminating in a later realization that that's all he really knows...or cares about (besides Renaissance festivals). Can name every villain Spider-Man ever fought, but can't remember your name or how to apply deodorant. A healthy appetite, who enjoys dining at Tex-Mex and buffet-style restaurants.  Age range:  35+.  See also:  Super hero chat room, Weight Watchers refugee and/or Wiccan.   C: Gangsta:  Not unlike Magic Shell, the Gangsta usually has a hard shell, which conceals a sassy, creamy soul sistah at heart. Big on " keepin' it real " while shopping at Academy Sports & Outdoors and/or Foot Locker. Listens to Rap and Hip-Hop only, because everything else is " queer. " Limited knowledge of current events, just knows that " The Man " is keeping him oppressed. Must be prepared to receive anal, 'cause he's got a macho complex and " ain't no bitch. " Age range:  20+.  See also:  Thug life, Closet case and Anal sex.   D: Nerd:  Pleasantly goofy, yet detached from reality. Like the Trekkie, socially awkward and normally a spendthrift. He's saving those pennies for some new software, a system upgrade or retirement. A stranger to fashion, but no stranger to buying in bulk. Don't get on his bad side by mentioning that you own an Apple computer instead of PC, or it's the beginning of the end.  Age range:  16+.  See also:  Red pubic hair, Pewter dragon collector and/or Computer technician.   E. Spooky Daddy:  The anti-Countess Fagula (* see part 1 ), this guy's turn-ons include: sniffing your armpits, not wiping thoroughly (if at all) and facial hair. Notorious for bareback sex, justified by bucking the "system." A lover of uniforms, leather vests, German Shepherds and water sports, this guy doesn't have a lot to say and looks forward to taking you back to his place and teaching you a lesson in humility. Sometimes harbors an effeminate underbelly, only exposed to those who he really feels " know him. " Avoid.  Age range:  45+.  See also:  B&D, Leather and/or Deodorantly-challenged.   Tomorrow:  You may say I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *Part 2 of a 4-part series    In order to weed through the multitude of gay personals, you must be able to differentiate between what it said and what is meant. Below, I've chosen a random personal ad filled out and placed in the Yahoo Man Seeking Man area.  The "About Me" portion: Now, not ALL answers are in need of translation and/or interpretation. I'm sure some people answer the questions truthfully. But keep in mind they are looking for potential dates, so some men will say anything. However, there are key answers that are sometimes more than meets the eye:    As answered by person placing personal ad:   Age:  33  Marital Status:  Single- never married  Smoking:  I'll tell you later  Drinking:  Drink socially  Living Situation:  With roommate(s)  Have Kids:  No  Want (more) Kids:  I'll tell you later   Possible interpretations:    Age:  33:  35, but 33 sounds more youthful   Marital Status:  Single- never married : Define "married." / Briefly dabbled in the straight arena, got married and possibly had kids, but don't want to scare potential suitors off right away   Smoking:  I'll tell you later : I smoke, but know it's a turnoff, so "I'll tell you later"   Drinking:  Drink socially : I'm an alcoholic in denial   Living Situation:  With roommate(s) : My "roommate" until I can find someone cuter to shack up with / My boyfriend / I haven't told my wife yet   Have Kids:  No : I do, but know it's a turnoff, so "I'll tell you later"   Want (more) Kids:  I'll tell you later:  A definite turnoff for a lot of gay men. A safe way of saying "I want a child/children" once a relationship is established, without coming out and just answering "Yes"   The "In My Own Words" portion: This portion of the personal can usually be taken at face value, though sometimes has hidden subtexts:  Examples of random "In My Own Words" portions:  (1) "I am 6"2'/180/tanned and toned/smooth athletic build/looking for someone to date/like to go out occasionally but tired of the bar scene here in dallas"  Translation:  "I'm arrogant and picky. When I say I'm "tired of the bar scene in Dallas," that doesn't mean I'm tired of barhopping. There are plenty of bars in surrounding cities where nobody knows me and my " I'll fuck anything with a pulse -reputation."  (2) "I enjoy spending time at the lakes running/walking/blading/biking with my dogs. I like sports (but not a fanatic) and am into just about any kind of adventure."  Translation:  "I'm a sports fanatic, but I said I wasn't to throw you off my scent (clever, huh?!). If you date me, you'll be a sports widow in under 4 months. And when I say I "am into about any kind of adventure," I mean there's no orifice off limits, anywhere, anytime. Why do you think I'm at the lake "running/walking/blading/biking with my dogs" so much? The fresh air?  The "About My Match" portion: Now this portion of the personal ad form is WAY open to interpretation. Again, keep in mind that they are trying to get a date:    As answered by person placing personal ad:   Location:  Within 10 miles of Dallas, Tx  Age:  23-40  Marital Status:  Single- never married, Divorced  Body Type:  Slim, Slender, Average, Athletic, Fit  TV Watching:  Any  Smoking:  Any  Drinking:  Drinks socially, Drinks Regularly  Living Situation:  Alone, With pets, With roomate(s), Family and friends visit often  Have Kids:  No  Want (more) Kids:  Any  Employment Status:  Full-time, Part-time, Self-employed, Student, Work at home  Occupation:  Any  Income:  Any   Possible interpretations:    Location:  Within 10 miles of Dallas, Tx : I say 10 miles, but I'll meet just about anyone, anywhere, at any time   Age:  23-40 : I say 23-40, but will jump at the chance to date a member of the cast of The O.C. / Won't hesitate dropping you like a hot rock, if you're a 40 year old who actually looks 40   Marital Status:  Single- never married, Divorced : I'll take anything, until I see emotional baggage   Body Type:  Slim, Slender, Average, Athletic, Fit : I pick a broad range, to give the illusion that I'm a real person, but honestly hope only hardbodies apply   TV Watching:  Any : We'll curb your TV watching habit, once we start dating   Smoking:  Any : We'll curb your smoking habit, once we start dating   Drinking:  Drinks socially, Drinks Regularly : Barflies need apply   Living Situation:  Alone, With pets, With roomate(s), Family and friends visit often : We'll curb your their visits, once we start dating   Have Kids:  No : I'll budge on the subject if you're rich or really hot   Want (more) Kids:  Any : If you're really rich or hot, I'm flexible   Employment Status:  Full-time, Part-time, Self-employed, Student, Work at home : I'll wait to see what you look like and/or how your financial limitations affect me in accordance to our dating experiences, before I dump you   Occupation:  Any : *see above   Income:  Any : * see above   And last, but not least, directly to the left of each personal ad is the optional area for a photo, or in some cases photo s . Those in-the-know, know that the more pictures, the more possibilities to show off what they've interpreted as their "fabulous" surroundings, "looks" and/or photographic techniques (i.e. the ever-dramatic "B&W photo." Red flags: Shirtless, Shirtless in front of the computer, vacation photos in fabulous destinations and, of course, the always popular nude photo.   Tomorrow:  Shattering the "all gay men are hot" stereotype.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      * This is Part 1 of a 4-part blog entry   Okay, we've touched on this topic before in one of my previous blogs, so if you have no interests in reading about how depressing the world of gay dating is, then feel free to bypass today-Thursday's entries.   Occasionally, I'll get an "Oh, what the hell"-attitude and take the time to fill out an online personal ad on some random site. I think I've done it maybe 4 times over the last 10 years. Most of which I completely forget about until I get some e-mail alerting me to the fact that I "have new matches." Everybody who places a personals ad gets matches. I've yet to ever receive an actual reply to any of mine, but from what my friend Derik tells me, it happens (to him). But then Derik has a picture on his. I'm not so brave. I should know better than to NOT include a picture, considering that the "success" of the whole gay dating experience in based solely on looks (and age).  Now, before I get too far along, let me preface this by telling you I'm not saying I'm some dream catch that everyone should be scrambling to get dibs on. I have my idiosyncrasies and physical limitations, just like anybody else. I'm very grounded in reality and know my dating potential. I know I'd probably look better if I lost some weight or actually ventured out into the sunlight, but I also know I've seen worse. And some of them even have boyfriends. What's THAT about?! So, just enjoy this blog on the satirical level in which it was intended. Thank you.  With that said, I've assigned a letter, A-E, to correspond with each photo, for easy referral throughout the various categories of men. I've broken down the usual suspects for the first set of pictures, which I like to refer to as 'Types.' Now, let's not be misunderstood. This is merely the tip of the iceberg. There are many, many more categories and subcategories of types of gay men. These merely represent the types I've come in contact with in the region of Texas that I live in:       A: Product:  These are the gay men whose bumper sticker might read: "If  my car was the Lancôme counter at Dillard's, I'd be home by now." The men who think they never seem to age, because they look so youthful and natural, all thanks to their incessant use of skin products. "Natural" translating into: I think I'm so adept at applying makeup that no one notices (trust me, we notice). The one who spends 1/3 of their paycheck on "maintenance." i.e. skin toner, pore minimizer, eye bag minimizer, mousse, gel, etc.  Age range:  30+.  See also:  Liza, Club whore and/or Narcissist.   B: Mullet:  Living in Texas, these are pretty abundant. And when I say "mullet" I don't necessarily mean literally. Mullets can also be a state of mind. For example: The "straight man" who got married, had children, then came out, got divorced and/or separated. Who now lives for the weekends, when he can put on his favorite boots, biggest buckle and Stetson cologne, in order to dance the night away at the nearest gay bar that plays country music.  Age range:  25+.  See also:  Complicated family life and/or Child trauma.   C: Mid-life Crisis:  Yep, one of the most prolific. Whether it's the 50-something sporting a ponytail, sportscar, blatantly obvious over compensation in choice of youthful clothing and/or the gym body of your dreams, this one was quite prolific last time I did the bar scene. Easily recognizable by their frightening self-confidence of their appeal to the younger man, as well as their overzealous effort to pay for a younger man's drinks, meals, room & board, etc. Also, a red light for those who are compensating for being radioactive (HIV+) because of their past sexual whoring, by living in the gym and sculpting those pecs and biceps. They're not stupid (now). They know that if they're going to drop an "I'm HIV+" bomb, that they better be bringing something else to the table that their chicken can work with. i.e. A bod, money, security, etc.   Age range:  40+.  See also:  Sugar daddy, Wannabe and HIV.   D: Gangsta:  It's popularity has slowly been sweepin' the gay nation for the last 4-5 years. Big pants, top of underwear showing (so you can hopefully read the impressive label), baseball cap (with mandatory bill curvature) and the ever-present cell phone clipped to pants pocket. The one shown here is 35 years old. Frightening, huh? This group of gay gangstas is in the hizouse, B! You betta recognize (that 98% of them are wannabe idiots)!  Age range:  16+.  See also:  Gangsta WASP and/or Clone.   E. Countess Fagula:  Ugh. The bane of my gay existence. This category, unfortunately is quite prolific as well. With the supposed ever-growing "acceptance" and popularity of gay-themed TV shows, this little lady has come out of the closet and girlfriend, she is fierce! (snap!) You betta recognize! This one is pretty self-explanatory. The eyes say it all. I lovingly refer to them as "fruity eyes." There are also those who have "fruity mouth." I know the reference photo is of someone of Asian persuasion, but trust me, those are fruity eyes, regardless of minority affiliation. Fruity eyes scream "I'm queer" and fruity mouth screams "These lips were made for blowin' dong." And while we're on the topic of "made for," Countess Fagula's feet were made for dancin'. Ah ah ah all night long!  Age range:  20+.  See also:  High maintenance, Drama queen and/or Diva.  A few more pitfalls to avoid, should you find yourself browsing, placing or replying to a personal ad, the first three of which are represented by the photo below:    Glamour Shots:  Steer clear of anyone whose only photo they could come up with for a personal ad, was taken at the mall. Glamour Shots are anything but.  See also:  Regis & Kelly fan and/or Wal-Mart patron.  Creative Cropping:  If the person has taken the time to crop someone out of a photo, this might be a red flag for several reasons: A) Ex issues, B) Friend/Family identity concealed could signify underlying issues that could pose potential problems later on down the line.  See also:  Closeted, Married and/or Drama queen.  Makeup and/or Creative Lighting:  Never a good sign. This also includes the junior college Beginning Photo 101-style B&W photos. These people's home decor usually incorporate the following  fagalicious touches: silk flower arrangements, 80's vase with sticks in it, Patrick Nagel prints, potpourri, family photos and sweatshirts from the Lillian Vernon catalog. None of these things are  ever  a good sign.  See also:  Hallmark employee and/or Craft mall patron.  Boi Syndrome:  Anyone whose screen/profile name contains the word "boy/boi" and they are over the age of 25, should be avoided at all costs. These people are the kissing cousins of the parents who think they are still "hip" enough to hang with you and your teen friends. Nothing's more embarassing/sad than seeing a 40 year-old accountant dressed in a "Hip Hop Don't Stop" shirt and baseball cap, getting' "jiggy wit it" on a crowded dance floor.  See also:  Peter Pan Syndrome and/or Mid-life crisis.   Tomorrow:  Cracking the personal ad code.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Okay, assuming that the basic things like water, electricity, bedding, toiletries, etc. were available, and you were being sent into outer space for an undetermined period of time, and could only take: 5 Meals, 5 Books, 5 CDs, 5 Movies, 5 Misc. & 1 Person, who/what would  you  take? *  These are my choices:   5 Meals:   01. Chicken and dressing w/mashed potatoes 02. Ham & provolone subs from Gallagaskin's w/dill spear 03. Special Chicken w/fried rice, eggroll & crab rangoon from Ho Ho Kitchen 04. Hamburger patty, shells & tomato sauce, chocolate pudding 05. Fried shrimp, french fries and rainbow sherbet    Books:   01. The Immoralist 02. Automated Alice 03. Catcher In The Rye 04. Cute, Quaint, Hungry & Romantic 05. Scars     CDs:   01. Enigma's Greatest Hits 02. The Best of Plumb 03. Ella Fitzgerald: Love Songs 04. Back To Mine: Groove Armada 05. Electroburn   Movies:   01. Pandemonium 02. The Locusts 03. The Goonies 04. Fright Night 05. The Parent Trap   Misc.   01. Boggle 02. Blank books w/ pens & pencils 03. My iMac 04. Nintendo w/games 05. Puzzles   1 Person:   Elijah Wood Alternate: Craig Bierko *  Use the comments area to tell me!  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's Friday The 13th, and as you may or may not know, today is  urlLink Alfred Hitchcock 's birthday. Hitchcock is one of my favorite directors, and many of his movies grace my DVD collection.   If you have cable and get the  urlLink Starz Mystery Channel , tonite they will be showing a Hitchcock double feature: The Lady vanishes and  urlLink To Catch A Thief , starring Cary Grant & Grace Kelly.  I've listed a few of my favorite Hitchcock movies below, so make this Friday night Hitchock Movie Night at your house!  I have hyperlinked each title below, to a brief synopsis online :  •   urlLink Psycho   (1960) •   urlLink Shadow of a Doubt   (1943) •   urlLink Vertigo   (1958) •   urlLink Rear Window   (1954) •   urlLink Murder!   (1930) •   urlLink The Birds   (1963) •   urlLink Rebecca   (1940)  And for those of you who are not into the classic films, here are a few suggestions that pay homage to the Hitchcock style, but were made more recently, that you might want to check out: •   urlLink High Anxiety   (1978)- A hilarious film by Mel Brooks, co-starring some of my all-time favorites: Madeleine Kahn & Cloris Leachman. Why this movie has yet-to-be-released to DVD, is a mystery to me. •   urlLink Dressed To Kill   (1980)- Directed by one of my all-time favorite directors, Brian De Palma. De Palma is often referred to as the American Hitchcock. •   urlLink Psycho   (1998)- Though many hardcore fans of the original film shunned this shot-for-shot remake by Gus Van Sant, I thought it stood on it's own, with a fresh sense of style in both the sets and the wardrobe. Also, it stars my favorite hottie,  urlLink Vince Vaughn . •   urlLink Still of The Night   (1982)- I recently stayed up late and watched this on television and was mesmerized by it's overall look. Great performances by Meryl Streep and one of my favorite actors, Roy Scheider.  Happy 105th, Alfred, wherever you are.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yesterday I was in a MST3K mood, so I had a mini marathon of some of my favorite episodes:  The Wild, Wild World of Bat Woman ,  The Brain That Wouldn't Die ,  Mitchell , and naturally,  Pod People  (" Good? He's the  best!  "). For those not familiar with the cult TV show, here's a quick synopsis, courtesy of  urlLink DVD Empire :   Mystery Science Theater 3000 , America's only show that makes fun of really bad B movies from the comfort of a spaceship floating above Earth. Joel Hodgson, along with his mechanical companions, wisecracking Crow and well read chick magnet Tom Servo, make suffering through Hollywood's worst films a breeze. Adding their own dialogue, barrage of witty remarks, and an occasional colorful skit, the nest hour and a half will fly by like it were only 90 minutes. There are no ushers with flashlights, crying babies, or women with big hair to spoil the fun.    I remember first seeing this show, late one night, when I first moved away to college. I was initially attracted by the cheesy monster movie, then totally sucked in, once I saw that they were making fun of it by adding their own dialogue and/or comments. Completely hilarious. If you enjoy the 'B' horror and sci-fi movies of the 50's-80's, then you're sure to love the show. I remember watching it on Comedy Central back in the mid-late 90's, and often looked forward to their Thanksgiving Day marathon: Turkey Day Marathon. Eventually, the show was removed from Comedy Central and new episodes starting showing up on Sci-Fi Channel. I used to get up every Saturday morning at 8, just to watch it. And now, the show is no longer on the air (not that I'm aware of, anyway). Oh, how I miss it.   For those who may have missed it, during its' run on television, there are the DVDs: 10 individual episodes, 5 box sets (roughly 3-4 episodes per set + bonus Shorts*), 2 NEW box sets coming August and September 31st, and, of course, the holy grail of out-of-print-DVDs:  Mystery Science Theater: The Movie , which I am proud to say is part of my collection. The movie was just a big-screen adaptation of the television show concept, featuring one of my sci-fi faves  This Island Earth . Absolutely hilarious. A must see, even if you just rent it.   Sometimes, before the actual feature film begins, the cast will watch what is called a "short." The shorts usually consist of ephemeral films from the 50's, and on their own are hilariously outdated and humorous. But once Mike (or his predecessor/show creator, Joel) and the 'bots get a hold of it, it's laugh-outloud-funny. I have a lot of the shorts, in their entirety on CD-ROMS and/or other DVDs, aside from the ones shown on MST3K, since I am a lover of ephemera. Two of the favorite shorts, that have been shown on MST3K, have been  Junior Rodeo Daredevils  and  The Home Economics Story . The scene that had me laughing so hard, I almost choked to death, was during  The Home Economics Story  and the short's narrator says something about Judy having a five pound potty (some 50's reference to Judy's new engagement ring) and Joel goes " Five pound potty? Somebody had a big breakfast! " I cracked up! OMG, it's still so damn funny to watch. Another favorite short was  A Date With Your Family , where a model 50's family displays the behaviors that are to be avoided at the dinner table: The robots chime in: Sister asks herself, " I wonder if I should have washed my hands after handling that dead woodchuck? "
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Are you familiar with these commercials for these scooters, supposedly made for the disabled or the elderly? The one I see advertised the most is,  urlLink The Rascal . Here's the commercial set up: An able-bodied elderly couple come home to find a message on their answering machine: A friend is calling to tell them how she won a FREE Rascal and now she's free as a bird! Flash on her shopping, meeting friends for lunch, etc. As the commercial goes on, the couple receive more messages from the same free-wheelin' friend, about how she is doing just about everything but pole-vaulting over Mt. Everest. The commercial ends with the woman of the couple, calling her friend and leaving a message "Hi Jolene, this is Caroline, I'm calling to see how we can win our OWN free Rascal!" Her husband gives her a thumbs up.  The commercial leaves me with s few unanswered questions: 1) Why would two able-bodied people want a Rascal to begin with? 2) How come the woman who has the new Rascal is able to stand up and walk on her own, when putting the Rascal into the trunk of her car? 3) Are all old people lazy motherfuckers?   I don't know what it's like where you live, but here, I see people with these type of motorized scooters, on a regular basis. Why, just the other day, I was at the post office, and some fat, black woman was at the counter, sitting in one. On my way home, I passed her, ON THE ROAD, Rascalin' her way home. WTF? And then a few weeks ago, I saw another fat, black woman (different woman, different scooter) Rascalin' her way through the neighborhood to the convenience store. And it ain't just black women, but it always seems to be a fat woman, whether it's at the grocery store, Walmart (As an absolute last resort, when everything else is closed) or other public places. The commercials sure-as-hell don't ever show some water buffalo with an open bag of  urlLink Cheetos  riding one. It's always the elderly, whom I've yet to see utilizing them.  My question is, when did people get so fuckin' lazy? I'm all for the person who has medical issues and actually needs some form of mechanical assistance, but don't expect any sympathy from me, just 'cause you "love  urlLink nachos ." I've seen these people get out of their scooters and walk, so I know they aren't paralyzed. What pisses me off the most is that their insurance is actually paying for it, while people who  really  need them, have situations where appointments, medication, etc. aren't covered by their insurance. Why should insurance pay for someone else's lack of (or disregard for) self-control when it comes to eating? Ridiculous! People stink.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'll be taking my computer to "the shop" to get its' 1000 mile checkup, early tomorrow morning, so I will not have computer access for up to 3 days,  supposedly . That's what the computer place always tells me, but then it ends up taking 5 goddamn days. Lying assholes. But I digress. So, in the meantime, I will try to make it up to the nearest library ( which is closed on Thursdays, naturally ) in order to upload my blog entries.  I blog to purge myself of built-up observations, frustrations, stories, etc. (and because I likes it), but I also blog to hopefully make someone out there laugh, but since I don't even know if any one else is reading this thing, I am gonna stop blogging on the weekends. I may just be talking to myself (not all that unusual, lol!), and if so, surely I can live without the sound of my own typing for 2 days.  -Kirk :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I love (and miss) 3-D movies. Granted, I wasn't around when it was first all the rage, but I was around, when it made it's comeback, in the early 80's. I remember seeing   Spacehunter: Adventures in the Forbidden Zone   (1983),   Jaws 3-D   (1983),   Friday The 13th Part 3-3-D   (1982),   Amityville 3-D   (1983) and even that lame   Freddy's Dead: The Final Nightmare   (1991) with the brief 3-D installment. I have to say that the old 3-D, with the black lensed glasses, was  far  superior to the "new" 3-D, with the red & blue lensed glasses. The depth with the black lenses was much better and so was the overall effect. I remember jumping out of my hide, during Jaws 3, and subsequently making a "yelp!" sound that everyone around me heard, making me sink down in my seat, from embarrassment.   There some 3-D system that you can buy now and attach to your television, similar to a cable box, that will enable you to watch specially designed 3-D DVDs in all their original 3 dimensional glory! They call the 3-D glasses "Field Sequential LCD" glasses. Unfortunately the system and the glasses are kinda pricey, as are the DVDs. I'd love to have one eventually, but as it is, I already have 2 boxes attached to the television and I dunno if I really wanna add ANOTHER one. And if I ever find a Nintendo that works, then that would be a FOURTH thing to stack. Ack!   There are some movies I would have LOVED to have seen in 3-D:   House of Wax   (1953),   Silent Madness   (1984) and  urlLink   Dial "M" For Murder    (1954), which is being released to DVD on September 7th. I guess I'll have to settle for my Jaws 3-D bubblegum cards for now. Maybe Hollywood will revive the whole 3-D fad again sometime. And maybe, just maybe, they'll finally get the 3-D right.   Now, for my cookie dough revelation. For as long as I can remember, the idea that people actually LIKE to eat cookie dough  raw , was a baffling concept to me. I remember trying raw sugar cookie dough once, out of curiosity, thinking it was gross. Later on, a cookie dough ice cream, candy bar and even milkshake came along, still baffled to its' appeal. Well, recently I saw the light (cue the choir of angels).   I recently bought some "Ready to Bake/Big Deluxe Classics" cookies from Pillsbury (the new peanut butter cups kind). I liked the idea that they came in a resealable Ziplock-style package, so I could make a few at a time + I didn't have to bother with slicing them. Well, as I was taking a few out of the package to put on the cookie sheet, one of them fell apart, so out of sheer necessity (yeah, whatever.... ) I ate the piece that fell. Raw. And you know what? Eureka! It was delicious! So I ate the rest of it, justifying my actions by telling myself this way, all the cookies would be uniform in size. That's it. Uniformity. So, now I can honestly say I came, I saw, I conquered the raw cookie dough's appeal. I don't think I'd want to eat that much of it, but I do appreciate it's yum factor now.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Preface:   A little history of the Automat:   urlLink Horn & Hardart  opened its first Automat eatery in 1902 to serve good dishes cheaply. Three nickels inserted in slot, a twist of the knob, and presto! -- the glass hatch popped open, enabling diners to help themselves to a fabulous selection of dishes, all made fresh that morning.    One of my all-time favorite movies is Dark City. It's such a brilliant movie, in so many aspects (most notably, visual): Set design, actors/actresses, costume design, score, soundtrack, etc. If you haven't seen it, and are a fan of the surreal, 40's and/or  urlLink Neo-Noir , then you are sure to enjoy it. One of the many things that stood out in my mind, during the movie Dark City, was a particular scene that takes place at an Automat.  For those not familiar with the Automat, it's basically a restaurant, with a wall of cubbies, covered with hinged hatches, that contain freshly prepared food. Think of them as a cross between today's vending machine and a cafeteria. Automats were before my time, but I am completely enchanted with the concept of them. I know that a spinoff of them, still remain popular in some parts of Europe and Asia, but I'm not sure if there are any still around in the US. It's sad how such a fantastic concept could ever go out of style. I'd think it would mesh perfectly with today's seemingly faceless lifestyle of automated everything, yet retaining a sense of history.   I love the idea of being able to go into a restaurant, any time of the day and/or night, with a pocket of change, and getting yourself a cup of coffee, club sandwich, etc. And then going to relax, relatively social interaction-free (i.e. waitress, hostess, etc.), in a comfortable booth to enjoy it. Relatively self-contained, yet refreshingly retro. Upon Googling our friend the Automat, I came across a book entitled  urlLink The Automat: The History, Recipes, and Allure of Horn & Hardart's Masterpiece , written by Lorraine B. Diehl & Marianne Hardart. They have also jointly published a book of postcards and a journal, both with Automat themes. Check em' out!   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't how many people out there actually keep up with any of the reality shows, but from time to time I'll tune in, depending on the subject matter, etc. I admit to being a fan of: •  Murder In Small Town X  (Who's winner, sadly died in the 9/11 bombing. He was a firefighter.) •  MTV's Real World  (I think I stopped after the 1994 "San Francisco" season with "Puck")  •  I'm A Celebrity, Get Me Outta Here!  (I was addicted to that cutie Cris Judd! What a great guy.) •  The Surreal Life  (Season 1) •  The Osbournes  •  Mad, Mad House  ("Art" was  so  hot). I also sometimes like Sci-Fi Channel's  Scare Tactics  and can handle  Simple Life  in small doses (I quickly lose patience with the whole snotty "fish out of water" schtick perpetuated by the spoiled duo). Oh, and if  Jackass  is considered reality TV, then I also used to love that show. Can't get enough potty humor and/or Johnny Knoxville (ROWR ROWR!).   In short, I have watched my share of "reality" TV. For some reason, I seem to be drawn to the ones that never last. Lol! I never got remotely interested or even seen most of the ones that seem to be so popular:  Survivor ,  Big Brother ,  The Bachelor ,  The Bachelorette ,  Who Wants To Marry A Millionaire , etc. And I just couldn't handle the high fruit-factor on  Queer Eye For The Straight Guy  (though the soundtrack is cool and I think the guy who does the interior design is cute) or  Boy Meets Boy , which had me dry heaving on the fab-factor, alone. Yeah,  Boy Meets Boy  is on DVD, but  good  shit like Square Pegs and/or Maude, isn't. That makes sense. Not.   So, back to the whole reason I was inspired to write this to begin with. I have a habit of recording That 70's Show every day from 6-7. Well, I let the tape run the other day and recorded UPN's latest turd-tastic reality gem:   urlLink The Player  . The name alone made me snicker (insert sarcastic fart sound here), but I decided to watch it anyway. A brief synopsis of the show: " An eight-week one-hour series set a palatial Miami mansion that follows a group of 13 self-described "players" in their quest to win the heart (or, at least, be the final selection) of a Miami model named Dawn ... assisted by her two girlfriends. " Wow. I can't wait! Lol. NOT. Some observations: The biggest geek/Guido-esque "player" of the group, named "Alex," is a self-proclaimed "entrepreneur" (that's just precious) from right here in Texas, naturally. Way to represent Texas, dawg!....rheeee (my retardo sound). Whatever. "JJ" (who busted a phat rhyme for the ladies...ech. Whatever) looks like he rents his head out as a scratching post. And it's not much better when compounded with a skull cap. Nice look, Scarecrow. How about a little fire? Yeesh. And I can't help but give an honorable mention to "Bryan" (yet  another  personal trainer) whose perpetually arched eyebrow and flared nostrils seem to say "I smell a fart." And as far as the "show me your playa skillz" round, where each guy had to show some kinda "skillz," all I can say is: If the black guys weren't allowed to Rap, would they still have had anything to bring to the table? My  urlLink Magic 8 Ball  says "Outlook Not Good."   The only guy who I think is remotely attractive, but whose actual personality most-likely leaves a lot to be desired (he's a personal trainer), is "Ben." He's a little hottie, but then I'm sure he tells himself that every day, during his "mirror time." When asked:  Best physical features? , he answered  Arms, chest, back, legs, face and abs.  Gee, so humble. He forgot "neck & feet." Good thing they didn't ask him his worst features, he'd be stumped. Poor kid. He lists his special talents as "Modeling & wrestling," and his role model is "Ashton Kutcher." I rest my case.  My question is: Is straight dating as shallow and cheesy as it's portrayed on television? Does everyone really fuck around pretty much immediately and are all the chicks money-grubbing ho's? If I was a woman, I honestly don't know if I could keep a straight face during some faux romantic candlelight dinner, preceded by that tired standard, the single rose. It's all a little too " urlLink Bennigan's  prom" for me to swallow, not to mention a little desperate. Am I just getting the wrong image, or what? I never get this uptight about dates. I figure we'll either get along or we won't. If so, cool, if not, so be it. Is straight dating really all this complicated, and if so, why bother? Is "couple" status really the holy grail?
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Omnibus. Laut Sprecher. © 2001   01. Omnibus (Radio Version) 02. Omnibus (Remix Radio Version) 03. Omnibus (Extended Version) 04. Omnibus (Remix Extended Version)    Dance Trax Links:    -  urlLink Discogs.com  -  urlLink trancEaddict.com  -  urlLink DanceRecords.com      Technology: The Force of Gravity. BT. © 2004   01. The Force of Gravity (BT's Edit)      02. The Force of Gravity (Tiesto Remix)      03. The Force of Gravity (Dylan Rhymes Push Up Mix)      04. Superfabulous (Scott Humphries Mix)      05. Superfabulous (Compufonic Mix)      06. The Great Escape (Attention Deficit Mix)      Push The Feeling On. Nightcrawlers. © 1993   01. Push The Feeling On (JCA Radio Edit #) 02. Push The Feeling On (Original 2 Step) 03. Push The Feeling On (Rosabel Club Mix) 04. Push The Feeling On (JCA Club Mix #) 05. Push The Feeling On (2 Step Club Mix) 06. Push The Feeling On (Sure As Hell Remix) 07. Push The Feeling On (Rosabel Dub)     Will I Ever Pt.1 [IMPORT]. Alice Deejay. © 2000   01. Will I Ever (Hitradio Mix) 02. Will I Ever (Hitradio Xl) 03. Back In My Life (Pronti & Kalmani Dub) 04. Video-Will I Ever    Even MORE Dance Trax Links:    -  urlLink Farfield Records  -  urlLink BestPrices.com  -  urlLink israel-music.com  -  urlLink Perfect Beat.com  -  urlLink Big CD.com   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last night I watched one of my favorite suspense thrillers on the Starz Mystery Channel: 1980's   Cruising  . The film stars Al Pacino and Paul Sorvino and was directed by William Friedkin, best known for his film  The Exorcist . The movie is based on the book by Gerald Walker and is about a series of grisly murders taking place in New York's underground gay scene of leather bars and S&M. Al Pacino is assigned to go undercover, as a leatherman in the gay community, to find the killer.  I was only in 3rd grade when the movie was initially released, but from what I've read, it caused  urlLink quite a stir  amongst the gay community at the time. From what I can deduce, they were upset by both the way homosexuals/their "lifestyle" was portrayed in the film, as well as the fact that the killer was targeting homosexuals.   Initially, the way that gay characters were portrayed in films did irk me, simply because I knew I didn't fit that mold and neither did the majority of gay people I knew. But realistically, I realized that it's just easier for Hollywood and the majority of straight people to have something simple, in regard to minority stereotypes, that they can identify immediately upon sight. i.e. The flamboyant man with the lisp: gay, the thrifty, big-nosed character: Jew, the guy with tape on the bridge of his glasses and pocket protector: nerd, etc. Once I came to terms with the fact that that's how it works, I no longer found it offensive. In fact, some of my favorite movies are ones that more sensitive people may find and have found "offensive." For instance, something similar happened 12 years later, when  Basic Instinct  was released. Again, the gay community was upset. What? There are never supposed to be  any  killers/murderers who happen to be gay? I just don't get that worked up over movies. I mean, it is a work of fiction, meant to entertain us. Geez people, relax, and enjoy the film for what it is. I think the problem lies in the fact that some gay people are disillusioned enough to think that homosexuality is going to be accepted by the populous at some point in the future. Trust me, it's not, let's be realistic about it. For every person out there who is okay with it, there's some parent out there raising their kid to hate, just like Mommy & Daddy do. It's a vicious cycle. Some people just don't have the mental capacity to think outside their own existance of beliefs.   Back to   Cruising  . I own the VHS and wish the DVD would get a release, but I'm not holding my breath. I love the movie because I find it genuinely creepy, bleak and on some levels, realistic. It's one of those movies that kept me stressed out: You know, that feeling during a scene, when say, someone is rummaging through the killer's belongings while they are out and the person whom they belong to could return at any moment.  THAT  kind of stress. Aaaiigggh! That seriously stresses me out, but I love it. Heh. I dunno why. Adrenaline, I suppose.    In addition to the suspense, I also liked the music, the performances and the unintentional slices of humor. Though   Cruising   stars Al Pacino, I consider it a sort of cult/underground film, since most people aren't familiar with it or have seen it. I have some straight male friends who admit to liking the film. However, if it didn't have names attached to it, like William Friedkin, Al Pacino, Paul Sorvino or even Joe Spinell, I guarantee you they wouldn't touch it with a ten foot pole (no pun intended). Most straight men probably keep repeating to themselves: The Godfather. Scarface. The Godfather. Scarface. Some male heroes can do no wrong in the machismo psyche. Just read some of the reviews on IMDB.com, if there's any doubt in your mind that the gay factor was a big "ick" factor for the majority of   Cruising  's audience. So much for progress.  One thing that drives me crazy about the film and has been argued through various articles, is how the film/characters are interpreted. I've read that 40 minutes of footage was left on the cutting room floor, so maybe some of my answers lie in those 40 minutes. Until a director's cut is released (if ever), we may never know. I also intend to track down the book at a nearby used bookstore and read it. Maybe it can give me more insight into the characters and their motives. * If you haven't seen the film and want to uphold the suspense, don't read any further right now. There are a few possible spoilers ahead.  Okay, here's some things that leave me scratching my head:  • Near the beginning, after Pacino is given his assignment and is in bed with his wife, they are talking and at one point he says "There are lots of things about me you don't know." Then the camera lingers on his face and sinister music plays. What's THAT supposed to mean? Is he gay? Is he the killer? What?  • Was Joe Spinell's character really a cop? The transvestites he and his fellow police officer/partner solicit for sex, seem to think he is (i.e. the uniforms/patrol car), but the police chief at the precinct they get taken to claims that there are a lot of people out there lately passing themselves off as cops. Spinell was driving a cop car, in a cop's uniform, so I assume he is, but then he's in the leather bar later on, dressed in civilian/leather clothing, cruising Pacino. What's THAT about?  • And last, but not least, the ending has me asking even more questions. The guy who lives in the apt. next door, whom Pacino and the victim's boyfriend fought over him, the night before, is found murdered,  after  the "killer" is taken into custody. Who killed him? Was it Pacino or his jealous lover? At the end, why is Pacino all weirded-out, staring into the mirror after shaving? Did something inside him snap, while working on the case? Is he the killer?    *The title of this blog is a reference to the creepy little song the killer sings before he kills his victim.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>