<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I wanna fall in love, real love, with someone who wants to fall in love with me. I wanna wake up in the morning thinking about someone and go to bed knowing there thinking of me. I wanna laugh, and cry with someone all in the same day. I wanna know that this person is here for me, and wants to see and be with me. I wanna spend my time with him playing, talking, sleeping, anything as long as i was with him and it was right. I wanna walk with him, and have him hold my hand, and be happy. I wanna be happy. I wanna light up when i see his name on the caller id just to sit and talk to him for hours about nothing. I wanna be able to have some where to go, and always have somthing to do. I wanna fight with him just to make up seconds later. I wanna be able to make him a promise and no i wont break it. I wanna have nothing, but feel like i have everything. I wanna get a phone call from him just becasue he wanted to tell me he was thikning about me and that he loved me. I wanna dream about him and wake up and have him tell me he drempt about me. I wanna no he fells the same way. I dont wanna care what everyone else thinks. I dont wanna have to question what i feel for him. I dont wanna cry my self to sleep. I dont wanna hurt him. I dont wanna be hurt. I dont wanna be afraid of what tomorrows ganna bring. I dont wanna look at someone else and second guess what i have. Mick Jagger said it best, "You cant always get watcha want, but if you try sometimes, you just might find, you get watcha need..." and everyone needs to be loved like that. Some people may not show it but we all want it, we all need it. Its what makes the world go round. But i guess, the only thing i can do is wait, just sit and wait. Wait for ones to come and go, wait for the day, that i realize, that ive found that person, and that im in love. I can count the minuts, i can count the hours, i can count the days, i can count the years, but it wont make it come any faster. So like i said, i guess ill just wait....
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why is there always those few people you cant bring your self to tell them that you like them? Im the kind of person that if I like you, you'll no. Because I figure, you may like me too and not ever tell me and well both never no. What's the worst that can happen? You'll say no, and well go back to the way things were, big deal. And Im sure a lot of you are like that too. But there's always those few, the ones that just intimidate you out of your mind. That you couldn't tell them you liked them if you were paid. Because there's just something about them that you ( the not afraid of the opposite sex, very open with your feelings, give it a shot person ) are terrified of. There are 3 people like that for me. Lets meet #1. For those of you who know me and go to Franklin you'll no exactly who this is. I first saw him goin to 3rd period everyday freshmen year. He'd walk up one side of the stairs and id walk up the other, everyday id see him at the top. And since the first time I saw him till now, I can not tell him. Im sure he knows because I have no problem telling everyone else but I could not tell him for the life of me. All my friends were like what happened to you? Your Mrs. Outspoken, say what's on your mind and your afraid to talk to a guy?  Your never afraid of guys? And im still not, just him, and the other two. But there's something about him that when I see him im like shit, and I almost have to walk the other way, and I have no idea why! It bothers me. He's the worst one cause I cant stop liking him, like ill stop and then I see him and im sk rewed again. The other too aren't so bad. Lets meet #2. I've known him for a looooooong time. Our parents are good friends and we hang out when they do, u no, memorial day, 4th of July, Christmas, one of those things. But since I met him I've always in the back of my mind had this thing for him. Not this OMG I love you thing or anything but its justa cruch that wont go away. He fascinates me, he's smart, and funny, and laid back, and kinda quiet( witch is odd if u no me because I usually go out with the super out there ADD ones...). Maybe that's why I like him cause he's different, oh and maybe its cause he's really really good looking. But everytime im like hum,there's something about him. And I cant tell him, I don't no if its cause it'd be weird cause its not like a voluntarily hang out thing like we havta hang out with eachother so it'd be weird, or if it's cause im just scared, or maybe cause were friends and I dunno...? Speaking of friends that I like lets meet # 3. Ok # 3s different. He's not super super good looking like the other 2 but he's just as hott if not hotter, u no what I mean? He's....mysterious kinda and I think that's what draws me to him. He's real artistic and I dunno he's not like anyone else, he's very much his own person. Anyway, he's hands down the coolest person I no, I no that sounds stupid but really he is. He's just...everything he does, like everything I dunno its hard to explain. But were pretty close and I think that might be why I cant tell him. But see I've been closer to guys that I liked and I've told them so I dunno? I almost told him, last day of school, but I freaked out and I couldn't do it. I couldn't. So damn you people who I like and cant tell! lol I just realized, they're all kinda the same. They're all real laid back, quiet, shaggy hair kinda guys. Hum, maybe that has somthing to do with it, or maybe not who konws? But really it sucks because for all I know there having the same problem and well both never know, and that's the saddest part. What coulda been is always the saddest part. 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Top 10 Things I Want to do Before I Die In no order~  * Visit Every Contient (maybe not Antartica)  * Get Married   * Have Kids  * Get My Doctorate in Something  * Go to the Super Bowl (a good one)   * Save a Life  * Find My One Thing Im Really Good At (everyone has somthing)  * Jump Out of an Airplane  * Run a Marathon  * Be Famous (for somthing...preferably somthing good)
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do you remember your first real love? I do. I remeber it very well, becasue it was not to long ago. On May 10th 2003 i met two people who have gone on to mean very much me. I met Jerad (who if i didnt have i probably would cracked a looooooong time ago) and this guy named Chris. I've talked to Jeared almot everyday since then but i didnt hear about or see Chirs till around the beginning of school when one of my friend was dating him and then not till Christmas time. Kelly started talkin about him and how she liked him and all that. So i was like oh yea i think i remeber him. And then nothing else for a while. Then on Super Bowl Sunday (one of my all time favorite days of the year)Chris IMed me and asked me if i wanted to go to a super bowl party casue he couldnt get a hold of kelly. I was all ehh why not? Havnt seen this guy in a year, have talked to him twice, whatever ill go, maybe i can help out kelly somehow. So this guy shows up at my door, tall, blonde, buff, really cute, and im like ehh kellys got good taste and i leave. As the night progressed I slowly started to be like hum, this guys really sweet, and fun, and....yea. So anyway after some small talk and a game of pink pong (witch i won bc i am a vitious pink pong player) we left and while we were waiting for his sister out side, we kissed. That started one of the best things ive ever had with one of the worst endings. He asked me out that week and it pissed kelly and my friend sarah off who had been dating him before. So we go out for a while, 3 months and i fell for him fast and hard. But then, things started to get in the way. School, his job, his mother, my curse of not being able to let somthing go if it makes me mad untill its fixed, little things like that, untill finally, it wasnt going anywhere anymore. And on April 24, at the Coronado prom, we broke up. It was the hardest thing i had ever done. Ever. To watch the person who i loved so much walk out of my life. It sounds like he broke up with me, but i broke up with and im still to this day im not 100% sure why. After a couple hours of feeling like crap i decided it was just a break kinda and we would get back together and i told him that. So a week goes by and all of the sudden were fighting about stuff again, and about when were ganna get abck together and so one thing/fight lead to another and as u guessed we didnt get back together. But at that point i still loved him. so about a month goes by mabey more and we talk about getting back together again i get excited, and of course since i just have the best luck, somthing happends yet again and we dont. So its over. For sure this time. We cant really talk anymore with out fighting, and i cant really talk about all of this with out crying. Someone gave me advice last night to get it out of my system and this is the abridged version but its out for the most part. And Chris if u do read this, just know that i am sorry. Take it or leave it.
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      DEAR BOYS-- Stop thinking with your dick. I no its hard, but if you thought more with your head youd get to use your dick a lot more. Think about it, a guy who uses his head and knows how to treat a girl right and respects her and is nice to her and wants more than sex, will get a lot more ass a lot more often. Becasue the more the girl likes a guy the more theyll wanna do stuff with them and the better u treat her the more shell like you...becasue we all know "lets just fuck" are the words that every girls wants to hear.
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone~ Well if your ganna be reading this i think is only fair that u no a little about me. Theres a lot to no actually so Ill just get started. My name is Ally and i live in El Paso Tx and im a jr at Franklin High School. Thats your first warning, im a girl in high school, there wil be drama. I try my hardest to get away from the drama but its kinda hard when thats all there is. I live with my parents, 2 cats, a dog, and i have a 23 year old borhter who goes to Texas State. I have a lot of frineds. Like, Lisa, Kelly, Jerad, Jaesek, Trey, Jd, Lindsey, there are many more but those will be the ones you hear about the most im sure. I have guy problems, that im sure youll hear me bitch about often. Guys and i.....i dunno its hard to explain, it can be really really good, or not. Its confussing, yes guys, you are confussing too. Well thats just scraping the surface but itll give u a little idea of what to expect.
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So this is odd, the painful realization that all has gone wrong.  And nobody cares at all,  and nobody cares at all. So you buried all your lover's clothes and burned the letters lover wrote,  but it doesn't make it any better. Does it make it any better? And the plaster dented from your fist in the hall where you had your first kiss reminds you that the memories will fade. So this is strange,  our sidestepping has come to be a brilliant dance where nobody leads at all,  where nobody leads at all. And the picture frames are facing down and the ringing from this empty sound is deafening and keeping you from sleep. And breathing is a foreign task and thinking's just too much to ask and you're measuring your minutes by a clock that's blinking eights. This is incredible. Starving, insatiable,  yes, this is love for the first time. Well you'd like to think that you were invincible. Yeah, well weren't we all once before we felt loss for the first time? Well this is the last time. This is the last time. This is the last time. -Dashboard Confessional
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Top 10 Things That Make Me Happy in no order  * New Found Glory   * Lisa  * My Pets (especally my fatty Leo, well and Holly and Mia)  * Finding out that someone i like likes me (rare)  * Disney movies/Disneyland  * Winning (at anything)  * Having a good time with people i love  * Pretty Cars (sports/muscle cars perferably)  * Shopping  * My bear (i still sleep with him) 
      
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is all ganna sound really weird and backwords but here goes. Overly positive people piss me off. You know the type the one that know matter what has got a smile on and is just like everything is fine things will get better :-).It really bothers me. Becasue think about it, when somtings worng, somethings wrong, its not healthy to bottle up feelings like that and if your always so cheerfull and have this BS attitude about everything being perfect then, your not expressing our self right. Like ive been talkin to people and they can say to me with the biggest smile on their face that "things could be better", its never "things suck" "fuck everyone" "i wanna die" it just "ehhh cant complain i guees, things could be worse!" And it makes me mad. And then another thing that bothers me even more is when somesone tryin to make me feel better. And theer just all cheerfull liek "thigs cant be that bad?" and im like ya they are. And the every cloud has a silver lingin thing, every cloud doesnt. And i dont liek to be to overly positive when im down case it just makes me feel worse, cause i look at it like wow things could be sooo much better, but there not. There crappy. It sucks. But like someone told me resently, thats "my fault" and im just "a bitter little bitch." Witch made me feel better, esp. since it was followed by and "its ok tho u can fix that if u look on the brite side more..."????? And then i was just like, grrrrrr. And when i get mad at them and tell them to stop they get all "mad" and are like im just trying to help, well your not. I love the people who dont sugar coat things, who are just like, dude that sucks. Like "itll go away eventually but that really sucks right now im sorry man." you no?  id much rather have a person tell it like it is ( casue that makes me feel better to no that people half understand) then for them to lie to me. And tell me how great things are when they dont even know. Like how do they no how great things are or arnt? Theyre not me? They dot go threw the same shit i do. But whatever, i guess theres nothing i can do then to just block em out and pretend there not all "mr. sunshine on my god dam sholders" all the time. 
      
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Member a while back when i worte about those 3 guys that i really like but cant tell casue im scared, well were ganna focus now on # 3. # 3 was the mysterious, coolest kid ever, just wow guy. Im fallin really hard for him, like im fixin to land face first on the ground. And i dont no what to do. I wanna tell him but im scared of gettin shoot down like usual, and like i said i tell everyone else cause u no if threy dont like me they dont like me, whatever, move on. but i really really like this guy. so i figure if he doesnt like me im ganna be upset, and i dont wanna be upset. but what if he does, then id be happy, but if he doesnt, ill be upset. SEE! it sucks casue i dont no what to do. do i risk it? or do i just skrew it and go on how it is?  We hung out last thursday, sunday, and talked on the phone for 3 hours sunday night, and im fallin fast. And like i accidently told his best frined, and im sure hell tell him and then i dunno, im just confussed and scared and all of those crappy emotions. If anyone who reads this, has any advise for me, id appreaciate it. Cause i feel like a little lost puppy. :-(  hehe
      
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday June 29th was the bast day of my life!!! I was at the Warped Tour and it was the most fun ive ever had. It totally made me forget about all the shit thats goin on and it was perfect. I saw Taking Back Sunday, Thursday, The Early November, Coheed & Cambria, Story of the Year, Yellowcard, and my super duper favorite of all time NEW FOUND GLORY. I got a shirt and a wallet signed by all of the members of new found glory and i think that was the happiest anything has made me in a long time. it was good. I went with my bestest frined lisa and we had soooo much fun!   im feelin it hard core today tho.  Ive got a shit load of bruses, cuts, im really sore, and my ears are still ringing, but it was def. worth it! I wish that was everyday, like i could follow it becasue it made me happy, i was genually 100% happy and i havnt been like that in a rally long time, it was awesome, im just upset its gone. 
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was really....interesting (thats a good word). Ok i got up this morning at 10:00. Thats amazing, but i got up to get ready to see a very very special person to me. My Kyle (well hes not really "my" kyle but i like to think so i love him to death) was in town for 1 day. He lives in San fransisco now and is in college. I hadnt seen him in a year, and i thought about him all the time and missed him like nothing else. So he had family stuff yesterday and so today before he left he came by to see me. I was so happy, happier than words can say. He pulled up, i ran out side and jumped on him and gave him the biggest hug. I was so happy to see him. We talked a little about how i had changed (for the better i might add...:-) ) and what we were doin and all that good stuff, and then he had to go. And thats when i had my first burst of courage, i kissed him, which wasnt really that big of a deal caused i had kissed him before, but it was kinda differnt. So then we said our good byes and he left...i almost cried. Then i go inside and dont no why but i text #3 and i told him i liked him, i didnt get a text back....but at least i did it and he knows from me now. So that was the second outta the blue brave thing i did today. Then i hung out with Vince, chilled, it was fun fun fun!  lol Then im eating cookies with my dad and all of the sudden hes like oh yea! i got #2's e-mail adress. im like wtf? really? why? and hes just like i dunno i thought u might want it if u didnt have it, and so he gave it to me, and i just emailed him. i gave him my #, all that good stuff told him we should hang out ect. ect. so yea, courage thing #3. I hope somthing comes outta any of those things, casue i put my self out there, and i wasnt scared, still not scared of whats ganna go down. you no i guess something already has come outta those things, i got over my fear (for now at least lol). 
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ive come to the conclusion that for now (untill x-mas probably) #2 is kinda outta my reach, witch is realyl no big deal casue its been years im used to it. So now ive decided to concentrate on #3. Like really i like him a lot. So im ganna go for it, im ganna focus and im ganna do this. I think my problem is im just kinda like i like you and you and you and ive never really set my sites on one person. And ive finally noticed that the people who are with who they wanna be with, worked on it, and waited, and concentrated on that one person, so ive decided im ganna change a little and try that cause i really like this guy. We get along real well, we have a lot of fun, we laugh and make fun of eachother a lot too. I dunno and like hes the only guy (literally) that ive ever met that im like we should hang out and usualy guy are just like for sure. but everytime if said that to him he like well yea! im free tomorrow lets do somthing. i dunno maybe a lot of guys are like that but none of the guys ive ever been around have been, its cool. And liike i no his friend told me that he wasnt sure if he liked me, but thats not a no, its a i could, its an ive got a chance. since he said that he liked the way things ae goin, things are ganna keep goin that way. and things well progress. i hope. but all i can do is try so thats what im ganna do, im  ganna buckle down and im ganna try, really hard. So wish me luck casue im on a mission. (i sound like an obessed stocker dont i.....? shit. im not tho! i promise!)
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate looking at someone else who has what i want and there is no way that i can get it. its always been a problem for me, its like my mom says, when i was little and i went to a birthday party and we got the kid somthing i HAD to get one to or i wouldnt give it to them, casue then they would have somthing i wanted. but with this.....this is somthing that u cant just be like hey i want that and go to the store and pick one up. Its somthing that hasta come to you. I no i sound like a little spoiled bitch but hey its something that i have a problem with, always have, but hopfully always wont. that would suck. 
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate this, the feeling of really liking someone and being afraid to do anything about it. Im not talking about #3 anymore, (his friend told him and told me he "wasnt sure yet" but he "likes the way things are") Im talkin about #2 now. It was a family get together, the 4th, so of course they came over and his little brother didnt come, so it was just us hangin around. He and i watched a movie, went to the fireworks and then played a game. Durring the fireworks i laughed more than i had in a long time and really got along really well with someone for once. We really hit it off, usually we dont really talk to much but we really got along really well. And then when they were leaving, in my head i was like, talk to him, get his #, ask him to hang out sometime, get his e-mail, DO SOMETHING!, but of course i coudlnt even do that. And why still boggles my mind, why there are those few people that i just cant do that with. I dont no why, i could probably meet like, Adam Brody and be like hey can i call u sometime, but no, theres those few guys who really to anyone else arnt that great or special, but to me there amazing. And now im sitting here, upset casue i did nothing and the next holiday that ill probably see him is Christmas witch is in 6 moths, and just being mad at my self and wanting to cry and just im really confussed...I hate this feeling its one of the worst feelings, wanting to do something but holding back and then wishing u had and u dont no why u didnt (did that make sence). Anyway that feeling i just tried to explain, its the worst. And i hate crying, but now i am and it sucks. But oh well, i skrewed up once again and i guess i got at least 6 moths to try to get some balls and do somthing, but ive been sayin that for years, and all its gotten is worse. I see him, it gets worse. I think about him, it gets worse. Someone mentions the family, it gets worse. Its the snowball effect, and i guess one day that snowball will hit a tree. Witch could be good or it could be bad. But untill i decide to be a big girl and do somthing i guess ill just be doin like im doin now, being upset for somthing i didnt do that i should of. And like i said thats the worst feeling... 
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ive always thought about what i wanted to be when i grew up, everyone has, but untill last night i hadnt really rthought about what i wanted to be now too. In the car last night Trey asked me, what i was ganna do when i was older. And i told him about what i wanted to do, about how i wanted to go to college and study peoples minds. I love all that stuff, like how ur mind works, it fasinates me. Anyway so we talk about all that for a while and have this real meaningfull conversation about our lives. Trey and i really understand eachother, like where were coming from. Were a lot alike. Later at my house, we were talking about this girl and he was telling me how she needed to find her self. and how he told her that "u no i really dont no who i am eighter but latley ive been sitting down with my self nad finding out what i want and who i am and just sorting threw my stuff." and after he said that i was like wow, i really need to do that. I need, just about more than anything right now, to find out who i am. casue i think thats a big part of my problem. I think thats a big part of why things arnt the way that i want them. Its the reasion that guys dont like me, bc im complex and how can someone try and get to know u and like u if u dont know and like your self...? He was telling me that right now hes living his dads dream, hes playing baseball, doin the good grade thing, ganna go to UT and play baseball and become a arcetect. and he just looked me in the face and said i need to find out if i really want to do that or if i want to go do what i want to do, go be a doctor, not go to UT, quit baseball, or am i ganna just live threw my father? And then i realized that i dont no what im living, im just kinda floating around, im real..confussed isnt the right word i guess but im a lot of differnt people right now, in a lot of different ways. Like half of me wants to be this laid back, i dont care, free sprit, but then the other half wants to be this preppy, fun, good grade, little girl. and so far ive tried to do both but its odd. I wish i had my licence, id drive up to ruidoso, and just be alone for a couple days, think. I need time to be out of my house and just think for a while, a long while, get my stuff together and straighted out. Im glad Trey and i had that conversation, casue for the first time i was around someone who was thinkin ahead. i mean all my friends think ahead but not like that. they think of tomorrow and like next year at the very most, but this was a bigger picture. This was now, and forever. and it was good for me to be with someone who, for the most part, has there stuff together and no realizes that hey, what i dont have together i need to get together casue thats important. Life is more than, who your goin out with right now, who your hangin out with, what your doing tonight, its who YOU are. Its not about aynone else its about you, your life is about you. and i think till now ive been rapped up too much in all that other crap that in 2-3 years wont mean shit to us anymore. I wont no 90% of these people then, i wont care who there with, but there will be some i will still no and i will ALWAYS have to no and care about myself. so i really really need to get this started an just find somewhere that i can just sit and think. Find out who i am, casue the sooner i find out who i am, then everyone else will too and i think that will help a lot...
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, wow.......wow. My mind and heart are both goin like 1,000,000 miles a min. I just had the best night. It was with #3 (of course, lol). There was a break threw in our relationship. He held my hand while we watched a movie and we kinda cuddled. Then we talked for a long time and then he left, as usual he huged me but this time, he leaned in and kissed me. Wholy shit. He held me all close, and it was sooo good. I swear i think i could have fallen down if he hadnt of been holding me. It came outta no where, i didnt think in a million years hed kiss me. I duno it just, wow. I cant even think straight, im so twitterpated (thanks cassie, stole that one from you).&nbsp; I honestly think hes the first guy whose kissed me, like made the first move. Im usually the one whose like im ganna kiss you and goes for it. It was so much better this way, it was, wow. Ok i need to go to bed now casue im to jumbled to write anything really i just had to get this out and share my extreme joy, lol. Well good night, and remember - "all you need is love."&nbsp;&nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Every day is new; everyday is beautiful! Thats a pretty exquisite way to look at life, if you think about it." Brittany Murphy said that in a magizine interview that i read the other day and after that ive had a whole differnt look on life. Ive been    happy  for no reasion really. I smile a lot. I look at my self differently. I always have this excited feeling in my stomach for no reasion at all. This has all happend in like 3 days and these have been some of the best 3 days ever. I havnt done a thing, exept i watched a movie with #3 (witch would have made me really  happy  anyway), ive been out side a lot, planted some flowers,&nbsp; got some picture frames to put some pictures up in my room. But really its just been very ralaxing and  happy . I think it makes me even more  happy  to be  happy  becasue i havnt truly been  happy  for a very very long time. Yea i would be  happy  for like a day becasue something happened. But im  happy  just becasue, i have no reasion and thats really a good feeling.   
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone out there in Internet Land!Sorry its been a while since Ive actually writen something but I was outta town, and these are my adventures...I went with my parents to Austin last wed. morning. We stayed at this super snazzy hotel becasue my dad had a meeting there and they paid for the room. WOW. Talk about a nice place....Luke Willson had just left, on tuesady, i miss one of my all time favorite actors by one day! I was pissed. We went to PF Changs 3 times in 2&nbsp;days.&nbsp; Sad isnt it. &nbsp;We went down to 6th street, hung out, shopped, Austin is weird. ITs one of the coolest places ever, but in little doses. I dunno its weird, I guess thats why i got one of those "Keep Austin Weird" shirts. Its a fun place, but i dont htink i could live there. Good thing my graes arnt good enough to go to UT.&nbsp; lol. Thursaday night i texted #3 a song lyric, just casue i was bored and thinking of him, and i found on that really fit, it was by Incubus.&nbsp; Then he sent me one back (bc hes just that cool) and it was also by Incubus, it was from the song I Miss You. It was a really good one, it kinda struck a nerve, i dunno it was sweet.&nbsp;I hope he likes me. Like i think he might but you never really no. Then on Friday morning we drove the 30 min drive down to San Marcos. For those of you who havnt been to San Marcos, its exactally in the middle of Austin and San Antonio, 30 mins both ways, and one of the most beautiful little towns in this state. There are about 37,000 people, 30,000 of witch are Texas State students. So its a lot of fun. Its perfect, i really really want to go to school there, you have 2 of the biggest cities in texas 30mins away but you live in the tiny little town. Its really nice. Anyway my brother lives there and i was stayin with him and we partied.....and we partied....and we partied. I can easly say that is the leat amount of sleep ive gotten in a looooong time. He had gotten a puppy, a little 9 week old blue heeler. Shes adorable. She had gotten hit by a car on friday morning, but thank God she only hurt her elbo, is wasnt even broken. But she had a little puppy cast just to make sure, it was so cute, and i felt so bad for her. Shes a trooper. On Sat. we tubed the river. The San Marcos river is the most pure river in the world (really it is im not just sayin that). It comes straight from a spring so its cristle clear and really cold. It was really nice tho. Beatiful surrounings, really relaxing, gave me my needed&nbsp;time to think. Then we left sunday morning, that was a gooood trip. Gabe, Lindsey (his girlfriend, who i just love)and Meha (the puppy)&nbsp;are comming&nbsp;thursday. Lookin forward to that. Should be some more good times.....&nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       My Top Ten Favorite Songs  in no order  &nbsp;  * Stairway to Heaven -Led Zepplin     &nbsp;   * Yellow Subarine -The Beatles     &nbsp;   * I&nbsp;Wish You Were Here -Incubus     &nbsp;   * Love Is All You Need -The Beatles     &nbsp;   * Imagine -John Lennon     &nbsp;   * If I Saw You In Heaven -Eric Clapton     &nbsp;   * All Of This -Blink 182 feat. Robert Smith     &nbsp;   * What I Got -Sublime     &nbsp;   * Long and Winding Road -The Beatles     &nbsp;    * A Rush of Blood to the Head -Coldplay      
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            I Miss You  - Incubus   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    To see you, when I wake up is a gift I didn't think could be real.    To know that you feel the same as I do is a three-fold utopian dream.    You do something to me that I can't explain.    So would I be out of line if I said, I miss you.(?)    I see your picture, I smell your skin on the empty pillow next to mine.    You have only been gone ten days, but already I'm wastin away.    I know I'll see you again whether far or soon.    But I need you to know that I care and I miss you.     
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Things are wounderfull. Absolutely faboulous. Just about perfect. &nbsp;Things are like they were about 6 months ago. Im super beeming happy, I care about someone who cares about me and things are good. I realized things kinda repeat themselves. Like lets use my situation&nbsp;as an example:&nbsp;Ok i was upset with things, with myself, and the fact that i didnt have someone. So i quit trying, just gave everything up and all the sudden things start fallin in my lap. Like i got some new friends, i starting passing math, and Chris came along. And i liked him a lot ya ya ya you no the story. So we go out everything is super duper and then things start to be bad, we break up and its over. Im upset with things again, with myself again, and also im back with no one. So im all bumbed for a while and then about a week ago things made a complete 180.&nbsp;&nbsp;Things are goin good, Im happy with myself, and also ive found someone who i care about. &nbsp;#3 (hes really #1 and only now but i dont wanna confuse yall with a # change)&nbsp;and I have been talkin on the phone every night since our little thing. Hes been outta town with his best friend but still calls and stuff and texts me about how much he misses me and stuff like that. I really like him a lot and i think he feels the same way. I cant wait till he gets home, hell be back this weekend. Anyway, this entry wasnt suposta be about how much i care but him, it was suposta be about how no matter how bad things get, they will always get better. Always. So for all you people ( i like to think a lot of people read this) who are kinda down remember - " everything&nbsp;moves in circles." 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey all! I was told to "update my journal" so here i am. I havnt been writing bc i really have nothing to write about. The reasion i started this thing was to get out and talk about things that bothered me, and stuff. But lately as you no, i havnt been bothered by too many things. Things are really good, and i havnt been givin you a play by play with #3 casue i duno, all yall need to no is that things are good. And things are good. In every way. Well execpt for my bother. ehhh. He has always done little things that buged me but this time (hes still in town) its just really been getting to me. Ok honestly, most of you wont believe me but my dad favors my brother. I swear to God. Its always aww poor gabe, oh you broke our lamp from paris, oh you got perment marker all over our couch, oh your really an ass hole to everyone, oh you leave us to baby sit your puppy, its no big deal. I swear to God if i ever, EVER did ENYTHING NEAR like breaking something like that or ruining the couch, woah. Id be yelled at for days, have to clean it up/pay for it and i would be in sooooooooooo much troble it would be unbelieveable. But no, gabe doesnt even get a slap on the wrist. It makes me so mad. Gabe went to jail for a bunch of pot in his car and what did he get, a "dont ever do that again speech" and a new car? becasue his old one looked like a stoner car??? wtf? If my dad knew that i had even smoked one cigrette ever, id be grounded till i was 18. I dont get it, for gabe-jail=new car, for me-jail=i dont even what to think about it but it sure as hell isnt anything close to a new car. And he is so rude and mean to my dad, like he brutally makes fun of him and my dad lets it slide. But i say one little thing and oh wow, its over. And another thing, since my dad has all this extra stress when gabes here, and no where to put it since he wont give it to gabe like he should, i get it. Ill sit on the couch and hell yell at me for it. It sucks. And im not making all this up, i thought i might have been exagerating it untill my mom and i were talking about it and she said the same thing. How dad takes all the gabe stuff out on me. But then my mom says "well its becasue he holds you at a higher standard than gabe, hes knows you can do more and that your smarter. And he thinks that if he slacks off with you like he did with gabe then you wont live to your full potentional like he could of, like he knows you can." But whatever, its still not fair. Ok now that the teeny tinyest part of the whole gabe thing is out i feel a little better. Well for now, until he comes back from ruidoso, does something else wrong and my dad looks the other way. I love my brother to death and i no hed do anythign for me but grrrr all this gets to me soooooo bad. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You no what, forget what i said/complained about yesterday. Things between #3 and i are great. Him even liking me is way more than i ever expected to come outta this and for him to not only like me but to have all this other stuff, its great. So what if were not goin out (yet) its just a title. I mean its not like wed like eachother differently just becasue he was my "boy friend". I like what weve got. I like it a lot. I like being able just to lie together all tangled up for hours and just talk and be together. I like likeing him and i like that he likes me. And Its not a big deal if were not going out. All in good time. School starts in 3 days and then well see eachother a lot more and things will turn out just fine, i know it. Things are super. :-)  
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok this is all very confussing and im sure all of this wont make any sence but i have all this stuff in my head and it needs to go somewhere. There all this emotions and questions that i need to get out there. Ok thigns between #3 and i are good. were hangin out a lot, talkin on the phone and stuff like that. We both really like eachother, we tell eachother all the time. But were not going out. And really im not 100% sure why, like hes told me kinda but i idnt really get it. I mean what are you waiting for, things are perfect, they couldnt get better, there cant be a better time? I dunno. And im sure your thinking, hes playin you. But i no hes not. I no it. Ive been with enough guys who have tried to pull that shit over on me and i can tell. But the things he says to me, and how he says them, i can tell. And hes not that kinda person. And when we kiss (witch is all weve done witch is another way i no hes not playin me) its different than anything else. Like the way he holds me so incredably close and the way that when were walking and he holds my hand so tight like he doesnt want to let go. And threw all these thigns, were not goin out. I dont undersatnd it. I dunno maybe im missing something. Like i dunno, we were talking the other night and my dad kept buggin me to ask him if he was my bf. So finally i was like fuck it and i asked him and he said "well the reasion i havnt done anything yet is becasue i wanna wait a little like till school starts and see what happeends"??? and so i was like ok. thats cool. Then i get off the phone and me texts me about how he "really really likes me but wants to get to no me better before anything serious happeneds"?And im like ok thats fine. And it is, i have no problem. I just dont understand why. We were together last night and after he left i texted him that "being with him feels more right than anything else", and he said, "i cant find the words to describe how i feel". What does that maen, help me out casue for the life of me it just confussed me. So all day all i can think of is how confussd i am, and honestly it boggles my mind. Like i dont even no. and if anyone, well whoever reads this, can help me out in anyway, the littlest piece of advice would help, please let me no. Post a comment, e-mail me, call me, cause im completly lost. its frusterating, to like someone like this, know that they feel the same, and to have them, but at the same time u dont.   
      
</post>


</Blog>