<Blog>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that by now you mangy lot who're reading this blog (if there ARE any of you, that is)have realized that I'm really a very cheesy person. But that's good! Cheese grows better with time. Or was that wine?  Hmm. Anyway, this is my first blog anywhere anytime! My sister, however, appears to be addicted to blogging. Its the cheese withdrawal, I tell you.  Soooo. I'll start first with some background, then every blog AFTER this will be detailing REAL EVENTS! GWEEEE!!  I'm a 11 year old kid living in singapore. I like to think that I'm cultured, so I play the piano and am now...grade five? I think?  Anyways, I actually don't play that much. I have weekly lessons of one hour, but that's about all I play. And what's amusing is that after two weeks of holiday, I came back and my playing still hadn't changed. :P  My teacher didn't make the connection that if I don't play for two weeks and I'm still the same, that means I don't practice at all! Lucky me.  I like playing the piano, but it's quite hard to remember, sometimes.  Also, I'm a geek. I spend most of my time reading Final Fantasy 7/8/9/10 but mostly FF7 fanfics, and I enjoy lots of animes too! Including Ranma 1/2, Neon Genesis Evangelion, DBZ...  For those of you who don't know, fanfiction is when you really like a TV show or a cartoon or game or whatever. As a result, you want to write stories about that TV show/game/whatever. The biggest archives can be found at www.fanfiction.net and www.mediaminer.org.  I think Shinji/Rei is the best pairing ever.  As might be expected, I also write (quite immature and bad)fanfictions. They can be found at www.fanfiction.net/~Silverdancer. Please READ AND REVIEW!!  All right, now that my rant is over, I can get on with the more important details.  Singapore uses the British education system, so we have 6 years of primary school, 4 years secondary, 2 years Junior college and then 4 years University.  Right now I'm in my last year of primary school. lucky meeee~~!!  I'm feeling kinda hyper -_-;;  *bounce bounce*  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today wasn't all that great. Yesterday, though, that rocked. I got 9 minutes 38 second score for my 1.6 run! For people who aren't from Singapore, that's part of the NAPFA test. National Assessment Physical Fitness awards. We do situps and inclined pullups and stuff like that. I'm...not a very healthy person. So that was pretty darn hard.  But...damn, 9.38 is pretty damn good, considering my past record! Last year I got 10.51. I suppose its due to my father making me run everyday.  Grr.  In any case, yesterday was a Tuesday. I know I haven't been updating for a while (or a month), but that's 'cos my exams are coming! PRELIMS ARE NEXT WEEK!  Crap.   urlLink     urlLink     Haiz. My friend got 6.45! And he cried because he lost to someone else by 5 seconds!  I can't run 6.45 if I train for the rest of the year!  Some people....  Anyway,I haven't really been studying. Fine, I haven't been studying at all. Hey! Don't look at me like that!  My piano exam last last week sucked ASS. I am so gonna fail.  So, what else? Oh yeah, shameless plug. Go to  urlLink www.fanfiction.net/~Silverdancer  ! All my fanfictions are published there. Read! You know you want to! *attempts telekinesis from far far away, making your hand twitch slightly but nothing else* Damn.  We had a party today! A mini party, at least. 6M   Which is a heckuvalot.  We threw our textbooks into the air and whooped. Mine hit the fan and tore, which kinda dampened the spirits of the occasion. But what the heck! The spirits were fully revived and dancing to "Blame it on the Boogie" when my friends pulled out a GIGANTIC packet of Twisties (tm)!  We have Chinese, English, Maths and Science and Social Studies as subjects.  Pei De was pretty depressed 'cos he got 7.45. Which....man, almost all of my friends beat me! Well, 9.38 is pretty good. I beat Zebedee, a skinny tall kid.  WaHaHa!  During Social Studies and English today I scribbled comics on a piece of scrap paper. It went something like this.   Pupil:  Goddamn! This is the Oral exam! Nevousnervousnervous!   Invigilator:  Mr. X, its your turn.     Pupil:  Calm down...calm down... *walks out to a chair and sits down. In front is a table, and further in front a examiner seated on a chair.   Pupil:  *Sits down* Oh FUCK! *Leaps up and says breathlessly* Good morning, sir/madam!   Examiner:  ...   Pupil:  Blah blah blah. Blah blah blah, blah blah.   Examiner:  Tell me more about this picture, please.   Pupil:  ...AAAAAAAAAGGGGGHHHHH! I CAAAN'T DOOOO THIS! *stands up abruptly, chair flies backwards, then collapses on floor and cries a fountain*   Examiner:  ...coherency: zero. *scribble scribble*  As you can tell, I have a disturbed mind. But my other comrade, brother in brotherhood, pal loser Keng Yong is even worse. His went like this.   Invigilator:   Boy, its your turn.    Pupil:   *Mind: Arrow bounces from  Sense  down to  Duh , then bounces back up and stays on top at  Mindless Crap .    Pupil at Examination Chair:   I like Barney.   We're both disturbed. Its official.       urlLink    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>