<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I woke up and went to LIT class and then i went to my dads house and helped him with the computer..then i came home and now im hear. I am really tired and iwasnt feeling very good either. This week i applied at Carters and ill be applyin other places also. I really need a job and some money! I need to win the lottery or somthin lol! I never understood why people say i need to win the lottery, andi m like how are you gonna win if u dont even play..lol like there gonna call you up and say "hey i know u didnt play but you won anyway congrats!! lol! but yea i do need money..i need braces...a car...clothes..shoes...and other stuff!!!But yea i finished my book GIDGET today!! it was really really good i liked it a lot! Ive beenreadin a lot this summer cause i dont have anything to do, so yea! Omg today it was so funny my mom was gettin in the tanning bed and she couldnt find her goggles while she was in there so me andm y sister are sittin in the living room watchin her try to meneuver around with like an inch of space..it was the funniest thing i ever seen... was rollin..she looked like a rertarded turtle on his back trying to turn over it was so halrious! But yea anyways! ive been really aggrevated a lot lately. I dont have anything to do and all my friends have either jobs or sports. but on to a better point i heard i might be gettin my guitar back!! I AM SO CYKED! but yea and heres an ammouncement..im pregnant!!!!! lol not really..well thats about it sorry these things are boring lol aloha!! YIKES! i love david spade!! 
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok last night me and my sister and my mom got into it..about DeAnna always stayin up late and sleepin in all day..I got really sick of my mom always believing everything DeAnna says and not me so we were talkin(no yelling) about it, and I was crying and I was thinking a lot about suicide and my mom heard me talkin to my sister about it and she came in there and hugged me and kissed me(she doesnt do that very often..its mega rare) but yea and i just started crying harder. I would never commit suicide but sometimes u cant help it b/c i know death is not an answer to ur problems! But yea so i just started praying.. and man ive just been so depressed! So please keep me and my family in yalls prayers! Then today i was with my dad and i almost broke my ankle! So yea and it hurts like a beast! I dont even want to know what it feels like to actually brake it!Then my mom came home today upset.. she heard that a friend of ours Jeff..is a moocher and i hope he doesnt try to come move in with us cause man he makesm e feel uncomfortable..and i could neverl ive in the same house as him and my mom said this is our home and he is not moving in so thats a relief...but it just seems that everything is going wrong right now i just dont even know what to think anymore... ive been so stressed out!Then ontop of that some stuff has been happening to my best friend and that is makin me real upset... and i just dont even want to get up in the morning anymore, im just scared of what new stuff ill learn about. I dont want my fmaily goin through the crap that i had to go through thats all i know. when i was little my dad used to beat the crap out of my mom...and he used to get drunk all the time..and that has seriously ruined me..i dont trust many guys...and i always dream about the times my dad beat my mom up right in front of me.. and the sad thing is my dad doesnt even remember ever doin that! But my dad is so much better now ...but theres always that fear that that might happen to me someday! I guess thats one of the reasons i havent had a boyfriend either! and i so agree with gabbywhen she says i wish i could win the lottery.. there is so much stuff i need.. i need a car...i need a cell phone.. i need clothes.. theres so much stuff....Idk i just cant wait to get married and have my own family..but yeathats kinda of what ive ben think about today and what all happened!
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Man sometimes i dont even feel like life is worth living! I am so bored in my life... and sometimes i get so depressed! I never feel good about my self or confident but how can i feel confident when my family is always putting me down..or guys are putting me down. I just dont even know what to do anymore. I find myself almost crying every night..sometimes i have to cry myself to sleep.. i am so lonely in my life.. ive also been slippin in my faith a lot.. ive been cussing and just not acting like a christian.. and it really makes me feel bad! Then me and my mom and my sister , DeAnna have been fighting  a lot. I just sometimes get so mad at them, i want to hit them so i have to go in my room and scream into a pillow or somthin... then no one ever calls me.. mym om is always like wheres all ur friends and im like idk u tell me! Sometimes I just want to get out of Louisiana, i hate this place so much! My mom is talking about moving to Florida but we cant really afford it.. we cant really afford anything now days. Ive been thinking a lot about my friends i never see.. like the people from New Iberia, and New Orleans.. and my family a lot.. I never get to see them and it makes me really upset.. Im ready to justl ive myl ife but it hasnt even started. Ive never had a boyfriend and it makes me really depressed just to think about it. Sometimes I feel like the virgin Mary.. ive never even kissed a guy! I feel like a walking disease or somthing.... its like what do i smell bad is that why ive never had a boyfriend.. or maybe im just picky.. i no im very picky..but if some people went through what i went through.. they wouldnt trust guys either... idk! and im tired of everytime i tell someone how im feeling they tell me all these comments like "o danni ur not ugly ur pretty" blah blah blah and im like thanks but i dont want any complements right now im just tellin you how i feel...and how do i know ur tellin me the truth its not like they would say "im ugly" to my face. but yea thats whats been on my mind lately! 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       ok hey everyone!! me and kayley had an awesome&nbsp; day yesterday!! we watched the butterfly effect!! ::grabs granola bar with fake hand:: rotflmbo!! it was so good and it was somewhat funny!! then me and kayley played a mean trick on this guy but hey " what comes around goes around" sucka!! lol it was so great! but hey he took itl ike a champ ill give him that!! o yea and mym om made up a new number "one thousand-forty eight hundred!" woohoo lol!! gah she is such a&nbsp; dork!! oops kayley did u spill ice cream on ur shirt let me geti t off ::dives across the room" here here here!! lol i love it then u got some on ur bra and i got some on my shirt that was so sexy!! lol! wont u be my neighbor? heck yea ill be mr. rogers neighbor!! lol !! that was so funny!! i love you girl all the way!!!    &nbsp;&nbsp; but yea then today! i went with val and we got some stuff and ran errands! but yeai thought about this one guy all day! i wish i could just get over him cause i dont think i even have a chance but right now im tryin to think positive.. and be positive! YEAH! but yea so ive really been thinkin about him!! then brandon from the amazing race comes on and he is just my latin lover i love him like fat kid loves cake he is so hott and hes a christian how cool is that!! all the way man!! totally cool!! but then he kissed his girlfriend i was like man im happy for ya but holy crap! but then kayley came to my rescue and made it all better ;) lol im jk she gavem e words of wisdom lol!! i love you girl !! but yea so thats what has been goin on love you all aloha!! bipolar i think not!  
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        ok last night i went to sams..and we played a little of our guitars!! lol and made up songs it was soooo great!! then we watched the heathers..and it was weird..especially when sam is practically humpin the tv ..b/c she loves christian slater!!! lol!! ok so we begin to watch black sheep and we fall asleep..this morning we woke up to the annoying birds outside singin louder than ever..and im not talk this sweet little tweet..im talkin obnoxious squawking lol! IT WAS SO FUNNY!!&nbsp; but yea then&nbsp; me and her went to the animal shelter i got in the worst of moods and then we went thrift store shoppin!! and we found like 6 pairs of the 80's ballet flats with bows in all these colors but none of them could fit us so we got aggrevated but thats ok!! lol!! and we were goofin off and stuff lol!! then there was this sexy acoustic fender in the goodwill for 100 bucks i wanted it sooo bad! and this guy there was makin a big deal out of it and me and sam were laughin loL!! then somebody like ran through the store or somthin cause when we got there all the workers were comin up to us askin if we were in the store when it happened werel ike how do we know when we dont even know what happened! lol it was very fun!! So yea thats what i did!! then i went in carters and they might be hyering me super fun!! i need a job sooo bad!!! u have no idea!! and a car!! me and sam decided that for prom she was gonna let her eyebrows grow out..rent a tux..and go as my prom date how super cool would that be! lol!! and she was like pokin herm om while we were drivin! it was so funny!! also, i made an amzing discovery.. THERE IS A CANDY CALLED GOOBERS!...HOW COOL IS THAT!!  totally cool!! i was like wow i thought that was a made up word!! but yea so thats what happened now my mom and sis are in my room watchin home alone!! im like i dotn want to watch thisbut they obviously dont care!! well ill ttyl aloha!   
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Ok....i am really upset today...i get so sick of people tellingm e their gonna do somthin and not do it..ok fist things firsti&nbsp; dont expect anyone to do anything for me or even talk to me.. but if you say ur gonna do it..u better do it...its so frustrating and depressing especially when guys do it and this has been happening with a lot of my girlfriends too! Im sick of me gettin hurt and them..guys if u say ur gonna call..call..if u say ur gonna come over..come over...we dont expect u to do these things but if u freakin tell us ur gonna do it !! freakin do it!! im sick of all u guys crap!! i dont care if we have feelings for u or not even if were are just friends dont say it if ur not gonna do it..i dont care if sometihng came up dont say ill come over tonight if ur not going to! say ill come over sometime instead or somthin!! gahh leee!!! Guys always complain about girls bein complicated..let me think about that for a minute..woooo glad thats over...no guys are the ones who are complicated their like a 1 freakin ring circus!! it gets on my nerves and im sure everyone else's tooo!! Im not a B.I. im just fed up!! this has happened to many times to me and my friends and im sick of it!! even if u and the girl are just friends im fed up of my friends callin me up set cause guys dont have the balls to keep their freakin promises!! and to me if u say it..uve promised it!! but whatever ! i give up on guys ive never trusted them and ive been tryin.. but forget this!! whatever!! im sick of cryin myself to sleep everynight cause guys are&nbsp;a**ho*es!!! Guys u just dont&nbsp;understand how easy us&nbsp; girls can get hurt and fall in love with you!! were not something u can pick up and drop whenever u want!! dont play us like&nbsp;its some kindof a&nbsp;game!! But yea just had to get that out!! sorry lol! &nbsp;&nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok... lets see i went to blue bayou/dixie landin with all my gurls tuesday..it was soooo awesome!! We met a bunch of hotties lol not really but we talked to a bunch of the hott workiers lol!! Then as we were drivin homem ym om slams on her breaks o the interstate and pulls over and shes like " omg there was puppies on the side of the road" so me and my cuz jump ou of the car..i have a shirt over my bathin suit but heather doesnt so were runnin as fast as we can down the interstate and we got truckers bonkin at us and whistlin out the window and me and heather are like o god lol save us! well were like where are they and turns out my mom saw some flowers and a garbage bag and thats what she saw that were the ''puppies'' so me and heather run back to the car and were like what the crap the puppies that u saw were a garbage bag and some flowers u psycho lol we were so mad but it was funny! THen i went to church wednesday..and were graduated from lit class sunday at the big church! i am so excited! then matt hit me... im so gonna get u back boy wait till i get u out of church im gonna knock u sooo far down  the street u wont beable to find ur way home lol!! then i talked to my new iberia friends today and alll my guy  friends are shavin there hair off im gonna beat some one up!! then my man came on tv yesterday..brandon from the amzing race he is soooooooooo hott i would sooo marry him! lol but neways! Ive been fostering these two dogs and waitin for a call back from carters! and ive been really really bored so if an yone wants to do somthin sometime call me !! im almost always home!!! o yea nad got my guitar back!!! yee haww!! i learned gchord and e minor!! and ive been practicing that!! its reAlly hard though and my fingers hurt like a beast!! theni ve been singin a lot aggrevatin my family but o well! lol ! but yea thats whats been goin on! o yea and im still single lol so is kayley!! lol o yea kayley ur fat!! lol jk!! hahhaah! love you aloha!!
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok I know I have been a lazy cow and havent written in this thing for a loooooong time now so yea! Lets see whats been up:  *Ive been really bored ....but at the same time very busy(is that at all possible)  *Then, i went and saw Spider Man 2 and it was so awesome and i have to say that toby mcguire is very sexy in that movie( but everyone knows that if they saw if him on the street(like if he wasnt famous) no one would look at him twice cause hes not that great lookin and hes like an average joe)  * Then i saw the love of my life on tv with another woman! lol jk well theres this major babe on the amazing race named brandon..hes super super hott! I love him! lol  *Ive been kinda depressed lately i havent been able to sleep cause all i can think about is this one guy! I dont even know why i like him but i just cant help it! i stay up at night and all i can think about is him(it sucks...b/c he prolly never thinks of me).....(heres a some lagniappe for all the guys out there...if u like a girl dont hold back..tell her..b/c u never know she might like u too...and earth to all guys girls most of the time do not admit to you when they like you so u do have to take a chance!!! just tell her how u feel!) but yea anyway so thats been really draggin me down..i hate bein this way  * O yeah i still dont have a job..if anyone knows anywhere i can get a job..tell me i would be greatful!!!  *I updated my pics i have three new pics up ...go to www.picturetrail.com/surfinforgod  *O yea...i am so aggrevated no one ever calls me!! omg its like i dont have any friends anymore..ok my friends mom calls me more than any of my friends do... how sad is that!!!   * then i went to biloxi..got stung really bad by a humongo jellyfish..and now im peelin like a rotten banana! I look like i have lepracy or somthin lol!!   *Ok now thism ay seem desperate but i dont care!! I am single to mingle!! I need a fine piece or real- estate cause im gonna get me some land you know what im sayin lol!! i have pics..but yea i daught ill date a guy that i dont know lol!! and not to sound like a beast but hes gotta be christian! like as if im not strugglin enough with my bleiefs all i need is a guy to pull me down !! i love beach boyl ookin guys!! o yes!!! shaggy blonde hair bring it on lol or any kindof shag will do !! haha i am such a dork!!   *Yea well thats my pathetic life!! hahhaha! City morg ill connect you!!!       love yall the great and wonderful danni 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey you guys..well i went to the beach last saturday and it was awesome!! Me, bekah, and kellee met a whole bunch of guys!! But they liked these 2 named chris and corey and so they talked aboutthem alot! But yea so while they were hangin out with them i hung out with tyler. He was really funny and cool! We got lost tryin to go get a drink from the store and it was all tylers fault cause he didnt want his feet to hurt lol he waqs complainin the whole time lol! i thought it was so funny!! But yea so we met back up with them but it took us like 15 mins to get back b/c of out "short cut" lol they were already atthe pool! lol tyler got crabs and this old lady with no tongue scared us all half to death lol! i love you guys! then they left and we met 2 new guys..they were like freakin giants..one of them had this super hott body but yea he was a meat head then joel was kool but he was like the jolly green giant! So while bekah and kellee were hangin out with them i went off by myself and met this guy that was playin his guitar named ruben! He was so kool! so me and him sang while he was playin his guitar it was really fun..then me and him ran into these guys that didnt like bekah and kellee and they didntl ike them either.. their names were steven and ricky...steven was drunk off his butt..but it was so funny... so we were all hangin out and they were downin my friends but i had to tell him to stop cause he was gettin mean.. then this guy and these girls come along..and the guy was this gurls bro. and his name was jon and he had like the most beautiful hair ever!! he was really cool. Then they all left and it was just me and ruben again and we decided to go in. So i saw him again the next night and hes a christian too so we were talkin about God and he was askin me questions that i never really thought about b4 and it really made me think it was so awesome he was so smart...but yea! then bekah and kellee come and find me again and some british guy and his friends come along and kellee and bekah were flirtin with them it was so funny and that british guy cussedl ike a sailor it was so funny! but it was gettin aggrevatin after while. then ruben had to sing the song he wrote like 20 times it was so pretty but i could tell he was gettin aggrevated! lol... so bekah and them left and jelly man came along( he was this guy that kellee asked how u can pick up jely fish andh e was like u dont lol..it was great) so we kept running into him...then there was this guy the other night that i kept seein and he said he was gonna go into a corner and cry so i was like awwww and so i gavehim like three hugs it was funny! but yea bakc on track! so it was so awesome we met a bunch of people! But i miss my main guys that i talked to the most ..ruben and tyler! yall were so awesome! and Ruben ill see you online lol!! Tyler are you ok buddy hahaha! u were great! always wear ur pink belt!      Well i finally came hime from bein there for a week! i was ready to come home but now im ready to go back! o yea and we met these hott hott hott 13 year olds i was like man if u were my age they were so cute!! i got their pic so it will be up soon! my sister was like u didnt get there number form e whats wrong with u! So yea school is startin monday!! gah i soo dont want it to start that sucks butt!!! but like criston said the quicker it starts the quicker it will be over with!! but i want school to be out forever! lol! well i really need to go ill tt you fools lata! call me if anybody knows if there are any job openings! well aloha!!!   
      
</post>


</Blog>