<Blog>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     “I’ll be there for you when you need me.”  A forewarning to the storm, I  will  be there for you… meaning I am not there for you now…but hey, maybe in a couple of months….  I wont be there until you need me, so if u can struggle on your own some more that would be appreciated.  ‘ A promise made, a promise broken… ’  Can you tell if someone needs you by looking at them? I try but often I am mistaken and make an utter fool out of myself…and how do you know its YOU they need?   My friend made this promise to me before and she was not there when I needed her. She made it again only recently, I do not think I can handle another broken promise. Maybe it is a ‘trust’ thing, maybe I don’t trust her to be there… but I don’t think that is the case, I think it is more like I don’t think she can handle being there for me. In eng we watched King Lear and Edgar draws a blade across his skin, I heard her yelp behind me. To be there for me… what if I need her to be there for me when I draw the naked blade across bare flesh, could she handle that? She cant bear to see the scars, any of my scars, could she sit and listen as I tell her my tale of woe or would she be disgusted with me.  “   Cut the skin to the bone, fall asleep all alone, hear your voice in the dark.”   She seems to handle things by passing the problem onto others who are more “capable” of “helping”. I do not want nor need them. I make her angry with what I say.  Theresa of Avilla said “ Pain is never permanent ” I guess she did not reckon with my “engraving” into flesh. Pain IS permanent, it always will be. A tattoo of suffering, of torment, of agony. My barcode as the child of shadows, the daughter of the darkness. Permanent. Forever.   

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    My friend emailed me yet what she wrote filled me with a foreboding. She remade a promise that has been broken numerous times. i did not expect her to fulfil it regardlessly but she made it again now and this time... i dont know, i dont wish to believe it because i dont think she means to uphold it and because it was completed before. i dont think i can rely on her to follow through, even though i dont want to admit that or seem to doubt her. I am not doubting her, i just think she has made a rash promise without realising what she would need to do were she to keep it.        "Will you live with me the darkness as i die?"         She does not have the strength to do so, and i dont want to let her....she ought not waste her life in this way, in a worthless pursuit.      ~Aine   

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    What a GLORIOUS day, oh God must be laughing at the distress this lonly daughter of darkness. Oh what a pathetic little brat, and not a scrap of intelligence in her. I had my maths trial...i could only do about a quarter of the paper, and of the quarter i reckon i only got a quarter right. I am hating everything. I swear, why bother with someone as stupid as i. I look around and everyone else is happy....HAPPY....  I wishing that it all would end. Oh it would have all ended were it not for my "friend" who had to have her own way. If i go no doubt she would blame me and hate me forever, actually i think thats what she wrote. that if i go i have hurt god and her or some shit....cant she see that being here hurts me. it hurts me more than anything. i dont want to be here.  It wont matter if i go now or later... i just hurt everyone when i stay here. I hurt everyone and i cant stand being here. i just want to go and i cant. i cant coz i dont want her 2 b angry at me. i am so scared. I...i just want to crawl into bed and stay there for as long as possible.       "Story of a lonely guy". There is no point to anything. Nothing. "I'm all torn up inside." What do i have to do? stupid. worthless. Useless. Its all pointless. No purpose. No direction. I wonder.... is it my "friends" fault. i wanted to go and she wouldnt let me.... so now, is all this pain and suffering her fault?       ~Aine   

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Perhaps i have become psychic, or i subconsciously play out the images i write for last night the very image that i wrote yesterday came to pass. It was odd, i have not been like that for a long time. I have not felt the absence of God so sharply or known so completely that I am not part of Him. I knew, i think i have always known. You know how people reckon that we are all sons and daughters of God? Well it appears i am not. The God who is all merciful and love showed no care for a child of the shadows whose face was wet with tears and body convulsing with silent sobs. When i am a mother i will always ALWAYS help my children, hold them when they cry, i would not turn my back on them.... do you think God could be arrested for neglect? Ah but i forget, He is not my father, that has been made clear. A child of the shadows can only be a puppet of that evil one.  ~Aine   urlLink www.mesmerisation.blogspot.com   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Wells here is the first post for the child of the shadows, the daughter of darkness. I wasted my day reading and writing rather than doing study or school work... I suppose i should start but not bothered to. Okay, fine! I'll do SOMETHING now....sit out in the sun and stick pages in my drama book. Adios      ~Aine   

						
</post>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Got told off by the librarian! Trust! Neways...a very boring day...supposed to be studying for trials but i dont want to...i'll be kicking myself when i fail.&nbsp; Hee hee! My drama teacher wont be here for the next 3 weeks so we get to do our group project without her! Whooo hoo!     &nbsp;  My friend asked a BOY to the formal! OoOOh! Lol! She is all growed up now!!! Awww! Kawaii!    &nbsp;  Anyways. I best b off!    &nbsp;  ~Aine  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I was going to post yesterday but I was too cranky to. Oh but I apologised to my friend who I annoyed and who snapped at me. Its all fine but I wish sometimes I don’t have to be the one who always apologises. I know that sounds selfish but I apologise because I am sorry where as I think she simply replies because she doesn’t want to put up with me asking why she is angry and wont forgive me. I am lucky to have her friendship but there are these stupid conflicts that keep coming up and I just wish…. Oh I don’t know! I love her more than life itself but….   Trials are in four days. I am going to fail miserably! In maths today we had a ‘revision’ lesson and everyone was like “alpha plus beta equals a over b” and I had no clue what was going on so set my mind free for a few minutes and settled on a particular image. A young girl (teenaged) walks carefully along the top of a grey cliff. She continues on for a while with her careful and precise steps and then reaches the point. She turns to face the wind and the light gale fans her hair out behind her like a cloak of gold and her pale blue gown is subjected to the caprice of the breeze. She holds her arms out before her as though embracing the element as she stands on the edge of the cliff face. Her wide blue eyes hold back the unshed tears of a life of pain and heartache. Her expression is one of a deep sorrow, the kind that steals into ones heart and settles there for eternity and her eyes flutter to a close. She stands as though she were a child of stone except for her flowing dress and hair. Her eyes open slowly and there is a small sigh before she lets herself falls over the cliff as though to soar with the wind just one final time…  This image plagued me all day and I believe it is a symbol of my own self, my own soul, wanting to be set free but I cannot. As the day progressed more and more details emerged from the image and built up so much I could almost sob with her pain. “Hold on. Don’t be scared… Cause all of the star are fading away, try not to worry, you’ll see them someday…”   ~Aine 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Aine's Attempt at Blogging...prepare to hide 
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I know i usually use the other blog at times like these, but i need to vent here for some reason. I am sooo cranky. Trials are over, however my ex2 eng piece is due in next week...as too is my drama group and IP... as i know drama will def count towards UAI i must work on it, also the fact that it is group and i dont wanna let them down. Ex2 probably wont count but i've put soo much time and thought into it... i WANT to do it, wells neways it was supposed 2 be due on Wednesday and i was thinking, maybe on Monday night after drama i could work on it, also mum said to take the day off on Tuesday to finish it./... now miss tells me it is DUE on Tuesday.. I want to do it, hella i feel like crying coz i love english and my teacher seemed really angry but worse, disappointed.... i mean i can handle anger, but not disappointment.       I am scared i will ruin our group piece for drama! I dont think i am up for it and i talk too fast and have a lisp and i dont want people to know that! I mean its really bad and i hate it. i dont even read aloud in public anymore it is that bad. its awful, just like the rest of me. i wish i didnt have to do this at all. I am so stressed out about it. We saw the de la ones tonight and they are really good, i dont know how ours will compare.     Worse of all...i finally had an opportunity i had been waiting for, and i botched it... twice today. TWICE, and i botched it. What a loser. The biggest loser in the world.       "remember when i was in the grocery store, now's my time, lost the words, lost the nerve, lost the girl, left the line, i would wish upon a star but that star it doesn't shine, so read my book with a boring ending, a short story of a lonely guy"    That is my destiny, to be a loser and a loner. I wait for that one moment, i wait and i miss it, gone. Lost the words, lost the nerve. I am so cranky at myself. i wish...     The stars dont shine for me, i am bathed in darkness all my life. Always and forever....eternity  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I know i usually use the other blog at times like these, but i need to vent here for some reason. I am sooo cranky. Trials are over, however my ex2 eng piece is due in next week...as too is my drama group and IP... as i know drama will def count towards UAI i must work on it, also the fact that it is group and i dont wanna let them down. Ex2 probably wont count but i've put soo much time and thought into it... i WANT to do it, wells neways it was supposed 2 be due on Wednesday and i was thinking, maybe on Monday night after drama i could work on it, also mum said to take the day off on Tuesday to finish it./... now miss tells me it is DUE on Tuesday.. I want to do it, hella i feel like crying coz i love english and my teacher seemed really angry but worse, disappointed.... i mean i can handle anger, but not disappointment.       I am scared i will ruin our group piece for drama! I dont think i am up for it and i talk too fast and have a lisp and i dont want people to know that! I mean its really bad and i hate it. i dont even read aloud in public anymore it is that bad. its awful, just like the rest of me. i wish i didnt have to do this at all. I am so stressed out about it. We saw the de la ones tonight and they are really good, i dont know how ours will compare.     Worse of all...i finally had an opportunity i had been waiting for, and i botched it... twice today. TWICE, and i botched it. What a loser. The biggest loser in the world.       "remember when i was in the grocery store, now's my time, lost the words, lost the nerve, lost the girl, left the line, i would wish upon a star but that star it doesn't shine, so read my book with a boring ending, a short story of a lonely guy"    That is my destiny, to be a loser and a loner. I wait for that one moment, i wait and i miss it, gone. Lost the words, lost the nerve. I am so cranky at myself. i wish...     The stars dont shine for me, i am bathed in darkness all my life. Always and forever....eternity  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well i have been thinking about this for a long time, parts of it are already written and other parts arent. There is a story that has been forming for a while and i have started on it today... its not much, but i might post some parts of it if i think about it... i am studying irish mythology, such as the Fir Bolg - The Bag Men.... its quite fascinating.       I will write when i can.       ~Aine  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I invite you all to visit my mummy's blog (not my real mum....u know what i mean....well i hope ya do neways!)!!!      its   urlLink  www.d3bd3b.blogdrive.com   ! Go for it people! :P!      Aine  
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am trying to study....really I am... i mean I know I should be studying... but... well you know when there are two roads, one that in perfectly straight and you can see there is no adventure on it, no music within its depths and another one that is bright and uneven and just waiting to be discovered. I cannot school my thoughts onto that dull road of studying... i long to set my mind free to let it wander to the furthest point of the earth and beyond. Would you not rather be dancing and twirling with the starlight as your guide or be chained to a desk, weighted down with doom and dread of the forcoming exam? Yes i know i SHOULD discipline my thoughts but they bring me a somewhat brighter image, a place i would rather be than this cold, harsh world. Who am i in the world i travel to? A young girl, with wide blue eyes and a wide smile. Ah, i remember what smiling is... indeed i do... but there just hasnt been any reason to smile lately. I guess a Child of the Shadows may learn to love, but are forbidden to be happy. Happiness... a long lost illusion. I cannot remember a time when i was truly happy. A life of sorrow and tears. A childhood of having to be an adult, my adolescene as a lonely outsider trying to uncover a place in this cold harsh world for a person like me. Perhaps there is no place for me.... Banish me to the shadows. There is no place here...  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I couldnt sleep last night...well not properly, i got myself into a horrible state and i got to a point where i would close my eyes and the creatures of the dark unfolded before my eyes... Believe me it was hard not to freak...    It is said that the images of eyes watching you as you wander through the forest is one of a warning of the evil that is to come. Eyes watching you, eyes of wild beasts, of monsters, following you as you wander. I close my eyes and i see it, two eyes glaring back at me, still in a distance but then they come closer and closer.... this is how it usually ends, i will open my eyes put the radio on and try to think of other things. However last night i reached a new point, one that sends a chill down my back to recall it. My face is still  wet from tears i refuse to wipe away as a definance to something inside my soul telling me to be ashamed of them. I lie in the silence, the darkness consuming me. Still and silent. Then behind my eyelids an image forms...from a black dot it grows into two distant eyes. I watch as they get closer and fear grips me but i will not give in. I flutter my eyes open before closing them to this image. One eye, the right eye, is glaring at me and it is the first time i see it properly and i chills me to the bone. It is wide, without eyelashes, and it glares. The colour of the iris is blood red and the eyeball itself is bloodshot, like some poor murder victim. The pupil dialates and it moves closer to me.    It is at that point i open my eyes wide and turned the radio on, willing for the meaningless melody to sooth me.. I would wake each time the radio would turn itself off, pressing the snooze button again, dozing until it turned itself off. The silent creatures of the night scare me as though i were a child again, only now these images are more grotesque. And like a child i will fight them...   ~ Aine    urlLink www.pain182.blogspot.com   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wrote a letter to my friend and this sorta came out....    "She sits in the dark, a child of the shadows. Light is her enemy and she refuses to submit to the darkness. She sits in a void of life as the world continues outside her door. Hands creep up to be placed over her eyes which overflow with tears. Tears that should be cleansing but only bring more suffering. The child of the shadows, a daughter of pain…"    Its an image i've had for a while... I really dont know right now... i feel like the girl on the cliff, the one with the sorrowful eyes...       My ideas evolved further:    "even this broken, destroyed child of the shadows can learn to love....were only her love returned."    Stuck in this void where i dont know if i am coming or going. A limbo that pulls at my heart. A sorrow, so deep within him, i wonder.... what if i only bring him sorrow... i know he will never learn of my love, i have nothing to offer him. Oh but to warm his heart to mine, to take away his pain, to show him the kind-hearted man he could become if only he would let himself...       Ah, it is true...  you donot choose who the heart yearns for.    ~Aine  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just fucked up 2 of my trials... looks like there is a pattern of fucked up trials for me... I couldnt remember ANYTHING about Islams belief on evil...or the authoritative system... and very VERY little on Sufism! SoOOoOo Stuffed! :( Neways... i have decided to try n have 2 blogs... one with all this whinging and another one with some of my writing samples...i know they are shoddy but... well i want to try neways, I'll never be as good as Juliet Marillier but there is just so many images i get and i wanna write em...  Wells i am off to study for my failure of the next exam.... adios  ~Aine
    
</post>


</Blog>