<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       about 6 people today told me that i look like marlyn monroe. how the hell do i look like her? 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       what is the difference between fur and hair? 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       woot woot. i had soooo much of a better day! so yesterday me jana and rachel were supposed to go shopping. but being the cool person i am, 2 other people called and asked if i wanted to go with them, so i bailed on the other 2, and went with erica. i'm sooo nice. me and erica had a blast. haha. we just drove around got slurpees, and bathing suit shopped. even though i know i dont have the best body in the world, i bought my first 2 piece swimming suit!! i'm so happy. i love it!! it's pink, and white polka dots, and a huge roxy sign on it. muahahaha. so then i had to go home, and then i remembered that sara was leaving me for a week and a half. i raced over to her house, and we hung out for a while then allen and this kid named.... josh... i think that's him, but he came over and we all hung out for a long time. but it was fun. everyone was passing eachother out, on purpose. i got scared. they tried to do it to me, and i was like ummm no?! thanks anyways. but i told them i'm going to do it when i'm high, cause when i'm high, i do anything. but little do they know, i dont smoke anymore. muahahaha. i feel so cool. but i must call someone to hang out with now that i'm awesomly popular, and have so many things to do now that i'm ungrounded. woot woot. i'm excited. i need to go tanning too bad it's not bright out. more to come. dun dun dunnnnnn.  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    a picture of myself from about a year ago, that's so crazy. i remember having to take it for my photography classes on self portraits. weird. &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       god. i fucking hate life right now. seriously. i'm having one of those mental break downs, where everything in my life is just going downhill right now. well.... last night was one interesting night. my family did go to sleep, thank god, and i got out just fine. but about 2 hours into me and alex and muffins night o fun, i got a phone call, i just figured it was someone else calling to see what's up, but it was my mother. i peed my pants. she told me i better get home right now if i wanted to have a good summer. so us 3 raced to my house, basicly going 90 on the connector. i was sooo scared. god, i've snuck out of my house so many times, and the first night that i've snuck out this summer, i got caught. so i get home, and my parents were just standing there, giving me the lecture on how they trusted me, and then i break the trust. i was mostly just upset, so i said alot of things i shouldnt of said, and alot of things happened that didnt need to happen. so i went to bed, and tried calling alex, and he didnt answer his phone. i think he's pissed at me, and i really dont want him to be. but oh well. but by the time i got to bed, it was about 2, so getting up was hard. i felt incredibly sexy at school, for not showering for 2 days, and dead tired, no make-up or anything. but i didnt really care. but when i got home, i talked to sara for about 3 hours, and we just talked about how confusing life is. she and i have been through so much together. i really dont think that i've ever been so close to a girl friend before. she was there for me through so much, and i was there for her through so much. lol, she and i decided that if we arnt married by the time we're 39, we're going to get married, because gay marriage will be available all around. lol. we're such losers. but it was funny. so then i took a nap. because what else do you do when you have nothing at all to do. so then i wrote a letter to ryan. man i miss that kid so much. i basicly started crying when i was writing his letter. i dont think that i've ever had that close of a guy friend. he's basicly the only guy that i trust. it took him 7 years to build it up. i've known that kid for so long. and i miss him incredibly. i wish people didnt use drugs. seriously. i see how fucked up it made me, and how fucked up i am, and i'm still having issues with it, but to take control of all your emotions. it's so confusing. i hate it. i hate it all. i just remeber my first time doing shrooms. god. that i was so fucking scary. but yeah. i just hate anything that has to do with screwing lives up. but arg!!! i'm just rambling on... i know that in a second i'm going to come on here, and either delete it, or write more into this. fuck life. fuck it fucking all.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so yeah. today was interesting. i was super tired to begin with, so school wasnt all that cool. i went and saw kirk (crap) and he didnt talk to me at all. which made me happy. weird huh? but i was kinda pissed that he was all over rachel.... but whatever... what's new. but yeah. so after school, me, jana, and camille were supposed to go on this date thing with sara, but it turned out none of us could go. so i slept. alot. i missed 6 calls on my cell. haha. but then i woke up, and blasted my get up song, taste of ink. so then surprise! jon came over! i was excited, but once again... NO MAKEUP! i dont see how that man sees me with no make-up. but i dont really care. so we talked for a while, and he showed me how to work my blog, which i'm slowly learning how to do, thanks to my mom's mad skills on the computer, i totally got it from her... not. but so he left, and jake and dan called to say they were coming over to pick me up, and we were going to swim in the boise river. so i was confused, and like okay? so we went to jake's mom's house, and hung out there for a while. a.k.a. camel and dan making out, and jake trying to explain those gameboy things to me, but it's funny to play with him, cause he gets so frustrated with me, and ends up throwing the remote and the t.v. and telling me that he's never selling weed to me again, cause i'm perma stoned, and dont need anything else wrong with me. haha. i found it really amusing, and so i laughed for hours on the end. THEN my mom called. no one knows how much i hate that woman right now. but she called screaming at me and demanding she knows where jake lives, so she can pick me up, because we need a 'family night' tonight. i was SO pissed. so i screamed at her, and of course, in the moment of screaming, blake and everyone came over into the room. thanks. i felt cool. i was like yeah check out the hot shit standing right here. so then she found of the way to his house, and so then everyone left. i'm saying everyone. i was stuck there with jake's mom. i felt like such a loser, so i talked to her for about an hour, talking about people i've never heard of in my life, while she's gulping down carmel chocolate kisses. so then my family finally came, and so we went bowling at the sub. and yeah. i saw so many people there, such as, freshman (!!!!!) jake epperson, hott jeff, and...... da da da..... BLACK LIKE DEATH!!!! i was sooooo happy! and the moment that i saw blk, i peed my pants! i called up camel, and was like OH MY GOD!!! she peed her pants too!! she thought it was so funny. i love inside jokes with people! so then, my ex-lova called and was like dude sneak out with me, and so i'm going to. well hopefully it works out, he's picking me up at 12:30, and it's 11:52 right now.... hopefully my family goes to sleep, cause i really wanna sneak out with him, and just..... have fun. haha. no you sick little minds, not that. but off to go gettin hott lookin for the ex! go being single for a month! haha!  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       oh. my. god. hot hot heat seriously always gets me in the best mood ever. i dont know why, but it does. i love it. even though they are a huge pop indie band, they're awesome and i want to see them in show. right freakin now. but i'm excited for tomorrow. i dont really know why. but me and camille are supposed to be 'secret agents' tomorrow at the movies. dont know why. well i do. but i cant say. hahaha. i'm so hyper right now. i have no idea why. but i totally am. but i just got my hair done, and i'm super excited, and i totally want to show it off to everyone that i know. i want kirk to see it, but i dont. but mind you, i'm not obsessed with him. i know i made a mistake with him, but shit happens when you do stupid things. *flinch* but anyways! i want to go camping so bad this summer. i know that i'm going to a.s.a.p. mostly after summer school. i know my family is going camping, and they said that i can invite 3 friends. go the 4 musketeers. haha. it just reminds me of last year when me and bear and camel went camping last year, we took a nap in a raft and fell asleep, and got lost in the middle of the most random lake, and we just got confused and burnt like hell. but in our lake, we came up with the nick names lewis and clark and sacajewa. how original. but this year the vajana is coming with us, and it's going to be awesome. i feel so hyper. i dont know what is wrong with me. but it's freaking rad. but i'm gonna stop now. because i'm just out of it right now like no other. it's pathetic. you are my only girl, but your the only girl..... go hot hot heat.  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the only thing i hate about summer, is that you dont usually know what day it is. that's just my random thought for you. but today was fathers day. i spent the whole day talking to my cousin. he and i shared our lover stories. kinda freeky sense he's a guy, but still...... but finds out, he's done stuff with people that i know, and i've done stuff with one of his best friends. that's so crazy..... more to come.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OH. MY. GOSH. TODAY. THE BEST DAY EVER. seriously. most people would say i'm crazy, but i dont care. it was amazing. so i'm going to start off from when i woke up. took a shower. put on my bathing suit, and clothes, went to summer school. went to school. didnt do a damn thing. went in rachels car. blasted fucking atreyu. fuck yeah. fucking rad. so we picked up kirk, and camille. went and met justin, and keving. went to the boise river. haha! this is where the fun starts! get to blow up the rafts, kirk came up to me, and.... dun dun dun.... held me!! ohhh... amazing. right in front of rachel. pure excitment. i loved it. so then we went floating. okay, we went at about 3:30. we were having a blast, getting a tan, you know the usual, and so then it started to storm. i peed my pants, i saw the lightning and everything. so we all decided (a.k.a. kirk, me, rachel, camille, kevin, justin, jana) that it was time to stop. then it started to hail. big time. if you went out in the hail, well it was just humongous. so we were freaking out. then jana's raft flipped over, and she got the biggest bump on her foot. so she couldnt walk. so we got out, and were sooo far away from our cars. so rachel and kevin found some people to hitch a ride from to get to their cars. so me justin, jana, kirk, and camille were all sitting with our rafts on top of us, oh it was so funny, everyone was pretending that we were in war. it was awesome. i think you just had to be there. so then, we went and stood by a metal shed with a huge metal pole. yeah we are sooo smart. so we sat under the shed for a while. then kirk thought that it would be awesome if i went and explored to see if there was any other place to hide. couldnt find anywhere, seeing as i didnt look. haha. so then we were all talking about how nice it would be to have a pizza, and hot tub, and a warm bed, and warm clothes, and hot chocolate. so then i had a huge kink in my leg, so i decided to run it off, i went running, and saw a double tree hotel, i got sooo excited, and started running to everyone. while in the process of running, i got my shoes stuck in mud, and fell into the mud. yes i am hott shit. dont you forget that. so everyone heard, and started laughing. so then i told them that we HAD to walk to the double tree. so we all walked, which was right across the street. no big deal. we walk in, and the lady at the front desk looks at us, and laughs. so hard. i asked if we could use her phone. so i called rachel, and she didnt answer her phone. so everyone went off to go get towels, and they ran into the manager, and the manager let us into his hot tub!! we were sooo happy!! then we were chillin in there for a while, and then rachel and kevin came, and chilled for a while with us in the hot tub. so rachel's mom called to see if we were alright. we said yes. duh, and she said she ordered us pizza and was going to make us hot chocolate. so we went to rachels, and ate in her bed, drank hot chocolate, with warm clothes. everything we wished for came true. so then kirk and i were secluded from everyone else, i told him everything i felt for him, he did the same, and we decided that it was best if it were done. yessssss. so then he was all over camille. i didnt really care, but it seemed soon. whatever! i dont care! but today was freakin rad!! i sooo want to do it all over again!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       arrrrgggg!!! I FUCKING HATE PEOPLE!!! seriously!! i'm sooo pissed that i'm listning to norma jean. actually i love that band, but still. so at school, i was talking to rachel about something, i dont remember, but she randomly brought up kirk, and was like oh yeah, well kirk said he had a sex dream about me.....i also spent the night at his house. fuck you. seriously. that made me so pissed. i mean seriously, i have no feelings like that for kirk at all! but still i did stuff with him, and i think that i have the right to say that friends shouldnt do stuff with people that your friend has done stuff with. well actually rachel was the one that told that to me. so that's why i didnt do anything with mike. but still! but then on the way home, kirk rode home with us, and rachel thought that it would be really funny to tell kirk that i have an std, which by the way, I DONT HAVE AT ALL. thanks anyways. so kirk said that if i have any at all he's going to kill me. i got sooo pissed off. so i had rachel take me home. i slammed the trunk in frustration, and kirk said 'whoa calm down babe, i'll call you tonight' screw you. seriously. i'm sick of guys. i know i've said that before, but this time was stupid, stupid mistakes that i decide to make, and then i get screwed over and try to feel sorry for myself. but ugh! he pisses me off. massivly, acutally it's not even really him, i dont really have that much frustration twords him as i do on rachel. i have been there for her so many times. so many fucking times. and she hasnt been there for me at all. all she's done is gotten me screwed over with parents, and police. swear to god. she's never been a friend. just a friendly enemy. that's an oxmoron. but seriously. but i want sara to be home. i miss my best friend. i need to talk to her right now. just anyone. so i can just cry. but on the bright side, i'm tanner, cause me and erica went tanning and swimming today, and i'm also excited, because i'm going to the art museum with alex tomorrow, and then he's coming with me to float the river. but i'm off to cry and get my depression food...... garden burger with french fries. i'm pathetic.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so i have a wonderful best friend. she had sex with my ex boyfriend....... 3 days after we broke up. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       woot woot! i'm so excited. so i'm now hooked onto this one thing called myspace.com i've found soooo many of my friends on there. it's so weird. if you go there, you can check out the hot pics of myself. haha. just kidding. but it's so cool! jon just put my picture on his website, and you can see me, and then it goes to my blogger! yeah!! so much is happening! more lata! brush ya shoulders! 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        i havent written anything for the longest time. i found this and found it entertaining. learn more about me..........     first best friend:  &nbsp;Kelsey Fisher     first kiss:  &nbsp;Joe Van Lith     first&nbsp;screen name:  &nbsp;something to the effect of girl. dont remember     first funeral:  &nbsp;my uncles. i was a few weeks old     first pet:  &nbsp;my goldfish i named him duck     first piercing:   earlobes     first true love:  &nbsp;alex taylor     last cigarette:  &nbsp;about a weeks ago     last car ride:  &nbsp;about an hour ago     last&nbsp;kiss:  &nbsp;today     last&nbsp;good cry:  &nbsp;yesterday     last library book checked out:  &nbsp;i go it about 2 weeks ago. great expectaions     last movie seen:  &nbsp;umm probally anchor man     last phone call:  &nbsp;talked with alex     last&nbsp;time showered:  &nbsp;this morning     last shoes worn:   my grandma flip flops!     last&nbsp;cd played:  &nbsp;bleeding through     last item bought:   some volcom jeans at zumiez     last annoyance:  &nbsp;i ran into a door. so now i have stupid written all over me.      last disappointment:  &nbsp;not able to see camille before she left     last shirt worn:  &nbsp;my 'deep plunge neck' shirt from urban outfitters     last website visited:  &nbsp;umm probally the venues website     last word you said:  &nbsp;you. ( i was saying night love you to my mom)     last song you sang:  &nbsp;dont know. probally this love. how stupid is that?     what is in your cd player:  &nbsp;fear before the march of flames, bleeding through, romeo and juliet     what color socks are you wearing:   barefoot!     what color underwear are you wearing:   bright pink     what's under your bed:  &nbsp;another bed. not a bunk bed, but a trundle. tricky.      what time did you wake up today:  &nbsp;5:30 i had summer school     current mood:   tired/excited     current taste:   my left over garden burger     current hair:   brown with blonde chunks and short and chunked out     current clothes:   pink hurley&nbsp;top with&nbsp;pink white and light pink striped pajama pants&nbsp;     current annoyance(s):   not being able to stay in town this weekend     current desktop picture:  &nbsp;sun valley&nbsp;mountains at night     current book(s):  &nbsp;great expectaions by charles dickens     current color of toenails:   pink     current wasting wish:   what?     current hate:  &nbsp;knowing that i might not go to nevada     black or white:   white     boxers or briefs:   boxers     coke or pepsi:  &nbsp;pepsi     salt or pepper:  &nbsp;i dont know. depends on the food. but probally salt     sweet or sour:   sweet     vanilla or chocolate:   mix     short or long:  &nbsp;what are we talking about here?     cheap or expensive:  &nbsp;again, what are we talking about?     firm or soft:  &nbsp;who made up these last few questions?!     hot or cold:   warm.     favorite...color is:   green     song is:   i'm obsessed sadly with the killers somebody told me. i hope cade doesnt read this.     scent is:   on guys, it's fierce, and my scent that i always wear is clinique happy heart. woot woot     alcoholic beverage is:  &nbsp;well when i drank it was whiskey and dr. pepper     food is:  &nbsp;anything vietnamese or spicy     5 things you're are wearing: &nbsp;  pajama pants, shirt, panties, undershirt, and ummm, a hairclip?     5 things you did so far today:  &nbsp;went to school, drove around, went to subway, went out to dinner, sang to people for the hell of it     5 things you can hear right now:  &nbsp;the t.v., music, me chewing my gum, my mom packing, and my dad walking upstairs     5 things you do when youre bored:  &nbsp;listen to music, go on computer, watch t.v., sleep, attempt to skateboard     5 things that never fail to cheer you up:  &nbsp;talking to my mom, watching charlie, listning to music, hanging out with my friends on our 'adventures', and, talking     5 things you can't live without:  &nbsp;music, my family, my friends, the blanket camille made me, and.......... wendys! (haha jana!)   
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this is so sad. i'm going to fill this out for you all to read, and enjoy. *Full name: Justine Jo Searle * Eyes: dark brown, with a tail * Hair: right now, light brown * Height: 5'1 or 5'2 cant remember * Shoe Size: depends on the shoes, usually from the range of 7 to8 * Have tattoos?: kind of * Have piercings?: yep * Have a BF GF?: dunno * Own a webcam?: no *HAVE YOU EVER... * Flown on a plane: no * Ever been so drunk you blacked out: yes * Missed school because it was raining: Nope, but i have because of snow * Told a guy/girl that you liked them?: Yeah * Put a body part on fire for amusement: Yep * Had a crush on a friends girlfriend/boyfriend: Maybe once? * Been hurt emotionally: who hasnt? * Had an imaginary friend: Yep * Ever thought an animated character was hot?: yes, aladin, or however it goes. the man with  the magic carpet * Cut your hair: done it a couple of times, and i still will * Had crush on a teacher?: not a crush, just thought he was really cute FAVORITE * Fav Color: green * Day/Night: miday * Summer/Winter: Summer * Cartoon Character: didnt really get into the cartoon character thing * Fave Food: anything spicy, or vietnamese * Fave Advertisement: those ones at 2 in the morning where they sell knives, or the weiner enlargment. i'm sorry. i feel bad for the guys that have to use it. * Fave Drink: iced tea * Breakfast Food: life * Ice Cream: cookies and cream * Fave sport: soccer WHAT ARE YOU: * Wearing: a blue polo, and my studded belt, and dark blue jeans * Eating: brown rice * Drinking: water * Thinkin bout: when alex is coming over IN THE LAST 24 HRS... * Cried: nope * Worn jeans: yes * Met someone: yes * Done laundry: No * Drove a car: Yes * Talked on the phone: Yes * Kissed someone: Yes * Said "I love you": NO * Picked a wedgie?: yup DO YOU BELIEVE IN... * Yourself: when i think i look good. i'm ugly. * Your friends: depends * Santa Claus: nope * Tooth Fairy: nope, found my mom putting money under my pillow * Angels: no * Ghosts: No * UFO's: No * God: no * Love at first sight?: sometimes FRIENDS AND LIFE... * Do you ever wish you had another name? No * Do you like anyone?: Yes * Which one of your friends acts the most like you?: sara * Who have you known the longest of your friends: alot of them * Who's the loudest: jana * Are you close to any family members?: My mom * Who's the weirdest?: all of us are. i dont think none of us want to be classified as the weirdest * Who do you hang out with the most?: sara * Who did you last speak on the phone with?: alex * Who is the last person you saw today: camille Let's walk on the: clouds Let's run through: the sand Let's look at the: stars What a nice: guy Where did all the: cowboys gone...... How can I: think Why can't you: just be quiet Tell me: everything Love me: with all you have WHICH IS BETTER... * Coke or Pepsi: pepsi * Girls or Guys: depends * Scruff or Clean shaved: clean shaved * Blondes or Brunettes: meh * Tall or Short: everything is tall to me * Pants or Shorts: Pants WITH THE OPPOSITE SEX... * What do you notice first: eyes, or smile * Last person you slow danced with: oh that was forever ago, probally jon * Worst Question To Ask: do you like me? it's okay if you dont........ *Last person you kissed: alex *Last time someone said they loved you: last night, said it to my mommy.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay. i hate my little sister. she's got this whole jessica simpson's little sister obsession going on, and contantly playing that pieces of me song. it bugs the hell out of me! oh well. but summer is such a drag. i'm wanting to go to nevada soooooo bad. i know. nevada? why the hell there? i really dont know, but it's the only place that i can stay for free. but i dont know, i'm getting so sick of boise, it's so boring here, i've lived here for my whole life practically, and it's just a drag anymore, and there is SO much drama. too much actually. i'm just wanting to start over, i want new people in my life, people that dont know about my past, and that they'll accept me for me, not the old justine.    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well i dont really do this whole blogger thing. haha. well i have fun with it. i'm just rambling. well i went camping with my family and sara this weekend the funnest thing ever. so she and i decided that we are going to get all of our friends and just go camping. it was a blast. i so want to do it again. i've now become obsessed with myspace.com it's pretty cool. ya'll should check it out and see my hot self on there. but i'm gonna write more later.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       omg i have a fight going on in my comment box.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i hate life. everything about it. and i'm fat. and ugly. very ugly.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       alllright. now that i've had my i feel sorry for justine time. i feel better now. i just hate the things that people say behind people's backs, and think that they can get away with it. i understand that i have to work in that too, but i dont think that i've ever said things like that before. oh well. but it's awesome! now i feel better about myself, dont know why, but me and sara went to go take pictures, and yeah, it was fun, it was like things havnt ever changed, we just screwed around and everything, just like old times. i developed them, and it was awesome, we got some of everyone else, and yeah. lol. but yeah, i'll share em..... once i can find out how to. but JOE VAN LISP is in town. i'm soooo happy. more points cause i'm single now. go on and off again boyfriend!  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>