<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I still have two weeks of the Associates in Internal Medicine, LTD left but I can feel&nbsp;my nerves tingling. Even Though it will be a full time job I really have no choice other than to view it as an endless learning experience. Which is is how I should really view everything. I will spend this time in anticipation and preparedness.  &nbsp;  Since this is the first open-ended full time job based entirely on theatre, I see the opportunities for my future knocking. Loud. Slowly, but surely,&nbsp; I will begin the steps that have seen throughout my life. This journey will only end at my destiny which has continued to become clearer and clearer since the age of&nbsp;8. &nbsp;It's truly wonderful to be working side by side with GOD all the way; Even if he only shows up every once in a while. But I have no doubt as to where I'll end up, my only confusion is&nbsp; how  I'll &nbsp;end up there. I guess that's the fun of the journey. I guess.  &nbsp;  The purpose of this blog will be 3-fold.  &nbsp;  First: This will be a way to keep in contact with all my friends and family about information that pertains to my professional life.(Audio Mote will be the personal blog)  &nbsp;  Second: This will be a way for me keep track&nbsp;of my learning curve. Excellent records should help expand and retain my knowledge as much as the application of that knowledge. And I hope to expand my exponentially for the rest of my life   Third: This will be an EXCELLENT way for me bolster my memory until I die. I've never been successful at keeping journals,&nbsp;yet I will make a valiant attempt to make this one stick. Constant recalls, admirations,&nbsp;regrets, and forlornings of all my memories will exercise and strengthen every one of them until the end of my days. This shall truly be wonderful tool.  &nbsp;  Please feel free to post as many comments as you wish. I need them.  Try not&nbsp;to get bored with my blogs. They don't bore me.  Respect my opinion no matter how much it is conflicts with yours. This can be very hard.  And as always, logic will prevail over the illogical. This blog and my life depend on it.  &nbsp;  read on and enjoy  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  -Dustin Mote  Chicago,IL   
    
</post>


</Blog>