<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm back in Seattle to visit my family and unwind a bit, even if I wasn't very wound up to begin with.  It's nice to get back and just be with my family.  Growing up in the military, family was the only real constant I had.  Of course, back then I couldn't wait to get away and make it on my own and now I know how much I miss them when they're not there.  It's finding that balance that's tricky.  Not too much on the agenda.  Visit my mother's church.  Play catch with my dad.  Check out the new science fiction museum they opened in Seattle Center.  Try to absorb as much green and rain as I can before I head back to San Jose.  People love to complain about the weather here.  Even people that have never been here.  But without the rain, it wouldn't be as beautiful as it is.  You take the good, you take the bad, you take them both and there you have....  But that's the problem:  people don't like to take the bad with the good.  It's gotta be perfect.  And they search and search.  I know something that's perfect.  Wanna hear about it?
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let me rant for a bit.  Why can't people say hi to other people, like on the street, when they walk by one another?  Seriously, is it that hard just to say hey, make eye contact, wave?  Hey, I got an idea.  America's the world's fattest nation, right?  Smile more.  Burn some calories.  Wave.  Do it enough and you'll burn off that #1 supersized.  Eh, maybe it's just me.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      While I've never been a real soccer fan, the desire to run around incoherently has not yet been dulled by the ravages of time.  So, every Friday at lunch, I play soccer with a conglomeration of guys from different companies, for the sake of exercise and a chance to reclaim lost youth/glory, ect.  One thing I noticed though.  If you watch little kids play soccer, it's a big mass of kids, chasing the ball wildly and with much gusto, unabashed joy and enthusiasm on their faces and in their voices.  As we get older, there's a whole lot less chasing.  The game becomes more "cerebral."  That's precisely the problem.  We'd all have a lot more fun if there was less thinking and more just running around wildly, enjoying the day and the fellowship for what it is.  Let's all be kids again, if only for an hour, once a week.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night I was reading a devotional regarding today's definition of masculinity.  As a new christian, learning what God intended men to become has been a journey of enlightenment and confusion.  As an added bonus, I have 25+ years of watching other role models to contend with.  For myself, the best measure of my maturity as a man had been my father.  He's a stern man, quick to criticize and slow to praise, but underneath all that, you can see the deep caring and love he has for his family.  He's also always been the go-to guy; so much so that when he comes to me for help now, it's still a bit unnerving.  The fact there are things even my father cannot deal with is a testament to his ability to shield us from his weaknesses and give us comfort through his strength.  But it's a rather lonely proposition and as I've become more his peer, I see the toll it's taken on him and gladly shoulder some of the burden he has placed squarely on his shoulders.  Still, there are questions about what makes a man's man.  I don't want to repeat the mistakes of my father.  So where do I turn?  Media seems to take up the flag and run with it.  I went through a Fight Club phase (I'm sure lots of guys did) where I was all about being a guy.  Aggressive, confident, live for the moment, rage against what society expected out of us.  A very selfish and ultimately unfulfilled path.  As I searched for my identity, I found myself going to extremes, thinking the answer lay in unconventional thinking.  My last serious relationship taught me more about myself than I ever realized.  I found it was the focus on the self which was ultimately unsatisfying, though I didn't realize it at the time.  But as I dated Ramona, I found myself changing and growing.  I began to live my life for someone other than myself.  Natural urges to love and protect, being needed and depended upon came forth and a transformation began.  Unfortunately, even this was not enough.  I was seeking something more, something I wasn't able to find here.  I needed Jesus.  He's the ultimate role model for men.  His strength is immeasurable.  A leader, a teacher, a friend, a servant.  He cast off his divine self and became a man to show us how to be men.  It's reassuring that guys struggled with what I went through 2000 years ago and will continue to struggle into the future and that Jesus came to answer all those questions for us.  And while I fail time and again to attain maturity in his image, I know what I'm striving for.  But even with the goal in mind, I'm continually baffled by the path to this goal.  No one ever said being Christian was easy.  If it was, there'd be more people flocking to His banner.  I urge you to learn about Jesus.  He's a remarkable man who saved my life.  I owe him everything.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had no idea what to make of this game when I purchased it at fry's 2 wks ago.  I was down there to buy Sacred, a Diablo clone with an absolutely massive world, when I came across BG&E for $19.99 and bought it on impulse.  It had a picture of the protagonist on the cover.  She had green lipstick on, with green eyes and a green outfit.  Really, that's all I needed.  Well, as it turned out, Sacred got boring, so I popped in BG&E into my Xbox and was hooked.  The story's based around government conspiracies and who you can trust and the quest for truth.  That's kinda where the name comes out, truth being beyond good and evil.  Except in the game, there's definitely good and evil and the truth: yeah, it's on the good side.  You control the aptly named Jade a photographer/orphanage owner on the war torn planet of Hillys, under attack by the alien race called the Dom'z and protected by an elite force of soldiers called the Alpha team.  You start out right at the beginning of a raid.  Your shields fail since you failed to pay your electric bill.  The aliens invade and you have to defend your lighthouse from the alien menace.  After all that's said and done, the Alpha team arrives and cleans up the mess.  The story starts from  this introduction.  Combat is pretty fluid.  The animations of Jade during combat are something to behold.  Her weapon of choice is her Dai-Jo, pretty much a staff, which she can wield with devastating effectiveness.  Combos go from simple 3 hit combos to near infinite as she whirls and twirls through multiple enemies.  Yes, you will be surrounded a lot, but it's not such a big deal.  Jade also has a special move, which is activated by holding the attack button to charge up the attack.  To be honest, I never found it very useful.  On this quest to seek out the truth, you will come across many many items to assist you.  Collecting Pearls will allow you to upgrade your hovercraft/ship.  You will gain items to increase your health bar and your crafts energy.  Certain items heal your life or repair your ship.  The most important item is your camera.  Using the camera, you can take photos of the conspiracies and publish them in an underground magazine, exposing the truth for all to see.  You are also contracted to take pictures of all the animals on the planet.  Getting a properly framed photo of a new species will net you some cash and other goodies, like a zoom lens or some pearls.  Some creatures are elusive and difficult to snap, which adds a level of thinking to the game.  There are also hovercraft races for you to enter and gain cash and pearls as well as a number of mini games for the same purpose.  This game does a lot of things, racing, fighting, puzzle solving, flying and while it doesn't do any of them spectacularly, it does them all proficiently and when you add a compelling story to solid, tightly controlled gameplay, you have a fun, enjoyable game.  And really, what more can you ask for in a game?  It's pretty short, 8 -10 hours so I would recommend a rental unless you really got $20 burning a hole in your pocket.  If that's the case, I'll sell you mine.  Graphics - tight Sound - heard worse Gameplay - easy to learn, too short Controls - tight Story - compelling Fun - yes  Overall - B+, you won't beat yourself for buying it
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I was younger, my appetite for food was near legendary.  Strangers, somehow connected to me in some bizarre parody of that Kevin Bacon game, knew about my innate ability to eat anything and everything set before me.  Lucky for me, I also enjoyed running around for no particular reason, thus saving me from the horrible fate reserved for  urlLink Jerry O'Connell , forever known as the fat kid from  urlLink Stand By Me .  All kidding aside, I've developed a fondness for trying my hand at cooking those things I enjoyed eating the most while adding my own flavor to the recipes to enhance the flavors I choose above others.  That usually means spicy.  Being half  urlLink Korean , I was introduced to the power of red peppers at an early age and the constant bombardment on my tongue has caused an escalation of the spice quotient on the food, not unlike the arms race during the cold war.  Fortunately, my inability to fully enjoy mildly spicy food won't destroy the world.  Tonight, I cooked up a big ol' batch of  urlLink Jambalaya .  I like to cook the brown variety since I don't particularly like the tomato taste.  But instead of following the traditional recipe, I give it a little flavor from far east.  Add in some enoki mushrooms for the texture, some soy sauce instead of salt, Thai chili peppers to crank up the spicy a bit.  And I added some okra to give a little different texture to the whole thing.  Cranked it out and brought it to my friend's for some Settlers of Catan and Jambalaya.  If they ate it, they liked it.  I might have to save this one and use it at a bigger event.  One day, I hope to have a big ol' collection of remixed recipes and publish a  urlLink cookbook .  And very painful is sneezing while peeing.  Just hold the sneeze if you can.  You'll thank me later.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just had an interesting conversation with an old college friend of mine.  By conversation, I mean email traffic with him complaining to me and me responding with a sarcastic/witty remark.  I'm posting so I don't have to email everyone, but I forget that not everyone browses the web everyday.  I suppose if I can keep the content up on a semi regular basis, the problem will be solved.  But then that wouldn't be very lazy, now would it.  What am I reading?   urlLink Penny Arcade    Current music - The sound of the guy in the next office banging a nail into the wall we share with a large hammer.  And he's not very good because I hear the hammer hit the wall too often for me to conclude he has any kind of proficiency with it.  Coming up next, my review of Beyond Good & Evil 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feels good to be free for the day.  What I'm reading -  urlLink James 1:26  "If anyone considers himself religious and yet does not keep a tight rein on his tongue, he deceives himself and his religion is worthless." .... Don't gossip!  Follow it up with some  urlLink Ephesians 4:29  "Do not let any unwholesome talk come out of your mouths, but only what is helpful for building others up according to their needs, that it may benefit those who listen."  A reminder to myself to watch what I post.  What I'm listening to - Soundtrack:  urlLink Cowboy Bebop   Stuff I'm digging - Pretty Chinese girls, Japanese language studies,  urlLink Beyond Good & Evil , Settlers of Catan, God's Word  Stuff I'm dogging - Pretty Chinese girls, 14 hours  urlLink work  days, 6AM test time, my car's lack of cleanness and 22-2 softball games.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I gravitate to games like a hummingbird to flowers.  The pull is irresistible, but only for a short time before moving onto the next.  Every once in a while, I find one with a nectar of competition so compelling, I can't help but be intoxicated by and irrevocably addicted to it, even after the first session.  Thus was my introduction to  urlLink Settlers of Catan .  It's been around since 1995 and yesterday, it informed me I have wasted the last 10 years of my life NOT playing it.  Like many successful games, it's easy to learn and difficult to master and to be honest, I haven't received a beatdown of the magnitude I received yesterday since the infamous Jeff & bicycle vs parked truck 2 on 1 tag team match.  I have to admit though, against the truck, we were caught off guard.  But I thought I went in with eyes wide open to Settlers, but my good friend  urlLink Brabus  unmercifully educated me on the finer points of victory.  My competitive ire has been stoked.  Time to get up, dust myself off and show my mettle.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was online reading some blog entries of an old friend of mine.  The circumstances as to why I was doing this are a post within themselves, but regardless of the motives, I couldn't help but think I'm way behind the power curve here.  Isn't it funny how everyone else's life is a little bit more interesting than yours?  Maybe it's not funny and it's really not true, but I can't help but feel this guy has just done more with the time God's given him on this earth.  But do we measure our impact by the grand gestures and wonderful stories we take back from places of mystery and adventure?  Why do I feel inadequate in the face of other people's grand adventures?  Envy?  Competition? (probably)  But in reality, all we have to do is look at the life we lead with unbiased eyes and see the wonderful stories we create everyday and the impact our lives have on the lives of the people around us.  Looking at another's treasures makes us blind to how rich we really are.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been inspired.  Though my thoughts hold no interest to anyone but myself, the exhibitionist within compels me to write out my musing for everyone to see.  I'll give him this one, if only to control the other urges.  More to come, not that you're reading.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This world has a funny way of working.  I believe in the inertia of everyday life.  We do what we do and continue to do us unless acted upon by an outside force.  Sometimes, life comes at us with an animal ferocity we are just not ready to handle.  One of the kids from the youth group I help lead was in a terrible mountain biking accident.  He's currently unconscious and has not been responsive since the accident.  He's suffered a terrible blow to the head and a tumble down a steep slope and is currently at the ICU in a local hospital.  Now, I had this idea of what I was going to do today.  Go to work.  Maybe get a workout in.  Pay my rent and bills.  And then I hear this and it's like everything else got the volume turned down.  This is important.  This is tragedy.  This is where my efforts and focus should be.  And it's so terrible that this had to happen to break me out of this self absorbed rut I find myself in.  To say this is a tragedy would be to make light of the situation.  He's a tremendous kid.  A skilled cellist, he's got phenomenal musical talent.  He's got such a zest for life, new experiences and a loving, outgoing personality.  He cares about everyone he meets.  And his love for God is second to none.  For his light to be extinguished from this world would be to rob everyone of a little joy, a little peace, a little love.  I can't understand or find the meaning to why this has happened.  But I take heart in knowing our God is a loving, wise, benevolent God.  No evil can come from him and I know some part of this is according to His design.  I am encouraged by the outpouring of love from friends and family and strangers, all brought together by this event.  The waiting in the lobby for news, prayer and conversation in the long whiles, encouragement and love and support for the family.  This is bringing all these people closer than before.  And while I wish this had never come to pass, his accident is not without its galvanizing qualities.  I pray and encourage you all to pray for him.  Pray for healing.  Pray for a miracle.  Pray for a quick solution, either recovery or passing.  Let not his spirit linger while waiting for his body to perish.  I don't know what a prolonged coma would bring about, but the suffering would be near unbearable.  I pray for his family to remain faithful and put their trust in God.  The doctors are doing the best they can.  Let His mighty hand touch his faithful servant and bring peace.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When things seem most hopeless, that's the time when we have to pull closest to Him.  I spoke with God last night and laid at his feet that which was causing me so much turmoil and pain.  And then today, He gave me an answer.  Not that answer I wanted, but the means to continue on the path in faith.  While this whole experience was a mixture of pleasure and pain, I'm glad overall I learned this lesson now.  I needed to learn this first hand so I wouldn't be "what if"  The glamourous life is best lived by glamourous people.  Make mine simple please, lest my pride get the best of me.  Current Mood: Relived and Depressed 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate the stock market.  Shoulda woulda coulda.  Current Status:  Tired  Things I'm digging: Niniane, campaign writing, softball, gmail, my faith  Things I'm dogging: faith crisis, 13 hour work days, getting outdrawn on the river, self denial 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ever notice how everyone's always looking forward to stuff?  Sometimes, so much so that they are unable to enjoy that which is right in front of them.  I look forward to the fun stuff on the weekends.  Looking forward to other things puts a comparison on the things happening right now, right in front of you.  And usually, it's going make what you're doing look really bad.  And it's sad really.  I'm coming to the realization it saps the joy out of the everyday things we do and generally lowers overall happiness.  So, given the above argument, as a christian, I'm pretty much doomed to suffer during my time on earth.  I'm looking forward to a better tomorrow, when Jesus comes to make the world right and I can live eternally with him in a new heaven and earth.  So really, this life, this place, I should feel nothing for since it's really just chaff destined for the fire.  I find happiness comes from embracing what you have and not pining for something else, something more.  And while I'm here, I'm always going to be wanting something more.  How utterly depressing.  Thus, I've resolved to enjoy myself a bit more.  We can enjoy this world without being part of it.  Like a tourist.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I saw King Arthur last night.  It was very Bruckheimer film, full of dramatic action, extreme closeups during pivotal moments and a very epic feel.  Suffice to say, these aren't the Knights of the Round Table we hear about in the legends.  Based on some historical figures during the time of the Roman withdrawal of Britain, these knights are rude, crass and generally very unchivalrous.  Even Galahad, called Galahad the Pure in the legends, was a frightened, selfish little man.  Seeing the knights in this new interpretation was a bit unsettling, but the banter and on screen camaraderie seemed very genuine and was pleasantly surprising.  Seeing Arthur as the bastion of Christianity in that pagan world was intriguing.  It's interesting to me how they portray Christians in the media.  He's very noble and self sacrificing and very devout.  However, all of his knights are non Christians and in the end he succumbs to temptation.  Very tragic and while there is resolution regarding the worldly conflict, there is none regarding the spiritual one, thus leading me to believe he's fallen.  And that saddens me greatly.  There are some shots at the perversion of religion by man, relating to the rise of the power of the church in Rome.  While it helps to cement the prevalent thought of churches as organizations which seek to control and manipulate through false divinity, I know it's historically accurate that these things happen.  At least the movie goes on to provide hope for a better tomorrow.  And one more thing.  If you're cavalry, don't you have sabers or something?  Why the longsword?  Straight edged swords get caught in the target and can be ripped from the grasp of the rider.  A curved sword slices through and releases much better.  You'd think the knights would have figured that out in 15 years of fighting on horseback.  Blah.  I liked it.  Kiera Knightly is hot.  There's action and sacrifice and nobility and courage.  It's uplifting.  And I don't have to see partial male nudity like they had rampant in Troy.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm twisted.  Conflicted.  There's a battle going on in my head right now between desire and duty.  I know what I am *supposed* to be doing, but right now, the reasons for why I should be following this course seem to be on very thin ice and I see the other side of me running around, jumping and stomping with all his might.   But for now, the ice holds.  Being a Christian is a lifelong struggle against oneself.  This is not to say that every action is a trial, but more like there isn't a time where you won't be tempted by the fruits of this world and the struggle against what you desire right now vs desiring something lasting.  I admit I am weak.  I also know what my weakness is.  And I also know even with the knowledge of this weakness, I still tempt myself with it.  Like a child playing with fire; I know it's really hot and it'll burn me, but it's so pretty and warm and inviting.  I have to believe in the promises for a new earth and heavens and lasting reward.  Without it, I'm denying myself for nothing.  And that's not making me very happy right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I usually play soccer on Fridays with a great group of guys from around the area.  Nothing too competitive since noone really wants to get hurt.  But sometimes, things happen, right?  We play with some small goals and the goalies are not allowed to use their hands.  And we rotate out whenever someone needs a breather.  Well, I just got done scoring a goal and with that sprint, I needed a little break, so I switched to goal.  The next part gets a little hazy.  Their player split the defense, came up the middle and shot, I blocked, there was a rebound and then I was lying on the ground with intense groin pain.  I'm wearing a cup next week.  On the bright side, I get to mark people tomorrow at a paintball course in Santa Clara.  I wish I could bust out my gun, but I just know that would get me in trouble.  Plus, I need an adapter to get it working again.  I should also replace some springs and oil it up and that's just going to take more time than I want to spend on it right now.  One of the problem with having too many hobbies is not having enough time to devote to any one of them.  Maybe I should cut back some.  Current Mood: shock and pain
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         I believe in the kingdom come    Then all the colors will bleed into one    Bleed into one    Well yes I'm still running     You broke the bonds and you    Loosed the chains    Carried the cross    Of my shame    Of my shame    You know I believed it           There's knowledge and faith, right? Are they mutually exclusive? I suppose you could have faith in your knowledge. What is faith? It's very abstract, hard to pin down. For me, it's the belief in something with which there is no explicit way to be 100% sure of. Because if you're 100% sure, it's a fact. You can't have faith a boxer will win a fight, *after* he wins. Then it's a fact. Your faith isn't really faith at all. Scientists, in their own way, have a lot of faith. Except they are called theories. Not Laws, but theories. Like nothing can travel faster than light. Is that true? I dunno, we've never tried. DO we have fine enough instruments to test whether light shined from a stationary object versus light shined from a moving object travel at the same speed? Big Bang. Did it happen? We theorize it did. But we don't *know* for sure. Evolution, my new favorite taboo subject. We came from monkeys. But we don't know that for sure. But we think it's pretty plausible.       What I'm trying to get to here is that faith is very much a part of everyone's life. It doesn't all have to be of the religious variety. And it's comforting. We fold these extrapolations around us in a vain attempt to stoke our egos by thinking we got it all figured out. Complacency. I urge you to keep looking. Don't be fooled. You can believe what you want and it will sustain you, but don't get comfortable in it. Challenge. Consider. Got the song yet?       U2 - I Still Haven't Found What I'm Looking For       Keep looking and you'll find the answer or you'll find you've known the answer all along. But not to look is folly.        
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I finally got my car back today.  Two days with the cavalier were more than enough, thank you very much.  It purred like a kitten and when I finally made it into 4th on the freeway, it just felt right.  Plus I don't feel like I'm in one of those one man suicide submarine torpedoes from back in WWII.  Yay!   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just had a most wonderful conversation.  It was about and hour and a half of just conversation about stuff.  All kinds of stuff: faith, truth, girls, guys, dating, school, papers, responsibility or lack thereof.  It ended when my phone decided it was time to sleep.  It tends to do that.  I feel wonderful right now.  We won our softball game tonight 12-2.  I only got to bat twice, but I went 2-2 with 1 run and 1 RBI.  Not too bad for not getting it out of the infield.  Glad I can still run like a gazelle.  Wonder how long that'll last.  I feel energized today.  I need to take this positivity and do something with it.  Be productive.  Ask questions.  Paint a self portrait.  Read something.  Do situps.  I haven't felt this good since last Wednesday night.  G'night all.  Current Mood:  Content 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a good talk today with my boy esheng.  He's always got an interesting perspective which I need to hear.  While I don't always agree with what he says, it's important I hear it since it's a side of myself I rarely listen to nowadays.  So during our conversations today, I was able to puzzle through some meanings and he gave me a wonderful little tidbit.  Stop making it so complicated.  Eh, easy enough to say, harder to actually apply.  But it strikes at the heart of what's bothering me here.  As if I had a disease and the cure came in the form of a pill the size of a half dollar.  Hard to swallow, but once I do, I'll feel a lot better.  Well, one of the unintentional outcomes of our conversations was the thought of juxtaposition.  I spoke of complications during my final conversations with my arthurian sorceress and she mentioned me not being over Ramona.  Interesting why this would be on her mind.  Anyways, I was wondering if working out my relationship with Niniane would then be absolution for myself with Ramona.  Projection?  Was Niniane my second chance with Ramona?  Is this why I'm going crazy over this whole thing?  Hmmm.  But now that I've started to really make peace with my old relationship, does Niniane still have as much to offer?  I dunno.  Rose colored glasses need to be shattered.  I know I feel better today than I felt yesterday, but it could be the jitters of my first softball game with a new team tonight than anything else.  If this is indeed the case, my conscience is at peace with my apology to Ramona.  I don't need a sub and I don't need a crutch.  Esheng says I should just fuck her and be done with it.  I'm inclined to agree with him.  At least I'd sleep better for a night. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had an epiphany last night.  And it led to a catharsis.  A complete rush of pent up feelings I've kept locked away for so long, so far down I had forgotten they were there.  Like sewing weights into your clothing.  I've been wearing them for so long, I've forgotten what it's like without them.  Last night, I finally took the first step towards peace with myself with the lost love of my life.  I apologized to Ramona.  I mean really apologized to her, not just lip service, or a "it's what you're supposed to say in that situation" sorry.  I apologized to her because for the first time, I was able to see what I was doing to her instead of constantly focusing on what was happening to me.  I sent it in an email, but I would have rather sent a hand written letter and I was too terrified to call her.  Especially since I don't know where she is right now and it was late.  Then I had the dream.  I don't remember most of it, but she was there.  I also remembering getting my back broken and having to negociate with the  urlLink big headed green news desk alien from futurama  to get better, but I think that happened after.  In my dream, I said goodbye to her.  And she smiled that smile she smiles with her whole body and waved to me, happy.  If that's the last image I have of her, that's more than enough for me.  And I'm starting to see how I can get those weights out of clothes, one piece at a time.  It's come as quite a shock to me, really.  I have a rather blown up opinion of myself, mostly because I'm ignorant.  Sure, I have a self deprecating humor, but only because I believe in myself so much, I don't believe any of it.  False humility, some would call it.  I thought I was the one in the right here.  I was looking out for what's best.  I was the elder, with more experience, a better grasp on things and thus in charge.  My need to control: frightening.  And there's a trend in that behavior.  I, I, I.  Never her, her, her.  Was I so evolved I couldn't learn from her?  No, but it sure looks like it.  I believe everyone has something to teach one another.  I shouldn't put limits on they can teach me.  I shouldn't be so narrow minded to think I can figure it out.  Someone once told me there's always someone out there smarter than you.  I think you can pretty much take smarter and put anything else there and be confident with what you got while always looking to better yourself in all you do.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Square took my favorite video game of all time and made a  urlLink movie  out of it.  I almost wept with joy the first time I saw this.  Oh, and this is pretty cool too:  Don't read this if you've never played and are considering playing it.  PSOne forever.  urlLink Explanation of themes in Final Fantasy VII 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And I had such high hopes for it.  About halfway through the movie, I just wanted it to end.  I started looking at the audience to see if their reaction was similar to mine, hoping to see my disinterest mirrored on their dimly glowing faces.  It was a mixed bag, but JD was slouching in his chair as if the seat was greased.  Not a good sign.  Big thumbs down.  Not even Kate Beckinsale in the rain could salvage this movie.  Complete with corset.  Sad.  Anyways, I promised to gush some about Niniane and my thoughts on the subject.  I'll just write something really disjointed here and maybe we can decipher what I'm really feeling.  Ever meet someone you're just instantaneously comfortable with, like you've known them for a long time?  I'm a very open person to begin with and I'm not ashamed of speaking frankly about, well, anything really, to anyone.  But with her, it's like being at my own place.  She's genius, but not haughty.  Elitist, but not condescending.  She's very sure of what she thinks, but not beyond listening to other points of view.  She exudes the confidence I see in myself.  She debates well, is able to articulate her thoughts with a well developed vocabulary and above all is honest with her feelings.  And that's just the tip of the iceberg.  However, I have noticed a few inconsistencies.  Especially relating to our last phone conversation, when she told me she didn't think it's a good idea if we see each other.  We both agreed we weren't looking for a relationship and at the time, I wasn't.  I was quite sure a Christian/Non-Christian relationship couldn't work.  Doomed from the start.  But she's incredibly attractive, physically and mentally and I liked being around her, so though this is frowned upon by my christian brethren, I wanted to date for fun and enjoy each other's company.  However, a funny thing happened on the way to the forum.  I found out I really like her.  And I think she likes me.  So why the 60-0 stop on Saturday?  Because we don't have the same views on evolution or a different view point about the reasons for homosexuality?  These are not reasons people who are dating to have fun stop seeing each other.  At least not anyone I've met.  So what's the reason?  Divine interventions, since I asked God to resolve the conflict in my heart.  Only one problem with that.  I'm not happy with it.  I think it's because of my frustrating tendency to admonish others when they are doing something I consider less than optimal.  Ramona had a HUGE issue with this.  When someone's doing something I don't think they should be doing, I suggest they consider a more rational course of action.  This is especially infuriating when it's a buzz killer.  Like when a child runs to her mother, telling her all about the wonderful mural she drew in crayon on the wall for her Mom, only to have the mom yell at her for drawing on the wall, not seeing the beautiful thing the child created.  I'M SO RETARDED!  Why can't I just see fun for fun and beauty for beauty instead of trying to make it all fit into the way I feel it should be.  I'm so self centered and narcissistic to think my way is the right way and that everyone else should follow me.  I'm condescending, haughty, judgmental, and most of all, self righteous.  And I have no right to be now or ever.  I'm so sorry.  I don't have anything left to type.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Anyone out there remember that  urlLink movie ?  It was the one where all the machines came to life and became hostile.  And it had a bunch of people trapped in a diner, terrorized by the big rigs which brought them their livelihood.  I think the ringleader had a big ol'  urlLink Green Goblin  looking head on it.  Why did I think of this?  Well, I took my car to the shoppe today to get the transmission looked at.  The problem was my car wasn't, in fact, going into maximum overdrive.  It gets to third gear and decides it's very happy there, revving about 1000 rpms than normal.  Apparently, there's a real problem with my transmission since they have it ripped open at the repair bay.  Not making my day.  The car is 3 years old.  At least I have the extended warranty.  This alone covers anything I paid for it.  Which I don't recall paying for anyways.  And it covers a rental car.  A Chevy.  Cavalier.  I feel so big in that car.  Just so long as women don't ask me what I drive, I should be alright.  We don't need to re-enact the scene from  urlLink Swingers  again.  (Thanks again, Xander)  I'm off to see Van Helsing at the cheepie screens with some OotT mates tonight and try to stop thinking about ways I can get back together with Niniane.  I'll gush a little bit more about her later on tonight and why I can't seem to get her out of my head, no matter what.  Other than the obvious.  Time to get 30 more minutes of work done.  Current Status:  HAN: (sounding official) Everything is under control. Situation normal.  Digging:  Radiohead, Trance, cleaning up my credit report, Li Hing Plum, movies Dogging:  My car, my rental car, lack of speakers at work 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Excerpt from Fake Plastic Trees by Radiohead:   She looks like the real thing She tastes like the real thing My fake plastic love. But I can't help the feeling I could blow through the ceiling If I just turn and run And It wears me out, it wears me out It wears me out, it wears me out.  And if I could BE who you wanted If I could BE who you wanted, All the time, all the time   Ever get tired of putting on your mask?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Silently speaking Sweet words promising rapture I can't make her leave 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm so unbelievably blessed, it makes me sick when I realize how much I take these blessings for granted. When I turn my powers of observation on myself to understand how I feel about one issue, I find I can't control the scope of what I look at.  Like trying to put out a candle with a fire hose, everything comes under scrutiny.  While struggling with what I felt was the source my faith and how I felt about  urlLink Niniane  and how all this was going in fit together or explode violently like an overfilled water balloon, I realized I had such wonderful friends all around me, ready to lend an ear to hear my musings, ready offer comfort when I was in need, ready to offer advice when I wanted it and ready to offer to introduce me to other girls to take my mind off of this.  A very sage friend of mine told me a girl was the last thing I needed right now and that's advice I can take the bank.  It's what's best for me even though I hate it.  Sounds like icky cough medicine.  Not like  urlLink Dimetapp , the grape one.  I would have drank the whole bottle of that if I could've gotten a hold of it when I was little.  I just wanted to say thanks to TheRealMeal, Yi Yi, TP, Yammer, Brabus, Craig O, Psyarch, and my little brother.  God gave me the answer to my prayers, He knew it wasn't one I was going to like, so He's placed you all around me to help me to understand, struggle and ultimately accept.  That's powerful stuff.  Current Mood: Hungry.  I'm trying to get down to 185 pounds.  My body isn't digging the smaller portions of food. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I watch her as she puzzles, eyes looking off into space while she chews slightly on her lower lip.  I'm curious about what's running through her mind, how she's thinking, analyzing.  Uh oh, she's looking at me now.  She smiles a sheepish smile, looks down and hugs her legs closer to her body, as if she's trying to take up less space in the room.  Or maybe she's just cold.  She responds with "I don't know" and giggles through her hand, trying to deflect my stare and lighten the mood, but I think she knows more than she's letting on.  Girls always know more than they show.  I smile my crooked grin and say "Let's talk about something else then."  There'll be another time.  Another time to ask questions and see her blush again.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My motivation sometimes wanes cause this work hurts my head. I'm tired of thinking of goals and aims and I'd rather do something else, instead.  Lines of code blur together and the meaning is lost in the fold. Distractions float through my mind like a feather or maybe I'm just getting too old.  Sunset pic in my sights, inspiration strikes, my fingers fly. Hold that thought, it costs a lot to get on that plane and say bye-bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, it's a commonly held assertion that no two snowflakes are identical.  Now, I don't know if that's true, but whatever.  It's all snow and when you get lots of them together, you have a snowball or a snowman or a wonderful medium you can use to attain astronomical speeds and then crash spectacularly in a cloud of powder, skis, poles and, in the true spirit of Calvin and Hobbes, mittens, boots, socks and a hat.  I was working out today and thinking to myself not many of my friends have this particular hobby of mine.  They find other means to get what lifting gives me.  And this thought flew into the face of something I've heard people say about Christians and I myself kinda believe:  Christians are all the same.  That it's about conformity and there's no place of individuality.  But as I look at my brothers, I realize that's not entirely true.  What is true is we all have the same belief and we agree on what the most important thing in our lives is.  And we agree we've been called to obey and seek after Jesus in everything we do.  But what's not true is we all do the same thing.  We don't have the exact same interests, thoughts, opinions, likes/dislikes, ect.  God leaves the details up to us.  Of course, he gifts us differently so as we can compliment one another.  As Edena said, if we were all the same, it'd be an insult to God's creativity.  Maybe it's not about changing myself to conform to what I think a Christian should be like.  God made me like this for a reason.  As long as I give praise and glory to God in all things, while showing my love for Him by obeying His words, it's all good. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a weekend this turned out to be.  Paintballing was good fun, though it was hot hot hot at the San Jose Fairgrounds.  I got a little too much sun, but all in all it was a great time.  Joyce and I got into a little one on one shootout.  She ran out of paint. =(  At least I didn't shoot her after she surrender like some punk did towards the end of the game.  That was uncalled for.  The highlight of my weekend was visiting Osh in the hospital in Vallejo Saturday night.  James and I braved the traffic on 80 to get there and were rewarded with a vital and engaging Osh.  He was happy to see us and took us on a tour of the hospital, showed us the gym where he does his rehab, explained to us the rehab process and how he felt it was going.  He also confided in us his feelings of what has happened to him and his frustration with his current situation.  But he always tempers his frustration with optimism and hope.  He's encouraged by his progress and it fuels his desire to keep on going, no matter how hard it might be.  And he's finding solace in God, relying on Him in this time and constantly seeking out His will concerning his situation.  Osh is an absolutely amazing kid and I'm better just for knowing him, but he's really showing me what true faith is all about, something I've been wrestling with.  Oh yeah, and I got to go to LSF Friday and have Bible study.  I find the LSF north people to be a different breed, but not in a bad way.  Just in a different way.  Friday night is really big and there were some visitors there (like myself) so it was almost unwieldy, but everything came together beautifully.  Eileen led worship and Albert led the study.  And the food was great!  And then after Edena was kind enough to hang out and drink cocoa while I downed a Double Cheeseburger at Denny's.  I think I'll skip the burger next time.  Service was very good with a nice bold message.  The CLM meeting seemed like more of a formality than anything else.  At least we all know what's happening and what to pray for (direction, small groups, growth, both spiritual and congregational, teachings and the leaders) and it was cool to get a chance to see Joe and Carol again, freshly back from Hawai'i.  Played Bball and Settlers at Josh's.  Jeremy did not win Settlers, but Josh did, sliding in under the radar while Jerm and I battled it out for most of the game.  And they played Tetris Attack non stop for just too long.  Sigh.  Aw well.  I should get back to work.  I'll write some about that later.  Current mood: proactive and productive. 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a brat.  I grew up on military bases until I went off to college, which is pretty much most of my life at this point.  And I can't say I didn't have a good time, but I know I never made the most of my opportunities.  I was fortunate enough to live in Japan for a number of years, but I never really understood Japanese culture the way I should have and desire to now.  I want to go and live in Japan.  Why?  Hard to say.  There's something very appealing about the people and the culture.  I don't have to live in the big cities.  I would be perfectly happy in the countryside, though I don't know what they'd make of me.  We used to go running for cross country practice up in the mountains in Ome.  It was nice, peaceful, quiet and friendly.  Even for us loutish American high school students.  The idea of honor and the behavior inspired by this resonates with my very core.  It just makes sense.  Now, how it rates in the pantheon of importance is a different animal, but I like the straightforwardness of it.  Sure, there are subtle changes and intricate relationships which are not apparent, but if you understand, you know where you stand, what's to be expected and basically never at a loss.  It's not necessarily honesty, but it's comforting.  And the deference to polite behavior is remarkable.  I dislike rudeness.  No matter the source of politeness, it's refreshing to be around.  I'm going to go there.  When?  Soon.  Next year maybe?  Why not this year?  I don't have a good answer to that question.  What are the ties that keep me here?  I'm not getting any younger.  I'm worried how I will get by out there.  I want to build for the future.  Maybe this is a step in that direction.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Niniane ----  urlLink Special   esheng -----  urlLink Everybody Wants to Rule the World   Big Sticks --  urlLink We are the Champions   Edena ------  urlLink Angel   Me ---------  urlLink Creep 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      She sits patiently, her face set aglow by the laptop screen; is it something more? She smiles, she pouts, her countenance bare, But deep underneath, there's something else there.  Her heart's aflutter, but will not be caged. Don't try to control, her ire engaged. Can't make her fit, like a card in your 'dex Cause everyone knows, she's very complex.  She's a princess at heart, commands respect. Treat her as such, else relationship wrecked. Listen to her thoughts, let her find her way Patience yields rewards, that's all that I'll say.  Dedicated to our princess
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've always wondered what it'd be like to be an actor.  Can you lose yourself with the myriad roles you play until you don't know who you really are?  Are you just a conglomeration of different aspects of all the characters you portray?  I'm guessing good actors are able to be people counter to who they really are, since that in essence is acting right?  But it's gotta stick with you, change you, mold you.  I think many of us are social chameleons.  We take on the aspects of the people and environment around us.  Why?  Because we want to fit in.  But at the same time, if we're always doing that, are we in danger of losing our own identity?  Some would say having a strong sense of yourself, knowing who you are can prevent such erosion.  Is it the rock upon which our consciousness rests?  Our true nature, as it were?  Are we to be mirrors then, shutting out the light of experience on ourselves?  No but I believe we can choose what we let in.  And so we surround ourselves with people like us or people we want to be like.  But then what?  Other people change.  Environments and circumstances change.  How can we hold true to our nature if it can be shaped and molded by the experiences and people around us and those things are then changing as well?  Maybe if we stop responding to the pressures of the mercurial world we live in and respond to that which is absolute, stable, forever.  Want to know what it means to know yourself?  Ask Jesus. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So my last post was a little off.  I've changed it up a bit.  Flip mode.  Last Friday night was Niniane's housewarming party.  So I was a little worried about seeing Niniane again.  Was wondering where I was with all that and questioning the reason I was going to the party.  I did get to meet all kinds of people and if I was the first christian they met, I think God and I made a good impression with my behavior there.  Even had a chance to discuss morality with Erin, who works at Google (Go UW Huskies!).  But inside, turmoil.  No doubt.  Why?  Well, let's dive into that, shall we.  It's hard to clearly see where I stand with Niniane.  She's an amazing person and quite fun to be around.  However, there's the very real and palpable sexual tension between us.  I think she still likes me.  My friends, from observing our interactions, think she still likes me.  She confided in me, depended on me, gravitated towards me.  Now, what am I going to do about it?  Good question.  Very good question.  And of course I go make this even more complicated.  But that's a post for another time and place.  Current mood: Cranky
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Make new friends but keep the old, right?  I've recently gotten an email from an old high school classmate of mine from when I lived in Japan.  I hesitate to say friend since we weren't exactly what I would call good friends back then, but definitely someone I would call an acquaintance.  And it wasn't because we didn't like one another, we just ran in different circles and different interests, blah blah blah, though I may have been interested *in* her at some point.  I think I remember her being very pretty.  But then, what?  It was high school.  I'm male.  Period.  Moving on, this email has been thought provoking.  This I know because I've been thinking recently, and these thoughts stem from that email.  Thoughts like what are my other old friends up to and why do we keep in touch with our pasts, even as we scatter to the four winds?  Curiosity?  I think that has a lot to do with it.  But if there's one thing I know, it's that it's hard to maintain friendships over distance and reconnecting with old friends spans 4 dimensions.  I'm barely keeping my head above water with the relationships I do have.  Growing up, moving around, it's easy to take friendships for granted.  You make friends, move, make new friends, move, lather, rinse, repeat.  Never permanently grafting into my tapestry.  I wonder if I still do the same things?  Are my friends now throw away friends?  Could I just pick up and move like I used to?  I've no fear of meeting new people.  In fact, I love doing that.  But are the relationships I've crafted here anymore concrete than they were when I knew I would be leaving them in 3-5 years?  Explains why I'm not married, yeah? =)  Is it better to have a few really good friends your whole life or a bunch of contacts scattered across the world?  Can you have both?
     

    
</post>


</Blog>