<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont no y i put that as the title i just couldnt think of anything. if any of my mates r reading this plz e-mail me as my in box has been empty for yonks. im soo tierd at the moment i got no sleep last nite as i was whatching rush hour 2. gotta go bye. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Help where is every1. i fell lost and bored and hugry and tierd. plz save me, im dieing here. well im not but hey. im allways hungry. i never get any fatter if i eat lots tho. im not even fat at the moment, im quite sporty 2. i sayi never get hungry as i hav gremlins in me that eat all my food so i never get enough nutrition gotta go bye
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi Hi Hi Hi Hi Hi Hi HI HI HI HI HI im bored im going 2 street on sat maybe hello any other blogs out ther. kath thanks 4 commenting. jo i wont eat a chicken as im a vegtable so :P to u. Emma what have u been sayin on ur thing as its fillterd at school. im bored and its 2 early in the morning 2 do anything exept sleep. so i thought that i would go on my blog. school starts 2 early. they say 2 enjoy ur childhood but u spend most of it at school. if any1 cs this go on www.evil-rabbit-is-coming.blogspot.com its my m8s blogspot enjoy. plz talk 2 me all u bloggers. bye
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im hungry 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey im new im mad im differant so Ha dont worry the men in white coats are coming to pick me up some time soon well thats what my bro says my bros stupid sept he plays the guitar well :p :p :p anyone who nos me will no im bezerk ha i hav all these weyerd ideas ha ha ha ha  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      prophetess is so rite. we will rule the world!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  butjnhjhuyynnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn0 sorry i dont like football but i was sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo sure france was gonna win euro 2004 but no greece had to come along and beat them. and now portugally r goona win. CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE CURSE GREASE  I HATE GREASE
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im seriosly going to have to go to bed early 2 nit or ill fall asleep on the sofa watchin the blues brothers
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im confused. matbee its cus i got no sleep last nite. well i actualy got 3 owers sleep. but my stomach was playing up so i read. whene i finaly finished a hole book i rumaged 4 mi watch and saw it was 4 o clock. i have a question. is it cus im so weird that people like me? and is it cus im so weird that i hav so many enemys. icud name millions but im 2 tierd. people say im not weird but i am. i mean the only best m8 i ever had was a dog called elwood but he was put down. mi aunty owned elwood but hes the only person i could tell anything 2. mi nan had a cat called jake. u no jake and elwood the blues brothers. hav u ever seen that film its old but its not ancient and its quite funny. theres a second won as well. im supposed to b doing work at the mo. its maths so i dont give a bleeding elash. sorry not allowed 2 swear on the school site. im 2 tierd 2 acctualy do any work and even if i cud b botherd im 2 tired to do it. did i say that? thats how tierd i am. so anyway cus im so tierd im just copying off mi mates hoo exelent at maths.we r in year 8 and she is allready at gcse paper level. ok maybee not the best at it but still exelent :0 bye
     
    
</post>


</Blog>