<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hell yeah it is. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I believe I am going to play around with the template in Dreamweaver tonight and see what I can do.  Probably not much since I suck at Dreamweaver/Flash.  I just finished my test and quiz I had today, and they were both easy.  Thank God for chapters 10-12 in Algebra 2.  So, now I'm sitting here listening to Junior Wells.  My playlist is like Isley Brothers>Blind Willie McTell>Junior Wells>Elton John>White Stripes.  How eclectic.  Or maybe I'm a weirdass...hahaha.  I haven't done anything in like a week, I guess because Britt isn't home.  July 4th is this weekend, and I have a small amount of fireworks, so hopefully, I will get to blow a  few  things up.  But it shouldn't be too fun since nobody I know is home.  STILL!  All of my friends have been on vacation for like 3 weeks, it's crazy.  And now Amie is leaving tomorrow and won't be back forever, so yeah...there goes another one.  Oh well, I need to focus on this online class anyway because my grade is...lacking.  Yes, I'm passing, but it needs to be higher.  Damned homework checks.  Looks like we're about to get our daily afternoon deluge outside.  I swear, I'm gonna build a damn ark if this doesn't stop.  And they say we're still in a 7-inch rain defecit.  It must not rain in Clayton County where it's measured.  I am increasingly being told I am very funny.  I really don't like to brag about myself, but I guess I am, to an extent.  It depends on who I'm talking to.  There are definitely a few people who I can joke around with and think I am pretty funny.  If this comes as a complete shock to you, you're not one of these people.  I'd love to do standup someday (hey- it pays damn good), but I am afraid I'd get boo'ed off the stage, which would make me feel like a Tech football player.  I was up early today, so I was in the living room watching (OH KILL ME FOR THIS) The View with my mom.  They had some dude on there singing, he sounded like George Strait, and was actually pretty good, but he had a guitar.  Now, there is an increasing trend in these fabricated boys of the music industry going onstage with a guitar, fretting a single note, and playing it the entire time, if they even play it.  Well, I didn't even see this guy play the guitar once.  Dude, spare yourself the criticism, lose the guitar, focus on writing songs, and be like Ronnie Van Zant.  The man couldn't read or play music to save his life, but he could sing, and made up for it with his singing and songwriting skills.  Ok that was a relatively stupid rant, but it bothered me, so whatever.  Anyway, speaking of guitars, I need to get my sorry ass to Guitar Center and buy strings and dream of owning a Gibson Firebird.  Ok, later y'all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Since I can't think of anything else to write about, I figured I'd dedicate a post to music, along with probably some other random things.  Anyway, I've recently started listening to a lot of Buddy Guy.  For those of you who don't know anything about music made before 1990, Buddy Guy is a bluesman, and the man who Eric Clapton says is the best guitarist alive.  Jimi Hendrix was often seen sitting on the edge of the stage at Buddy Guy shows taking notes.  So yes, I jacked a CD from my dad called "Buddy Guy and Junior Wells Play the Blues" and was very impressed.  In fact, it is now probably my favorite CD.  Junior Wells is one of the best harmonica players I've ever heard, as well.  I bought Hoodoo Man Blues by Junior Wells the other night and I liked it pretty well too.  But, Buddy Guy's music (and much moreso than most blues artists) blends blues, rock, and funk.  And Buddy has the best voice of any bluesman I've ever heard.  John Lee Hooker is the only one that comes close.  The man can SING, and contrary to popular belief, his voice is definitely not gone.  Just got his show from 3-6-03 and his voice is strong as ever.  So, I'd say Buddy reminds me of Jimi Hendrix at age 70, but with a ton of energy.  So yes, I'm definitely gonna catch Buddy the next time he comes through Atlanta, especially since he is one of my dad's favorites and I know he'll pay since he's never seen him.  Getting off the music subject, I called Britt today...he's in Myrtle Beach until after July 4th and had forgotten to tell me he was going, so I guess that rules out the possibility of me having very much fun until after July 4th.  Talked to Alex...he said he went to Australia, but I don't know how much of that to believe, hahaha, but it is nice to know he's alive.  And I texted Carbo last night and he was stuck in Dallas waiting on a plane, guess he got home today since he had an away message up earlier.  I'm sick of everybody being on vacation and I'm not, dammit all.  I haven't been anywhere since the summer of 2002 when I went to Jamaica.  Maybe if my dad wasn't so addicted to his job, he could go do something.  Oh well, that's all I have to say right now.  Oh yeah, and pray for my grandmother please...she is pretty depressed right now because of some stuff that is going on with my uncle.  Some of you know what happened, but if you don't, then I don't intend to tell you.  Anyway, keep her in your thoughts please.  Thanks.  Ok, I'm gonna go find something to do to pass the time until late tonight when me and Amie have another crazyass conversation. :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was about midnight last night, another uneventful night (why the hell isn't Britt calling me?) and an IM pops up on my screen.  I didn't even have to read it to know who it was, I knew by the bright pink AIM theme.  It was Amie and I hadn't talked to her since February.  I'm not going to detail the circumstances surrounding why I hadn't talked to her since then, most of you know anyway, but if you don't, I don't intend to tell you.  Also something nobody knew was that I had missed talking to her very much over the past 4 months.  Evidentely, she felt the same way.  Actually, on a few circumstances, both of us picked the phone up and almost called each other, but then decided not to.  I told her when we stopped talking before that she knew where I would be if she wanted to speak to me again.  I didn't think she would, but suprisingly enough, she did remember that.  So anyway, I talked to her for 3 hours or so and we are officially speaking again.  Most of what we talked about is none of y'all's damned business, but we'll just say she reaffirmed to me that I am definitely her best guy friend and she is definitely my best female friend.  The comfort level talking to her is nowhere near what I have with any other girl other than Ashley (and maybe Blair- if you read this, don't feel bad, you're cool as hell), but Ashley is different somehow.  So hopefully me and Amie are gonna hang out sometime in the next few weeks but since she lives at the gym and constantly goes out of town, who knows when it will be.  Anyway, I just hope I don't regret speaking to her again.  I thought it was nice that she cared enough to think of me and let me know how she felt.  Thank you.  Ok I'm out...later y'all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       About what, I don't know.  So last night was the first Friday night in I don't know how long that I sat at home.  I haven't heard from Alex since June 7th, which kind of worries me.  Today, I don't know what I'm gonna do...just hopefully more than I did yesterday because sitting around the house is the worst thing ever.  I got my more detailed SAT scores thing in the mail today.  My verbal score was 92% higher than everybody else's in GA, so I'm thinking about applying to the journalism school at UGA, especially since I enjoy writing.  Anyway, it's 2 in the afternoon right now and I just got out of bed, so needless to say, the creative juices are not flowing.  Hopefully I'll be able to write later about whatever I did tonight and that it was fun...hopefully.  By the way, a band suggestion - The Black Keys.  2 guys, a drummer and a guitarist that also sings, and they have a very raw sound, but sound like Hendrix.  I love them, so if you like Hendrix-sounding stuff, check them out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       To bed, I guess, which is where I'll be as soon as a write this, seeing as there is nobody to talk to.  Sitting here listening to Gavin DeGraw, man what a voice.  It is good 2 AM music, very relaxing, as is Warren Haynes acoustic, by the way.  I already have all of my online work done for today (Friday) so if I need to go out and do something (hopefully I will...be damned if I sit at home on a friday night) then I can do so.  It only took me about 20 minutes to do, which is cool.  Oh how I love probability.  And as I do it, the probability of me passing this God-awful class also rises.  Random rant: Damn Michael Moore and his Farenheit (that is how I will spell it because I don't know the real way) 9/11 movie.  Quite honestly, I don't know very much about what it's about and the previews shown on TV where Bush is playing golf actually look decently funny, but Michael Moore is still a fat pompous asshole.  Perhaps somebody should have made a movie about Bill and Monica WHILE he was in office.  I guess there aren't too many Republicans in Hollywood.  The damn leftists in Hollywood attack all the oil prices and some even attack the use of oil because it pollutes the environment and damages the ozone layer (I have yet to understand how a permanent hole can be cut in something made of gas), but I'd like to know what they think powers their private jets and delivers their cocaine to them?  (Thanks Anne Coulter!)  Well, I guess that's all for now since I can't think of anything else to write about.  Hopefully me and Britt will get to do something tomorrow, errr...today.  I think I'll call him and ask him if he wants to see Farenheit 9/11, to which he will likely respond with something to the effect of "I'd rather masturbate with a cheese grater."  I whole heartedly agree.  Y'all have a good one.  Sweet dreams. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Me and my mom went out to eat lunch today at Frontera and after we left there, we went to the store to get something to fix for dinner and there was a woman at the store who looked as if somebody plucked her straight out of Gainesville, FL and didn't even have the common courtesy to notify her she was in the Brookwood district.  I was looking for her 1985 rusted out Firebird in the parking lot, but had to settle for a rusted out early 90's Toyota to laugh at.  Anyway, I do not understand why some 40+ year old women think they can look like they did when they were 20 and why some even try.  But this woman was really bad.  I wouldn't even go out of the house with my mother if she looked like that.  And what was she buying, you might ask?  You guessed it...Clorox.  More later.  I'm off to go sit on my ass some more since it's summer, which is totally awesome. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       And I love it.  I woke up at about 11 (extremely early for summer) and did my online work and since then I have sat here and done nothing, partly because it has been raining like a mofo outside and I don't wanna go out in it.  Is it wrong to like the rain?  For some reason I do, I guess because it is a change of pace from the usual sun and hot weather we have here in Georgia.  So last night after I got home I talked to Blair on here for 3 hours (Thank you for staying up until 2:15 with me).  Sounds like she had a nice birthday, which is nice.  And she is probably the only person who has read this thing...hahaha.  My dad said he won't buy me ABB tickets...he is EVIL.  I wish I had a job so I could buy them.  But hey, it's not for lack of trying.  I don't guess I'm doing anything tonight unless Britt does one of the "I'm pulling in your driveway in 10 minutes" kind of things like he has before hahaha.  UGA got eliminated from the College World Series after blowing a 5-0 lead over the best team in the country...ridiculous.  Oh well, only 72 days until football season.  I can't think of anything else to say right now, so I'll write more later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So this morning about 10:45, Britt calls me and asks me to come to his house and eat lunch and then go bowling with him and Ashley and Aaron.  Ashley makes damn good chicken melts, for whatever it's worth.  Anyway, I am usually a relatively good bowler.  I have bowled a 175 once, in fact.  It is one of the few "sports" I am actually good at.  So the first game I bowled a 37, which kind of pissed me off, but we were all laughing at each other so it was fun.  Second game I got a 72 and the last time I got a 118.  118...hmmm, that sounds like my golf scores.  Anyway, when we came out of the bowling alley, there were ambulances, police cars, fire trucks etc., going down Ronald Reagan toward Lilburn.  We started home and got to the Web Gin House exit and there was about a 10 car pileup on the other side of the road, I guess do to dumbass drivers added to rain.  Now if it wasn't for dumbass drivers, my dad wouldn't have a job, but this was a really bad wreck and somebody died in it.  Anyway, we got back to Britt's house and watched Secret Window with Johnny Depp in it.  Hell of a movie.  I don't like Johnny Depp's political views, but the guy can act.  If you want a movie to watch because you're bored, I highly suggest Secret Window.  It's like 3 hours long too.  So now I'm at home and I guess I'll be here the rest of the night doing nothing at all.  God I love summer. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1:42 in the morning and I'm wide awake.  I'm the only one in the whole house that is.  This is probably my favorite time of day because it is so peaceful.  Nobody is bothering me and I can do whatever I want to.  Right now, I'm playing PS2.  NCAA 2004, the game I am addicted to.  NCAA 2005 comes out on July 15, should be even better than 04.  This is random, but you know what pisses me off?  When somebody that is incredibly nice to you blocks you.  Here is what happened.  I IMed a girl I was good friends with in middle school the other night.  It was about 2:15 in the morning, actually.  We talked for about 30 minutes and then I went to bed.  We reminisced about some things that happened in middle school and how surprising it is who my best friends are now.  There was no harsh feelings between either of us, we had just kind of drifted apart and I was wondering what she was up to.  She was very nice to me, told me good night, etc. And I told her that we could talk late at night every night during the summer since neither of us had anything else to do and she said that was cool.  So, I began to notice that in the days after our conversation, she did not appear on my buddy list.  Knowing that she is constantly online, I put her on my buddy list for the screen name linked to SimpleMan8499.  Sure enough, she was online, at which point I knew she had blocked me.  I don't really care since I've talked to her once in about 3 years, but what the hell?  If you don't like me, tell me and I'll gladly shut up.  For Christ sakes, Amie doesn't have me blocked and I wouldn't say I was her favorite person in the world.  Enough on that rant.  Some other things- where the hell is Alex?  I haven't heard from him in like 2 weeks and he usually calls me more than once a day.  Kinda makes me worry about him.  Allman Brothers tickets go on sale this saturday morning and there is probably going to be a pre-sale toward the middle of this week.  3-night run at the Fox in September.  HELL YES.  Hopefully dad will pay.  I'll probably buy "cheap" $45 balcony seats since it's the Fox and you can see well from anywhere.  I hope he gives me the money.  He  did  pay $90 apiece for Jimmy Buffett tickets, a concert I didn't think was worth it.  Not many people are worth that, and certainly not Jimmy Buffett.  But whatever, it was a hell of an atmosphere and I didn't have to pay.  Got my SAT scores back.  1070.  Not good, not terribly bad either.  Makes me feel good that I got a 1070 and a friend of mine is 75th in my class and made a 1100 on his AFTER taking a $550 SAT prep course.  I made a 650 on the verbal though, so that is 89th percentile, which means I made 89% higher than everybody else that took it.  But the math was only 420, which makes me feel, well, like the mathematical dumbass that I am.  19th percentile, bitches!  Carbo's out of town, Alex has seemingly dropped off the face of the earth, and Blair is, well, I don't know where the hell Blair is.  Hopefully she is back from the beach so I will have somebody else to talk to, and hopefully she had a sweet 16.  My birthday is in not even 4 months.  I'll be 18, and I can buy cigarettes and porno, neither of which I will probably purchase, unless they are for other people.  Quite honestly, porn magazines are lame and a waste of money, as are cigarettes, if you really want to know what I think.  Sorry if I offended anyone.  If I did, too bad. :-) Ok I'm gonna hit the submit button now.  Tomorrow will likely be another Britt, Justin, and ASS-ley (I call her that because she has a nice ass) adventure.  Later y'all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I figured I needed somewhere to get all my thoughts down on "paper", and I am also bored as hell (that was the predominant reason), so I created a blog.  The name, Tales of Ordinary Madness, is the title of Warren Haynes' first album. A  blog , mind you, not a stupid Xanga site that high-school girls write on about their love lives that change seemingly daily.  Hey bitch, I don't care what you did with some guy that was lame enough to do it with you.  Some of you may be able to figure out exactly who I'm talking about.  Blair especially.  Anyway, my purpose in creating this blog is that I love to write, and I don't really care what it is about.  It will most likely turn into a chronicle of what I did every day, with a few thoughts on some issues thrown in.  I hope it is interesting enough for me to have at least  some  readers.  Anyway, today, Ashley, Britt, and myself went to Lennox Square, which we have all agreed is the best mall in this state.  Mall of Georgia pales in comparison.  Britt's ability to shit money never ceases to amaze me.  We walked around in Rich's and a few other stores for a while and he decided he wanted something Polo, so we went to the Polo store.  Ashley wanted him to try on a pink shirt for the hell of it, basically so I could take a picture of him in it with my camera phone and we could laugh our asses off at a later point in time.  He refused.  Finally, we were helped by a gentleman named Arthur.  NOTE: If you ever go to the Polo store at Lennox, ask for him.  He is badass.  I will explain why in the following sentences.  Anyway, Arthur walks up and finally convinces Britt to try it on since we had come all the way from Lawrenceville to Atlanta and he may as well at least try something on.  An hour and a half later (After he had tried on about 10 more shirts), Britt made the decision that he wanted the pink one.  Now, back to Arthur.  This guy stood there and talked to me and Ashley for the entire time and got us cokes and overall he is awesome.  So anyway, he spent $80 on one shirt that he said he wouldn't even try on.  Hilarious.  Now he doesn't like it.  Then, we left Lennox and went back to Britt's house.  I had a quiz and a test today for online (Yes, I failed Algebra 2, 2nd semester and I am retaking it online), so Britt helped me with both of them while Ashley laid in the bed and made lewd sexually enticing comments towards me, to which I did not yield to.  HAHAHA, so now I just got home and I'm going to start on some more homework I have for online so I can get it out of the way and go out with Britt again tomorrow.  I need a job.  Damn you American Eagle.  Thanks for telling me you'd call and you never did.  Side note: I wish I had half the money the people at Lenox Square do.  One guy in the Polo store spent $2,000.  The general categorization of Brookwood is that we are rich white kids.  Compared to the majority of the kids at Lenox, Brookwood people have nothing on them.  Ok that's all, I'll write in this thing again at some point in the near future. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Get to the mall this weekend if you can.&nbsp; There's no tax on any clothes purchases under $100.&nbsp; Went to Gwinnett Place with Britt yesterday and&nbsp;me and him both got good deals on Hilfiger stuff.&nbsp; Tonight, I'm going to see Retrospect,&nbsp;VA Coalition, North Mississippi Allstars, and Collective Soul at On the Bricks.&nbsp; Traffic is going to be hell, but I'm not driving so I don't care.&nbsp;&nbsp;Oh well, I'm out...gotta go take the Expedition to&nbsp;get the oil changed and then go to Britt's house to hang out before we go downtown.&nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Damn it! I was just reminded that I forgot Blair in my entry about the past 3 years.&nbsp; So, I will dedicate an entry to her.&nbsp; Thank you for letting me vent to you.&nbsp; Thank you for having badass taste in music.&nbsp; Thank you for not&nbsp;being afraid to tell me what you really think.&nbsp; I really do appreciate it, and as I've said before, there's only two girls right now that I really give a damn about.&nbsp; Thanks Blair, for always being yourself, and letting nobody change you.&nbsp; You kick ass.&nbsp; And you're not that bad looking either.&nbsp; ;-)   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You can't do it anymore.&nbsp; If you have something to say to me, you can IM me.&nbsp; Asshole.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I always lose track of days during the summer...LOL.&nbsp; Me and Britt hung out yesterday and it ended up turning into me spending the night with him because Ashley, Becca, and a friend of hers, and Ashley's mom&nbsp;were coming from Alabama and we all wanted to hang out.&nbsp; It was pretty fun.&nbsp; And here's some earth-shattering news.&nbsp; I drank alcohol.&nbsp; AHHHHH! LOL!&nbsp; I actually drank a relatively large amount and I didn't feel hardly anything.&nbsp; Anyway, so we went to the grocery store at like 10 to buy cokes and stuff because we ordered pizza and didn't have anything to drink, and as we're going in, we all notice (Me, Britt, Becca, and Elizabeth) this strange as hell Asian dude with his arm around a girl walking out of the store and he is staring at us with this evil look on his face.&nbsp;&nbsp;We didn't think very much of it and we walked on in the store.&nbsp; So I'm standing on the drink isle and all of a sudden the guy pops out of nowhere, along with another equally as freaky looking guy (I don't know where the girl went, they probably raped her or some other sinister thing) and the Asian says to me "You from around here?"&nbsp; And I said "Yes, what do you need?"&nbsp; I thought he was going to ask me for directions or something.&nbsp; What came next was a total shock.&nbsp; "YOU threw a rock at my fuckin' car!&nbsp; A '97 Eclipse!"&nbsp; I was like hell no I didn't, you've got the wrong person.&nbsp; Keep in mind this guy is pretty big and had his hand in his pocket like he was about to pull a gun or a knife or something on me.&nbsp; So Britt asks him "Where'd the rock hit it?"&nbsp; And the guy replies "Stay the fuck out of this, this isn't any of your GD business!"&nbsp; So he asks me how old I am, I tell him 17, and he told me to take my faggot ass home and go to bed, to which I told him I'd definitely be doing.&nbsp; He told me that I better watch out when he catches me in a wide open space and that he'd bust a cap in my ass.&nbsp; How pleasant.&nbsp; So, terrified, we quickly got our drinks and I had Britt and the girls go get the car and pick me up at the door of the store and I never saw the guy again.&nbsp; So, other than that, last night was pretty fun.&nbsp; I'll write more later, probably.  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was sitting here a few minutes ago, definitely in a writing mood, and I was trying to think of something to write about.&nbsp; As is human nature, my mind began to drift across the past few years of my life, the friends I've made, the friends I've lost, the major events, and all that kind of stuff.&nbsp; I figured it was only appropriate that with the beginning of my senior year just a little over two weeks away, that I take the time to recap my first three years of high school and my opinions on a few things that have happened.&nbsp; This may freak you out, but as many of you know, my memory is hauntingly amazing, so I will probably list some dates on here...LOL.&nbsp; Thinking back to my first day of high school, I was, as I'm pretty sure everybody else that was going to Brookwood for the first time that day was, optimistically terrified.&nbsp; Definitely not the stronger, more mentally developed person I am today, I climbed aboard the bus at 6:35 A.M. and began the journey that would lead to two of the best friendships of my life.&nbsp; The bus was packed, as I was close to the last stop.&nbsp; There was a stereo system on the bus blairing "Genie in a Bottle" by Christina Aguilera.&nbsp; Not a particularly good song, but it kept me awake.&nbsp; I don't remember who I sat with that day on the way to school, and I don't really remember much more about the first day than that.&nbsp; I was amazed at the size of Brookwood, but I never really got lost on that first day.&nbsp; I had memorized the room numbers.&nbsp; Football began soon after, and my first dome game was August 25th, 2001.&nbsp; Brookwood vs. Harrison.&nbsp; We kicked their ass 31-14 and then proceeded to have the worst season Brookwood had ever had under Dave Hunter.&nbsp; However, 8-25-01 is significant in that if I wouldn't have went to that game,&nbsp;my high school experience would have been pretty different.&nbsp; I went with Alex to that game, and following it, we went back to some friends of his parents' house.&nbsp; There were 2 girls there (I'm not listing names).&nbsp; Immediately, I was attracted to one of them.&nbsp; Alex was attracted to the other.&nbsp; He ended up going to homecoming with her freshman year.&nbsp; Through getting to know one of them, I started eating lunch with her and some friends of hers at school.&nbsp; Sitting across from me was a girl named Amie...she had transfered from South and didn't know anyone at Brookwood, except the girl I liked.&nbsp; So, I figured, what the hell, I may as well be friends with her since she&nbsp;was friends with the girl I liked.&nbsp; I don't even think Amie liked me very much at first.&nbsp; Freshman year, I was admittedly a know-it-all asshole.&nbsp; I didn't really think she was incredibly attractive and throughout the first semester I didn't really think much of her.&nbsp; Then, somehow, she got ahold of my screen name.&nbsp; (This would be a nice time to note to all you dickheads out there who claim you've known her so long that I was the first guy she knew at Brookwood...just wanted to get that out of the way ;-)&nbsp; Anyway, so, December 15, 2001, I am at my grandmother's house on my laptop and Amie IMs me.&nbsp; I sat and talked to her forever, mainly about her friend that I was interested in.&nbsp; We started talking like every day on here for long periods of time and I began to realize that I probably liked her more than her friend.&nbsp; Throughout second semester, I began to like her more.&nbsp; I'm sure she probably figured it out, and I don't really give a damn now because she knows all this.&nbsp; I wouldn't be writing it here if she didn't.&nbsp; Second semester, I started eating lunch with Britt, Katie, Tori, and some other people.&nbsp; I'd kill to have this lunch group again.&nbsp; I laughed my ass off EVERY DAY.&nbsp; I had known Britt in 8th grade because we had eaten lunch together then, but I didn't really know him very well and never saw him as somebody I could really hang out with.&nbsp; He definitely changed from the first few years of middle school.&nbsp; I'm trying to make this somewhat chronilogical, but I'm gonna jump around probably, so whatever.&nbsp; Anyway, on to the summer of 2001.&nbsp; Me and Amie got closer...we basically told each other every secret that we both had.&nbsp; I could ruin her if I wanted to, and she could do the same to me.&nbsp; On to sophomore year.&nbsp; There was nothing good about sophomore year except our football team going to the state championship.&nbsp; Other than that, it utterly sucked in all aspects.&nbsp; I seemed to lose the ability to study, I became frustrated that the girl I was head over heels for didn't seem to know I existed, and I became pretty depressed, and I had to hold it all in.&nbsp; I don't even remember much about sophomore year.&nbsp; The only good thing that came out of it was that me and Britt got a lot closer.&nbsp; January 29, 2003 was one of the worst days of my life.&nbsp; A bunch of crap (that I'm not talking about here)&nbsp;that had built up on me culminated and I had just had enough.&nbsp; My relationship with everyone I knew tumbled from then on.&nbsp; I was so depressed I couldn't think straight.&nbsp; My grades sucked, I felt like nobody gave a damn about me, and I didn't know what to do.&nbsp; In May, I pissed off Amie so bad (something I once thought was impossible) that she stopped talking to me for 4 months.&nbsp; Looking back on it, it was definitely all my fault.&nbsp; I was a jealous dickhead.&nbsp; Over those next 4 months, I got myself back together, got over her, realized that she would always be a much better friend than a girlfriend, and wanted to be friends with her again.&nbsp; (We are moving on to junior year now).&nbsp; Anyway, to make it short, me and her spoke from September of '03 to February of '04 and then went on another 4 month hiatus due to me being a dick again.&nbsp; Ok, now I'll talk about the other aspects of junior year.&nbsp; I loved my junior year...it was definitely the best year I've had of high school.&nbsp; The summer between sophomore and junior years, I really changed.&nbsp; I think the main thing was that I finally got some self confidence.&nbsp; Finally, I felt like I was relatively decent looking and I liked the person I was.&nbsp; I had definitely learned over the first two years that being nice to people was crucial in being friends.&nbsp; Me and Britt had three classes together, so we got really close and started hanging out a lot.&nbsp; He has introduced me to so many awesome people and made me so much more of an outgoing person that I an indebted to him forever.&nbsp; Something happened that I never thought would...I had a lot of friends.&nbsp; People liked me...I didn't feel like I needed to idolize people anymore.&nbsp; I could just be myself and people liked it.&nbsp; It was an amazing feeling.&nbsp; I guess that's about it.&nbsp; If there's one thing I've learned in high school, it's that people change so much.&nbsp; Looking back over the past three years, I have definitely changed a lot, I think for the better.&nbsp; Right now, going into senior year, I love my life.&nbsp; The only thing that sucks that's going on is my grandmother being in the hospital.&nbsp; Me and Amie are friends again, and this time I don't think it's going to end because of some stupid BS...I think we've realized that we appreciate each other too much for it to do so.&nbsp; Ok this has been long and rambling and I hope somebody reads it.&nbsp; Later everyone.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally...they hired me at the Gwinnett Arena and I have to go for training 1-5 saturday.&nbsp; Starts at $7 an hour and goes up&nbsp;to $7.35 after 60 days and then to $8 after 90 days,&nbsp;I believe.&nbsp; Thanks for getting me a job there, uncle Bob.&nbsp; And you can work whenever you want to, as much as you want to, so it won't interfere with football season.&nbsp; My dad came home from work today and has a stomach virus, so now I've locked myself in my room trying not to catch it.&nbsp; I've been so bored over the past 2 or 3 days with Britt gone&nbsp;until saturday&nbsp;and Amie having Adam at her house for 2 weeks.&nbsp; &nbsp; I really don't have anything to write, thus, not many updates lately.&nbsp; I'm sitting here downloading songs for a CD for Nicole.&nbsp; Damn shame she lives like 200 yards from me and we never hang out or anything.&nbsp; She is my ride to school this year, though, hopefully.&nbsp; Maybe I'll get a parking place, but I doubt it.&nbsp; No way I'll get that lucky.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Even though not much has been going on.&nbsp; Saturday I went to see my grandmother...she is doing decent I guess, but knowing she'll probably be gone this time next year isn't too comforting.&nbsp; Today, I did absolutely nothing.&nbsp; Amie said she was getting back saturday and I haven't heard from her, so I suppose I'll call her tomorrow because I miss the hell out of her with Britt and Ashley gone now and I have nothing to do.&nbsp; Dad wants me to go to work with him tomorrow, but I don't want to.&nbsp; I hope I don't end up getting dragged into going...uggh.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hung out at Britt's all day with him and Ashley, and then at about 5:15, we left and went down to Dailey's in Atlanta to eat dinner, and then to the Braves game.&nbsp; The food, as always, was excellent.&nbsp; I had peppercrusted swordfish with honey mustard sauce and garlic mashed potatoes.&nbsp; Then, of course, for desert, I had the black&amp;white cake.&nbsp; I got it to go and haven't eaten any of it yet.&nbsp; I have a picture of it that I'll post.&nbsp; It is incredible.&nbsp; Of course, I tried to pay for my meal, and Britt's mom would only let me pay $10 of the like $40 it cost.&nbsp; So she told me to also buy her a beer at the Braves game, which wasn't a problem.&nbsp; Braves lost, which wasn't very good, but we had fun and the seats were great.&nbsp; Then, on the way home, me and his mom started talking about music and I told her the Allman Brothers were coming to the Fox September 24-26 and she was like "Let's go" and I was like "Well, my dad said he wouldn't pay for me a ticket and I don't have any money."&nbsp; She told me not to worry about it, that she'd take care of it, and that Britt, her, and myself would go on September 26th.&nbsp; I called her and let her know what tickets were available when I got in the house and she said she would buy them tonight or tomorrow morning.&nbsp; His mom is awesome...I feel bad because I always try to give her money and she refuses to take it.&nbsp; Oh well, I love my Aunt Rhonda! Hahaha!&nbsp; Here is the Dailey's cake:  &nbsp; I'm out.&nbsp; Amie comes home tomorrow :-)  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        It's now 7-16-04,&nbsp; but that doesn't matter.&nbsp; Today was fun.&nbsp; It was the first day I've had in about a week that even bordered on being fun.&nbsp; Today, I went over to Britt's and basically we did nothing but hang out.&nbsp; We went and had lunch at Eppy's and then came back and just hung for a while.&nbsp; Tomorrow night we're going to the Braves game and maybe out to eat, idk, so that should be fun.&nbsp; Me and Ashley sat out on the patio for a while and she told me a bunch of stuff that I'm definitely not posting here, but it was cool.&nbsp; She has made some stupid decisions in her life, and she realizes that, but she is very mature to be 16.&nbsp; My grandmother's surgeon told my mom today that he thinks she has a year to live.&nbsp; Her cancer is the fastest spreading kind.&nbsp; Oh well, what can you do but enjoy the last year with her?&nbsp; It's one year she didn't have if she wouldn't have had the surgery.&nbsp; I got my online class grade.&nbsp; 77 in the class and a 79 on the final.&nbsp; I damn near passed out when I saw that I'd made a 79 on the final, considering I didn't study for it AT ALL.&nbsp; Oh well, I can't think of anything else.&nbsp; Tomorrow should bring some interesting pictures from the Braves game, hahaha.&nbsp; Later.   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Had my final today for my online class.  I thought I did decent on it.  Hopefully it was above a 58.  That's all I care about.  Then, I came home for a while and went to the hospital to see my grandmother.  She is still very weak, but she was more alert than she was yesterday.  She can still hug really hard and squeeze the hell out of my hand...LOL.  Nice to see she's progressing nicely.  Amie called me on the way to the hospital, didn't talk to her long because I was almost there, but I was shocked she called me because she is in FL with a certain guy, so it made me feel good to know she really does give a damn about me.  After me and my mom left, we went to Frontera and now I'm home.  I just got an email from some girl that was in my online class that wants to complain about the teacher.  I had no problem with her.  All her email responses were prompt and she helped as much as she could.  Don't really see what the big fuss is about, but my opinion is that if you have a problem with an online teacher, get over it because you got yourself into the situation to begin with.  Anyway, I'm gonna go play guitar, probably.  Tomorrow, Britt, Ashley, and myself, should finally do something.  :-) Later y'all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       -UGA football -Brookwood football -Hot chicks wearing thongs -Racing -Golf -My ability to remember things that amaze even me -The Allman Brothers Band -Derek Trucks -Bulldog Pizza on Hwy. 29 -Girls with extremely nice asses (Amie...LOL) -Gibson Firebird guitars -My Motorola V300 -70+ year old musicians that still tour (Pinetop Perkins, you are the MAN) -Tom Hanks -Atlanta, GA (Sometimes) -The fact that I am not from some weird shaped state above VA -My southern accent -Playstation2 -People who will listen to me bitch to them (Thanks!) -CKOne cologne -Chocolate chip cookie dough ice cream -Bruster's chocolate chip cookie dough ice cream -Ray Allen -Dentyne Ice -Mark Richt -70X-Takeoff (UGA 24 AU 21, November 16, 2002) -P-44 Haynes (UGA 26 UT 24, October 6, 2001) -The fact that UGA owns Tech in EVERY sport -The Dawgvent  There is a lot more, but I'm sick of typing.  There will be a list of things I think suck coming soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Even though it is 7-14-04 now.  Got up this morning and went to the hospital with my mom.  I didn't really know what to expect and neither did she.  I'd never been in an intensive care unit until today, and let me just say I hope I never go back in one ever again.  It is extremely freaky and very sad.  I'm not going to cut any corners here (but know that my grandmother  is  fine).  We went in, down a long hallway, then you turn right and go into a large open space full of nurses' desks.  Off to the sides of this room are the intensive care rooms.  The doors to these rooms are like airtight doors, the closest way I can describe them is like the automatic doors at some stores, except you have to open them manually.  Some of them are covered up because the person in the room is near death.  There was one family standing outside the room next to my grandmother's in tears because they couldn't decide whether or not to pull the plug on their grandmother.  Anyway, I went in my grandmother's room and she was laying there on the bed.  She looked asleep.  Ok, quite honestly, she looked dead, even though her color was good.  I had been told before that it was normal because of the pain killers she was on that she would act like this.  So I go in and say "Nana, do you know who I am?"  She couldn't talk (she can now, I'll get to this later), but she shook her head yes.  I asked her if she was in pain and she shook her head yes again.  After seeing her on saturday as the vibrant, funny lady that she is, it was very depressing to see her like this.  Ok, now enough of the doom and gloom BS.  After me and my mom left, the pain medications began to wear off and the swelling in her brain began to decrease more and more.  My aunt said that, as of now, she has "awakened" and is acting relatively normal and was cracking jokes with everyone that visited.  She is very tired, but they're moving her to a regular room in the morning.  The doctor came and said everything looks great right now.  She can't move her right arm or leg, but physical therapy should allow her to regain movement in them.  He rated her cancer as a 4 on a scale of 1-10, so that's pretty good too.  Anyway, on to something else, I have my final tomorrow at Berkmar for my online class.  I have to make a 58 or above or I have to take it again.  My test average is 78 and you can't have a final exam grade of less than 20 points below your test grade.  I haven't studied at all for the final yet.  Oh well, I should be fine.  I made a 61 on the one in the regular class and I know the material much better now.  Me and Andrew were talking tonight about how he misses a female friend of mine and it made me think of what I may be dealing with in a year.  I'll be in college somewhere.  It has dawned on me that this is the last year with some of my favorite people in the world.  Britt is going to Tech, probably, so me and him will still see each other, but lord knows where else everybody else is going.  Alex will be in the Naval Air Corps school, most likely, so that will be weird.  That SOB flying fighter jets is scary. :-)  Oh well, I'm gonna shut up now.  Keep praying for my grandmother.  She is doing well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Surgery on my grandmother went wonderfully today and she should be fine, considering the circumstances.  I don't feel like writing a lot right now because I am kinda tired, so I'll make a bigger entry tomorrow. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmmm, not much has happened since the last time I wrote.  I went to see my grandmother yesterday and was amazed at her condition.  I thought she wouldn't remember who I was, or much of anything else, but in 3 hours of talking with her, the only thing she couldn't remember was what church her former preacher had gone to.  Still, she has a brain tumor, and it is a very serious condition, regardless of how she acts.  Hopefully, the doctor will fix it bright and early monday morning and she will be fine.  The surgeon told her "I'm not God, but I work for him."  I like that.  Was talking to my uncle yesterday and I may start working at the Gwinnett Arena.  Interview is July 21st.  Get paid to see concerts, basically.  Sweet.  If anybody actually reads this, I'd like to thank my friends for the thoughts and prayers for my grandmother.  Y'all are great.  Ok, I'm out...I need to find something to do because I can't sit here and have a 5 hour conversation with 2 hot girls because they're both in FL now.  :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Found out today my grandmother has surgery on monday.  I don't know very much about it, but if it goes correctly, then she  may   return to normal.  Of course, if it doesn't go right, then, well, let's try not to think about that.  Surgery is the only option.  She was told that if she didn't have surgery that she would die within a month.  I guess I will have to go to the hospital this weekend to see her.  It is something I don't want to do, but I know I need to.  I hate hospitals...they freak me out.  Britt just called me and wanted me to go to the movies tonight (again).  I told him no, because I just didn't feel like getting home at 1 in the morning, and because, hopefully, I'll get to talk to Amie tonight before she leaves for a week.  I can't think of anything else to say, so I'm gonna go find something to do to occupy myself.  Later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       And it's going to cover a few topics, especially the most prevalent of the past day.  As I said yesterday, my grandmother had had a few mini-strokes and I feared for the worst.  However, I definitely wasn't expecting it to happen so soon, not even 24 hours later.  This morning, she called here and talked to my mom.  I don't know what was said, but evidentely she couldn't remember very much.  This led to my mom and my aunt going to take her to the emergency room.  My mom left here at 1 this afternoon and didn't come home until 10:30.  She called me once to ask me for a phone number and I could tell there was something wrong, it wasn't just a little stroke or memory lapse or something.  Anyway, when she got home, I was told that......they think my grandmother has a brain tumor.  Y'all, I know nothing about these things other than that sooner or later, they'll kill you.  And I also thank God that they're not genetic.  By the time they got to the hospital with her today, she could not remember who any of her own children were.  They ran a CTScan on her and said it looked like a tumor, and that it had been there quite a while, and it also showed that a few small strokes had occured recently on the upper right part of her brain.  Now, I do know that brain tumors are treatable, and in some cases, through surgery, totally cureable, but I don't know how good the outlook is for an almost 80 year old woman with a history of strokes.  Naturally, I hope that they will be able to operate and she will return to the full of life person she has always been.  However, if she is going to have to suffer for a long time, I kind of hope the Lord spares her, as my mom also said.  My mom also said there are some things she can remember fine, and that she can somewhat carry on a conversation.  It's just very freaky.  I'm trying not to worry about it, because I know there's absolutely nothing I can do about it, but of course, when something like this happens, it sticks in your mind regardless.  I just ask that you pray for her, as well as the rest of my family.  It is appreciated.  I am a firm believer that everything happens for a reason, even when it seems horrible.  Ok, next topic.  Guys that treat girls bad are SHIT.  Yes, there are girls that I don't like, but no I would never say the stuff a particular dick said to a girl tonight.  Any guys out there that expect action from a girl, get over yourselves.  Build a relationship first and then maybe you'll get something, and you'll sure enjoy it a lot more.  I feel like posting the SOB's screen name on here for everybody to see, but I don't think I will out of courtesy for the victim of his asshole syndrome.  But this dickhead just pissed me off at the end of an already less than stellar day.  There is some other stuff I want to say, but I don't think I'll write it on here.  Ok I'm out...I need to press the publish button before I say something I shouldn't.       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally got around to seeing Dodgeball tonight with Britt.  What a funny movie, the funniest I've seen in a long, long time.  But going to the movies at 7:30 was weird since I usually don't go until NOW.  I'm pretty bored right now because nobody is online.  My grandmother had another mini-stroke today.  This isn't good...I have a bad feeling it's builing up to a really big one and then she'll never remember who I am again.  What a horrible thought.  Anyway, I'm gonna go find something to eat and wait for somebody to get their ass on here...and oh what a nice ass it is! :-) 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I figured I'd just start naming the titles of these posts the date since I don't feel like thinking of something to call all of them unless it is necessary.  This afternoon, me and my mom went to the Forum (it's a big nice shopping center over off Peachtree Parkway in Norcross) to get my aunt a birthday present and then went to Harry's to get something for dinner.  Tonight I'm going out with Britt and Ashley.  It will be nice to finally go do something again, albeit not with the person I had originally intended, but as always, she was busy, and I know she can't help it, so it doesn't piss me off.  I called Britt earlier...hahaha, it's crazy that when I call him I end up talking to Ashley more than him.  I hate to talk on the phone when my mom is around because she tells me I shouldn't say things that I say because she can't detect sarcasm worth a damn.  Anyway I'm gonna go play guitar and then eat dinner and then go out and have a damn good time because I haven't seen my best friends in over 3 weeks.  Later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have now been up 20 hours straight and I don't feel tired.  So today work with dad wasn't too bad.  He taught me how to use the computer program he uses to write estimates, but I cannot look at a car for the life of me and know all the parts on it.  I'm not gonna go into detail on going to work with him because it isn't very exciting, so I'll just skip to what we did next.  Since my grandmother (on my dad's side) only lives about 5 mins from where my dad works, we decided to go make a surprise visit.  She made us lunch.  God it was good...steaks and potatoes.  It's always great to see my grandmother (either of them) because they seem to love you and find good in you no matter how bad you suck at life or whatever.  Not saying I suck at life, but grandmothers in general kick ass.  We stayed and chatted with her for about 2 hours.  It's always great to hear the stories she has to tell.  She definitely hasn't lost any of her memory.  She gave me some money and a ton of candy too, so that wasn't bad either.  Then, we came home and I've been here since.  Britt called me tonight, he is home and we're gonna do something tomorrow.  He still wants to go clubbing, but I fit about as well in a club as a vegetarian does at a BBQ cookoff.  I really don't wanna go.  That's not what we're doing tomorrow anyway.  Tomorrow (meaning today, 7-6, since I haven't gone to bed yet), we're going bowling again since it's $6 for 2 hours unlimited games.  Ok I'm tired...talk to y'all later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've actually been up about an hour now.  My dad asked me last night if I would go to work with him today, and after he pleaded with me, I obliged so he'd shut the hell up.  He wants to teach me how to write an estimate so "I will have something to do to work my way through college".  If you don't know what my dad does, he is the body shop manager at a car dealership.  For what he does, he makes an obscene amount of money, and believe me, I'm definitely not rich, but the average for his job is like 30,000 and he makes 6 figures, so he is one of the best in the country at what he does.  Anyway, he will probably work his ass off today while I sit around and don't do anything and I'll never learn a damn thing.  I do wish I knew how to write estimates though, because one of his estimators just quit and he said he would have replaced him with me, even though I have no idea how I could have a full-time 8-6 job when school started back, but it would have been good money for hmmmmm...a month.  Britt comes home today, finally...so tomorrow should be fun.  I haven't seen him and Ashley in...3 weeks.  Damn.  Anyway, last night I didn't go to the fireworks thing, just as I said I wouldn't.  Watched all 3 of them on TV.  Gwinnett county spends $60,000 on fireworks.  That fireworks show lasted about 25 minutes, so that is roughly $2400 per minute.  I could think of better things for the county to do with $60,000, but fireworks are cool, and I can think of far worse things to do with $60,000...like giving Wayne Hill a raise.  Tonight should be busy.  I HAVE TO do homework from 2 sections of online and then do tomorrow's work if I feel like doing anything tomorrow.  Bastards even give you an assignment over the 4th of July "holiday" that thankfully I found out about because I didn't think I had one.  Even more thankfully, the "holiday" extends through today, so I can still do the homework.  Sorry for bitching, I failed the class the first time, and I agree, I should be punished for doing so.  Ok I can't think of anything else to write about.  Off to work I go, and I'm not getting paid. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       228 years ago today, some of the best men ever to live signed one of the most famous documents ever.  Then we proceeded to kick some British ass and became free.  So, thanks to all the great folks who defend the best nation ever.  34 years ago today, Jimi Hendrix played one hell of a show at the Atlanta Pop Festival.  Just a useless fact.  Anyway, this weekend has been relatively dull.  Yesterday (Saturday-I'm sure the 2 AM entries are confusing as to what day I mean when I say yesterday) I finally went to guitar center and got strings so I can play again.  $12 for 12 packs...not bad.  I should have gotten 24 for $24.  Then I came home and watched the race.  Yes, NASCAR is a guilty pleasure of mine, been watching it forever and if I am a redneck for doing so, so be it, but I enjoy racing.  I don't have a mullet and I don't wear blue jean shorts so I think that disqualifies me from being a redneck.  I'm just a "suthuna".  So yeah that's all I did yesterday, and today we got up and went and ate breakfast and Waffle House.  The All-Star breakfast is awesome.  Then, I came home and did nothing all afternoon and now here it is 6:05 and I would guess I'm not doing anything tonight either, unfortunately.  Fireworks are badass and I don't have very many to blow up and didn't feel like going to South Carolina to get more.  It's been raining, so at least I can't catch anything on fire.  I swear it rains every day.  I wanna go to the Gwinnett Glows thing.  Well, not actually up by the courthouse itself because the traffic is horrible, but go sit somewhere and watch the fireworks, but I'm sure my parents will be anal about it, just like most other things.  Anyway, I'm out...gonna go find something else to do.  Happy 4th! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       6-24-72 in Fort Worth, TX.  What a great concert.  I wonder if they're any good nowadays.  On Mick's newest CD he still had his voice, but I would guess they cost $150+ to see in concert, which is ridiculous.  Anyway, Britt called me tonight from Myrtle Beach.  He's coming home monday and we will probably do something every day next week.  He was on the way home from the House of Blues.  They had a teen night which he said was incredibly lame so he left.  However, he wants me and some other people to go to Wild Bill's on a sunday night, and if you know me, you know I am not a club-type person.  But knowing how I am, I'll probably end up getting dragged into it.  The main reason I don't wanna go is because I don't wanna hear 2+ hours of shitty music.  It's like Blair said the other night..."Why do people listen to shitty music?"  I guess because they like it, and if they like it, then they're usually not worth talking to.  Anyway, I talked to Britt for about an hour and we're gonna play golf this week maybe, so if we do, it should be fun and I should kick his ass again. :-) I just wanna shoot a 2-digit number and I'll be fine!  Hopefully this time we won't get paired up with 2 meanass old men.  Thank God those dickheads left 4 holes into our round last time.  It sucks when you start talking to somebody again and then they have to leave for like a week.  Uggh, I miss you. Hahaha, yeah.  So this weekend I have zero plans for July 4th other than to hang out here at home because everybody is gone until next week.  Alright, I'm gonna shut up now.       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Figured Hendrix may have been a little hard to read to, so I changed it to Warren Haynes acoustic from 6-29-97.  If you want to download the song, go here. http://home.comcast.net/~simpleman8499/images/wh1997-06-29-d1-2_t05-10.mp3 It's called Before You Came.  I'll have another entry later on. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       JIMI! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You hold on to love that's gone Run a mile to see him smile But you don't know he's door to door Playin' you for the fool  Black Keys lyrics.  Nothing more, and no it doesn't relate to anything.  I never knew that song was on the School of Rock soundtrack.  I still need to see that movie.  So today I did nothing, hahaha yeah my life is dull as hell right now, which explains the frequency at which I am writing on here.  I think me and my mom are actually going to do something tomorrow, so that should be fun.  She has been being a bitch lately though, but we get along 99% of the time.  She's definitely not as bad as I sometimes make her out to be.  I am trying to get music to play on here.  Hendrix at the Atlanta Pop Festival, 7-4-70.  Badass show.  Ok that's all for now...I think I'm gonna go to bed here in a few mins. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Because I'm about to leave to go to "work." I get to see Hilary Duff and get paid for it...LOL. Anyway, friday night, I went to see Blues Traveler and Cypress Hill at On the Bricks. It was the worst concert I have ever seen in my life, bar none. Blues Traveler, I have always heard, is great in concert, but friday night, they SUCKED. Saturday, I went to the outlet mall in Dawsonville with my parents and I got a lot of clothes for school, so that was fun. And now I just got in from cutting the grass and I've gotta be at the arena at 2:45.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       But I got my license, it just took 4 hours.  Yes, I'm supposed to be at a concert right now, but my grandmother got moved to the nursing home today and we had to go visit her and all, and I didn't get home until about 45 minutes ago.  More about my day later...whenever I feel like writing.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmmmm, I haven't done much this week. Me and Britt went to the Mall of Georgia on monday, yesterday I did nothing, and today, me and my mom went out to eat and then we went out to dinner for my dad's birthday at Macaroni Grill. Tomorrow will be busy. Registration at 8:30, then FINALLY I get my license at 10:30. I hate to admit that I'm almost 18 and don't have my license, so after tomorrow I am FREE. Then, tomorrow night, I am either going to see Blues Traveler for free at the Variety Playhouse with Britt or to see Bob Margolin at Blind Willie's with my dad. I'd rather see Margolin again because he is a badass. Oh well, that's all. Ron Isley is the biggest pimp ever.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmmmm, let's see.  Last time I updated was friday morning, and it is now sunday night.  Well, friday, me and my mom went to the mall and looked around for awhile.  Ran into Blair...it was nice to see her since it's been a while. Then, I went over to Britt's and we hung out for a while, then he called Briana and asked her to go with us to On the Bricks and she ended up not being able to go, so me and him went and met Laura and Tim there.  Virginia Coalition was pretty good, North Mississippi Allstars are awesome live...their lead singer/guitarist is great.  Collective Soul surprised me in that they are much harder sounding in concert.  Their frontman is a badass.  The concert was packed.  Next time (Friday- Blues Traveler, Rehab, Cypress Hill) we're going to do 2 things that we didn't this time.  Drive instead of taking MARTA and bring lawn chairs.  Other than the MARTA ride from hell on the way home (there were like 150 people in the car we were on) and having to sit on the ground, it was a great time.  Ok, so saturday, I went to the mall with my mom and my aunt and got a pair of pants and a shirt.  Then, I came home and washed the Expedition.  Today, I washed my dad's car and then went to the hospital to see my grandmother since I hadn't seen her for 8 days.  Today was the best she's been since the surgery.  It was great to see her talk a lot.  They're finally starting to take her off a lot of the medicine she's been on, so she's getting a little more "normal" every day.  Oh well, that's my weekend.  If all goes well, I'll be hanging out with a hot chick some this week. Hahahaha :-)  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>