<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Given that the presidential election is about a half-a-year away, it's seems unlikely that I'll be able to avoid thinking about / discussing / writing about politics. This is unfortunate, because that is exactly what I'd like to do. Well really, what I'd like to be able to do is replace all time and energy spent on politics (expand that to include political-type-things, e.g. wars, terrorism, economy, etc.) with time and energy spent on something much more useful and fulfilling to me. Like, working on all these ideas I have for books, screenplays, short stories, songs, poems, and so on. In essence, I'd like to give up Reality for the next six months or so and go live in some other world of my own creation.   The likelihood of this actually happening is doubtful at best. I heard about the accelerated "transer of sovereignty" in Iraq on NPR this morning, and sitting there in traffic, I could feel the cynicism like adrenaline being dumped into my bloodstream and rushing straight to my brain. The radio says this move supposedly marks the end of U.S. occupation in Iraq and all I can think about is the 150,000+ troops still firmly rooted there, my best friend's brother among them. Is it not enough for our Commander in Chief to make a mockery of our own county? How can you possibly claim sovereignty when your country is litterally overrun by a foreign nation's military? Sure, we'll let you control your foreign policy now, but just in case you get out of line, don't forget the gigantic military presence we're leaving here...   This is what must stop. I've reached the point where I'm absolutely dead tired of thinking about all of these sorts of things. I spent my entire Sunday afternoon (and evening) reading the fifth Harry Potter book, which I passed up on last summer for reasons I don't remember. It was fantastic (both the book and the leisure of sitting around and reading for some 8 odd hours) and I felt so much lighter, going upstairs to bed. Back in the car this morning and I made the mistake of turning on the news and that feeling of lightness, of peacefulness was crushed, gravity pulling harder and harder until I was typically slumped down in my seat and cursing the traffic under my breath.   I've always thought I understood why intelligent people sometimes do things that appear to be very  un intelligent - like tuning out the very world they live in. I've felt like I understood why they could do that, but I've never really respected them for doing it, or wanted to do the same myself. Now, I think I'm going to join them. I'll still vote in the election - I'm not going to become  that  irresponsible - but I'm fininshed with the world at large for the time being. Actually, I should qualify that... I'm finished with hearing about the world at large through the media, the so-called "news". I'm tired of being fed what the corporate backers of CNN and NBC and ABC and CBS (etc. etc.) deem is "news" and I'm utterly sick of thinking about it all. People can be car-bombing eachother to pieces, but I'm not going to hear about it or listen.   At least, for a while. Eventually, I'll have to get back to paying attention to things again - I care too much about my country and the people who live in it to completely ignore them. But as for now, I don't even know what it's like to try and think anymore without thoughts of war and politics and blah blah blah pounding in my brain. It'll be nice to hear what else is going on inside there for a change.  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://slate.msn.com/id/2102723/  I have always been a bit suspicious of Michael Moore and his intentions, and this article quite clearly and lucidly said a lot of things about him (and his new "movie") that I had been struggling to find the words for. I think it's sad that, because Bush and his administration have fouled things up so badly, people can oppose him without needing a reason. I don't like the guy either, and I'll be the first in line to vote him out of office, but I could also write you a 20-page paper on  why  I'm doing so, and support it with enough facts to choke a camel. I'm scared that so many of these people jumping on the "Anybody But Bush" wagon are doing it without really knowing why. And these are the people that could be the most affected by Moore's "documentary." I hope people don't forget that, regardless of the intentions or motives behind Farenheit 9/11, it's still a movie shown in movie theaters and is part of the movie industry. Michael Moore is not doing this for free and isn't showing it to you for free. There might be some goodwill involved here, but there's also an enormous (well, for you an I) amount of money involved too. Money affects everything... and the movie industry in this country is one of the most affected... and is consequently one of the greediest industries. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's a good bet the empire knows we're here.   Suspiciously appearing out of nowhere, a new kind of journal (er... blog, or, you know, whatever these damn things are called), scarcely out of its original packaging with that factory-fresh smell and smug, un-smudged or fingerprinted, glossy exterior -  ready to  rock  (well,  blog ... woo) and or  roll .   And now, I would like to invite anyone unfortunate enough to have stumbled across this to beat me unmercifully if I ever use the word "blog" again. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes - sometimes you just want to sit back on your couch and  urlLink blow up stuff as a little yellow alien dude .  I can't wait till this game comes out. I wish more video games were as creative as this.   EDIT (4:23pm):   urlLink This guy  is amazing. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OZMA    1995- 2004    R.I.P.    "I knew that the night had an end soon in sight, until you called my name / I knew all along I was right, but I'm wrong, somehow you knew my name / After the last dance, you lose your last chance...      you've lost your last chance"   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's good to know that I have the emotional fortitude of a new-born kitten. After just a sad four days, I collapsed and bought some cigarettes. I could get the chemicals via the patch, but nothing can replace the habit - my crutch. To say that I have an addictive personality is somewhat like saying "the sky is blue", or "the force due to gravity near Earth's surface is -9.8 m/s^2" ... it's a constant, a given for any word problem I happen to be involved in. It's going to take much more than a sticky little circle of time-release nicotine to escape from this passively aggressive addiction. And of course, they tell you all of that in those convenient little pamphlets that the patches come with - it's all about "behavior modification", or some shit. I don't need  modification , I need a fucking lobotomy.      Well, really, I know  exactly  what I need to beat this, but I'm coming up way short on that right now. And there isn't any need for me to elaborate exactly on what "that" is - I could look back on this in a decade and know exactly what I mean by "that". Hopefully in that much time, if I should happen to be looking back on this by some incredible means of preservation that I haven't the tenacity or desire to pursue, I won't be lacking for "that". Hopefully, there's a decade in front of me that includes a lot of things that come up absent right now from recent roll calls. At least (I guess) I'm aware enough now to know just what is missing. Maybe that's enough. I can't help but feel like luck has way too much influence when it comes to all of this. Or, did I use the wrong word - is it luck, or is it destiny? Do I really believe in that kind of New York Times best sellers list shit?  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My characters are stuck in their dorm room.       I'm nearing the end of the first chapter. All of the key character introductions have been written, relevant back story has been established, threads for possible side plots have been vaguely hinted at or exposed. I've got everything right where I want it... except for the actual plot, and so my characters remain stuck, waiting to respond to whatever it is I figure out to throw at them.     This is only a problem because I have too many ideas about what is going to happen in this story. I've put off writing my first novel for so long now that I have a ridiculous back-catalog of plot lines, stories and ideas. Time to start whittling through them all to get down to just the very best... and then pit the winners against  e ach other in some kind of WWF (oh, sorry, I guess it's WWE now... I feel old) plot/story line royal rumble.      And not that it necessarily has anything to do with writing, but I may be quitting smoking soon. As in today, after work, after I go to CVS and buy a couple boxes of patches. There is a good chance that I won't go through with it at all, or go through with it only to give up inside the first week. Perhaps, at the very least, I'll get some insanely strange transdermal-nicotine-induced dreams that I can use for my story.     Oh yeah, and I've been thinking about doing some of that  exercise  stuff that I've heard a lot about. Something about this past birthday has left me feeling particularly old and mortal. I'd like to get back to feeling young and indestructible. Or at least, cleaned and refurbished.     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember waiting all winter long for Apollo 18 to come out, every night rushing downstairs when my step-father got home from our record store to see if he had the tape in hand. Every week he came home empty handed was one more week of fuel for my mass-colliding anticipation. And then, one evening in March he dropped the tape in my lap and I disappeared to my room for a private listening. At first I was scared... but quickly "Dig My Grave" gave way to "I Palindrome I" and spent the rest of the night grinning from one headphoned ear to ear. I probably played the tape 10 times before finally falling asleep on my floor, headphones still in place.   Tonight, I came home with my copy of "The Spine" expecting... something. After nearly a decade of one brutal let down after another (beginning with "Factory Showroom" and plunging painfully down from there), my hopes were expectedly low. However, I knew a couple of the songs on the album before I even had the shrinkwrap off. "Thunderbird" was a song I had heard back in 1998 or 1999 which, at the time gave me false hope at a return to the Giants I once knew and love, but the song was lost and forgotten it seemed until now. A poorly recorded version of "Museum of Idiots" discovered online a few weeks ago dared me further to think that maybe, just  maybe  I was in for something other than bitter disappointment.  For the two minutes and 56 seconds of "Experimental Film", the lead track on "The Spine", I almost started to Believe. Quick and poppy in all the ways that I've known They were capabable of, with lyrics that reminded me of a John Linnell of times past, I was almost about to get my hopes up.   And then, just as I expected, just as I was sure traffic would be horrible on the ride home (which it was), They lost me. "Spine" was 30 seconds I could have better spent stubbing my toe. "Memo To Human Resources" was a song I was already familiar with from their EP, and while possessing some clever lyrics, it possesses not much else after a couple of listens. And then, "Wearing A Raincoat" which just didn't work. On their earlier albums, I could tolerate such weirdness (the insane "Absolutely Bill's Mood" comes to mind) because those songs served as interesting buffers, quick breaths of air (well, nitrous maybe) between moments of pure genius, but on an album that was already dead after one song, it needed some serious defribulation, not this. "Prevenge"? Sometimes I wonder why Flans is still allowed to write songs for this band. Most times I wish he would just stop. Rhythm guitar, fine. Back up vocals, fine. Songsmith? Once upon a time, but no more.  Moment of truth... I skipped the last few unbearable seconds of "Prevenge" to get to "Thunderbird". "Any minute now," I thought, "they're gonna rock it." And I waited, and I tapped my fingers on the steering wheel and I bobbed my head. And then, the song was over. I felt like a teenager lying next to his girlfriend after they had just had sex for the first time. "Well, it wasn't  bad ... it just, wasn't what I expected." A song with so much potential, so many years spent waiting for a properly recorded version, and then... this whimpy, out of breath delivery... sigh. The voice in my head I had been carefully ignoring was saying quite loudly now, "You should have known better, you fool."  "Bastard Wants to Hit Me" was enjoyable, but with the annoying synth on John L's voice, I can't see myself playing this over and over. "The World Before Later On" is probably Flansy's least offensive offering in years, which is to say, I was able to listen to the whole song (it's not even 2 minutes long) without cringing the whole way through.  And so it comes to what I feel is probably They Might Be Giant's best song in nearly 20 years, "Museum of Idiots". There is not much I can put into words to describe how good I think this song is, from the lyrics to the instant-grin factor of the catchy melody. I can say with all seriousness that if TMBG never wrote and recorded another song, this one could stand as triumphant finish for their 20 year long career. As soon as the song finished, I was still smiling, but felt sad for just a moment when I realized that this probably  will  be the last great song they ever compose as a band. As hit or miss and sketchy as they've been in since 1996, I can't possibly see them ever topping this song.   The rest of the album isn't even really worth mentioning. After "Museum of Idiots", you could stop listening and not miss a thing. "Broke In Two" would have been better served as a replacement for one of the earlier songs on the first half of the album, but even as it is somewhat catchy in it's pseudo new-wave poppiness, it can't sustain itself surrounded by such horrible messes as "Damn Good Times" and the ridiculous mess that is "Stalk Of Wheat". Finishing up the album ("I Can't Hide From My Mind") is another Flansburgh failing, in which he manages to waste a fantastic opening verse on his indulgence in cheesy lounge-esque crap.   In a way, I'm glad I own the album. I would have paid $15 just to have "Museum of Idiots", and it's nice to have "Experimental Film" as kind of a b-side bonus. But in all other ways, I'm sitting here in the disappointment that almost seemed to be inevitable. After the travesty of "Mink Car", I swore I'd never buy another one of Their albums. "Museum" proved me a liar, but that song is so good it almost has to be an accident, and so with that I can fairly confidently say that my 15 year long love affair with this band is finally drawing to a close.    They built this whole neighborhood Out of wood, out of wood I guess I'll still be around When they burn, burn it down I will be standing around when They burn it down Here in the museum of idiots 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weather is quality southeastern July, brutal humidity punctuated by sporadic but intense late-afternoon or evening thunderstorms. I once was a Summer person, but now I'm Fall. To hell with this rainforestness.  I'm up to ~6000 words for my story/book/thing. I've now spent more time on it than any other single piece of writing that was not work/school related. Jynxed!   Review of new TMBG album coming soon... 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Most Memorable Shows Attended:    Summer of 1992  - Flood Zone (Richmond, VA) - They Might Be Giants  Summer of 1993  - N-Sect Club (Hampton, VA) - Face to Face, NOFX  Summer of 1994  - Flood Zone (Richmond, VA) - Rancid, Avail  Fall of 1995  - Flood Zone (Richmond, VA) - They Might Be Giants  Winter of 1996  - Twisters (Richmond, VA) - Less Than Jake  Summer of 1997  - Shafer Court, VCU (Richmond, VA) - Skeleton Key  August, 22, 1997  - Birchmere (Alexandria, VA) - Moxy Fruvous  November 2, 1997  - JMU (Harrisonburg, VA) - Lincoln, They Might Be Giants  November 10, 1997  - Flood Zone (Richmond, VA) - Travis, Ben Folds Five  July 30, 1998  - Birchmere (Alexandria, VA) - Moxy Fruvous  Summer of 1998  - Twisters (Richmond, VA) - Sense Field, Jimmy Eat World, The Promise Ring  July 26, 1998  - 9:30 Club (Washington, DC) - Neil Finn  June 20, 1999  - 9:30 Club (Washington, DC) - Ben Folds Five  Winter of 1999  - Twisters (Richmond, VA) - Jimmy Eat World  April 30, 2000  - Mayo Island (Richmond, VA) - Guster, Ben Folds Five  April 13, 2001  - Alley Katz (Richmond, VA) - J Mascis and the Fog  November 2, 2001  - Millhiser Gym, UR (Richmond, VA) - The Prom, Hey Mercedes, Burning Airlines, New End Originals, Death Cab For Cutie  October 5, 2002  - Alley Katz (Richmond, VA) - Quruli, John Vanderslice, The Dismemberment Plan  May 30, 2004  - Alley Katz (Richmond, VA) - The Fire Theft  I'm a little fuzzy on some of the dates, even the ones I was able to find on the Web, but overall it's is pretty accurate. What's missing from this list are tons of local shows I went to throughout late middle school and high school (Inquisition, Pee Tanks, Fun Size, Uphill Down, Algebra One, to name the best of the lot) ... they were in many ways every bit as memorable, but mostly as an aggregate memory - no one particular show stands out above any other. Also, I doubt this is  all  of the best shows I've ever been to... but it's enough for now. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alcohol effectively destroys short-term memory for brief periods of time, and can cause serious damage to it after prolonged abuse. This does me no good whatsoever. I need an effective strategy for eliminating select pieces of my long-term memory. Some kind of futuristic, Isaac Asmovian "memory scalpel" that can quickly and painlessly remove whole blocks related structures of memory from my consciousness while leaving everything else perfectly intact. The gaps left behind from such a procedure could be reclaimed by the brain, like empty sectors on a hard-drive. Maybe older, less well-remembered memories could be promoted from the dustier parts of my mind and stored in those freshly cleaned and scoured gaps. I could remember with better clarity, the summers in elementary school, riding bikes everywhere and the novelty of Nintendo, or maybe those trips down to Panama City Beach and the go-carts and the fireworks. It sounds like a great idea, to me, though it's obviously something that could very easily be abused. And of course, it's probably impossible. But to be able to see her on the street, and not know her from the next random passerby, to have all these sad splinters removed from my head, to not ever again be able to even think about her... I sometimes wonder what I would give for that. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Books Read:    "Harry Potter and the Globlet of Fire" - J. K. Rowling "Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix" - J. K. Rowling "Microserfs" - Douglas Coupland "Girlfriend in a Coma" - Douglas Coupland "Hey Nostradamus!" - Douglas Coupland     DVD's Watched:    Aliens 3 (Special Edition) Aqua Teen Hunger Force Vol 1 (Disc 1) Peter Gabriel - Growing Up Live What Dreams May Come The Simpsons Season 4 (Discs 1 and 2 w/commentary)     CD's Listened To (mostly while reading):    "Glass Floor" - Maritime "Her Majesty" - The Decemberists "To Bury Within the Sound" - Engine Down "Led Zeppelin IV" - Led Zeppelin "Onward Quirky Soldiers" - Chomsky "Who's Next" - The Who "The Sea and the Bells" - The Rachel's     Number of Words Written for Story:    615   And that is what I've accomplished in the last 7 days.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Clean sheets mean a lot To a guy who sleeps on the floor   Work productivity is still high... it seems that getting things done here at the office has supplanted getting things done at home. Normally a hyperactively clean person always fighting that uphill battle against entropy, my house has, as of late, fallen into a somewhat uncontrolled chaos. There is a problem, however, with being a compulsively neat person and complaining about messiness: Normal people use an entirely different metric when evaluating cleanliness (or messiness - I guess that's a glass-half-full / half-empty issue) than do OCD-neat-freaks, like myself. For example: A few dirty dishes left in the sink instead of placed in the dishwasher is usually an inoffensive and largely ignored thing by most normal people... for those predisposed to order and tidiness, it nags and tears at us until like a three-inch splinter in the foot. So, when I say that my house is suffering from disorder and disarray, when I speak of neglect and that bathroom that badly needs cleaning, what must be remembered is that, if a regular-type-person were to survey the damage the response would likely be something to the effect of, "What the fuck are you talking about?"  My house really does need to be cleaned, though.   No, really.    Shut up.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You're not punk, and I'm telling everyone   It's really a waste of my time to sink down to their frozen and soul-less circle of indie-rock hell, but I  urlLink can't let this slide by  without comment. There's a scrawny, foolishly ideological, Descendents-t-shirt-wearing 16 year-old stuck somewhere in the back of my brain that is dying to take a shot at this, "Hey, here's a chance to really fuck with them!" In a quick span of about five seconds, I hatched this plan to submit a really smarmy and self-important record review of some new indie record, ripe with juicy amounts of pretentiousness and indie 'leetness, all of it carefully composed to fit the Pitchfork Media mold and yet completely mock it at the same time. Of course, another five seconds later, I realized how utterly stupid the whole idea was and that the people I wanted to make fun of at PFM wouldn't even get that I was trying to joke on them anyhow. It was a funny thought though, if only for the moment. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No big breakaway in routine, no variance from the grind, just the same as it ever was (this is not my beautiful house). A little Doom 3, a minor league baseball game thrown into the mix, but otherwise the flavor is the same. I'm still ruminating about getting out, though, still ready for the Big Change. Not sure when or where it will occur, but I feel like it's getting closer - I caught a whiff of it last week (it smells like humid summer air right before a storm hits) and again this week. Maybe all that it means is that I'm about to explode into a purple-ish white ball of charged energy and leave a flinchingly loud clap of thunder in my place.  That  would be something different. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Oh let the sun beat down upon my face, stars to fill my dream I am a traveler of both time and space, to be where I have been   My productivity at work has reached an all-time high - I'm ripping through lines of code, stored procedures and subroutines like a coke-addict running late. Everything else has become jokeless punchline; weeks-old broken guitar strings, empty refrigerator, hard-water stains growing in the bathroom. It's this lifeless routine I've fallen into: work, booze, sleep, repeat. Definitely time to snap out of it and reacquaint myself with reality - stop living in this tiny, single-function world. Surviving is not living, or at least, it's a spartan version of it with not much color or texture. I think I'm about ready for something different. I think. 
    
</post>


</Blog>