<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Employees at certain companies are blogging about work because their employers view it as good marketing. The idea driving this train is that the brand community becomes stronger. I have a few reservations about this concept.  One, for some companies this could work nearly as promised. Users of the company's products will enjoy the interaction afforded by the blog. What about insurance companies? How many policy holders want to read the thoughts and musings of a claims clerk? An insurance agent? An actuary?  Two, most companies will need to establish guidelines and boundaries. Everybody knows Micro$osft is working on a OS code name Longhorn. What about Longhorn's successor? Or an OS that controls your kitchen appliances? Micro$oft probably is working on those items and more; most of these ideas will never see the light of day. Do you want employees writing about them?  Three, not all these people reading and responding to the blogs are customers. Your competitors absolutely should be reading these items. When will Longhorn be released? Officially, Micro$oft says X. But if an employees writes Y, which is 1 year later than X, then would you as a retailer, the marketing manager at Bob's Generic Computer System, or a project manager at Sun want to know this information? How will your company handle such loss of sensitive information. You cannot reprimand or fire an employee for doing exactly what you said to do.  Four, success is always relative. How do you as a manager know the blog worked? How can you tell if your brand community is stronger?  We will talk about this concept more in our section on Integrated Marketing Communication, IMC, later in the semester. Also, look at the link to the Nike blog. Gawker, which runs the Nike site among others, proves a company can make money in blogging.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following story appeared on the front page of the Wall Street Journal. A Brazilian rancher understands that business practices must change to meet local customs. He also sees that ranching is more than simply selling to the local meat packer. And he is undaunted in his quest to extend his beef sales beyond the local market because he is competing with ranches in Argentina and Australia. These are the two of the top exporters for beef in the world.  Besides the Israeli market, the rancher spotted an American trend; the desire for grass-fed beef. Later in the semester, we will meet a local rancher who also saw this trend.  This is a dead on example of market orientation in action. The rancher collected information, then created and implemented a plan. As you progress through the course try to match the Brazilian rancher's actions to the marketing principles we will discuss and read.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the official blog for Marketing 3350, section 003, at Texas Tech University. Part of your participation grade will be determined by the quantity and quality of your postings. I encourage you to start threads in addition to posting comments.  Please keep the messages civil. I will delete messages that I perceive as threatening, hostile, or rude.  Your comments should be more than "ditto," or "I agree." Try to think beyond an example, and attempt to explain the example.  Please use the spell checker on the above button bar. Proof your post before publishing it as to avoid grammar errors. Nothing harms a message and affects a messenger more than a poorly written or conceived post.  Changes to the course syllabus will be posted here.  Have fun in class. Remember, the more you contribute, the better the class and the more you will get out of the course.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a great example of a solid marketing plan in action. Notice how the good doctor changes distribution over time? He starts with a pamphlet and moves into different distribution chanenls over time, and to gain more customers.  Is Rodale out to simply make as many sales as possible, or does the publishing company want something that is longer lasting? The key to that answer is found later in the article when the author discuss the internet.  Finally, what is Rodale really doing? Is it to sell books? Build a brand name? Create a community? By the end of the course, you should have a definite answer to those four questions.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Those of you who asked about the relationship between Economics, the law, and Marketing, will find this New York Times article appealing. DeBeers, one of the largest cartels, began a shift in the late 1990s from a cartel to a marketing cooperative. The firm argued that the value of its brand, which will talk about later in the course, exceeded its sales revenue. In other words, DeBeers could make more money as a label for quality diamonds than engaging in the process of mining and selling diamonds.  In its effort to become a marketing firm, the company has been settling various lawsuits filed by the US government. These suits involved various violations of the Sherman antitrust Act.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Folio, a trade journal that covers the magazine industry, features three stories about the magazine market in Canada. The articles are posted here:     urlLink Canada 1     urlLink Canada 2     urlLink Canada 3      As you read these stories, you should be thinking about chapters 2 through 4 from your text book. What strategy are Canadian publishers using to compete against the titles from the lower 48? To answer the strategy element, think about the 5 Ps.  Communication used to be intensely localized. With the advances in technology during the last 50 years, the United States successfully exports Levis, Marlboros, Hollywood, and now Information. What effect does that have on other countries such as Canada?  If Time, Sports Illustrated, and People sell strongly in Saskatchewan, then will those titles appear in England? Why or why not?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday's Wall Street Journal carried two stories that develop at the intersection of haute couture and marketing. In the first article,  urlLink which appears here , Wal-Mart's private label, George, is not meeting industry expectations. In Marketing, many professionals examine the congruence, or fit, between a brand and a product. Wal-Mart appears to have congruence issues. Do consumers think that Wal-Mart offers affordable, trendy clothes?  Wal-Mart could be taking on H-M, a European retailer that has successfully exported its model of ever-changing fashions geared to families. George, which was a European label, may not translate as well. Also, George just may not appeal to Wal-Mart's rural demographics? After all, H-M has stayed primarily on the East Coast and IKEA, another European retailer, has opened two stores outside of the coasts.  In the second article,  urlLink which appears here , bags are the next women's THING to be surprised along with homes and SUVs. Do these bags match women's lifestyle, or do they enable women's lifestyle? A subtle question, but with different answer for managers at Coach, L.L. Bean, and Gucci.  Perhaps designers saw how women used backpacks in college. Backpacks are not the most feminine article, and I doubt many would pay over $400 for it. An all-leather bag from Coach with roughly the same volume is a different matter.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two stories from the New York Times illustrate two points. First, stories about marketing appear outside business publications or pages because these stories were printed in the Times' Art section. Second, non profit organizations face the same strategic challenges as its for-profit brethren.   urlLink In the first story , the City's more famous museums are struggling with shows. Specifically, their exhibits fail to resonate with patrons. The Whitney has struggled almost since the day its doors opened with its shows. The Guggenheim is interesting, but its strategy seems more concerned with the satellite museum that opened in Spain along with its Las Vegas presence. More showmanship than show.  The Museum of Modern Art, or MOMA, drew new breath by moving across the river to Queens. It is set to open a new space in Manhattan. But there is little doubt that MOMA has found a regained sense of purpose in its move. But is it worth the price of admission?  And then there is the Met. A patron can feel the history weighing down on his very essence when he walks through the august building that abuts Central Park. Yet the Met lacks a symmetry to its exhibits. Why are they there?  Except for MoMA, I have been to the other three museums mentioned in the story. The Whitney is confused. The Guggenheim tries too hard; although, the Mapplethrope exhibit was disturbing but top notch. The Met could stand a good editor.  What are the overarching problems with the museums? Almost all of them have issues related to the 5 Ps. People in this story goes to the consumer (the patron) and the executive boards but not the artists. Interesting.  The Times piece fails to mention another issue that has could become a greater problem in the future. There are so many niche museums in the City. The Tranist Museum was great, and it is has improved since its remodeling.  There is a children's museum, a firefighters' museum, the Tenement Museum in the lower Eastside. And we have not even mentioned all the art galleries and attractions like the Bronx Zoo and the Aquarium and the USS Intrepid and Central Park. Are these museums and other attractions chasing too few dollars or too little time from patrons?   urlLink The second story  relates to value. How do nonprofits deliver more value for the dollar? Especially when the price of admission is free. For profits are coming to grips as this  urlLink Wall Street Journal story  reports.  By creating value does the city theatre project violate its original mission? If so, why is that important? Think back to Chapter 2 and the role of mission within the creation of marketing strategy. How should this project proceed?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend who worked for Ford, and whose dad toiled at GM, said Detroit could never wean itself from consumer rebates, which started in the late 1970s, and dealer incentives, which started almost the day the first independent dealership opened.  Although GM and Ford offer increasingly larger incentive packages, several name plates like Honda and Toyota have so far resisted the pressure. Honda did offer discounts on Civics and Toyota occasionally uses the sales & promotion trick on close out models. Otherwise, the Japanese name plates simply do not raise sticker price for the upcoming model year, or lower it in several instances.  Which strategy is Detroit following? Which strategy are the Japanese using? Think about the July 12 lecture. We discussed the difference between promotion and price in one of our examples.  How has DiamlerChrysler avoided the path walked by Ford and GM? The underlying assumption is that consumers will perceive Chrysler as a European brand given its parent. Is that a good assumption?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      J.C. Penny’s scored strong sales growth in the late 1980s and early 1990s with its private labels such as Strafford men's dress line, Hunt Club collection of casual clothing, and Arizona Jean Company. However, quality suffered and sales dropped. How much did Penny’s acquisition of Eckerd’s hurt the company's focus on its private label lines?    Now, the Plano, Texas, wants to reinvigorate the brand, but not necessarily reposition it. How will Levi’s and Wrangler’s respond? Will those labels bolster relations with retailers that lack private labels such as Kohl’s? Given the competitive pressures from Kohl’s along with Target, Sears, Wal-Mart, and Gap among others, should Penny’s management spend another amount of its company’s resources on Arizona Jean Company?    I think the decline in quality will prove hard to overcome. Customers fled to mass retailers like Foleys, specialty stores like Eddie Bauer, and discounters like Target. Penny’s faces a daunting but not an impossible task in getting those customers back to these anchor stores. I do not think those retailers will let Penny’s take its new customers away without a fight.    Penny’s should drop quietly its private labels and concentrate its resources on better relationships with manufacturer labels and end customers. Does that make Penny’s too close to Kohl’s?  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As part of 1996's Telecom Deregulation Act, Congress required local phone companies such as Verizon and SBC to open its telephone networks to competitors. The act set the rates, which were far below market value according to the local phone companies.   A judge ruled last week that the FCC lacked the authority to enforce the rate structure. Local phone companies could determine the price that AT&T, Sprint, MCI, and smaller telephone companies would pay to run local phone calls over the networks. In the past few days, there has been a rash of articles detailing how phone companies are responding.    urlLink In this Wall Street Journal story , many of the companies are raising fees. MCI, for example, increased fees on 18 plans. Why does MCI have 18 plans? Actually, the company formerly known as WorldCom offers more calling plans. This represents a gross inefficiency and suggests that MCI managers are not stewarding the company's resources to the best of its ability.   AT&amp;T has announced it will no longer seek residential customers. Qwest, a local telephone service provider in the Midwest, will execute a print campaign to poach current AT&T residential service customers according to  urlLink this New York Times story .    As we will discuss later in customer relations management, there are occassions when we do not want a customer or a group of customers. Rivals to Verizon, Qwest, Bell South, and SBC may have a pricing point when they no longer want local residential customers.   Of course, local phone service may become moot. Despite AT&amp;T's waffeling over its Voice Over Internet Protocol, or VOIP, cable companies are quickly adding the service to its customers.  urlLink This New York Times article  questions AT&T's decision because VOIP could provide a better competitive advantage against local telephone providers.   When the 1996 Telecom Deregulatin Act became law, its framers, industry lobbyist one and all, could not have foreseen the techonological changes. In less than 5 years, the local telephone service providers will not be Verizon, Bell South, SBC, and Qwest; rather, they will be Comcast, Time-Warner, and Cox.   That prediction assumes that a form of KaZaa will not destroy the pricing structure of the market. In  urlLink this Wall Street Journal article , Skype relies on similar software that powers KaZaa to emulate a telephone network. As of this writing, the difference between Skype's service and those offered by Verizon, AT&amp;T, and Vonage looks like price. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Clear Channel, the nation's largest chain of radio stations, made two significant announcements. In the first,  urlLink posted here , the San Antonio based company will limit the number of commercial time. In one market, advertising breaks were reduced from 16 to 12 minutes. However, the article does not mention whether this will include house advertisements. In other words, will the station reduce its clutter? Also, where will the reduction occur? During the morning and evening drive time? For all day parts?  In the second story,  urlLink posted here , Clear Channel will spend $100 million over 10 years to test the feasibility of digital radio. The technology promises to deliver stronger, clearer signals.  Neither article really mentions the force behind these actions. XM and Sirius have achieved enough subscriber mass for Clear Channel to perceive the two satellite operators as competitive threats. Although XM and Sirrius carry commercial stations, its competitive advantage comes from a commercial-free service with a sound quality perceived as superior to FM or AM stations.  Are Clear Channel’s two strategies examples of sustainable competitive advantages? Will these decisions make its time inventory more desirable to media buyers and marketing strategists? 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At least $25 million later, the University at Buffalo cannot out draw high school football teams in Texas. The opportunity cost stagger the mind when considering UatB's bonfire to the vanities, a Division I-A football team at a public university in New York.  Think about the July 19 lecture. What is UatB really selling? What are they marketing? Is the core football group large enough to support a Division I-A team? Do the schools that also suffer from low attendance face the same problems as Buff? These are not hypothetical questions. This is a real problem with real consequences.  Buff's sister institution, Binghamton, spent a ton of money on its men's hockey program. Binghamton plays to sell out crowds and attracts top flight hockey recruits. University at Albany upgraded its men's and women's basketball program. University at Stony Brook is building up its men's lacrosse and basketball teams. I would argue that those three institutions better spent its money when using service marketing as the criteria.  How is UatB trying to improve its crowds for the 2004 season? How are these efforts different than 2003?  I think Buff would have been better off giving every incoming student $1000 just for enrolling. That would be a better use of the money that has been thrown down the hole known as Division I-A football.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      About two years ago, I advised a chain of weekly newspapers in southern New York and northern New Jersey about putting together a web site. As part of that process, I scoured web sites from different stripes of newspapers and other media outlets such as radio and television.  It quickly became apparent that newspaper web sites were achingly dull. Their presentation was horrific; the content limp. There were a few web sites here and there that offered some nice surprises. But the good stuff was found outside of mainstream media's domain. Where was the interactivity? Where was the feature that kept me hitting reload every hour? The alternate papers were the worse about it. A feeling of be happy we put the content out there pervades these web efforts.  Few industries are more market oriented than media especially print journalism. Why then are blogs and home grown web sites the places to go? I am not talking about content, but interactivity. When companies - newspapers, television stations, magazines included - launch a web site, it neglects what it is really doing. A web site launch should be treated like a new product launch.  We will discus new product launch on Monday, July 19. But you should be familiar with the steps of creating a new product, the various types of new product, and the diffusion process. When a company launches a web site, what type of a new product is it?  By not treating a web site for what it is, a new product, explains why so many horrible web sites exist in this world.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When the Atari 2600 and the Intelivision video game systems roamed the Earth (circa 1981), boys accounted for nearly 9 out of 10 console and cartridge buyers. As hard core gamers moved from the consoles to the Commodore 64 and Apple IIe computers, boys continued to account for 90% of game title sales. Where were the girls?   In this Wall Street Journal article, the title sellers and the console manufacturers may have ignored the girl market at its peril. Females prefer to play more low key games. Sony and Micro$oft may have poured money down a hole convincing boys to play games on line.   We talked Thursday, July 15, about the consequences of targeting the wrong market. Ford's Mustang survived the company's target market miscue. What should Sony and Micro$oft do?   For these companies and the software titles like Electronic Arts, the market leader, and Sega, a fading star, women playing online could bring a needed product shift. Critics say that games are predictable, pedantic, and trite. The titles offer nothing new as far as gaming experience.   The women were there all along. Now, will the software people be there too?
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Fellow student Avery Cowan submitted a link, which appears in the title, about advertisers' attempts to cut through clutter.     This article explains how advertising affects people’s daily lives.  We  see advertisements at the store, in the home, and on the street.    Many advertisements are viewed and mentally noted without even realizing it.    The article also looks at how advertisers seek out new, untraditional ways to get people’s attention.    There is so much clutter in all advertising mediums these days that it is hard for companies and products to stand out among the others.    The article goes on to point out that it is no longer the bigger budget has the best ads, but instead the most innovative and creative ways of presenting ads that capture a person’s attention.    With advertising at an incredible high, it is easy to see how it can become an intrusion on people’s lives and daily activities.    It seems that nothing is holding advertising agencies back from figuring out the newest and best way to get into people’s minds. In closing, the article refers to the movie  Minority Report  starring Tom Cruise and what the landscape might look like in 2054.          
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have posted the rubric from the HCA case along with the SWOT we wrote in class. Please review them before submitting the SWOT and case for PapaJohn, which is due July 28 according to our syllabus.     urlLink Rubric     urlLink SWOT   Also, I returned the previous cases, NBB and Base Pro Shop, to the respective writers. They should have forwarded the case with my remarks to the rest of the group. Please review my comments as you prepare this case.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Update 07.26.04   Volkswagen announced declining profits and issued a profit warning in  urlLink this Associated Press wire story . VW blamed everything but the obvious for slowing sales in North America and Europe. Namely, the German manufacturer needs to reposition the Jetta and the Golf.  Toyota's attempts to woo Generation Y buyers have missed the mark so far in  urlLink this New York Times article . The second largest carmaker will drop the slow selling Celica and MR2. The Scion's first two vehicles, xA and xB, have inched off the sales line. The problem bedeviling the Scion also bit Honda with the Element.   End   When Toyota was designing its first Lexus vehicle, the engineers poured through junkyards across Europe, the United States and Japan. They looked at how cars aged. What pieces broke? What equipment fell apart? The results were in subtle but appreciated touches.   For example, fabric seam was across the seat. For the Lexus, engineers stretched the leather across the seat and stitched on the side. This meant the seat would last longer, and Lexus has been atop almost every customer satisfaction survey since its introduction. Toyota showed it was adept at understanding competitive intelligence.   As a side note, David Halberstam wrote an exhaustive, and illuminating account of the automobile industry called Reckoning. To understand how Japanese nameplates thrashed the American, look at how Nissan stayed with its market orientation strategy even when sales were terrible.   In this Wall Street Journal article, Chevrolet appears hopelessly stuck in its product orientation. The Cobalt lacks the buzz of the Scion, the angles of the Focus, the longevity of the Civic. In short, it is another piece of Chevy metal.   If I were running Chevy, I would pour through every junkyard looking at Jettas. I would listen to every Jetta owner. I would read every Jetta web site. Why? Because the Jetta is over priced, satisfaction as a measure of quality is dropping, and sales have slowed to an inch worm's pace. This is a great time for a rival to knock down Volkswagen while the German car builder struggles with its own self inflicted wounds.   If Chevy could out Jetta VW, then it would be the small car sales leader and not the Koreans or the Japanese. Of course, to accomplish that objective requires Chevy become a market oriented company and that barrier may prove too high. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fellow student Rachel Griffin submitted the following comments  Wal-Mart executes a nearly perfect marketing strategy, which is hard to beat. But is that good for the welfare of our country? I think Wal-Mart is an example of too much marketing. They enjoy a competitive advantage with all the 5 Ps are in place, but they ignore what society needs in favor of profits. I think the government should step in and prevent this from happening.  The US government took similar action against Microsoft. Why not Wal-Mart? The laws against monopolies don’t apply to Wal-Mart but soon they will. And small towns across the nation have unemployment rates through the roof because very few retailers can compete. Isn’t that a monopoly?  Wal-Mart’s CEO earned $1.2 million in salary and $4.2 million in bonus while at the same time they won’t pay their hourly employees a few hours of overtime. In her book “Nickel and Dimed: On Not Getting By in America,” Barbra Ehrenreich went to work at Wal-Mart and struggled to make ends meet. She had more than the average worker with a car and $1,000 for emergencies and no children. If she couldn’t do it, what makes anyone think an average wage worker can?  Wal-Mart is going to be the decline of our country because they have a strong competitive advantage. Shouldn’t there be federal intervention against this kind of company? Isn’t it the government’s responsibility to protect the impoverished people of the nation? Didn’t anyone see this coming?   urlLink This New York Times article  presents more commentary on Wal-Mart. This web site,  urlLink Wal-Mart Watch , also provides links to information about the company.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We reached the end of our class. And I am happy. We put a lot into the course and, based on your comments, y'all got a lot out of it. I know I did.  By today, I felt exhilarated because I taught something of value and meaning. I saw several instances from almost everyone that you took ownership of the lessons and made the knowledge yours. That is pretty powerful.  Some general comments about the grades and your feedback:  Grades: They are posted. I set a personal record for the percentage of students who earned As and Bs. Prior to this class, around 25% earned As and 30% or so earned Bs. As I wrote on the board, your total reflects 34 bonus points, which is a lot given the overall grade distribution. I am pretty comfortable with the grades for this summer.  Participation Points: I gave credit if you showed up to class, turned in exercises and SWOTs, and said something during the past month. You cannot participate if you are not in class. It is that simple. I then went to the blog to look for more participation points. Most of you maxed out the 50 points, and a lot of you got 40+. I really liked the level of participation, and tried to give all of you as many methods of contributing. Looking at your comments, most of you took advantage of these methods.  Power Point: A lot of you like the slides. Your comments reflect my lack of appreciation for this technology. At the start, I said this was my first teaching experience with Power Point. I am not completely convinced I should keep it, or scrap it. I will give it another try; yes, I will slow down.  Cases & SWOTs: Many of you wanted a clearer direction in terms of writing cases. Not a problem! I try to balance student creativity with instructor's demand. I will keep working on that balance.  Blog: I probably would have scrapped the blog idea. In reading your comments, I gathered that most of you were reading at least twice a week. Like other items, I will retain this idea and refine it.  Finally, thank you for the time and effort. The course required a lot of work and time. Y'all more than met the challenge; you succeeded. I could not ask for more than that.  Have a good summer.  cheers, Michael
     

    
</post>


</Blog>