<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I make no bones about it, i hate clowns.  Anyone who knows me knows this.  I feel they are alcoholic child molesters.  They need to hide behind that white makeup and a haze of nasty cigarette smoke for something involving pure evil.  Now there is a major distinction between me and a clownophobe.  I am not afraid of them, just hate em.  I would punch one right in the face if I needed to (Legally..this would be in the case I was in clear and present danger, which is pretty much 100% of the time that a clown is present, they eat children you know).  But clownaphobes, man they got it bad.  I know 2 people that will get anxiety attacks just talking about clowns, now that is some funny stuff.  One of them, when she was young, spent the night over a friends, and the friend had clown figurines in her room.  My friend insisted that they could not sleep in that room, so they slept out in the living room. www.clownz.com and www.ihateclowns.com, join the movement, fight the grease-painted ones.....                 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate going to the gym.  It's like doing fake work.  I can lift this thing up and down, don't accomplish a darned thing, go home a little stinkier than normal.  At least if I went home and lifted one of my dogs up and down, something would be accomplished, real work would be done, Ernie would get to see life from a slightly elevated perspective.  Ernie is 60 pounds and over 10 years old, but I think he would enjoy the new experience.  Goldie on the other hand, would cry like a freshly beaten red headed step child, and DFAX would be on their way over to investigate the sounds of child torture.  I hate going to the gym.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i decided to take a walk over lunch, all the way to the bank, then stop for a bite to eat, then make it back in time for a media interview (I am telling you this so that you will be impressed with how seemingly important I am).  Is about a 3 mile round trip.  I stop at the Chinese, Japanese and now Thai diner.  I order the sesame cold noodles (with peanuts).  It was very good, in fact I am still eating them (with a now garnishment of vending machine M&Ms.  But... where are the sesame seeds?  Nowhere, that's where.   And it is not like you can complain, because with all that walking i needed refills on water, and if you complain, your water may have a little extra something special in it.  Anyway, still good noodles, but a hole is felt from the missing whereabouts of my sesame seeds.  What was the fortune from my cookie you ask?  "What does not destroy you makes you stronger".  I always thought it was "kill", although "destroy" is so much funnier.  It brings to mind limbs being blown off and muscle hanging out and stuff.  Still trying to figure out how i can be stronger after that.  I kinda get the feeling that I am going for the handicapped sticker after such destruction.  Toodles.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings and all that crap.  Since everyone including Jimmy Hoffa has a blog, I thought, "hey...whatever".  No really, I actually had that thought.  I really don't have a thought to share at this moment except for 'does everyone reading this (me) believe that the world is halfway to hell, being delivered to its underworld overlord in the carefully crafted wicker handbasket?'  I could understand our current situation if there was something really important to destroy the world over, like, if some tv network tried to bring back "Alf".  But really, are we this dang stupid?  Discuss amongst yourselves.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All I need is not a whole lot when you look at the big picture.  In order to meet my goal (and don't "they" always tell us we need goals?) i just need a butt wad of money.  I know what you are thinking (I am a little psychic).  You are thinking "yea, don't we all?".  But you are wrong.  If most people had a butt wad of money (including you, yes I am talking to you) you would just tinkle it away.  I however would do great things, like quit my job, and like...get a bigger TV, and yea, I would probably help the homeless somehow.  But just giving them money is not the answer, I mean come on, they'll just spend it on smack and booze.  I am still working on that one.  Anywho, I don't have children, and am average smart.  I wear 5 dollar 'pluma' shirts from Sam's Club for goodness sakes!  I would invest the butt wad wisely, so as to 'live off the interest', which if you have not guessed it already (not psychic), living off the interest is my goal.  Remember "they" tell us we gotta have them, and I cannot think of a more noble and and less hostile goal to have.  Just think about it, there would be one less person out there bitching about life.  Now, couldn't the world benefit from one less person bitching about something?  So, for world peace's sake, for the homeless's sake, send me money!            
     
    
</post>


</Blog>