<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Meh I didn't do an entry for yesterday so I'll do it right now. Hm... interesting day, talked on the phone to Dylan for like the entire day. Chad was trying to get through for like the whole night cept my phone was busy hahah.... cept as I said to Dylan, hes a lot more interesting to talk to than Chad because he actually listens to what I'm saying instead of ignoring me.  Then when I called Chad he was all "I've been trying to call you all night, your phone was busy, who were you talking to?"...."Dylan..."........Then I kinda got pissed off at Chad.. oops but thats cause he was like yeah we're going to the lake tomorrow morning. Oh really kinda like, so now I wont see him till like monday and only then if I'm lucky. And hes all lets go see a movie on monday, okay. I aint getting my hopes set on that cause in all likelyhood it wont happen. And then I was kinda like well your away but I'm like busy the next 2 days anyways. And hes like oh what are you doing... well tomorrow (meaning today in here lol) I'm going swimming... oh who with.... jess and mark and dylannn....you know I hate dylan and mark... yeah well they're my friends... and hes all well if you knew them you'd know why they arn't popular.. and I was like, well I'm not popular either and hes like yeah you are, no, and then he was like well you have me which is just as good. yup.....(I used to think so but lately...erg). Then he's like well what are you doing on thursday, going to the zoo.... why go to the zoo it sucks (this is why I didn't try and see if he wanted to go to the zoo with me), who are you going with...... dylan...(notice a pattern) I think.. he might feel like Dylan's taking over me but you know what, dylan is just a friend and when Chad makes no effort to get together with me then I'm going to make plans with my friends and those ppl include Dylan and he kind happens to be the one that's not busy most of the time lol.  Also picked up our report cards yesterday, didn't do badly, (90 in social, 82 in gym, 83 in math, 86 in science, 78 in french, 78 in l.a., 69 in art)... my dad didn't say much but he usually doesn't, he wasn't mad about art at least, (I was kinda worried about that one... worst mark I got in 3 years at that school.. true by one percent but still.)... Yeah we had to go in for an assembly... it was a really good thing cause Holly was getting her nose peirced last night, was going to at the assembly so she wasn't crying or anything which would have made everyone else cry, so that was kinda good.   Oh well.... but yeah so we're supposed to go to the pool but jess can't make it in time so we were going to take the lrt but her mom wont let her! how stupid is that, my parents would let me ride it alone and she's going to be with 3 other ppl, we don't even have to change trains it just brings us straight there... soo stupid. It's like last year when I wanted her to go to the labour day game with me and she could except then she couldn't because we were going to walk home after the game! meh her mom is wayyyyyy tooo overprotective of jess... wayyyy too.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was fun....  Basically the highlight of my day was that when I got up I made chocolate chip pancakes for breakfast... they were soo good! Yeahhh then I sat on my computer for like the entire day.   Talked to Aaron and he's like all depressed and shit and it really isn't a good thing. Aww I felt so bad and whatever I said didn't help anything. Then he like cam online at like 2 in the morning his time and was like... "couldnt sleep, im sorry, I didnt been to blow up at you. I love you." aw it was sweet. And yeah that sounds so bad because I have Chad.   Meh... Chad got his frame back so now both his bikes are working which means what little time he had for me before will now be taken up and the chances of me like ever seeing him are so small. Ugh he was being stupid today... when I got the chance to talk to him he like hardly talked at all and shit and right now, as it stands, I'm thinking about breaking up with him and thats bad. I mean I have so much fun and stuff WHEN we get together and shit but he like never even trys to make an effort to call me even when I like call him and shit and then hes just like "oh do you wanna do something and im all like yeah and then hes like oh no wait I cant. and its like WTF if your gonna ask you dont just then go no nvm all the time, just things like that that really piss me off.  I mean maybe it would be best to just break up with him... one less thing for him to think about, not that he seems to think about me anyways, then he could just go biking whenever the fuck he wanted and he wouldnt ever have a girlfriend that he had to see. I donno... I aint gonna do anything yet, wait till I can talk to Melissa. Maybe I'll call her tomorrow or sumtin or maybe today... I donno I need to think about shit first before.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So supper was good. We had subs and stuff... lol then we played air hockey and pool and had the cake that my dad had baked for my mom for her birthday but because she felt really crappy on her birthday we didn't bring it for her.. plus she cant eat foods so we brought it and we ate that which was yummyness.  Then because my brother was being an ass I had to take the dog for a walk even though it's his turn to take her, plus I have to take her for a long walk tomorrow during the day because no one else is going to be home...but then again that can be a good thing because I'll have the house all to myself for most of the day and I can do basically whatever I want to do.   I'm debating whether to call chad.. because it's really likely that hes biking and I don't want to call him when hes biking. And if he was home he would probably be on the computer which would mean he would be on MSN which he isn't. Meh I wont... I don't wanna see like I have to call him all the time, if he wants to talk he'll call me, and if he doesn't well then he wont call... which no... it doesn't bug me.. well it does to the extent that I would like to talk to him but he yeah I don't know... It's another one of those things that make sense in my head but not when I try and put them into words.  So tomorrow I really should clean my room... I didn't exactly do that today... meh.. if the oppertunity comes to do something more interesting I aint cleaning lol.   Apparently I'm going to see the third happy potter on friday with a bunch of people... hmm I don't know, could be fun though... better than sitting at home and doing nothing thats for sure. But with my luck I'll commit to that and it will be the one day that Chad will be free to do something... but he has to know that I'm not free all the time and I aint going to drop everything for him just because he's my boyfriend... Plus he certainly doesn't do that for me.   Yesterday Meredith's grandma had her 75th birthday and yeah it was at Meredith's house and some lady said to Meredith about this really ugly pot that she like loved it and if she could buy it off of Meredith! And she asked Meredith how much to buy it and Meredith was like... I donno um maybe 5 bucks? And the lady paid for it... I wanna do that! lol.. make money off of some of the pots I make! That would be so awesome! And it's not like I need all the pots.. It's not even close to needed them all.. I don't even like use them, they're basically for decoration pretty much... And then theres the really ugly ones that end up in the box in my closet but that's okay! At least I don't make as many ugly pots anymore.. they're getting wayyy better!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You know what's sad? The fact that I woke up 45 minutes ago and I'm like already bored out of my mind. Thats just like not good. At least I slept in tho.. ppl didn't wake me up which is really good cause if they had I would have been incredibly pissed off.  Ughhh... my brother just came home all pissed off at his friend because his friend wanted to play Risk and Anders didn't want to. God thats fucked... now they'll be like pissed at each other for like a week and I'm gonna have to sit through Anders talking about his "problems" because my mom isn't here to listen to them... dammit!  I'm thinking that it woulf be fun to paint a room right now... maybe our front entry, cause my mom has wanted to do that for like a year and she already bought the paint... I could do that for her so when she gets home it's all done... except I don't think my dad would let me do that until I clean my room because he would prolly want me to do that more than paint, and painting would just give him more of a mess to clean up. So maybe... I should clean my room today and then it would be done and I wouldn't have my dad yelling at me to and then he'd like leave me alone... maybe I'll go do that now. Cept not RIGHT now cause I like need to wake up a little more first... no okay I just don't feel like it at this very moment... I'll go in a little bit just not right now.   I wanna play The Sims... but I have to get off the comp soon cause my bro is gonna kick me off so by the time it loads and I start playing I'm gonna have to get off the comp anyways... man I can't wait till the Sims 2 comes out... in september... why couldnt they have released it in the summer cause then yeah everyone could have played it a lot more. Meh... at least this way I wont be completely hooked on just doing that for the entire summer. So maybe it is a good thing that it isn't being released in the summer. But I'm prolly going to spend just as much time on the comp doing nothing as I would have playing it... oh well maybe I'll figure something to do on the comp thats helpful... meh I'd actually have to look to find something new... right now all I do is type shit in here and surf the Student Center forums and talk to Dylan and the occasional other person on MSN.  I want someone to play ouija with... it gets kinda boring after awhile but I mean you can still spend like an entire afternoon playing it without realizing you've been playing that long.  Chads coming home tonight... maybe we'll be able to do something tomorrow... that would make the day so much less boring. But for today... it seems that I will be cleaning my room and then tonight we're going to our neighbours house for supper... which hopefully will be good, and then maybe tonight to see my mom again. It's really hard because we went to see her last night and she like has a tube down her throat draining her stomach and stuff and I don't think I've ever seen her like that down. She needs to get out of the hospital.. that's like what will make her better. Being in her own house with her animals and family around and just being away from the smells of the hospital and that room she's been in for the past like 3 weeks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First full day off.... boring lol. I babysat from like 12:30 till 3.. which was good cause now I'm not as broke as I was before.  So my dad made the decision that he's going to cancel the trip to Oregon. He knows my mom's not going to recover enough by that time and he doesn't want to go without her again. Which is fine, and I wouldn't want to go without her either, it's just too bad. He said we might go to Jasper the last week b4 my brother goes back, and just ignore how much it's going to cost and rent a nice place for a week. That would be awesome... especially Jasper, it's so pretty there.   It's too bad that we're going to miss it cause I was looking foward to it but I mean, it's a good reason why we arn't going to go, it's not like oh.. yeah lets not go or something. Well maybe I'll get to go visit melissa then.. that would be fun.  My mom's still not feeling well... on monday she will have been in the hospital for three weeks, suckky. My dad said that she said or rather wrote... that it would be okay if I came up to visit her tonight, which would be nice cause I havn't seen her since tuesday and I really miss seeing her. And it prolly wouldn't be okay for my brother to go because she has tubes down her throat to pump her stomach and he would be really freaked out to see her like that but he's going to a friends house for a sleepover at like 7 tonight so me and my dad will be able to go.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So supper was good, we had burgers...(hahahah mr. burger!) yeah it was all good... and then it started raining so we didn't go to the soccer game... well actually other ppl did when it stopped raining but I decided I wanted to come home.  We're going to someone elses house on sunday for supper apparently now too! lol... and I'm babysitting tomorrow from like 12:30 till 2:30.... it's good though cause if I can babysit for them a few times this summer I'll be able to make some money, which is awesome cause right now I have like none... none being like 30 bucks but still... not very much, I havn't babysat in such a long time... hopefully I'll get to more this summer cause I'd like some moola.  I'm tireddd it's like 10:30... that sucks... and I have to get off the comp soon or my dad will come home and like yell at me cause I was supposed to get off at 10 which is completely unfair... it's summer and I'm like almost 15 and I can't be on the comp past 10 like every night, it's so gay, oh well... at least I CAN get on the computer, plus I have it like most of during the day since I have NO life whatsoever. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yay! I'm finished my last test!... We have to go back on tuesday to get report cards and stuff but thats fine! It's all over... doesn't feel like it but it is!  So my dad was away til like 1:30... Chad came over... wasn't supposed to... but whatever... I'm getting away with it arn't I? We took the dog for a walk and stuff.. hmmm...  So I downloaded a ton of music today after Chad left, now I'm listening to that. Hmm what else...  We're going to lmy brothers friends house for a BBQ tonight... should be good, and its not like they're not nice or anything, plus Chad's going to the lake tonight anyway so it's not like I would get to see him again.  Melissa left for the campgrounds! Awww I'm gonna miss her so much.... she'll be back in three weeks for a bit but I'm going to be so bored without her to hang out with! Hopefully Jess and I can get together a few times before she goes to her dads on like the 6th of july or somthing like that.  So I figured it out, we have 73 days off school... that's like a fifth of a year... and hahah my brother has to go back to school like 3 weeks before I do! hahahah  Okay so I have to go... dad wants on the comp, I'll prolly add more later.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. holding hands 2. arm around 3. good-night kiss 4. kiss lasting over three minutes without a breath 5. open-mouth kissing 6. toungues 7. upper body fondling - outdoors 8. upper body fondling - indoors 9. below waist activity 10. the full monty (sex)  Had to put that in here... I can never find it when I want it.... and for your information.... I've been to 8....before...... 6 with Chad lol... just thought that I should share that information with you... even though you is probably no one but myself... THATS OKAY!!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay well so guys may know how to wreck your day but they also know how to make the next one pretty darn good. But I'll get to that later.  So we finished our L.A. exam... one more to go! yay! And then I was hanging around the school and my friend didn't wanna take the bus home so she came to my house for a bit and we made fries.... they were frozen fries but they were still pretty damn good! lol and then she had to go but it was all good.  And then so yeah... I called Chad and talked to him on the phone for awhile and then when my dad got home... cause he doesn't want us here by ourselves... Chad came over and yeah we hung out in the basement for a bit (i hadn't seen him in a week! so sad lol) and then well we went further than we have b4 which was awesome lol... Further being like making out but still... thats as far as I've ever been pretty much and it was pretty nice lol... and since I'm his first girlfriend... he was kinda worried or nervous I guess and yeah he was so cute about it.. and I mean I don't have a ton of expeirience or anything close to but yeah it was sweet.  And then he tells me about this dream he had... and like he was on a ship or something and there was a bomb planted in it and it blew up and he died.. but he came back as a ghost and like I could still see him and stuff but like... we couldn't like feel each other there and stuff.. man he told it better than I can but like... It made me cry... I donno it got to me... the whole him dying and I couldn't be in his arms and stuff and like I started like crying and yeah.  Then I went to Wendy's for supper... and we were supposed to go see my mom in the hospital cause it was her birthday and we were gonna bring cake and a few of her friends were gonna come but she was feeling really crappy so only my dad went. But we picked up the vase I made for her from the art studio and I filled it with flowers from her garden and gave it to my dad to bring to her... so at least she'll have something and it'll be something new for her to look at.  And you know whats even better.... Chad got the dates changed so he's going to be her efor my birthday! yay! that makes the day even that much better.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      People really know how to mess up your day don't they. In other words... Chad has decided he is going to stay with a friend for like the week of my birthday! how fucking nice s that... I'm sorry but I wouldn't go stay at a friends house for HIS birthday! ARG fuck... I was having such an awesome day too... i got like a new necklace and make-up and shit and hung out with my friend and it was like awesome and then he has to to to tell me that he is not going to be there for my birthday... like SERIOUSLY! arg stupid ppl.  On the bright side... to that I FAILED MY SOCIAL TEST! yay... not..... this day sucks balls. And then on top of that... i WAS going to go see chad this evening but I have to go visit my mom which isn't bad at all but I'm also apparently going to my dad's friends house for supper like we did just last week... I don't wanna. This day totally sucks... I just wanna go like curl up in a ball and sleep... cry do anything... I DONT KNOW I wasnt to get away from here... Its not that bad but I just wanna go on vacation or something.   We saw our french sub who was like our sub for like 3 months today coming out of our school and we said hi to him. And yeah like I said we we being our entire class failed the social provincial... I mean with Mrs. Lowe... she didn't teach us anything except shit about Rasputin and there wasn't ANY questions on him... I mean we studied him for like 5 months out of ten... thats all we did... learned about Rasputin... HE HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE CURRICULUM! oh well I don't really care... if was worth marks but...meh  Me and my friend were shopping and I was waiting for her to get sumtin and ther was this guy... and yeah he was lets just say "adjusting" himself and yeah it was funny.  Okay so I have another story.  We were in this park and just sitting there and this guy came along and I was like HI and then he layed down on a bench and I said HAVE A GOOD SLEEP and yeah he kinda waved and yeah... anyways theres these two sets of slides with 2 slides each and they're like 4 meters apart or sumtin... anyway me and my friend were laying on one of the sets of swings and then he came over and layed down on one of the other slides that was in the other set and yeah so we got kinda freaked and we walked away but before we did I was like BYE and then he said peace out but i didnt understand him so I was like... WHA? lol and he said it again and I still didn't understand but I just asked Melissa (my friend) what he said and yeah thats my story.  Oh and my brother was talking to someone but anyways apparently one of his friends whos in grade 5... like 4 years younger than me thinks im "good looking" except my brother said he actually said I'm hot... I was like EW thats not normal... but yeah.  Oh and I don't think I said... 2 months today! for how long Chad and I have been going out for... that time went by really quickly... especially the last month... jusy like WHOOSH and its gone... that time again and it'll be 3 months.... wow and its less than a month till my b-day right now which is even better.... even tho chads not going to be there.... oh well
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay seriously... do gusy ever EVER call when they say they will. For example I call my b.f he says he will call be back when he gets home... he gets home... I know cause he went on MSN... never calls at all... never even talks to me on MSN. NEWHO just had to bitch about that.  And what the hell is up with guys... all they have to do is wake up and throw on clothes... we as girls have to make ourselves look good.... IM GIVING UP... no more making myself pretty for no reason!  Oh and by the way... me and melissa have decided we are buying an island and moving there so theres no one there but we have tv and movies and internet and shit and we can olny see ppl when we want to!!!! and no one can find us!! yaayayaya
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hm.... so today I had my math test.... I think I did okay... I hope so at least, I mean I can't have done that bad... oh well  I'm supposed to be cleaning my room but I don't feel like it so I'm on the internet instead...  I fell down half of my stairs today when I was coming down here to go on the computer! I fell and yeah it hurt cause I hit my head at the bottom.  3 more exams left!!! and then I shall be freeee as a bird! lol  My mommy was supposed to come home from the hospital today but now they're saying she might be there till thursday :(... And that's her birthday too! awww....  Dylan... this guy was trying to get me to go to the pool with him today, I woulda gone but I didn't really wanna go with him, plus I thought Chad was going to be around and that I might be able to get together with him considering I havn't seen him in almost a week... OH NO! lol not really oh no but yeahh.. I gotta stop waiting around for Chad and doing other stuff cause hes usually doing something and it's boring waiting around.  Okay... so this one guy, who I used to like so so so much... anywho he was talking to someone when I was waiting for Melissa, and Jess and Holly and Brennan and all them to get out of the test (our teacher let us out early) anywho he came by and was talking to someone and he said that they had already marked his test and he got 14/50!!! Like I'm sorry but how the hell do you do that! I mean Mr. Condie (our teacher) said that if you just guessed the average mark you would get would be 7/50.... so he got double that... STILL holy crap I don't get it, and like those questions, at least most of them were not even hard at all! and even if you just got rid of the answers that were really crazy you would like HAVE to do better than that!... I'm sorry but that is just sad.  Okay so now I'm gonna type up all thats on my keychain cause it's boring not doing anything and no one is on MSN, well people are but they're not talking much. -house key -car key (no I don't have a car, I don't even know how to drive I just felt like having  car key so I took one of the many copies my mom has.) -a back to nature (a store) pocket-knife, with a little knife, nail file, tweezers, toothpick and scissors on it. -a little chain thing of those little hoop things for keychains that I found -3 hair elastics (don't ask why) and one PINK, light blue and WHITE lol -a little necklace charm thing thats the chinese symbol for the year of the snake -a Tom Tompson keychain with his painting "The Jack Pine" -a big rock bottle opener -a Charlesglen Toyota keychain -a missisippi chemical corporation keychain... one of those ones that you can like take apart! and I think thats it... I just put all these on this morning when I was waiting for my dad to take me to my exam.... I'll add more tonight and say what I did cause it's fun! lol
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      BLOG! hahaha welcome!  Oh god, today was so boring, I have like four more exams and then its summer break... except we just had a three day break and I'm already bored... this summer is gonna be boring. Oh well it's still summer!  So what did I do today.... I slept in, went on the comp, did my laundry, "cleaned" my room sorta... took the dog for a walk, wondered where everyone was cause like no one was home and yeah. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So yeah...  All those pics are from our grade nine grad. FINISHED Jr. HIGH! yay.... into high school next... I still have exams but those arnt too bad... theres one tomorrow :O.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Group pic.... Brennan, Me, Chad, Holly, Jess and Lisa.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me and Chad (boyfriend) at grad.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me (Left) and Melissa (Right) at our grade nine grad.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me before my grade nine grad.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I havn't written since since I wrote about swimming... yay new stuff to write lol.  So... on thursday (CANADA DAY WAHOO) I did nothing until I like went to a bbq at my dad's friends house.. fun fun and I talked to melissa!! yay... man I miss her... and Chad... im not gonna see him till like monday either *cries*.... theres a whole story about that too.  So you know how I said Dylan saw jess' boob... well he saw mine apparently too... when I was still underwater but w.e. lmao.  Hm.... yesterday I hung out with jess and dylan again... we went to his house and had milkshakes and stuff and, yeah then we went to macs and had slushies or frosters and suckers and stuff and hung out at the park near there for like the entire afternoon. Then it started raining and we were dancing on picnic tables in the rain in barefeet... and then there was this guy that rode by on a bike and we were all looking at him and he wiped out and yeah it was funny. And then my shoes were all wet so I walked most of the way home without shoes on, including walking across the trans canada highway without shoes on... haha... bet you there arnt many people that can say they've done that... hehe. Ummmmm what else.. then we had food for supper and I went to the hospital to visit my mommy with two of her friends. Then then after we went to Starbucks and i had a mocha frappichino and it was sooo good. And then I was like all awake for a long time.  Then I talked to Dylan on the phone from like 10-2 last night and now apparently he doesn't remember anything we talked about after like 11:30 and that was a hell of a lot of stuff.. including him saying hes starting to like jess.  Hm.... Dylan's brother is coming to visit tomorrow till wednesday and apparently I'm going swimming with them on tuesday and on monday we're having a waterfight.... i was like okay.. cept I told chad I was going to do something with him on monday... but with him the chances of that actually happening arnt really all that big because hes a big poo poo head.  So yeah I'll tell my story about chad because I'm bored and its yeah lol. So I havn't seen him for more than a week now and havn't talked to him since tuesday but yeah. Since then I've been thinking about stuff a lot... like he doesn't seem to aknowledge the fact that he has a girlfriend. He just like he'll not be doing anything one day and I mean I'm not gonna call him everyday to see if hes busy but he wont be and he will just sit at home doing nothing and so will I and its stupid and thats like not even yeah I donno. But like I just wanna see him more than once every like week and a half cause thats what its been like so far this summer and thats so not what I want. Just cause I mean he's my boyfriend and I don't wanna never see him cause thats not fun... he just is like always biking and if he cant make time to see me once a week then thats sad. That all im asking too... once a week which is way less than I would really like but at least I'd see him sometimes. I donno I've been thinking about breaking up with him but I like him way too mcuh to just do that without trying to fix what I don't like first. But if he can't make the effort to make some time to get together then thats not what is really fair and I'm gonna break up with him because thats not fair to me to not like ever be able to see my boyfriend.   Then theres him who apparently was telling brennan how far we've gone and stuff and I'm like... I don't want his brother to know that because like his brother is in my classes and if he knows then he'll tell everyone else and then like.. I don't need everyone knowing about what I do with Chad. But I guess I donno I'll ask him about that too. Meh I donno I'm confused.... I'm just used to seeing my b.f more often and kinda getting more attention than Chad has been like willing to give... I mean with Mike and John it was like they'd call and I'd talk to them like every day even when John went away and stuff he'd call... and then theres Chad whos all yeah I can't call from the lake yet brennan calls jess from the lake all the time... I mean how nice is that... I'm really starting to wonder if he cares at all and if maybe he just doesn't know how to break up with me.. maybe he's worried about hurting me or something... either that or it's just his lack of expeirience and he doesn't know whats like normal in a relationship.  Meh well thats kinda a summary of the last few days... a kinda more detailed one lol... I've gotta go get dressed and stuff... I'm meeting Dylan and we're gonna go to macs again and stuff.... possibly go by jess' house and see if she can sneak away from packing for an hour or sumtin to come with us and hang out for a bit before she leaves on monday.. cause tomorrow she's really busy so she really cant get together and she said seh might be able to get away for a bit this afternoon... man I gotta dry my hair and find something that I can wear that isn't really dirty lol... prolly my shorts cause those r the cleanest things I have right now aside from my skirts lol.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okie, so yesterday I went swimming with Jess and Dylan and Mark, which was awesome.... 8 hours of swimming, 1-9, with a few breaks to get food but still. It was so much fun! And then there's this diving tower and so I was like, "I'm going off the 5 meter!" which like is pretty high, not for some ppl but for me... and yeah so I did and then finally convinced Dylan to and then Jess and then Mark who was kinda being a party pooper cause he wouldn't like do anything. Meh whatever it was so much fun. And then like, taking all the floaty things and making like a huge raft and just floating on it.  Then Dylan got us into (us being jess and me) running off the platforms into the water so you like doubled your air time and like were like flying and it was so much more fun than just jumping off the platform. That was just on the 3 meter but then near the end I decided to go off the 5 meter like that... only cause Dylan kept telling me to (he had done it tons of times before) and yeah it was fricken aweseome.  Oh and using the flutter boards but standing on them and trying to balance, all of it was fun, everything. And jumping into the cold cold pool (for lane swimming) after you've just been in the hot tub.   Then theres Mark who didn't bring any money at all so I had to pay for him to get into the swimming pool. And then jess, when she went off the diving board she didn't pull he top down enough and Dylan was like... uh jess? your your... and then yeah lol... but he was like all saw,turned around kinda thing. And brennan's been pissing Jess off lately (and he likes her and they went out and yeah it's complicated) but yeah Jess was like it would piss Brennan off so much if he knew that and so yeah just to piss him off she's gonna tell him about the whole Dylan thing.   It was all so much fun I mean like, prolly the best day I've had in awhile, just hanging out with friends and just having a complete and utterly good time together. And Dylan really is so incredibly nice, I don't get why Chad and Brennan both don't like him but that's their problem and if Chad tries to tell me shit about him and tries to make it so I'm not friends with Dylan then I'm going to tell him, he can't pick my friends and if he doesn't like some of them well then he doesn't have to see them but he can't stop me from being friends with them.  So we've decided that once Jess and Dylan get back from their vacations we're going to go to like all the leisure centers and prolly back to the Talisman center cause it's so much fun!  So then I got home and like hit the bed and I was out till 8:30 this morning cause my dad phoned to tell me to take the dog for a walk and now I'm here typing all this up.   So today, we were gonna go to the zoo (dylan and jess and me) but now my dad decided that I can't because we're going to a bbq at my dad's friends house for Canada Day, which shouldn't be bac or anything and people I know are going to be there it's just I would have liked to have gone to the zoo because I would have been able to see Dylan and Jess again before they leave... well I might still see Dylan cause he leaves in a week tomorrow but Jess is leaving on monday. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>