<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O give me sweet as ancient wine              The longed for end of day  O give me framed by gothic spires        Her far off gallaxies,  Beneath the full moons silver glow        With ivy o'ergrown  Amid her dark woods lay me down        Let day be overthrown.
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 9, The view up Horsleyhope ravine,Derwent gorge.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 10, Base camp in Horsleyhope ravine.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 11, Looking down on one of the more inaccessable parts of the gorge.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic'12, Nearby farmland above the gorge  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 13, On my latest trip, taken above Derwent gorge  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Originally on this trip I had intended to paddle down the gorge by kayak, unfortunately the river being too low at this time of year forced me to rely on leg power alone. This was unfortunate because not only am I getting on a bit now but some of the woodland clinging to the sides of this fabulous gorge are virtually  inaccessible by any other means.      In all I spent three days exploring the more accessible parts and viewing an amazing amount of wildlife  two Badgers,two foxes,one grey Squirrel and numerous Roe deer to be precise. Having never seen a Badger in my life before, to practically fall over two in the twilight was quite an experience I can tell you,a bit like buses really, you wait a lifetime for one and two come along at once!      
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When transient nature draws a veil        Upon the lies they've spun  Even Bible punching pedants in        Cahoots with Hell die young,    Even barbarous sadists, smirking on        Their low and squalid deeds  The humble Earthworm times devours        With quite forgiving speed,    But oh! how slow the endless drip        Of time can seem to one  Whose major fault in life has been         The good he has not done!
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pensive poet ponders.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 24, journeys end.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 23.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      PIc' 22, big scary rapids!  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 20, bend in the river.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 21.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 19, ancient woodland reflected in the river Tweed.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 18, into the heart of darkness!  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 16, meeting of the waters, Leader into Tweed.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 17.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 15, looking back to Leaderfoot bridge.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 14, Start of Journey by Leader water, a tributary of the Tweed.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 7, deep in the wildwood.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 6, the glorious Durham landscape.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 5, sunrise in Horsleyhope ravine.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 3, into the wild.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 4, looking down into the depths of the gorge.  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 2, deep in Horsleyhope ravine  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      pic' 1, crooked oak  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pic' 8, happy days  urlLink   
    
</post>


<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Despite the impression the border countryside might give to the casual observer; that of being a relatively well-wooded area replete with It's own share of ancient sites similar to other regions in the UK. The truth is in fact virtually the polar opposite, what you see is almost wholly a result of centuries of intensive management and exploitation, any natural woodland having long ago been cleared or relegated to steep slopes, ravines and rocky ground unfit for agriculture or sheep.          On this trip my aim was to get a closer look at one of the few remaining survivors, an ancient wood clinging to the steep slopes above the river Tweed near Scotts view; a view made famous by sir Walter Scott.
    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm afraid the doggerel in this one's couched in that curious survival from an earlier age called Scots/English.I know It's hard to believe, but we do actually still communicate in this way down here.For this reason I've translated some of the words into boring old English for the hard of understanding.(see bottom of page}    Of mans first disobedience,and the fruit  Of that forbidden tree,whose mortal taste  Brought death into the world,and all our woe,                                 From Miltons Paradise lost.    As I walked up the Pipewell brae  Content enough amid the play  O' sun on leaves that golden lay  Ain late November  Taewards a glade where aince I'd played  Though dim remembered,    It came tae me that as a child  As free as Pan ower field and style  Through these same wuds while roamin' wild  I'd chanced tae see  Ain day as caperin' ceased awhile  Beneath the trees    Tae Gods eternal shame near lying  A pair wee Starlin' piteous dying,  That in it's death throes still seemed striving  Despite the might  O' deaths desire; tae tak up flying  Again; the sight    O' sich distress brought hame tae me  There as a child Gods cruelty  In placin' death beneath the eaves  On earth; 'What pow'r'  Thought I 'wud deign sich things tae be  If he had our...    ...An' a' sich creatures guid in mind  Oh God ca'd love yer no' sae kind!  Aye either that; or when devine  Impatience grew  Wi' man an' a' his ways; resigned  Ye were; then threw...    ...Wi' heavy hirt our snake lulled pair  Ootside the gates o' Eden; where  Content afore the twa as fair  As angels stood',  (Nae wonder doubt within me flared  Back then for good)    Aye; set against this view was I  (For though a child) cauld sense arrived:  'A bible fu' o' silly lies  Tae fool pair man  Wud suit jist fine those wha contrive  Tae rule us' an'...    ...Wi' this last thought I traced my way  A sadder, wiser child that day  Back hame; convinced that nought held sway  Beneath the sun  Save man an' a' his hideous ways  Beloved bi none.    brae: hill/slope o': of ain/aince: one/once taewards: towards tae: to ow'r: over an': and wuds: woods pair: poor wee: small tak: take sich: such hame: home wud: would a': all guid: good ca'd: called ye/yer: you/your no': not sae: so aye: yes wi': with hirt: heart ootside: outside afore: before twa: two nae: no cauld: cold fu': full jist: just wha: who                                                    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having had for many years an intense fascination with ancient woodland,particularly those least affected by  human activity, ie sites most resembling what Oliver Rackham  (author on the subject} termed 'Wildwood' I find  myself now constantly on the lookout {hence Blogging) for ways  to contact those with a similar passion to share info' with.  Unfortunately I have found that most writing on the  subject tends to focus on areas with a long history of interference by man, which although fascinating in itself tends  to overlook my own particular interest, an interest I can directly attribute to another author: Robert Holdstock.  Holdstocks book 'Mythago wood' set me on a course I've  never regretted taking; that of identifying and exploring the  most natural woods in these islands, for although no doubt  incredibly rare and tiny in comparison to Holdstocks I assume  wholly fictional 'Mythago' I'm convinced that such places do exist.  To date the nearest approximation to such a wood I've come across grows on a small island in the middle of a bog near  Tullamore in Ireland (this wood is mentioned in one of Oliver  Rackhams books, the title of which escapes me).The trees here are truly magnificant, with Ivy covered giant Oaks leaning every which way but straight, while others long dead loom like&nbsp; Mammoths in the gloom of the interior.  Well, thats my reason for Blogging I hope it makes some  kind of sense.  If anyone out there has anything of interest ie locations,  photos, descriptions of natural woodland they would like to share  please don't hesitate to e-mail me at fatfirkin@yahoo.co.uk. In  return I will e-mail back an invite to view all my photos on  webshots.com  Catweasel.    
    
</post>


</Blog>