<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Greetings, I hope this post find you all well. God is moving again in my life today. So I wanted to share be thoughts on forgiveness. I must admit the a lot of the content of this post will be based on a sermon series by Dr. Joe Stowell from the Moody Bible Institute. With that said, lets begin...  If you would like to review Dr. Stowell's 4 message series you can visit this site :  urlLink Proclaim! Transcripts  and look for the messages dated from 6/14/2004 - 6/17/2004.  As Christians, we are expected to exercise forgiveness at all times. Yes. It is difficult, there is no doubt about that, for we are not perfect like our Lord is. But, nevertheless, we must forgive. If we do not forgive others of their trespasses against us, we open the door for Satan to grab us by the throat and begin injecting chaos into our lives. Lack of forgiveness hardens hearts and leads to grudges. So what are we to do? We must forgive, yet our flesh demands restitution.   The answer lies in fact that forgiveness has NOTHING to do with the offense, or even the offender and everything to do with your confidence in your relationship with God. What do I mean?   Remember this : God knows all. He knows everything about the offense that you are upset about. Remember Genesis 50:20a that reads :    "But as for you, ye thought evil against me; but God meant it unto good,"   That tells me that everything the comes against me in this world, all of the tribulation that you face maybe brought against you be the power of Satan. However, God intends all of this for good! Good will come from it. Trust you God. Remember always that HE IS GOD, no matter what. Always has been and always will be.   If you trust you God and he let that offense come upon you, then don't you think God will take care of your through it all? Don't you think God "has your back" Of course he does!  Satan can do nothing that God does not allow him to . So have peace amongst your strife.  If you take nothing else away from this text, just remember. Forgiveness is  NOT  only divine. As it was given to us, we must also give it freely to each other. Recognize the need to forgive each other and do so. It is God's will for us and it pleases Him.    Have a blessed day!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An associate of mine sent me this little joke. I hope you enjoy it as much as I have.    A new pastor was visiting in the homes of his parishioners. At one house it seemed obvious that someone was at home, but no answer came to his repeated knocks at the door. Therefore, he took out a card and wrote "Revelation 3:20" on the back of it and stuck it in the door.  When the offering was processed the following Sunday, he found that his  card had been returned. Added to it was this cryptic message, "Genesis 3:10."  Reaching for his Bible to check out the citation, he broke up in gales of laughter.  Revelation 3:20 begins "Behold, I stand at the door and knock."  Genesis 3:10 reads, "I heard your voice in the garden and I was afraid for I was naked."  Remember when the funniest jokes were the clean ones? They still are!  "A cheerful heart is good medicine" (Prov. 17:22a)   Have a great day! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have so much to cover and so little time to cover it in. I hear these words in my head far too much of the time. Perhaps if I can spill it out upon this digital paper, I can make some sense of it. Many thoughts and themes have surfaced in my life, requiring much thought and consideration. Grace, forgiveness, and the conversionary path for the non-believer. I want to explain and discuss that act and concepts of God's grace for us.   God's grace is given freely to both Jew and Gentile. We as believers enjoy the unending flow of grace upon our lives. God's Holy Spirit intercedes in our lives on a daily bases. At the end of your day, on the day were you can't think of what God did for you, think about this: What did he keep out of your life today? That is a solid thought to ponder on.    Romans 3:24 NKJV says this : "Being justified freely by his grace through the redemption that is in Christ Jesus"   Wow, that means you and I both are given grace freely and as a result of our faith in Jesus Christ. We are given salvation. This is important. You see, the Mosiac law, that is, the commandments and the first covenant established between God and Man, was a sort of guideline of how we were to conduct ourselves in order to be in alignment with God's will. However, human nature proved to be too strong. Our nature is to do exactly that which we are forbidden to do. Some say it is because it is an exercise of our free will and shows that we are the commander of our lives, not God. Thus the law and its standards we not attainable by us.   This is ultimately why Jesus was sent to us. For it is only by His grace alone that we are permitted to enter into the Kingdom of God. Salvation is attainable through no action or merit of our own. The following passage confirms this for us. Paul writes :    "Therefore by the deeds of the law there shall no flesh be justified in his sight: for by the law is the knowledge of sin." Romans 3:20   I think it is very important to understand that we are dependent on Jesus for every action in our life. Through Him, all things are made possible. Without him, we are lost. When God made his promises to Abraham, it was not through his deeds, or the law that justified him. It was his faith in God's grace. Remember, God is always faithful in his promises. If God tells you something, you can go to the bank on it. Count on it.  Obedience to God's will is always rewarded .  Again from the book of Romans, Paul writes :    "For the promise, that he should be the heir of the world, was not to Abraham, or to his seed, through the law, but through the righteousness of faith." Romans 4:13 NKJV   I pray that you who read this can take some insight away from this text. Remember our new favorite five letter "f" word :   FAITH  . I assure you I will get better as I go!   Have a blessed day.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Check the sidebar to the right of the page to check out the newest wallpaper I have created. I used some new techniques I have been learning in Photoshop to achieve my success. I like to express myself via my art. Thankfully, God has bestowed a moderate amount of artistic talent on me! Comments are welcome!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I will begin posting content to this blog very soon. Please be patient until I can get things rolling. I am also going to do a wallpaper for the site. Something abstract.. and blu, because I like blue.    Thanks
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I will not be posting regularly in my blog for until July 12th. I am currently in Miami, Fl on vacation and will be in Orlando, Fl next week enjoying Disney World. I will return to posting regularly when I return. Until then,   May the Lord watch over you and, of course,  Have a blessed day! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Time for another quick sidenote comment. After our conversion to Christianity, we partake in the believers baptism. While having nothing to do with the act of salvation (I say that because some faiths believe that baptism alone is the way to attain salvation, according to the Bible they are incorrect.), we do this as an act of obedience to Jesus. The baptism is a declaration to the church family that you are saved and are now walking as a Christian. By doing this, we take on accountability for our actions.   Think about it like this, once you have announced to the world: " I am a Christian. I want to live my life for Jesus and follow in his ways to edify His church." You have no choice but to make every attempt to attain this goal because, now, people are watching you. That's right, from that little boy in church that watched you to see how you do things, to your spouse that makes sure you keep your eyes focused in the right direction while you are at the mall.   So how can we do this successfully if we know we are going to fail constantly in this walk with God? Well, God knows that we will fail just as we do. We must keep a heart of open faith and always ask forgiveness for our sins. God is faithful in that, he will forgive you and use His Holy Spirit to show you His will for you each day. I find it helpful to pray to God each day as I awake and recommit my life to Him. This helps me to take on the day in a manner where I can be in constant prayer and can sense the Spirit leading me to do God's will.   We can protect ourselves from the pressures and lure of worldly sin against us. How you ask? Just as the warrior puts on his armor to deflect the enemy's blade, we too must don the armor of God. Read these two passages:   " Let us walk properly, as in the day, not in revelry and drunkenness, not in lewdness and lust, not in strife and envy. But put on the Lord Jesus Christ, and make no provision for the flash, to fulfill its lusts.  " Romans 13:13-14 NKJV   " Finally, my brethren, be strong in the Lord, and in the power of his might. Put on the whole armor of God, that ye may be able to stand against the wiles of the devil. For we wrestle not against flesh and blood, but against principalities, against powers, against the rulers of the darkness of this world, against spiritual wickedness in high places. Wherefore take unto you the whole armor of God, that ye may be able to withstand in the evil day, and having done all, to stand. Stand therefore, having your loins girt about with truth, and having on the breastplate of righteousness; And your feet shod with the preparation of the gospel of peace; Above all, taking the shield of faith, wherewith ye shall be able to quench all the fiery darts of the wicked. And take the helmet of salvation, and the sword of the Spirit, which is the word of God: Praying always with all prayer and supplication in the Spirit, and watching thereunto with all perseverance and supplication for all saints; And for me, that utterance may be given unto me, that I may open my mouth boldly, to make known the mystery of the gospel, For which I am an ambassador in bonds: that therein I may speak boldly, as I ought to speak. " Eph 6:10-20   I know that one was long, but the more I read it the more I wanted to include the next verse and the next one to help illustrate the Armor of God.     Have the blessed day! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In my recent readings I came across a passage at the end of Chapter 12 in the book of Romans. In verse 17, Paul writes:   "Repay no one evil for evil"   In verse 19:    "Beloved, do not avenge yourselves, but rather give place to wrath; for it is written, Vengeance is Mine, I will repay, says the Lord"   Think about what God is telling us there. He understands that we will tresass on each other from time to time. When someone trespasses against you, we must keep this in mind: We must forgive the person from the offence and embrace them as a friend. God tells us not to be vengefull towards the offender. We are to let God handle the situation, for he has promised to repay the trespass against you. This is time for us to be faithful in the promises of our Lord.   Finally, Chapter 12 of Romans finished with the verse :    "Do not be overcome by evil, but overcome evil with good"   This is a beautiful concept to me. This is a passage of hope in a tough time. With God "at your back" who and what can stand in opposition to us? Jesus is the Good Sheperd, and he will watch over us, responsible for our well being.   Rest easy in the knowledge that our Lord and Savior, Jesus Christ is caring for our every need at all times.     Have a blessed day!   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The conversionary path was going to be my next series of posts. However, in my journey through Romans I have found some other topics to work with until I am ready to string together some comments on the conversion to Christianity and the resulting salvation experience. The following posts will be from the book of Romans, specifically from my new MacArthur NKJV version of bible. If you do not have a MacArthur, I would highly purchasing one. It is quite an investment. I was able to get one for $27 on Amazon.com.  Thanks,
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have been inspired by a&nbsp;colleague at work to produce another wallpaper that involves the "fish" symbol commonly seen on many vehicles around town. More on this endeavor later.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, I'm back an in the swing of things. I had a lot of class work to complete in order to get back even in my work. My vacation was wonderful! We were truly blessed in this undertaking, for all went well.     I will begin posting again soon. I have purchased a dramatized audio bible (NIV Zondervan) and have covered Romans, Galations, 1 Corinthians, 2 Corithians, and Ephesians. I want to focus on Romans 14 and the ideas expressed in that chapter, for there are many and they are important to the believer.     Also, I will attempt to cover the points in a new writting style that I believe will allow me to express the thoughts and concepts I want to share with you all. I have learned much from the writtings of Paul, the apostle to the Gentiles, whom came from the Mosaic law in Judaism.     Until then,  may the grace and peace of our Living God be with you always and forever.            
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Greetings friends, I write this posting to one of my brethren. Today I speak to my brother, he who believes in the way's of the Judiac diet. My brother is a member of the Catholic faith. One that, to me, seems to seperate its self from the scripture by worldly and human rituals and rites of passage. But that is not my focus today. In my recent study of the book of Romans I found several interesting messages and revelations in the text. It is in Chapter 14 that I begin today :     To the Christian that holds on to the old ways, the ways before the coversion to Christ: The scripture says :       "For one believeth that he may eat all things: another, who is weak, eateth herbs. Let not him that eateth despise him that eateth not; and let not him which eateth not judge him that eateth: for God hath received him." - Romans 14:2-3      What does this mean? What is Paul trying to tell us. It is this, God has extended His grace unto you because of the atonement of your sins through Christ Jesus. The kingdom of God is not about what you eat or do not. But the kingdom of God is of rightousness, peace, love, and joy in the Holy Spirit. In the text above, Paul instructs that the one who does not eat all things would be wise to not despise, nor judge, that one that does not eat all things. For if, to one man, it is a sin to eat meat and his conscience is not clean, then to him it is a sin and he should refrain from eating of it. But if, to another man, eating meat is no sin and he is of clean conscience, then to him he is free of blame. But know this, God created all things in His creation and nothing in and of itself is unclean.     In this, I apologize to my brother, for I judged you as folly and unwise. But in the scripture I have seen that I was judgemental and in sin. Perhaps you will read Romans 14 and understand God's will for you in your life.     May God's peace be with you always  -Amen       
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Greeting friends! I pray this message finds you well. Let me begin by extending the grace and peace of our Lord, Jesus Christ to you. With great misfortune, I apologize for taking such a long span of time before returning to my electronic ministry. For I could tell you all of the many tasks I have partaken, I will not. For the love of the ministry of Christ ought to motivate me unto action. But alas, I have be mired with worldly thoughts and jobs.       It is on this topic I write to you, brothers and sisters. For those who attempt to extend the kingdom of God are forever persecuted. For Satan himself plots to bog down and wear on those he seek God's face. What am I speaking of? Procrastination. Putting those things off that should be attended to at present times. Procrastination is, indeed, a disobedience to the Lord. For if He commands it, it should be done. And done with a glad and thanksgiving heart.       It is this weakness, that I am guity of. But have faith my friends, for since you are reading this, I have be granted passage by our Lord to write again. My prayers of reconciliation and forgiveness have been answered. For you see, what Satan would have done to me in evil, God has changed into good. For is it not written in countless words in the epistles of Paul, how the Lord saved Paul many times over, from the sword and from the lions.      Have faith as I did, that God will deliver you from every evil. For through Jesus Christ we gain God's grace. And with His grace, we are given the power to defeat sin, even the power to defeat Satan with His word. For even Satan is bound by the will of God. He can not do nothing that God does not allow. So rest in the embrace of Christ and have faith that your Father will deliver you.       The message I wish to speak unto you this day is one on temporal and worldly busyness. Who is he that toils incessently with worldly tasks and thinks his deeds will bring him credit and rightousness? I believe he is a fool. Does not the love of worldly tasks bring about worldly desires and expectations of awards? Indeed, this is called pride, and bring sin upon the man that reviles in it. But what of the one who toils day by day with the works of God and extends the kingdom of God? Be not busy in concern with worldly tasks but be swallowed up in the tasks that God would have you do. Does God keep His will from you? Does He mask His intentions? Certainly not! God reveals His will to us in the scripture and through spiritual intercession with His Holy Spirit. Recall the following scripture from the Gospel of Jesus Christ written by the apostle Luke :      "   Now it came to pass, as they went, that he entered into a certain village: and a certain woman named Martha received him into her house. And she had a sister called Mary, which also sat at Jesus' feet, and heard his word. But Martha was cumbered about much serving, and came to him, and said, Lord, dost thou not care that my sister hath left me to serve alone? bid her therefore that she help me. And Jesus answered and said unto her, Martha, Martha, thou art careful and troubled about many things: But one thing is needful: and Mary hath chosen that good part, which shall not be taken away from her." Luke 10:38-40"            Martha was concerned with the wordly things that were happening around her. She was more concerned about making things into elaboration around Christ instead of taking on an attitude of worship, awe, and open desire for the words and teaching of Christ.     Should we be like Martha or Mary? Indeed we should be like Mary, sitting at the foot of Jesus, listening to His words and teachings like a child listens to a story before bedtime. I pray that God has given you personal revelation as you read this. Be sensitive to God's will and be obedient in your actions and God will bless you many times.       Grace and Peace from our Lord, Jesus Christ, and the Father be with all of you.     Amen.        
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Greetings,     May God bless you, and open your heart to the words you are about to read. I pray that He will bring you personal revelation from the words found below. With that, I will continue :     Leading the lost. It is our duty and mission, given us from Christ. I find myself upon this topic because I have failed in it. For the mind and spirit longs to comply and minister to the lost and give testimony, but my flesh is slothful. Surely, I could press on and provide guidance to others but yet, I do not.     I say these things to you, not to boast in my failures, but to keep you from doing these things. I want to see the kingdom grow, as I am sure you do. Alas though, Satan works constantly to hinder the Christian from this calling. He works to throw the stumbling stone in the path of the believer in Christ. To the one weak in the faith, from newness or sin, this stone causes the believer to falter and stumble. If this stumble causes you to turn from God and leave the path to Him, then Satan has succeeded. Have faith! For we will surely stumble along our walk, but Christ is always there to help us, to take up our yoke with us.     What do these things mean? It means to us, we should always strive to do God's will. God will often require us to move outside our "comfort zone" and do works on His behalf through faith alone. We must have no care for the account of what man thinks of the works we perform for our Lord. Scripture tells us to store up treasures for ourselves in heaven, where rust and moths cannot ruin them. Scripture warns that we are not to look for and build up earthly treasures , for we came into this world with nothing, and with nothing, we will leave it.     Have courage to do right. Always obey our Lord when He speaks to you in the spirit. Obedience is always rewarded and think of the glorious day that will one day come, where Jesus will look upon your face and say, "Well done, my servant! For you obeyed my father's commandments and did all that you were asked to do!". I pray that day comes soon.      Peace be with you all.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Greeting all! Recently, I completed the entire New Testament. After reviewing the writtings of the apostle Paul, the apostle to the Gentiles, I have been inspired to draft a list of ideals and truth points that I feel that a Christian should follow to maintain the utmost faith in his or her walk in Christ. I will be working on this draft for several postings. After which, I will resume my revelations in the book of Romans. This list, surely, cannot be all inclusive. We must not try to make this list like the laws of Moses and try to interpret other meanings into the words I will write. Until then, I will begin:     I will love the Lord, my God, with all that I am and in all I do.  I will look to the Lord for guidance in every thing that comes against me, for He is a soverign Lord.  I will trust the Lord, my God, in every commandment He gives me.  I will work to better the kingdom of God.  I will, if required by Him, release all my wealth, possessions, and personal needs to serve Him.  I will work to serve my fellow Christians, for in doing so, I serve Jesus.  I will take the things God has given me and invest them in the edification of His kingdom , so that I may return to Him a great return.  I will pray to my God daily, giving adoration, praise, and thanks for all things before supplication.  I will commit myself daily to His will.     More later, comments are VERY welcome.   May God's grace fall plentiful upon you.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>