<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ho-kay, so, my father is going out to the desert, and since that doesn't involve my computer, I'm going to stay at fuckin Andy's house. I'll try not to murder him, and try to sneak away with Melly so we can have hot passionate sex, minus the sex, but whatever. Moving on, I'm going to be without my beautiful run-every-game-imaginable computer for a few days, and I weep for my 5900. Serious, I love the computer more than I love my own penis. Even though my penis is small and insignifigant. Tiny. Electron Microscope...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jesus
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, it started out ok. Me and Melly were gonna hang out. Then of course Andy, the girlfriend stealing prick (not that he's going to steal my girlfriend), invites her to the movies. He knew I wanted to hang out with just her today, but I'm sure if I asked him he'd say, "Well you did hang out with her..." Which I did, so it was still a good day. I'm not going to act like anything is different between us, because Melly was freaking out because this entire semester best friends have been fighting over her. I'm just that lucky bastard in the back who hadn't been involved in any of it but suddenly went out with her. I also proved that I can, in fact, be a good person.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, after an entire weekend of pure boredom, then a return of a girlfriend (who then ditched boyfriend), and a sudden lapse in sanity, I come to blogger. Could be fun... Just remember, when you think you're free, the crack inside your fucking heart is me.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reading Doug's journal makes me wanna bash my head into a wall until it's as open and free as his seems to be...  With my feet upon the ground I lose myself between the sounds, and open wide to suck it in, I feel it move across my skin. I'm reaching up, and reaching out, I'm reaching for the random or whatever will bewilder me. (whatever will bewilder me) Following our wills and wind we may just go where no one's been. Ride the spiral too the end, and we may just go where no one's been... Spiral out, keep going Spiral out, keep going Spiral out!  This song makes me wanna do the same... Today I tried to reflect on all the good things left in my life. My dad, a nice house, food, the best computer anyone in Simi has, the best friend an asshat like me could ask for. Of my friends that are left, I got some of the smartest, or more unique, although being smart usually goes a long way towards being unique. I have an almost-constant supply of Dew, which rocks hardcore. What else do I have? Nothing big I can think of... considering I only sit at the comp and drink dew. I was reading Doug's LJ when I came across him describing a meet-up with Cheryl, from what I'm reading it looks like Cheryl is to Doug what Jackie is to me... So based off of what he wrote, here's my view...  When we talk online, it's always akward. In fact, for me, it's like that a lot. I can't read people if I can't see their face, pick up on the subtle movements in their eyes, so I don't know exactly what they mean. With Jackie, I'm at a total loss online, but when we're in person we just connect. Everytime I've seen her for a long period of time we just sit around and talk, and talk and talk and talk. We could easily babble for days. It's a crystal moment, frozen forever in it's own singular beauty.  As Doug said: She's the most beautiful person I've ever known, and I'm still in love with her. but unlike him... Now, God, I wish I wasn't.  It's ok though, most guys never even see beauty because they're looking at all the wrong places. The average guy could never understand this feeling, never experience such happiness. In a more depressed entry, I would have written, "or such grief.", but right now I feel alive...  Remember, we are eternal, all this pain is an illusion.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>