<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, it is undoubtedly...  I am starting a god-forsaken blog!  Reason:  I need a magic "place"...  i.e.:  " I need a place to bring all my ALC Newbie friends together" " I need a place to put up info about the sale at Helen's this weekend" " I need a place to get a group of friends together about Hairspray"  THIS is going to be that kind of place.  AMAZING!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the weekend is officially over...  I feel a void right now, but i also feel somewhat satisfied.  What is it from?  Usually holiday weekends with gatherings make me feel like I want someone in my life.  But at the sametime I have an amazing amount of freedom because I do not.  At the same time, i think things like the trip to COSTCO alone remind me how single i really am.  It kinda sucks.  *fizzle* - I'm just emotionally tired right now.  S 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rant:  When someone describes something, and you don't understand, so they proceed to describe the same thing, the same way they just described it, thinking repetition will help the situation.  -=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-  It DOESN'T help.  When someone doesn't understand something, it usually helps to try and describe whatever it is you are talking about in a different way.  Many times, at work, I hear representatives speaking to a customer, repeat EXACTLY what they just told a customer two or more times, not because the customer didn't hear them but because the customer DIDN'T UNDERSAND.  Not Hearing vs. Not Understanding require two different remedies.  OYE VEY!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So... This week has been a roller coaster of emotion at the office and away...  Monday we were told that Sandra, our director, my informal mentor, and our fearless, smart, witty, compassionate leader is being pushed aside by the corporation, our center to be taken over by her former peer from the East.   Background Note: The EAST center is about half as productive as the WEST because the EAST has their workforce split up into teams all doing essentially the same function but just for a subset of the work - like one ISP or one State per group.  The WEST = Everyone does Everything.   I took the news well until Sandra started packing her office and files up this week.  Depressing man, very depressing.  I don't know who's office I'm going to be able to pop into just to get a 10 second sanity check, and to share the latest KCET, KCRW, or NPR blips with.  On a more positive note:  My personal evolution - AIDSLifeCycle has given me a way to not feel powerless.  I think the feeling of being powerless has been a great negative force in my life.  Powerless over the community that I am part of.  AIDSLifeCycle provides a way to positively influence the community and bring affirming change to the HIV/AIDS epidemic.  I AM DOING SOMETHING.  Since the ride, I've been a changed person, but just subtly, and I can't put my finger on it every day.  Sense of Purpose?  Maybe that's part of it too.  So back to gloom and doom at the office - we got an email today that basically tells us changes are on the horizon and we will likely be moving to the more inefficient way of doing business.  I was involved or was privy to the BATTLE Sandra and our team had waged against this change for YEARS.  Now changes are not even open for discussion - AMAZING.  I am going to turn up the heat on the Job Hunt, I no longer want to work for this company.  These changes will probably result in the organizing (unionizing) of our center, which doesn't make good business sense either.  *sigh*  I hope to find a great job with a more human-like company soon.  Weekend: Saturday - Tucky Party @ DelanskyMV Sunday - LoLo Schmitz Party or Davey Party Monday - Recovery
     

    
</post>


</Blog>