<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today both my mother nad I are PMSing and that's NEVER a good thing. Usually it's first my mom who goes balistic when she's PMSing and I just ignore her and then comes me and I go totally CRAZY and she just ignores it but now it's BOTH of us going balisting and we bother CAN'T ignore it. It's madness! Today, she IMed on AIM and asked me if I wanted to go to the mallw ith her. I said yes, of course becuase I LOVE shopping. So when she got home I had to get dressed really quick and she started yelling at me for going to slow. So I was brushing my hair and she's like: "HURRY UP! Or I'll leave without you!" and I said: "No! I Have to go!" and she's like: "You know what?! You're not going! Stay here!" so. . .I went balistic and threw things aorund the house, y'know, the usual PMSing shit. When she was out I got a call from my friend and so we three-wayed my mom top ask her if I could go over her house. She said yes, of course. Any excuse to get rid of me.   So she got home and started rushign me again. Then I had to eat dinner. She watched me through the whole thing and after, like, 5 minutes she started yelling at me and said: "Stop eating now! Let's go!" She was taking me to my friend Erin's house and she had to go pick up a friend for her friends birthday. She was late so she was taking out her wrath on me.  I got ot Erin's house and we played some video game that i totally couldn't win, we wrote some songs nad had fun screwing up, and then, the real hell of all sorts broke loose. Erin wanted me to sleep over and I really didn't want to because her house smelled and her room was crowded and I really didn't feel too well because I'm allergic to cats and she had 3 of them. She started crying and yelling at me to get out and so I did get out. . .ugh, I felt awful for doing it to her. She was crying! I don't like to make people cry. . .I want to die!  I hope she calls tomorrow to ask me to go too the beach with her, still, because i really want to meet her friend Andre. She said maybe we could fall in love! Haha, yeah right. . .he wouldn't like me, I'm ugly! So that's everything, all the crap that happened today. . .it sucked! And I can't believe my "best friend" didn't call to ask why I was absent at camp today. The BITCH!
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm officially making it a goal to get a record contract with 'Epic Records' which means, as you probably guess, I want to be a singer. And I'm a new big fan of Ashlee Simpson, since myname, is, Ashley and because I can TOTALLY relate with her. Too bad she's all famous. Well, w/e, I just wish I knew another Ashley (or however other people spell their Ashley variation). I also had "A Talk" with my father. It was long a boring and I really didn't pay attention, cause then he started talking about how sex wasn't bad. That's not something you want to talk to your dad about! Anyway, I'm at his house today, waiting for the dishwasher people to pick up the dishwasher. The last time I met this "dishwasher man" he had a very heavy accent and I couldn't understand a ward he was saying. Well, w/e, now my dad is here to try and understand him.  Last night I also had a really weird dream. My mom wanted to take out the left side of my brain and then I was at school and kids were bullying me (Which NEVER happens in real life, I'm really liked at school) and I had to hide from them in some glass house, it was soo weird! But I had one of my many best friends there with me but she was trying ot fit in with her "best friend" so i couldn't stay with her. It was so weird! So my mom was trying ot take out the left side of my brain and I remember one of the things my dad had said: "Wouldn't it be hard getting used to not having half of your brain?" And it's true! My mom was planning on chopping off half of my brain for no apparent reason (well, the reason WAS apparent, I just don't remember what it was) and she was going to cut my head open! I was NOT into that, not even after she tried to brainwash me! So, yeah, me and my dad ganged up on her and then I was afraid she'd murder me, or backstab me!  Weird. . .I wonder what it means?
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was totally uneventful. The occasional annoyingly long and unwanted call from one of my best friends, the occasional need to eat something, and the occasional nausia period. . .yep. . .that's my boring day. But I don't know how I'll face my dad tomorrow. . .scary. . .
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Let's start off with this:  My dad is a jerk.  How? Because on father's day, "his" day, my brother and I didn't get him a card, gift, whatever. So today I called him because some guy came to the door asking for some package I DON'T have. He started trying to guilt me and saying that I don't worry about him and turning everything I've said and done around so that I sound like the bad person! He also changed the date I was supposed to sleep over his house (my parents are divorced by the way) and go to work with him. I was supposed to go with him tonight and tomorrow but he changed it to Thursday and Friday so he didn't have to drive me back home and whatever. What if I didn't WANT to spend 4 days with him being a jerk and being all retarded with his girlfriend? Huh? Did he ever think of that?   Well, whatever, I just hope he doesn't yell at me for what I said about him behind his back to my mom. She sent it to him and now he's going to be all at my throat trying to "talk" with me. I don't even want to talk to him anymore. Now I know why Joe (my brother) doesn't always want to talk to him.   Why does this have to be so hard?  So in conclusion:  NEVER let a man get to your head. They'll try and lower your self-esteem by saying everything is your fault!
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got a call from my daddy and he said it was okay for me to go to the carnival with Erin. He's going to pick me up on Saturday for my piano lesson, I'm so glad!  I got atext message on the cellphone from my very long ago ex "boyfriend" Tyler. It was great but when I sent him a picture of me all he friggan said was: "What's that disease you said you had?"  How rude right?!  Here's his picture:  urlLink Tyler 
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks to my  loving  father I CAN'T go to Festival Night tonight with Erin, and to top it all off, I have to spend the WEEKEND with him. Yet again he's sought out to crush any home of changing up the weekends.Last weekend I asked him if I could go home early from his house and he said NO. I couldn't even leave his house because I'm like his friggan prisoner! I really don't enjoy the company of my father, he's very annoying and fun crushing.  On another note I've started camp, and it's very fun! Yesterday I went to Six Flags, the day before that we went to the most BORING place in all of New Jersey, Waterloo Village. It was aweful, buring hot, and we had to do some stupid scavenger hunt.  We went ot Mountain Creek the day before that and it was SO much FUN! I loved it! But first thing in the morning I had to go take a swim test -.-' I passed, though.  So anyway, at MOuntain Creek, it was kind of chaotic. First our group of 7 girls got split up because the bitchy half of us ditched us. Then, in the wave pool, I scrapped my knee on the ground after trying to dive into a wave, then I scratched my thigh on the outside of one of those ultra heavy tubes on the Colorado Rapids, and then I hurt my pinky somehow. ALl my injuries STILL hurt very much.   I colored my hair blonde, i stole my brothers Religious necklace, and I've tried numerous times to clean my room. . .which hasn't been a success yet.  Hope things get better and I hope my mom tells my dad to pick me up on Saturday. I REALLY wanna go to the festival with Erin!
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday I recieved my first PC laptop. After having a Mac iBook for, like, 3 years I've finally returned to my roots. I learned all my computing skills on a PC and I was thrown into the world of Macintosh one fateful day when my mom wanted to take my PC desktop computer. She gave me an iBook in return which I was rather partial to using but got used to it fast. I'm now getting, gradually, used to this computer although it's trackpad pisses the shit out of me because whenever you press on it it acts like a mouse. I'm also aware that I have no clue how to use Paint Shop Pro so now I feel really retarded. I used to know the whozits about whatzitz but now I'm asking just about every minute: "How do I. . ." " Where is. . ." I feel like a computer reject!  Well, I'm getting used to it, I just hope it happens quick, I'm sick of asking dumb questions. . .
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As of late I've felt eyes upon me and it's rather unsettling. At night I can feel someone behind me, not the same feeling of when a human if behind you, more like a light presense hovering behind me. You know that feeling, right? Well, it's a constant feeling for me and I know the long-gone are among me. Not as profound as some but I do have thatsupernatural ability. Now that i think about it, I've felt presenses around me my whole life, I only notice it when the "being" is just about on my back. I also know when someone is sad, depressed, hurting, or totally FAKING happiness. If they laugh I can always tell the emptiness inside it. Maybe everyone can but when I know someone is hurting it hurts me too. And when I know someone will be hurt in the future I try and cut back from voicing my--ehem--violent thoughts. Supernatural stuff really intrests me so lately I've been extra keen on listening to things, maybe pick up something that's always been there but I haven't paid attention to. Who knows, maybe I have some MYSTICAL powers!! YEAH!  
      
</post>


</Blog>