<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ans: Probably.   For someone who never used to like beer I'm drinking an awful lot of the stuff lately....and it's all Carlsberg :-p   AHHHHH..sucked in by phony 'it'll improve your life...probably' ad campaign!' Erk.  Actually I can also blame Euro 2004 (more advertising). And our local. For being a female watching a football match is one thing..being a female watching a football match who doesn't drink beer? Quite another. So we drink beer, watch football and the boys observe us with a degree of mistrust and fascination,  (it's a small town masquerading as a city you understand). But the necessary beer/footie combo aside...I have concluded cold beer on a hot day....niccccce.  Perhaps an even more worrying tendency is the liking I've taken to the black stuff (actually it's dark brown but advertising again whadda y'know) ;) Yes. Guinness. Very much viewed as an 'old' drink..lately it's like 'hey I'm Irish...I'm in an Irish bar..what about drinking an Irish drink?'. Shocker ;)(ignoring the fact that the Earl of Iveagh is totally not Irish..once again advertising) I actually really like the stuff and I-  hang on a sec...it's a penalty shoot out between Holland and Sweden...  ..heh.. and Holland are through on sudden death..woo..*ahem*..they're the one team I've supported consistently throughout so they'll probably get knocked out next match ;-)  Now where was I? Ah yes...black stuff that is actually brown, liking of. Yes I really actually like the taste and as the advertising will have you know..it's worth the wait. ;) Not that I'm one to heed advertising. Nope. Did I mention that I don't like advertising? :-p (it's really not obvious at all is it?)  Well 99.9% of it I dislike. A pure advert I don't really mind..in that I mean..if you're going to advertise a car..use the car to advertise itself. This whole attaching things and qualities to products in the relentless march of commercialism...not a fan of. As for the 'celebrities' hocking themselves to the highest bidder..grr..don't get me started. An out of work actor I can forgive. Someone who has 20 million+ in the bank? I don't think so. 'You big sellout you' has sadly been my catchphrase du jour this year. Ack.  Anyway..how did I get here? (how the hell..oh right..Christmas Eve last yeaaaaar!'..er sorry slipped into RENT there..ignore me (those of you who aren't ignoring me already of course).   Anyway..can.worms.everywhere. What else was it?..Ah yes Holland losing their next match. I have a fairly good indicator of this as apparently me bigging up Ivanisevic resulted in him crashing out less than 24 hours later so Henman should watch out on People's Sunday tomorrow. Pity I am not one of the people that can be at Wimbledon this particular Sunday...then again...  
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (or how to be Goran Ivanisevic and not get sued) :p  Today at Wimbledon:  *Flying tennis rackets? Check. *Insane Croatian? Check. *Lovin' it? Lovin' it?, Lovin' it? Check. ;)  Now that's what I call tennis. I can't help but love Goran. He not only threw his racket into the (hysterical) crowd...but his also his shirt followed by his (non figurative) towel ;) On top of which he played like a man possessed and threw caution to the wind.   So tennis + throwing things = Best viewing so far.   Go Rusedski and Roddick too....not as crazy as Racket Man (come on now Elton..record that cover) but still superlative viewing. The rain's made them all a bit madder..just the way I like em. ;)  Next on schedule: The Tim Henman Heart Attack Plan.  Ah the joys of being an unemployed tennis fan. To the envy of my worker bee friends.  
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That is the question.  But you're sick of questions right?   So for now...I have some answers...or more accurately just not   the   answer.    Why am I here?  (I mean, of course, on this page as opposed to on, say the planet, universe or general stratosphere naturellement)   Well the pure and simple truth (which is you realise, never pure and rarely simple... but I digress) is that:  I wondered if I could,  I could,  So I am.    What's this all about?   The sanity of it all and conversely the insanity of it all.    Will I make sense?   To quote a comedic Shakespearean actor I once saw "Maybe...maybe not".  Enough with the answers...they pose too many questions all by themselves :p  And now I will leave you there (and keep me here).  Welcome to  What Sanity? . 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ..where does the end appear? (yes Buffy fans).. I know ;-) &nbsp;Life feels like one big question mark right now..  But maybe that's a good thing..I'd certainly hate for it to be a foregone conclusion :-p  But I all of a freakin sudden feel like I've reached one of those moments where I'm tripping over myself (figuratively this tiem as opposed to the literal of two weeks ago&nbsp;I mean ) ;)..to try and do 20 things at once and achieving none. In the words of the Biscuit.I'd like to take a moment:  (0)  AHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!  Okay..okay..out of the insanely matrix like system it is....why did Yoda just pop into head? Hmm..away with you...  But..as all who fail-ed before me..I need a&nbsp;plan. Not an evil plan..as much fun as that would be..just..a plan. Or maybe no plan. Plan=procrastinate? Probably...  Anyhoo..it feels like the roadblocks have been removed..I've done my thing with my friends (Doors concert last weekend.Amazing with a capital A)..family (sorting out years of clutter and selling/donating on)...I'm close to getting my life into a box..but where do&nbsp;I take it?  I feel kind of surplus to events now..like&nbsp;I just need to disappear in the best possible way...and get on with it...I'm teetering on the edge..  ...I just need to take the leap. 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ans: It should be.  Okay time lapse between here and there *dons quantum physiscist glasses* lost time (divided by) arm damage (please note ARM not 'arms', arms damage a whole different equation where I come from) ;-)= % empty space-relative to how the world turns..so..huh..what?   Anyway to summarise time was lost and thoughts of mind were wasted ;-) To backtrack (on second thoughts maybe not because I'd probably fall over) I..er..fell over (my own feet)..tore three muscles in my arm and twisted one in my leg. Not a bruise on me...just y'know your regular internal agony :-p  So the arm was slung up and the world carried out without me. Tennis ended (Sharapova-Yay!, Federer-Yay! Roddick-Yay-yay-yay!) ;-o  Ditto football: Soccer pundits in shock shocker! The Greeks are (suprisingly it seems) cunning stratagists? Never! ;-)  Otherwise arm recovery aside (relax special squad...I said ARM recovery)..it's good week..tomorrow The Doors..next week the world! (hmm..there probably is a band called The World you know)..but..yay..The Doors..spirit of Jim be with us ;-p I am also staying in a hostel fo the first time in 6 years..so..interesting. But I have 4 boys looking after me so I think I'll be okay ;-)  Hmmm..why am I seized by the urge lately to die my hair raven black?  Answers on a nomad please...  
    
</post>


</Blog>