<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Your icon is....... by beautiful1      Full Name           Age           Favorite Color           Your icon is....                  Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Who were you in a past life?  by  urlLink  Kat007        Name:           Birthdate:           Favorite Color:           Country:           You were most probably:    Edgar Allan Poe       If not then you were:    Katsushika Hokusai              Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
               i woke up kinda early today, just wanted to check out stuff on ebay. emm this week is starting off pretty crappy. I'm just confused and have caught someone in some lies. THey don't even know it. confrontation is the only way to know actual truth. things happen i guess..  for the worst and best at times.           To end a crappy week, i propose that i get drunk and have a good time this weekend. I invited my best/f yasmin to stay over for as long as she wants. i think my humor and her are the only things keeping me sane these dayz. We're planning on having a good time, maybe chill with anthony, if he's around.          Just a while ago, i was talking to kurk (ex). He says his day will consist of cutting his beautiful long hair, which i threatend to make him in trouble if he cuts it all off. its long and cute. he says he's just gonna trim it. i hope thats all. any how, i told him about my problem and he was just all ears, and that was great of him to do so.                                               laterz
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         now as things have come to arise. . everything seems kinda well. I called nick yesterday and as soon as i said the way i felt he completley understood,it was great. he said he would never stop having feelings for me, but that we should just wait it out and see how things go from here. i think thats only the truth. So we're willing to wait, both of us. and things feel great again.            Today i went to a show, where one of my fav bands were playing, once again awesome! lol jake was all like hi, and well the rest of the band were out of it, it was so hot inside that place.      emmm and now i am just lounging around doing nothing, well maybe i might help my mom garden, if not go in my room like always and be boring cause i just find that oh so much fun.                                               life goes on. .     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           YES, confused is the word, or maybe just not sure. .  I dunno, all i know is that i finally realized i have commitment problems. I woke up like yesterday and a light bulb flashed in my head. I'm a bit afraid of commitment.      Lets rewind by like 2 nights ago. . .           I couldn't go to sleep so i was online about 1 in the morning. All of a sudden nick logs on and we're talking (i.e- Nick is a friend ive known for aprx 4yrs.)   So everything is well and i dunno, he just started pouring his guts out to me in a very beautiful way. a while back i did ask him out but he said no. so it was like fine whatever, i wasn't going to be angery, instead i continued to befriend him like i had always did. Now, he has feelings for me.. and i don't know what to say.      I'm flatterd, and afraid. i care so much for him, but i'm just afraid of getting my heart broken, i think the reason is because i've grown up around heart break and don't want to have to feel that kind of pain ever. I've been like this seriously for as long as about 2 yrs and it sucks. Lets just say i'm good at running away from my problems.          I don't know what to do. . 
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Breaking the Habit"            Breaking the habit to stop failing at looking like someone i'm not in others eyes            Breaking the habit to letting my heart play with so many "friends" antics.                     The beginning of somthing. . .
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           lifes has been boring as usual, . . . i'll finish this later
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           What do people really think about you?  by Raven319      Name           Age           favorite song           Parents think    You&#39;re an angel      Strangers think    You&#39;re hot      Friends think    Your psychic              urlLink  Quiz created with MemeGen  !     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  i woke up kinda early, but its ok, i had to start on my laundry before i go over to yasmins house. I'm gonna stay over and chill with her, then we have to wake up super early and get up on monday so we can go downtown so she can get her I.D.&nbsp;     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; emmmm i talked to anthony yesterday. he's been cool, but kinda nervous about the up coming school year at juarez, i told him that everything will be alright. > thats what i like about our friendship we believe in each other at&nbsp;the worst moments in life.    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; laterz&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Kris      3 's   Nick  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 07-24-04  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I was at my cousins house yesterday and it was so boring, she said we were gonna go to the movies then when i got there she was all like, "oh we might not go to the movies"&nbsp; lol wtf   anyhow the whole time that&nbsp;i was there she was helping her sister watch some kids&nbsp; although she didn't have to.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; sooo around 8 my other cousin came home from work and we were set to prolly go to the movies and then there all like "oh ceci won't take us" whats wrong with taking the bus? i said, "ohh this late? and who will pick us up?"&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; : P   whatever so i wasted another day doing nothing once again, no big diffrence there.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; to add to the baddness of it all, the whole time i was there, before my other cousin came home, my other cousin was just sitting there, not even talking to me.&nbsp; oh well, happends all the time.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; emm i went home at around 9:30pm, with 25 bucks still left in my pocket and a wasted day to look back on.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; oh well   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; i tryed calling anthony, but i couldn't reach him,&nbsp; i really needed to talk to him.&nbsp; so that sucked.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; laterz  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and my sister&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SCORPIO Your emotions may take you on a roller-coaster ride today, but there's no danger of falling off the tracks. You have more stability than you realize, even if you feel like you are lost in a deep fog. The more closed in the mists are, the more you'll need to rely on your intuition to figure out what's on the outside. Hang out with good friends now, for they can give you the support that you need, in order for you to maintain your direction, no matter how poor the vision is at this time.   LIBRA You already know that you don't have to express every emotion that you feel. But this doesn't mean that you shouldn't feel them. If you bury emotions, you will end up being controlled by your fears instead of by love. Even in the workplace, you'll be pulled between the safety of rational thoughts and the vulnerability of feelings. Logic may create security, but it won't cure loneliness. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
               lol i read yesterdays entry. pretty hard core, i seem really mad              as a matter of fact i am still but i'm all mellow about it now, i don't care.       today sucked and yea thats about it. Laterz         _morbid*
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             This week has been pretty bummy. . . i literally threw a quiet tantrum in my room a few days ago, because i guess i just realised how much my life sucks. i mean yea it sucks but i think i really needed to confront my anger, and it felt good.  and a couple dayz ago my pops told my ma, that he sensed i was unhappy, lol yea your thinking parents are suppose to know that kinda thing but he's my step pops, any how that draws the conclusion of knowing wheather any type of parent can feel a person that they love's emotion without having to say a word.    emm but i guess they felt my sadness and decided to cheer me up with a gift that i very much enjoyed. They bought me a new tinkerbell journal with satin lace as a lock, emm a pink kitty bling bling necklace. a packet of stationary/ notebook paper with a farie design and a folder with tinkerbell on it, it was like old skool though with a spray paint effect. as i said i enjoyed it, it cheered me up but i still don't feel all that well. i'm grateful to have parents that care like that i know, even thought i call them losers and stuff. lol         : ) i love yellow card, heh just had to say that, i always have, even after all this bs about fame. i knew they were gonna be big one day. . .           i talked to nick on sunday and em i don't know wheather i should be mad or confused or whatever, as a matter of fact i shouldn't be anything, its not like we're going out, but i asked why he seems so disclosed off and such, i mean at first i started to understand but then he just basically gave me an excuse that eaither anyone can use or he really ment it, and i think he ment it. i just can't figure why i'm the one feeling like a loser at the end , when he phrases that telling ppl how u are is a foolish thing to act apon. any how it made me think, and i myself have always been an open person , but not retartedly open where i'm spilling about my whole life. lol believe, believe ppls there are ppl like that, it happends to me all the time, and i don't know why. but in a way i sense this thing he has as being selfish, and if he's not willing to open himself a bit up more for me then i can't possibly understand how he can go and tell me he has feelings for me and he cares and stuff.   In all actuallity it adds up to nothing, i've known him for quite sometime and it seems he's closer to his other online buddies then to me, and i'e been there, i've never been a problem yet it would be a foolish thing to open up to me, and as a matter of fact our conversations have been a rather bit dull since the whole confession thing.        This has taught me to keep my mouth shut and go on with life. that right there has added another reason to quit the whole online thing. i've already told him that but this ones another reason.           I hate ppl who think the only way to reach someone to talk is the internet, that fucked up bullshit and i will not stand for that.    in total i must have about 8 friends on all messengers *i.e  yahoo,aim,aol    and eaither they are all the same pple on each messenger and i know them in person, sooo whats the problem?                                                     Laterz P.s  Erica is the best and she knows it, shes having a hard time, and i'm there         
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lets talk this over,  It's not like we're dead,  Was it something I did,  Was it something you said?  Don't leave me hanging,  In a city so dead,  Held up so high,  I'm such a breakable thread.  You were all the things I thought I knew  and I thought we could be...  You were everything, everything that I wanted  We were meant to be, suppose to be but we lost it  All of the memories, so close to me just fade away  All this time you were pretending,  So much for my happy ending.  You've got your dumb friends,  I know what they say,  They tell you I'm difficult,  but so are they.  but they don't know me,  Do they even know you?  All the things you hide from me,  All the shit that you do.  It's nice to know that you were there,  Thanks for acting like you cared  and making me feel like I was the only one.  It's nice to know we had it all,  Thanks for watching as I fall  and letting me know we were done.  He was everything, everything that I wanted  We were meant to be, suppose to be, but we lost it  all the memories, so close to me just fade away  All this time you were pretending  So much for my happy ending                 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          so my parents threw me off yesterday, emm where was i? yea so we stayed for a while over there with erika, we all just chilled at the picknic table and talked. emm we left around 10pm, and anthony walked us home, lol *confession* i was happy to see him, only because i have few friends that i hardley see and he was one of them.  We got to my house, he couldnt stay for long so we walked him half way back and that was possibly the end. emmm as soon as we got back, we ate, and richard, one of my ma's friends was all spilling, and saying everyoen had a bet the me and my pal were gonna get wasted, so we drank a shot and that was the end for me and her drinking up,  i drank mines for nick, cause i missed him so much, i still do.  So that was for nick,    emm after that we watched a movie and watched as richard threw up outside my house because he was more drunk then he expected everyone else to. lol it was funny, then we fell asleep.        That was the end of that.   overall i had a great 4th of july.                  laterz          
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              Yasmin just left.  I'm bored already.  lol We had a great time these dayz she stayed. She came that saterday i complained about the rain. Our 4th was pretty good, we chillaxed in the pool for a few hours till some pple showed up for the party my parents were throwing. We drank up kinda early, but it was ok riight? it was 4th of July. We had some jello shots before we visted Erika at her uncles house. She completley awesome, i hadnt met her before, we just only talk on the phone or what not. Yea she was straight.  emmm we stayed over there for a while         i will continue this later. . .
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Its raining outside, and me and yasmin are bored as fuck. nothing more to say.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                 so i have waken up, and its boring all over again, well not until maybe later on tonight when my sister leaves to her grannys which therefore will continue on to a 3 day RV drive to KY for the week. And i might go pick up yasmine for our week of funn. Hopefully she can come today, if not some other day. emm, i cleared things up with nick and all is well. he mentioned his past relationships were haunting him, whatever that means. but i'm sure he will be fine. i truley do care for him. he's been on my mind so much latley.                         i think i was completly under the in fluence of something bad, because i woke up this morning and fire was buring in the pit outside and my sister told me i had lite it yesterday night like around 2 while keily was here and we were just sitting around the pit laughing about nothing. oh well, another memory i can't remember.                                              Laterz
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                 i havent written in a while. . . emm i left off with the pedicure, emm i can't wait to go to florida on the 19th, i'm countin down the days, i picked up my contact lenses a few days ago, i can finally see   : )             i'm going job hunting this week coming up before i leave to FL. me and yasmin really need to start our plan, once we get jobs, things will be on good terms, i'm so excited, i can't wait to move out next year around this time i hope. Shes going through hard times right now, but our plan is holding her, us up, so many ppl don't believe but she and i will prove them wrong.             i start school the 24th, day after i get back from vacation, i'm gonna be bummed but its ok, that day is a start to so many new and great things to happen, hopefully i'll start working that day. i feel like i'm on cloud nine. . . atleast for this moment, i know maybe i might not be on cloud nine some other day, but one of these days to have is awesome. i know i've only just talked to nick yesterday but i miss him already.    he's the greatest to me. . . my heart belongs to u   ~  yellowcard  ~   . . .   everything is gonna be alright  . . .  be stong  , . .   believe  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      todays monday? yea ok,   emm i went and got myself a pedicure a few hours ago, and now i'm just lounging around talking to baily. . . i will continue if i get the time. . .
    
</post>


</Blog>