<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dear readers  this is just a quick note to say that if u r reading this could u please post a new thingy and put ur blogger address in eg: http://akkadian_halliwell_akasha.blogspot.com/ is mine  thanking you greatly  deejay
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey there people who will read this  my name is akasha brown. my nickname is deejay. don't ask me how i got that cing as my name is akasha jayne brown. i am 16 years old and i am in yr 10. (high school). i love reading and surfing the net and watching tv/movies.  my fav serieses are harry potter and deltora quest (1,2,3) and of course artemis fowl. i am currently reading harry potter and the chamber of secrets for like the 2rd or 3rd time and deltora quest 3-dragons nest.  my fav movies are troy, harry potter (all 3), 2 fast 2 furious, the fast and the furious, pirates of the caribbean, lord of the rings (all 3), the mummy and the mummy returns.  my fav actors are orlando bloom, eric banna, tom felton, daniel radcliffe, billy boyd, dominic monaghan and sean astin.  my fav food would most likely be pizza and chocolate moose.and my fav drinks would have to be lemon aid and diet coke.  there will be contests and piccies on here so keep a sharp eye open. also there will be questions about urself.......  well must go  deejay  ps. there must always b a ps. (tradition) pps. my fav colour is green and i am single (almost)
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey there every1...you guys said that u wanted quizzes so here is another 1...  in which movie (came out between the years of december 2000 and january 2004) would i find this saying...  "Cold be heart and hand and bone Cold be travelers far from home They do not see what lies ahead When sun has failed and moon is dead"  ok....i have posted my email address/es on here at least twice so u can contact me at 1 of those 2...  heres wat u need 2 email me...   the date (day/month/year) of the movie being released in the cinemas  the name of the movie  the name of the character who speaks those lines  the name of the actor who plays the character   ok.....u got all that???  well good luck....  thanks 4 checking out my blog...  deejay 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       in wat book would i find these words??? &nbsp; "Rohan had come at last"  email me at  urlLink akkadian_halliwell@hotmail.com  ur answer must include:   wat book  the author of the book  wat page it is on  wat chapter it is in.      email me with ur name, ur blogger spot and&nbsp;ur answer. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if you want a 60 question quiz on Lord of the Rings - The Fellowship of the Ring then email me at  urlLink orlandos_blondbitch@hotmail.com   also i am very new to this so don't ask much more of me....i am still a learner...  &nbsp; thanks&nbsp; to those 2 who have posted a comment onto my blog...thanks  &nbsp; decifer this  "delelltorelaneeleledselelyoeluelel"  post a comment &amp; tell me if ur answer. 
    
</post>


</Blog>