<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today quite uneventful, which is fine with me, seeing as any day in the hellhole that is Terre Haute South Vigo High School is worse than being infibulated by a searing hot steel stake. Okay... so maybe I exaggerated a bit but it really isn't fun being at school. I was watching the news yesterday and I saw a segment about racial profiling. For those who don't know racial profiling is basically picking someone out of a crowd because of their race. There are many kinds of profiling from gender profiling, religious profiling, social class profiling, etc. Mr. Pedde (a man who has a blogspot, atavist.blogspot.com) reminded me in his latest blog that profiling has been happening for a very long time. It is sickening to think that anyone could just pick someone else out of the crowd as a target for their aggression, etc. just because of how they look. If the people here on Earth don't grow up and stop fighting and judging each other then I don't think the human race is going last past till the end of my grandchildren's lifetime. We need to start working together and start working out our problems without guns and violence. The thing that sets the humans apart from the rest of the kingdom animalia is our ability to see the difference between right and wrong. Well now that I'm done ranting about the flaws of our society I think I'll leave who feels the need to read a while to ponder what I have just said. Until next time salve.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i still have a headache from my stupid braces. i went riding dirt bikes with my dad and his friend yesterday in thompson's ditch. i went down this crazy steep hill and almost killed myself. then i was going down another hill and i killed the bike halfway down, but then the momentum of the bike started it back up. heheheheh. i got very lucky. i ride a 1996 ktm 250cc, its crazy big, for me anyway. my dads friend is crazy, and he was getting like 2-3 feet of air out of the ditch. he didnt even have a helmet on. then after that i came home and saved my zelda game and went to sleep. well, today i slept until noon because i felt like crap, and then i went outside (arghhh) and took my sisters swimming. and now after being on the interweb and looking at other stuff, im here. so i'll just leave you all with that, bye bye.
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      o if anyone knows of any websites where you can custom configure a computer please give the url.
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i'm probably going to end up forgetting all about this blog in about 2 weeks, but hopefully not. today sucked because i had to get braces on. they dont feel too good and make eating a pain in the a$$. im planning on buying a new computer from digitalstormonline.com. if all goes as planned then i should have it ordered soon. im going to see a movie on saturday sometime after 4 o'clock if anyone wants to come. just IM me or something if you want to go. well im off to frolick on the interweb now, so bye bye.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I think there might actually be a something that might make school bearable this year. This one person that I have had on my mind at least once everyday this summer. But I don't think that she feels the same. We used to talk all the time, and we were good friends, but now I don't see her because it's summer and I don't have a car. I think about her everyday. I don't think that I've felt this strongly about a&nbsp;person before. Is this love that I feel, or is just an overblown case of infatuation? I want her to know that I feel this strongly about her and that I have ever since we started talking. Well I'm off. Salve.     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well its been a while since I've felt the need to post. Well actually I don't even know why I'm this, but oh well. I'm thinking about learning how to play guitar. It seems like playing guitar has suddenly become the "cool" thing to do now. But I don't think I should let that stop me considering that I don't want to play just because "everybody" is doing. At least I don't think I am.&nbsp; Well I think I'm going to go look around on eBay now. Salve.    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whelp, it's been a while since I last posted, partially because I've been to busy and because I've been to lazy. Nothing new has happened that I can recall since my last post. My dad just bought a 1996 Trans Am convertible with only 9k miles on it for $15,000. He traded in our 2000 Chevy Venture. I personally think the dealer raked him over the coals on the trade, the van, according to them is only worth $8,700 when the Kelly Blue Book price is around $14,000. But he wanted to get rid of the van so he went for it. Right now, I'm working on finishing Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic for Xbox. I've had it for a while but I've been playing other games and riding dirt bikes. It's definitely worth picking up if haven't already. Well I'm off to finish beating it now, so until next time, salve.
    
</post>


</Blog>