<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      this is truly not what I had in mind when I decided to start this blog post.  But hey I just had breakfast and my mind's a blank and the only thing that I can think of is the way I had eaten my breakfast.  I started eating the dessert first.. I do that often..   Anyway, I had this cute cake from Bizu, a small cake that looks too good to eat.. it was given to me by my officemate, Ariel, as a bday gift 4 days ago. It has 2 cherries... and since I was bored beyond recognition I decided to do this thing with the cherries..I got so tired of trying that I quit it..conceded.. and thought that maybe I wasn't a good kisser after all ;) got no complaints so far..so maybe that thing with the cherries are all talk. haha!  After that my typical breakfast would be beef noodles (which was quite salty by the way).. so it was kinda weird eating the noodles after eating something so sweet.    But hey, life's like that.. happened to me once, twice, countless of times.. I started with something sweet and ended up tasting something salty and hot and sometimes when noodles are not cooked properly, its soggy.  I go thru relationships that start out like the cake I just ate.  It just  looks too good to be true.  I finish it off and then I start with the main course.. the meat of the meal.  The one that may burn your tongue and yet its the one that fills you, the one that makes you think that you're full and that you better stop eating..   Going out on dates are like that... (in my opinion anyway).. You eat dessert first.. everything's sweet and perfect..(phone calls, text messages, movies, and coffee table conversations) and then you decided to make it official.. you take a bite of the main meal..(more phone calls, more text messages, scheduled dates every weekend..you don't even call it a "date" anymore..since you two are now officially together)  and then its up to you to decide that you've had enough.. and it may just end there.. or maybe.. just maybe...the two of you may be all game for another round of the dessert.. and its all sweet all over again.  that i envy.  
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      go ahead and read the lyrics of this song that I find myself singing lately.. i'm sure some of you have been in such a hopeless, pathetic and totally sad situation...  You give your hand to me  And then you say, "Hello."  And I can hardly speak,  My heart is beating so.  And anyone can tell You think you know me well.  Well, you don't know me. (no you don't know me)   No you don't know the one  Who dreams of you at night;  And longs to kiss your lips  And longs to hold you tight  Oh I'm just a friend.  That's all I've ever been.  Cause you don't know me. (no you don't know me)   For I never knew the art of making love,  Though my heart aches with love for you.  Afraid and shy, I let my chance go by.  A chance that you might love me too. (love me too)   You give your hand to me,  And then you say, "Goodbye."  I watched you walk away,  Beside the lucky guy  Oh, you'll never ever know  The one who loved you so.  Well, you don't know me   (For I never knew the art of making love, )  (Though my heart aches with love for you. )  Afraid and shy, I let my chance go by.  A chance that you might love me too. (love me too)   Oh, you give your hand to me,  And then you say, "Goodbye."  I watched you walk away,  Beside the lucky guy  Oh, you'll never ever know  The one who loved you so.  Well, you don't know me (you don't love me, you don't know me) 
      
</post>


</Blog>