<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so yesterday was good..i felt like i was finally worth something to someone and i even got to talk to people that i havent talked to in so long. i went to the zoo and had a party with kt and suzy. It was great. we flung food to the baboons and they ate it!! i was like...oops...i didnt do it. it was just ice cream..or that ice thing thats like ice cream but its not and i cant think of the name of it. anyways, we went to a bunch of exibits and saw lots of coolio little animals and they were all spiffy and such. hehe. i saw this one animal called a...ok i dont remember but it was cool...OH WAIT!! it was a tapir...its pronounced...tape- er...lol. yeah so we went to the water place and we brought in food and talked to the turtle for a while. after that, we leaned on this water wall where there was water going all over the place and we got really wet. it was funny because after that, we jumped on a random stage and like started dancing... this guy was checking us out and his friend goes, "hey! stop checking them out!" haha it was funny because we just kept going. ok so then after all the fun times at the zoo, we decided to buy stuff from the stores and food places. we got this big giant pretzel and i was throwing random pieces at the birds. oh but before that, we bought these animal head chomper things... like you squeeze the trigger and the head on top bites down!! its so freaking fantabulous!so anyways, back to my story.... we were making the animal heads chomp down on pretzel parts and its just too hard to explain haha it was great though. ok so we left and we talked on the grass for a lil while talking about random stories...haha boozin susan! ok im done. then kt's mom came a got us. so we went to borders and suzy was listening to something weird so we(me and kt) went and hid in a random isle and started screaming...MARCO!!! some dude was like...POLO!!!! so we did that for a bit and then i screamed MOMMY! for some reason and this lady goes...WHAT!!!!!!! hahahaha we stopped and suzy finally found us. we bought cheesecake and ate most of it and ....i like those  forks  that we "used". so we left with our little notebook and went to kt's. we tried to set up the tent and then climbed all the way across the bridge...and yes i did say..CLIMB! that was great. ok so the tent was all set up and i was going crazy with that damn bug spray(i still got bit too! bastard mosquitoes!) then lauren came over and we decided to walk to jackie's house (our other dazzler friend)and we got the grand tour of her house and we told stories of past years on our teams and the horrors of lauren whittaker (the coach last year). after all that, we skipped home and threw coins at each other. oweeeeeeee yes someone threw it at my head but i didnt say anything....if anything it was probably me doing it to myself.hehe. ok so we got to her house and showed jackie the creek. then the hard part came. we tried to start the fire.... hahaha it was so funny. i was a little...um...how to say this without making myself sound crazy?...i think i was high off the fumes because i burned my hand on the stick that i was roasting marshmellows on. lauren was spraying the logs with bug spray so the fire would light...that was funny. so the fire took 2 hours to get going and i was throwing like so much newspaper in and it looked like i put a tree in it...hmmmm...shut up i didnt do that!! lol ok yeah i did. then we roasted stuff and suzy tried to burn...marshmellows, hot dogs and bread...yeah it was great. so we put the fire out and we drove jackie home. lauren and suzy sat in the trunk....*weird look*. then we went home and started to get ready for bed.we had the flashlights on and we wrote in our note book for a while then talked for a while longer.we tried to sleep and i have nooooo idea what time it was. i got to lay on a rock and a bean bag. lauren and suzy stole the warm comforter and me and kt were stuck with a damn sheet. it was freaking cold....so me and kt were like laying on each other and suzy and lauren were on top of us so we were just rolling around the whole time. later it was silent and i got a few moments to myself. i looked out the partially unzipped tent that had a mosquito net and i just watched the stars until eventually i could barely see them because i was half asleep and half still watching. that night was a good night... a night where i can say i really was happy...a night where my wishing star was watching me and making my night be a good one.  the next morning... 6am and we were woken up by mrs hughes. slowly we got ready to skate and headed out to the rink. we got there and lauren, suzy and kt all went out and i didnt have to until 9:45. so i sat there for two hours randomly talking to people or playing with the little kids. lauren had a rough day today...damn rough days!! *shakes fist* and everyone left but me and a few others because it was my turn to skate. i did ok... and then i went home and took a shower and now here i am!!! :) lol im done...wasnt that great ok i have to go now because i feel like it....bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok on the survey one the time wasnt right but the one before this one was right..
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      rawr the stupid time wont fix!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ABOUT YOU  Your full name:: jamie trillana Age:: 15 Height:: 5'6" Natural hair colour:: brown and black Eye colour:: dark brown...sometimes purple Number of siblings:: 1 Glasses/contacts?:: both..damn bad vision! Piercings:: ears Tattoos:: none Braces?::yes...rawr  FAVOURITE  Colour:: blue or red Band::hoobastank, evanescance, im sure there are more.. Song::wow i have alot... uh..too many to name Stuffed animal::my tiger thats says "someobdy loves you" my mommy gave it to me when i passed fs 5 Video game:: DOA, super smash brothers, final fantasy (theres alot of those)grand theft auto TV show:: chapelle's show, simpsons,crcodile hunter..lol..whose line is it anyway Movie::something about mary, pirates of the carribean, all the home movies me and my friends make.  Book:: queen's fool Food:: eggrolls.. Game on a cell phone:: someone "stole" my phone. CD cover:: i dont know i usually just get my cd's burned or i steal cds for a year...(sorry kt lol) Scent::dazzling, beautiful, miracle, bikini Animal:: dog, fish, flamingo with skates Comic book::dont have one. Cereal:: frosted flakes or cinnamon toast crunch  Website:: none Cartoon:: GI JOE!!!!!! hahahaha suzy!!!  DO YOU  Play an instrument?:: saxamaphone Watch TV more than 60 hours a week?:: probably..actually maybe not because im out skating Like to sing?:: yeah but i suck.. Have a job?::not yet unless you count skate rental whenever i go.. Have a cell phone?:: no :( Like to play sports?::yes'm skating, football, volleyball  Have a boyfriend/girlfriend?:: nope Have a crush on someone?:: i did...it fades in and out Live somewhere NOT in the united states?:: for like a month i lived in the philippines Have more than 5 TVs in your house?::no we have 4...1 doesnt work Have any special talents/skills?::i can skate and do spirals... thats it..lol Excercise daily?::hell no...hehe i should im gonna get fatter Like school?:: nooooooooooooooooooooooooooo  CAN YOU  Sing the alphabet backwards?:: why the freak would i try and do that Stand on your tip toes without wearing shoes?:: yes but last time  did my toe cramped for an hour.. Speak any other languages?:: filipino Go a day without food?:: yeah Stay up for more than 24 hours?:: if i wanted to...not likely Read music, not just tabs?:: yeah  Roll your tongue?:: yeah...it makes me laugh Eat a whole pizza?:: only if was like reeeeeeeeeeally hungry  HAVE YOU EVER  Snuck out of the house?:: no asian parents have those weird shifty eyes and watch you all the freakin time...its creepy. Cried to get out of trouble?:: YEAH!! Gotten lost in your city?:: yeah i got lost walking to a store and ended up in romeoville..haha thats sad Seen a shooting star?:: i dont thinkg so Been to any other countries besides the united states?:: philippines Had a serious surgery?:: no Stolen something important to someone else?:: no Solved a rubiks cube?:: hahahahaha thats funny!! me?solving a rubics cube!!? only if i just buy it and lie and say i just did it. Gone out in public in your pajamas?:: of course Cried over a girl?:: not exactly over her...but because she said or did something to upset me.. Cried over a boy?:: a few Kissed a random stranger?:: no Hugged a random stranger?:: yeah!! all the time...most of them are friendly and think im high or something Been in a fist fight?:: no one has angered me that much...except my brother...then yes....i fight alot Been arrested?:: no Done drugs?:: no Had alcohol?:: yeah once when i was at a batmitzfa and i thought it was juice...and then there was the other times...im not gonna get into those. Laughed and had milk come out of your nose?:: yeah...it was weird Pushed all the buttons on an elevator?:: yeah! omg i didnt know what floor my room was on so i went in all of them and there were at least 30 floors and other people came on the evlevator and they were all confused like. Gone to school only to find you had the day off because of a holiday/etc?:: almost.. Swore at your parents?:: no Been to warped tour?:: No  Kicked a guy where it hurts?:: oh many times! Been in love?:: i believe so Been close to love?:: yeah Been to a casino?:: yeah...its kinda hard not to when you go to vegas...and when your parents have issues about going there. they made me go there for my birthday...what the fluck am i supposed to do there... they wouldnt let me in so i had to stay in the car..on my birthday Ran over an animal and killed it?:: no i saw a bunny get run over on the way to my friends house.. Broken a bone?:: never  Gotten stitches?:: no Had a waterballoon fight in winter?:: yeah i actually have...but i was bad because when i got hit with the balloon it was frozen and so i got hit with an ice balloon...owe that hurt.. Drank a whole gallon of milk in one hour?:: not in an hour.. Made homemade muffins?:: nope Bitten someone?:: yes Been to disneyland/disneyworld?:: yeah  More than 5 times?:: only once when i was like 4 Been to niagra falls?:: yeah...at first i thought that said viagra falls...i was really confused Burped in someones face?:: yes  Gotten the chicken pox?:: yea   WHENS THE LAST TIME YOU  Brushed your teeth::an hour ago Went to the bathroom:: an hour ago  Saw a movie in theaters:: i went to see stepford wives and snuck in like 3 bags of chinese food with my friends Read a book:: school Had a snow day:: no idea  Had a party:: when i was 8 i think Had a slumber party:: at my house? or someone elses? because that only happened like 3 times at my house...stupid parentals you know Made fun of someone:: just now Tripped in front of someone:: this morning Went to the grocery store:: iono Got sick:: no idea Cursed:: just now.. i did just for this question  PICK ONE  Fruit/vegetables:: fruit Black/white:: black  Lights on/lights off:: lights off TV/movie:: movie Car/truck:: car Body spray/lotion:: lotion  Cash/check:: cash Pillows/blankets:: blankets you could roll up blankets to make a pillow...pillows dont really do much...lol. Headache/stomach ache:: headache well actually...i wouldnt want either.. Paint/charcoal:: charcoal Chinese food/mexican food:: chinese food Summer/winter:: winter Snow/rain:: rain Fog/misty:: misty  Rock/rap:: rock  Meat/vegetarian:: meat Boy/girl:: boy Chocolate/vanilla:: chocolate  Sprinkles/icing:: sprinkles  Cake/pie:: cake French toast/french fries:: french fries Strawberries/blueberries:: strawberries Ocean/swimming pool::swimming pool because i freak out at the damn fishies trying to eat me Hugs/kisses:: kisses Cookies/muffins:: cookies Wallet/pocket:: pocket  Window/door:: window  Emo/goth:: iono Pink/purple:: pink  Cat/dog:: dog Long sleeve/short sleeve:: well i like short sleeves except when my arms break out. Pants/shorts:: depends on the weather Winter break/spring break:: winter break i like cold Spring/autumn:: autumn my bday is there and everything is all pretty like Clouds/clear sky:: clear Moon/mars:: Moon  FRIENDSHIP  How many friends do you have?::well it depends on what you call friends... i have good ones and bad ones What are their names?::kt, suzy, lauren, leah, meghan, riza, rutter, nathan, and so many more Do you have a best friend?:: yes Have you ever liked one of your friends?:: yes..  Do you have more guy friends or more girl friends?:: girls Have you ever lost a friend?:: yeah  Have you ever gone to an amusement park with a friend?:: yeah...at that time i called a pole a tree..hehe Whats an inside joke between you and a friend?:: oh man theres alot...rip slip brush ahhh...rip snip burn ahhhh... poles and trees... suzy is gonna be a hooker... gt in laurens basement...me breaking beds...and wow!...tag blanket chair and belt... meghan falling into creeks... me walking into things..damn purple unitards...ana crying because of frogs..omg theres so many more!!! Have you ever gotten in a big arguement with a friend?:: yeah  Whats the nicest thing youve ever done for a friend?:: i dont know...ask them Whats the nicest thing a friend has ever done for you?::they all stood up for me when certain people were just upsetting me..(cough lauren w and barb cough) Do you miss any of your old friends?::yes...alot because i htink of them when some things come up and i just wish they were still here What friend have you known the longest?:: michelle kenney Do you regret anything youve done to a friend?:: yeah How often do you spend time with your friends?:: any time my parents arent being stupid and let me go out or anytime i can just go without them knowing Do any of your friends drive?:: yeah.. Has a friend of yours ever died?:: yeah...my next door neighbor was my friends and he died because of his athsma Whats the dumbest thing youve done with a friend?:: oh...well id tell you but thats ok What do you think your friends think of you?:: maybe they like me...  LOVE AND ALL THAT CRAP  Have you ever been in love?:: didnt you ask that already? If you have, with who?:: thats for me to know Are you single?:: yup Are you in a relationship?::no If so, for how long?:: i said no Do you believe there is someone for everyone?:: well...i dont really know about that...i believed it for a while but that doesnt nessasarily mean that youll find that person What is your idea of the best date?:: well...walking outside at night where you could see the stars and watching the rain What was your first kiss like?:: oh man.... i was like freaking out and so was he so he completely missed my face and kissed my head...it was soooo very sad  How old were you when you got your first kiss?:: 6 lol one of the kids i hung with liked me and therefor he decided to kiss my head...lol Do you think love is a load of shit?:: well it really depends because sometimes it could lift you up from all the pain you feel but other times, it knocks you further down than youve ever been Whats the best experiance youve ever had with the opposite sex?:: we sat together and we watched fireworks. he gave me his sweater and for once i felt perfectly happy and forgot all my problems If you are single, have you had any boyfriends/girlfriends before?:: yeah Have you ever been dumped?:: no Have you ever dumped someone?:: yeah sorry guys...i just get bored really easily   WORD ASSOCIATION  Slippers:: fluffy Hat:: peterpan Hard:: knock life Free:: cigerettes Space:: stars Taste:: of chicago because i finally went this year Good charlotte:: nathan...i dont know why i think of him.. Red:: love Deep:: emotion Heart:: pump Cord:: cordless Cheese:: yellow Rain:: sleep Work:: hard Pedal:: bike Head:: bobble head dolls Bed:: sleep Fluff:: pillow Hardcore::bands  Race:: flag Knife:: eh...i think you know Jump:: high  I....  am:: jamie want:: to skate need:::to skate crave::skating love::to skate  hate::when people are two faced did::your mom  feel::weird miss::my friends am annoyed by:: pop ups and bastards would rather:: jump in a lake am tired of:: frustration will always:: love you...haha now that song is gonna be stuckin my head SILLY STUFF  What is your favourite genre of music?::stuff What time is it now?:: 1:40 What day is it?::wednesday Whens the last time you called someone?:: 15 minutes ago How much money do you have right now?:: 24 dollars Are you hungry?:: no Whatcha doin?:: what the freak else would i be doing Do you like parades?:: only when i dont have to march in it Do you like the moon?:: yes'm What are you going to do when youre done with this?:: practice my synchro program Isnt cup a funny word when you repeat it over and over?:: no...i like the word nisspee. hahaha try saying that 10 times... (make sure you know that if you say it, youre actually saying penis...) If you could have any magical power what would it be?:: i wish i could be telepathic and talk to animals  Have you ever had a picnic?:: i havent had one...but ive gone to one  Did you ever have one of those skip-its when you were young?:: no i wanted one though What about sock em boppers?:: no but i made one and blew up a plastic bag and punched someone but it doesnt work Are you wearing any socks right now?:: no...why do u care?  DO YOU THINK YOU ARE  funny?::no pretty?:: no sarcastic?::sometimes lazy?:: yup  hyper?:: i have my moments...espescially when i have pixie stix... friendly?:: sometimes evil?:: i dont know about that one smart?:: no strong?::no talented?::no dorky?:: yea  ASSOCIATE THESE WORDS WITH SOMEONE YOU KNOW (or dont know)  high:: snoop dogg skip:: that dude from lord of the rings...pippey? dance:: meghan lauren suzy barbi everyone who did that dance at suzy's house!!haha lonely:: beetlejuice pen:: my brother because when he was little he couldnt say ball point pen...  flower:: my mom because she likes flowers window:: uh i dont really think of anyone psycho:: lauren whittaker brain freeze:: i dont know  strange:: leah sassy:: wtf? jelly:: kt when i ate it at her house  FOR OR AGAINST  suicide:: against  love:: for  drunk drivers:: against  airplanes:: for war:: against canada:: im neutral united states:: for rock music:: for  gay marriage:: neutral school:: eh..iono surveys:: for  parents:: depends  cars:: for  killing:: against  britney spears:: hmmmmmm....  coffee:: for pants:: against  WOULD YOU EVER  Sky dive?:: maybe Play strip poker?:: yeah if i knew how and if i could shoose people playing Run away?:: yes Curse at a teacher?:: yes  Not take a shower for a week?:: ewww.. no...id smell Ask someone out?:: maybe if i liked them Lie to someone to make them think better of you?:: depends Visit a foreign country for more than a month?:: yes! Go scuba diving?:: yes Write a book?:: id get up to the 15th word and id quit Become a rockstar?:: who said i wasnt? Have casual sex?:: possibility...lol..  LAST QUESTIONS  What shampoo do you use?:: garnier fructice What kind of computer do you have?:: dell What grade are you in?::sophomore  Do you like to throw popcorn at people in the movies?:: yeah espesially if theyre doing sommething they shouldnt be doing...lol  Or just make out?:: depends on my mood How many posters do you have in your room?:: one How many cds do you have?:: a lot..most are random mixes What time is it now?:: 1:34
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi everybody...look its me typing crap again :) lol i have no life so i do it everyday. well its still morning around 11 something.i had a weird dream last night. it was like i was a regular person and then all of a sudden this weird guy pops out of nowhere and says...i have a disease where i turn into a monster... so i started like walking away and going..uh ok... but then he like grabbed me and goes...IT RENEWS ITSELF IN YOUNGER PEOPLE! i was like...uh thats great. he was all teary eyes and such.so i walked away. next thing you know it, i have the disease. i get angry and for some reason everything around me is flying everywhere and for no reason im sitting there eating corn. hehehe....its kinda like the hulk only instead of turning into a giant green dude...i turned into a corn eating freak that could throw things around by eating corn...i told you it was weird.hehe. i dont know...it was just...eh you know?lol  anyways.... i woke up and i wanted to go skating. that was like 15 minutes ago. isnt that weird how i could just wake up...go down the stairs...then fall down the next swt and then laugh and end up here? hehe. now im listening to my brother's tracks that he has on the computer... he has hillary duff... wow. ok anyways changing the song. what should i listen to? blah whatever...itll play anything. i have nothing really to say seeing that i just woke up and like nothing has happened yet. OH WAIT something did happen! i got up, put in my contacts(i lost my glasses...oh well) and came downstairs where my mom told me to get her 4 hangers...and i did and then got online.thats it. and then i talked to no one because everyone was away and no one would want to talk to me...lol. ok yeah.   i have NOTHING to say so i guess ill talk about talking about nothing. its really weird. its like you have nothing to say o you say that you have nothing to say and talk about saying nothing. yup. i type really weird... you know what i hate? i hate it when everyone goes away at the same time and then comes back and IMs me at the same time so ill have like 7 pop ups and cant even finish saying "hi". OH thats another thing i hate...i hate pop ups... those are bastards...its like youre typing and for no reason some weird advertisement like totally pops up and asks you if you want to buy a bottle of skhfiahgfakh that does something weird to your butt.. so next time a pop up called skhfiahgfakh asks you if you want something weird to happen to your butt... just say HELL NO LEAVE ME THE HELL ALONE!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHH! and then itll go away...for at least 15 minutes and then the bastard comes back and asks you if you want it again. (sarcastic voice) oh yeah... im really gonna change my mind about something happening to my butt in the last 15 minutes. ok i think ill stop because people are actually IMing me and i get distracted... thats what happened during the previous post..hehe... ok bye all! you rock my socks!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was kinda weird. i woke up around 10ish...and i like walked around my house. then i got online. talked to a few people...then i ate some food...then i decided that i wanted to try and eat a quart or rainbow sherbet...i tried...but it didnt work and i was cold so i made some soup...you know my little cup of soup..hehe. those cups of soup are good. then...i dont know im blakning out. ok well i dont fell like typing.ok im outie bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MATCHBOOK ROMANCE LYRICS  "Tiger Lily"  we drive tonight, and you are by my side. We're talking about our lives, like we've known each other forever. the time flies by, with the sound of your voice. its close to paradise, with the end surely near. if i could only stop the car and hold onto you, and never let go... i'll never let go. as we round the corner to your house you turned to me and said, "i'll be going through withdrawl of you for this one night we have spent." and, i want to speak these words but i guess i'll just bite my tongue, and accept "someday, somehow" as the words that we'll hang from.  and i... don't want to speak these words. cause i, don't want to make things anyworse.  why does tonite, have to end? why don't we hit restart, and pause it at our favorite parts. we'll skip the goodbyes. if i had it my way, i'd turn the car around and runaway, just you and i.  and i... don't want to speak these words. cause i, don't want to make things anyworse. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what happened to those things you used to say? what happened to the things we used to share? im beginning to feel like i did in 6th grade...like i did so many times before... just like when i cared. i feel like nO oNe ReMeMbErS me.. or that no one can see me anymore..  ive got a sudden change of heart.   im sick of you playing games with me...pretending you care one bit. im sitting here taking all this crap from you... this is all bullshit. im sick of standing here pretending i know you love me when you dont.. i end up turning away because its not true. all this is the crap i feel  because of you.   whatever...who really cares about that right? so what did i do today? i woke up at like 9:00 to go to church at 9:30 and then me and my family went to the taste of chicago. we got samples of random food and yeah. we got pad thai, curry fries(those were gross), some roasted corn, fried mustard catfish (that was surprisingly not too bad), like these weird cheesecake thingies, a giant turkey thing...man i should be fat by now... but then again i didnt eat much, i made my brother eat it.hee hee. anyways... after that we went home for a while and i fell asleep in the car. At around 3:25 i went back to church for this special church minister dude. It was kinda cool because it was a filipino ceremony...and ive never really seen anything from my culture and it was all spiffy and such. anywho, it was like two hours in church and me getting high off the inscence and like dying because of the fumes...(oh DAMNIT!! i left my inhaler in the pocket....oops.. oh well) yeah then i ate food...then i went to taco bell with my mom so she could get everyone else in my house food...and then she yelled at me because i supposedly "slammed" the door... sorry of the damn wind blew.. haha it didnt blow i DID slam the door but said the wind blew..oh well. yeah well she makes me mad.... always talking about how she buys me things and i get pissy... yeah mmhmm i get pissy...but im not the one yelling and screaming about me getting sick or whatnot. this year im finally sick of all the crap of her just like totally dissing my opinions...she gets mad when i fall and bruise my knees... theyre my damn knees and everyone falls when they figure skate! thats what really makes me mad... she cares more about how i look than how i feel and she thinks materialistic things like clothes that i dont even want are gonna make me happy. yep...listen to this...we go to the mall or something and she sees this shirt that she likes and i dont really like all that much...so she yells at me because i say i dont like it so i usually end up getting in a fight until i just scream fine i love it its freaking awesome!!(even if i think it's the most hideous thing on earth)nd she buys it no matter what. so since i dont like it, im not gonna wear it so she bitches at me for not wearing clothes that i "BEG" her for at the store. yeah freaking right. when i actually do want something she says i cant have it because i have too much clothing and id end up wasting it anyways. ok back to the rest of my day... after the whole taco bell thing, i went home and watched tv. then i think i went to the bathroom a coule times... got frustrated at my skin problems... then got online. I got angry at some stupid people online. i mean people can usually tell when im not in too great of a mood..and it doesnt help if you call me stupid and PMSy. that makes it worst...so pooh on you!!! you know who you are! so my day has been ladida RETARDED.   hopefully tomorrow goes better...  i wanna skate.. skate away the tears skate away emotion skate away my fears skating in fast motion...  open my eyes open the door open closed lies open my wings and soar. rip up ugly dresses rip up the feelings inside rip up inside edges in my skating i will confide within my skates, within me, theres something strong something so right and not so wrong its the place where i can always start my strongest muscle...my only heart so when im alone and i know that i am ill turn to my heart, where i will and can i no longer have to depend on you... because the only way im happy is when my heart is happy too my heart is only happy not when im on a date but my heart is happy when i smile and figure skate!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i loved someone...at least i think i did.. we used to talk and talk about everything.. you know... promised to never not love each other... that was a load of crap. look at us now... we dont talk and i spend my time thinking...what if he does remember me? so i call him up..ask if hes busy...and yes he is. so he says he'll call back. he didnt. so this all just made me understand that what i felt wasnt love... it may have been in the past... but thats just it. its in the past... well this is what i wanted...i wished on so many stars and prayed to find love or to find someone who would love me for me.. but it was a different kind of love... a love that was never meant to last. yet here i am again..searching once more for a person to love me for me. im smart..hehe.  i think i finally saw it when two of my best friends fell for each other. saw what i wish was mine... saw what i wish i had.... but i think i learned because i dont want to look for it anymore. im happy being the one and only retarded jamie who has friends who love her... and friends that she can love.  so im donating this blog to "someone" who made me realize all this... and most of all i donate it to my  friends  who were never there whenever i fell apart. dont worry im not mad... im happy now.   i remember alot of the things you used to say...so i called you up on so many days... you said the same things just as before...but now i dont care about you anymore. :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      kt says say something about her so here tis something about kt.... we like to cheer about squirrels and kt is afraid they will bite her and give her rabies. im on the phone with her right now...just like many times before...shes talking about her brother making pancakes...oohhh thats hot! guys who cook....just kidding..no offense kt's brother...ur just not my type.hehe. anyways....now kt is running around because her cat is trying to eat her. that sucks! ^because of that...i fear cats...plus the fact that they always seem to like biting me...  YEAH I WOKE UP AND FOUND SOMETHING TO WRITE ABOUT!! then i forgot it..so yeah...this is a party.  i love friends... sometimes we fight.. when i think im right...  but usually im wrong.. and then i sing a song.  Nobody knows everything about everyone..  and mothers sometimes dont even know their sons Because we all grow together... just like a goose's feathers...  yet at the same time we grow apart...  because we might need space and a new start
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      looking back on all the great times we've had...there are so many.. we had our classes together...we had so many things in common... there are so many inside jokes...soo many moments where i could laugh for hours... and yet it really makes me sad. it makes me sad that i know that i wont have things like that anymore..you moved... i guess i could take that...but now you chose the other school. well.. i guess i have to support your choice no matter how much i may hate it. we'll always be friends right? god i hope so. there's so much that i would lose if i ever lost you...meghan i never want you to go.. ive never wanted you to leave... and if i could ask for anything i would ask to have you here...and most of all for you to be happy. I know this year wasnt the best year for you.. but you have to admit we did grow through it. Ive heard that highschool changes people... and its true.. sometimes for better and sometimes not so much better...and i think that being friends with you really did help me become a little better as a person. It helped me realize things... whether it be good or bad, i still finally saw them and i have you to thank for that...thats all that matters. I feel bad because sometimes i know i wasnt exactly the best friend i could be... and im sorry for that. I love you so much. and i dont ever want to lose you...EVER. Freshman year was hell...but sophomore year is gonna be hell too.. ive already lost people i care about.. already done enough damage to myself.. and now one of the best people i could ever know has to leave. It hasnt quite hit me yet... that soon one day we might just not talk...and not realize it... but im scared of that everyday. you were the reason i made it through this year... and i knew i could always count on you. there are so many things on my mind.. and yet i cant find the words to let it all out. but then again... ive always been that way. I never could find the words to make up beautiful songs on the phone with you :) ill always have the memories that we hold dear... like you falling in the creek or me running into the door and freaking out. meghan.. i love you so much...and i will ALWAYS be here... this is so cliche... me telling someone ill be there.. but i really dont care. you are a miracle and i hope you never put the worst blames on yourself.. i love you so damn much... and dont you dare forget me..
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont understand alot of things in life...one of which...this whole blog thing. how did they think of blog...the name itself is like unique and kinda weird..heh..   ive been acting different lately. summer has started and its like.. im happier..and not just because school is over for now..but its just like soooo much easier to smile for some reason. so be happy people! :) haha  well here's the mushy part of this blog... im dedicating this one to my friend   brian rutter  . you are one of the coolest, nicest, awesomest (shut up i know its not a word)guys i have ever met. if i could thank you, i would thank you for changing so many people's lives. just to see riza look so happy just made this year great... you also changed my life a bit. i know it seems like now a days everyone says that but.. its true. i dont know what would have happened to me if i never became friends with you. we've been through alot..and i came to you for alot of advice..and i thank you so much for being here. i dont know why but when we started talking..the first thing i did was trust you.. and believe in you... and you did the same for me...and i guess thats all i ever wanted. There's much to come from the rest of my life.. but you are one of those memories that stick and dont you ever forget that. you forget to think about yourself sometimes... and i wish i could always be there to remind you.. but lets face it, im not always gonna be here and youre not always gonna remember you have me to talk to...but i can always try to talk to you....and i know all the people that care about you will too. Basically im gonna sum this whole paragraph up by saying...GODDAMN IT! i love you and   i will miss you   so freaking much.     
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmmm....weird things happen...you expect one thing and the other always happens..   when will that miracle come in my life? 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi... youre in my blog...yaay...good for you. im eating soup...i have some good news...kt comes back tomorrw and i landed a double flip today at public skate :) im kinda happy... but you know how it is...life has its ups and all those damn downs. oh well. today at skating i remembered alot of stuff...i know i basically say that everytime but i just have the most random memories sometimes. Like today i remembered how like 2 years ago my friends all went on vacation and i was stuck at home so they were all sending me postcards so me being my loserself, i made them post cards of my room. and then i had another memory where my brother knocked me down when i was little and i started crying so he hugged me..... yeah my parents have a picture of that...i love it. lol.. then i also remember good times at school, like riza falling down the stairs (haha riza you know that was funny) and then her screaming that Baker was a fool. wow that was fun man. ok yeah then i also remember going to the movies and falling down the stairs after the movie because i sat on my foot the whole time. yeah...theres more...should i say it? no...             ok i lied...yeah so i also remember watching fireworks with my brother and for some reason i realized i really do love my brother and he means so much to me. then i remember trying my double sal for the first time and landing it in class...oh that was cool. and i remember so much more but i dont want to bore you with all these memories...afterall the memories never stop because your life keeps changing.  ok i lied yet again...i also remember being a june bride in the ice show and i remember ripping my pants at band last year...oh that was not good at all. OH and there was this one time where i was in the bathroom and the  toilet flushed by itself and i screamed and everyone thought i was crazy. lol they prolly thought i saw like a big crap in there or something.lol. OMG I also remember this time i went to a portipotty and there was some sort of rat crawling around in the hole so i freaked out...that was this year....that was really bad because then i spazzed and i never ever go to a potipotties anymore. hmmmmmmmm....ok well now im drawing a blank...no im not i just seriously want to stop now because im annoying myself.. you know what else is annoying? my feet...they are ugly and they smell like poo on a humid day...lol. yeah i just typed out the word "meow". its a weird word. how did we get that word...i mean i know its from a cat but still its really weird. oh and i was wondering....how did they think of the name elmo? hes a red monster...how come people arent scared of him. i used to be. i had this dream where elmo was evil and he was like running after me...even with his strings. dude that was freaking scary i was like screaming and then i woke up and got that weird tingly feeling. yeah. ok so i think im gonna go because i want to...        i lied another time...god im such a lyer....did i spell that right? i dont know. im really going now bye bye....maybe....bye....        that time i was telling the truth but i guess since im typing now i did lie...im sorry im going..  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so far today has been crap.... skating..omg that was hell. i hate my damn program and right now i hate my damn coach. oh well....im such a freaking baby...i cant do my scratch spin or my axel or my doubles or my sit spin or anything!!!!!&nbsp;AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! OK I THINK IM OK NOW... sorry caps lock was on... man i really hope today doesnt get any worst. u know what also helped...my mom of course... god damnit she was making me so mad. She was doing the whole you're a kid i know everything and youre dumb...whatever...im outie 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      maybe i need to change... i think about last year...it wasnt that far away... and i realize in my entire life ive been the same. ive been trying to act like someone and my own personality is a mixture of everyone elses. where is me? where am i hiding?&nbsp;i dont know.... no&nbsp; wonder why i feel so lost..why i feel so confused...im ignoring what i have to do...and becoming something im not.   im still reading what you write... looking back on things and seeing that we werent as great as i thought.   i cleaned my windows today...and i sneezed because of the dust...then i got mad because i kept sneezing. so i got the vacuum cleaner and i turned it on so it would suck up the dust. oh yeah you know im smart...lol. then the blinds got stuck and i was freaking out trying to get it down. i broke the twisty thing that closes the blinds so i had to do it manually. yup. then after that i went to walmart to develope pictures. i bought some stuff for next week....stupid summer band. after an hour, i got the pictures and i had to hide a few pictures from my mom...lol. (suzy and lauren!! omg the basement!! i totally forgot about those pictures...)anywho...after that i came home and watched  pet semetary II  which was eh supposed to be scary... it wasnt scary though. yeah...im boooooooored....i think its time for me to got get some sleep. i have to skate tomorrow and im not skating at all next week except saturday...how thrilling... ok im going now...bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys today (well technically yesterday) was my brother's bday. yeah it was kinda interesting. i went skating and when my mom picked my up we ordered 60 dollars worth in chinese food from wongs.. holy cow it was kinda heavy. after that, we went to dairy queen and bought my brother a cake...it was a good yummy cake..lol. im done. after that we went home to about 7 or 8 people and then the food started getting eaten. yep... so here i am now...all his friends left&nbsp; to get erik's x box and some games and stuff. i have a cold so im like sneezing and sniffling everywhere..lol. i hate be sick...when i get sick, i get sick for like months at a time. oh and by the way i watched this tape that my cousins sent me from the philippines. it was a video tape of their new house...oh it was spiffy. i think that my family is going there over the summer next year. i wanna go but its an 18 hour flight and i hate flights.   i havent gone anywhere all summer and it kinda sucks...i was bored as hell and im like dying. but thats ok..i got alot of time to relax and such...oh its going to end soon because og band. oh joy. 8am till 12pm&nbsp; then 1pm till 4pm then 6 till 9 for a week. ahhh thats gonna be poopie. i bet im gonna be an alternate. whatever.   so theres nothing rally new in my life...i have nothing i need to talk about.   oh i started my pre-juv prgram...oh its a tiring minute and 25 seconds..lol. god im watching these music videos thing and they always play that damn usher song confessions...lol... my brother knows all the words in the beginning and i just know the song. i have a weird taste in music... i like video game music..hehehe i like that game "metal gear solid" it has some good theme music. the theme music is the music im using for my program. yeah well my brother's friends just&nbsp;got back so im gonna go before i bother them.  tata..i miss lauren and meghan and rutter and everyone :( 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i had tears in my eyes last night... first time i really thought about this... today is my parents anniversary and they didnt even speak to each other. i bought them presents and i gave my mom hers and she said, "there's no such thing anymore..." then i gave my dad his and he wouldnt take it until i told him i would get mad if he didnt. so im sitting in my bed thinking....what if they split up...i wont have them both anymore. i dont know whats gonna happen if this gets any worst.... mom and dad...please get along... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tomorrow is my parents anniversary and friday is my brother's bday....AI NAKO!! i dont have any money...yeah...well i have nothing to say...im kinda bored actually...im almost bored...im gonna get a drink now so bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its kinda weird... im sitting in front of the computer seeing what people really think about me...some good, some bad... but yeah...i guess its all good because i dont expect myself to be perfect.  yeah i really dont know what im doing...lately all i do is go online, watch tv, and like do that for the rest of the day. ahhhhh i am so freaking bored. nothing new is going on in my life and nothing will prolly happen till summer band starts. i was supposed to go on vacation and go and watch tv in some other place instead of rotting here in bolingbrook. lol no offense to bolingbrook though because i like bolingbrook. yeah...good thing though because ido alot of thinking and i write alot more than i used to....not in here but i write in my spirals and stuff. i wanna be a singer... but the thing is i cant sing and uh....yeah im not a brittney spears or some sort of jessica simpson...so yeah i guess thats a little out of the question. i really dont know what i want to do after highschool. i was thinking, maybe ill be a lawyer...but no thats too hard. then i was thinking id be a chef...but i think ill get fatter and ill burn my arm (i did it making my brother a cake....he didnt even eat it....butthead..) then i was thinking i would be an army nurse they make good money and yeah...then i was thinking maybe a regular nurse? uh...lets see i almost passed out the first time i saw my own blood and i like freaked out...yeah so now...um..then i wanted to be a skating coach...i think ill stick with that dream for now...i dont know where that'll go but yeah whatever.lol.   ok so lets go through my possible future jobs... -lawyer -chef -army nurse -nurse -skating coach watch me grow up to be a prostitue...lol...oh yeah you know me...i like to hump stuff for money *wink* ok im outie 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi today is sunday...you know what i did today? i went to church, the to ihop, then to home, then to sleep till 4pm lol.. then i went to sleep again and got up at 6...so i think i may be up for quite a while tonight. yep. so i was playing with the measuring tape today...  &nbsp;  ankle to upper thigh=30 inches  wrist=6.5 inches&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  shoulder to wrist=22.5 inches  waist=28.5 inches  &nbsp;  yeah i didnt really measure anything else...i just kinda blanked out and watched tv.... so if you put 4.384615 of my wrists together it would be my waist...lol.yeah well i dont know what im doing right now... wait yes i do  &nbsp;  1. i am watching james bond on tv  2.talking to people online  3. wrapping the measuring tape around my toe..lol 3 in around  4.typing in here  5.drawing a blank  6.  7.  8.  9.  10.  (i thought i could make it up to ten but i only made it to 5...oh well)  &nbsp;  anyways...im really bored...like really...like shoot me im bored only dont shoot me because i dont really want to get shot. oh i think ill measure my neck because i want to...lol. its 12 inches... ok. they already showed this james bond movie....rrrrrr. so who do you think is the best james bond? i think sean connerly was good...its kinda funny because i only know two of the people who played james bond. hmmmmmm... hey what if james bond got AIDS? he has sex with every &nbsp;girl that he meets except that old lady...wouldnt the world like be in trouble because of his HIV spreading ways? DAMN YOU BOND!!!! oh well...  damn sex wanting-doing every girl-prolly would do a man in jail-JAMES BOND!!! DAMN YOU! *sigh...i guess its ok since you like to save the world... so thank you for saving the world  sex wanting-doing every girl-prolly would do a man in jail- james bond. well im gonna go now. bye...  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well today was interesting... i went skating at 7:15am then i kept skating and stayed at the rink until 5pm. at like 1:40ish, the rink was empty other than me, lorae, and jesus(pronounced hey zues....lol.) and me and lorae were looking at the schedule for the rink. there was supposed to be a team on the ice but no one was there. then the schedule thing said that girlscouts were coming at like 2:30...well there were no coaches and the girl scouts came. oh it was kinda bad...no coaches and girl scouts taking a class that usually has coaches..thats bad lol. long story short, i taught for twenty minutes and had no idea what i was doing...then i did public skate and went home to sleep. skating from 7:15 till 5 is so tiring...especially if you are only on 3 hours...ok i think im gonna go now bye bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yo its j to the me. im bored....really bored... i have nothing to talk about...nothing happening in my life...nothing really at all. well today is jackie's birthday..HAPPY BIRTHDAY JACKIE!! and leah does come back from camp today! yaay leah!! &nbsp; im really weird...one day im pissed at the world and the world is pissed at me..and then the next day goes like perfect.. moodswings? no... menopause? hell no! just weird jamie? yes.  &nbsp; well i have nothing to say...hehe...lauren ill miss you!! i dont want you to go...but i know youll have fun there. -_- ill miss you and when you come back we should have a party..:) i love you &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; bye all &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ~!jamie!~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi...im kinda in a good mood today. maybe its because i actually slept and got alot of stuff out yesterday. (thanks tanya) yeah well its summer....its been pretty boring and im never busy except when i go to skate. im so weird...i love skating an all but when i get on the ice i dont feel like skating. Yet when i get off the ice i want to skate....thats funky. ok im done. did you ever hear that if your right palm itches you are going to spend money. well right now my left palm itches so does that mean im gonna get money? ok i have to go...ill be back to type again sometimes 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate the way i type how i feel yet i feel obligated to highlight then delete because there wouldnt be enough paper in the world. i swear i could write a book. i dont think anyone could understand let alone myself...  ah whatever that doesnt matter...   how are you guys today? im fine im kinda bored and i started typing this a long time ago but i kept deleting and typing again and yeah.ok yeah i really am not in a mood to type... so im gonna go now. bye
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im tired of trying to impress you.. always striving for something i dont even know.. all it ends up being is me feeling more insecure than i started out as.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im gonna miss you...im gonna miss days where id come over and we'd chill out and watch tv.. ill miss days where we'd talk on the phone for hours just to hang up and call each other back 5 minutes later...im gonna miss those songs we'd make up about random things on the phone.. im gonna miss crying on your shoulder or you crying on mine.. im gonna miss the way you always seemed so happy to see me...god.. im gonna miss you. i love you so much..  i know you might not get a chance to read this... or even to know how i feel..but to anyone who does read this...just to let you know.. this girl right here... this meghan kumzi has been a blessing for me and i thank god for her everyday. I know shes been through so much...and i know people take her for granted...but thats one of the things that i cant do..because in this world.. she made me truly be me... she stopped all my insecurities and made me what i am. so i thank her...and all i can say is that i love her past friendship but as sisters.. -love from me to meg 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3 days have gone by already and i havent written in here. ok lets think what did i do 2 days ago? thursday....hmmm...oh yes suzy's surprise party.oh that was fun. me and lauren went over to suzy's and woke her up with pans and spoons being slammed together...mwahahaha. lol so we go there and wake her up and tell her to get dressed and she cant look shitty at all. so she gets dressed while i start breakfast (frozen pancakes oh yeah...lol) then lauren comes down helps me put them in the microwave..yes i AM that dumb.. i cant do it on my own.. after that we eat the pancakes and hang out for a little bit. then we leave to go to her surprise party and go to jewel instead. we left her blindfolded in the car with her sister for like 15 minutes. hee hee me and lauren had a party getting the cake.. and running around doing our synchro program in the store. while we were checking out this lady asked lauren if she was suzy.. lauren was like.. no shes in the car. and then out of nowhere the lady  asks her where she works..uh huh..ok ...that was weird.lol so then we leave and come back to a blindfolded suzy and her sister. suzy grabs the bag of fruit and asks.."Did you guys get me a turkey?" haha of course not. it had like strawberries, blueberries, grapes, cherries and these milano cookies. In the car charlotte(suzy's sister) was passing me notes and suzy stole the pen and she kept reaching for things and kicking the cake.so we finally get to shavon's house and we crowned suzy "birthday girl" with a crown that said "birthday girl" on it and it was cool. we hung out and "fell" in the pool. this is when i realized something.... swimming with all your clothes on is sooooooooo much better than wearing a swimsuit.oh yes it is...it is so much better.anywho. we swam and ate and swam more and got freaked out by one of those fake rubber snakes. then around 1 kt and jackie came and we partied because i wanted to push them in the pool. yeah...i hit my head on the bottom of the pool a couple times...hehe yeah it kinda hurt. then kt left at 5:30 or something like that. so we did this till like 6:45 or something and then shavon left and we had a ...dance contest. oh it was pretty um...interesting... some very good interesting moments. hehe music+chair+suzy+emily+3judges=fun times ok so  shavon comes back and we're all done with the contest so we play some other stuff and and eat the other pizza that lauren said was for her "brother's party" then we ate cake...well alot of it was on suzy's face but then again my face was the only one without cake (that was surprising) then that changed when everyone just put frosting stuff all over. OH THOSE STUPID "TRICK" CANDLES SUCKED!!! RAWR!! OMG THE ONLY PERSON WHO WOULDNT BE ABLE TO BLOW IT OUT WOULD PROBABLY BE A BABY....lol. most of them sucked anyways...i think that there were a few that worked. so after that emily was starting to feel sick so we just started cleaning up and such... yep..then slowly almost everyone left and it was our turn to go. so we said our goodbyes and left. i got home (thank you lauren's dad!!!!!) and then i took a shower and went to sleep. ok that was what happened on thursday  on to friday!!hehe ok so i wake up at like 1...that was the latest ive slept all summer and then i go downstairs. my dad tried to wake me up earlier in the morning and i snapped at him because i was tired and you dont wake me up at 6 in the morning when i can sleep...its just not right. so hes outside and i keep thinking hes mad at me so i stay quiet and call up kt. we talked for a bit then my dad comes in...im all worried that hes gonna yell at me so i ask my dad if he needs help. he tells me to make mashed potatoes...lol.that was kind of random. so im still on the phone and im trying to make mashed potatoes.lol it was kinda weird. i kept burning my hand because the potatoes were boiling for like half an hour...im smart.after that my dad calls me outside so i hang up on kt and look outside. there's this big ass storm cloud coming in. OMFG it was sooo dark in like 2 minutes and i had to turn on the light. so after that me and kt are talking and i have to go. i go upstaris and ask my brother to drive me to skating and he says later...its already 2:45 and he still wante to take a shower and blah blah blah. so im like noooooooooooooo...so my dad takes me. i get there and put my skates on and me and kt get on the ice. we do the synchro program and kt tries double toes...and theres me...doing who the hell knows what. after that lauren and suzy come for class and we have some fun times. so alot of our doubles werent working (except lauren who landed 3 doubles!!! wooooo)and it was great. (to the skaters: i love the way that people dont know the difference between doubles...so i didnt really specify.lol) ok after that lauren kt and i practice our synchro program and almost run over like 5 kids. oh man that was kinda bad. that was over so i went and taught my classes and then got off everyone left besides me and the people in the office and mike (the zamboni guy). i met his mom it was funny because he kept calling her mommy and i love it when guys do that...i dont know why...im weird..lol. ok so i did skate rental for a bit then my brother picked me up. i went home changed then i went to starbucks then bought my brother food from mcdoanlds. (awwww arent i the best sister? lol just kidding) then i go home and talked to people online and i dont remember i did a bunch of stuff. then my mom came home and my dad came home then me and my daddy watched the matrix revolutions till like 1:30 then he told me to go to sleep. so i did and then i woke up and it was morning.lol.  i did dream though. i dreamed i was...uh..ok nevermind i forgot it already! rawr i hate that!!! lol ok i have to go. not really but im going to go call my buddy kt and see if she wants to chillax or something...lol. i love you all...and if you ever find the urge to chillax with me then you know the number...or at least ask me for it..lol.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so what i do today? first i got up at 8:45 to skate at 9:45 and then i took a shower and went to skating. after skating i went errand running with my dad. we got him a new phone and he said he would give me his old one...*fingers crossed. after that, i went home and ate lunch. a few hours later i went to skating again at 3:30.... but techinically i left at like 3:12ish. after skating i went home at like 6....actually first i did ballet and then i go home at 6. ok then i started running around everywhere and signed on. after that i walked to dairy queen and realized that i dont like peanuts. so i started flinging them all over as i was walking home. then i still had alot so i decided to see how far i could spit them....5 FEET THANK YOU VERY MUCH! lol oh it was fun then i started practicing skating jumps in the grass and tried a double axel...it didnt work very well. so i decided to come inside and i dont know do whatever. then my friends called and i talked to them and we 5-wayed someone.lol. that was fun . then we hung up and now here i am! lol i started typing this a long time ago and then i stopped for like a half an hour... so im done now and its 9:31 what time does it way i started it at the bottom?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is for all of those people who were there.. this is for all of those who cared this is for life when its at it's best this is for the north south east and west. this is for reality when it doesnt bring you down.. this is for the smiles that you send around. this is for those times you let me cry this is for the times when i felt i was going to die. this is for everything youve all done for me this is for the things you let me see. this is for the dreams we all dream this is for when we are put back together by the seams. this is for that last breath we'll take this is for the hardest choices we'll make this is for the question "who?" this is for life and for you.    thank you everybody... i know it may seem like im quiet or sad alot..but i have my reasons for that. thank you for making my life everything it is..:)   "....love isnt about finding the perfect person...its about seeing the imperfections perfectly..and excepting them for who they are or become" -me 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jenny is my hero. thank you jenny i love you very much...   well i have nothing else to say
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love spiderman.. spiderman is soooooo cool...hes is my hero and i love him.  do YOU love spiderman?              hi... i dont have anything to say. life is pretty ok right now...or maybe im too tired to notice...hee hee. oh you know what my brother did today? we went to the mall and he sprayed 4 different types of colognes on me.. i smelled like sweaty man mixed with that zesty scent of ass...      bye...i have nothing to say which is scary..
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      some inside jokes with people...find one we share...if we dont then lie and say one of them is yours..lol...or you can talk to me and we can make one...it would be fun *smiling upside down *poles and trees...whats the difference? *wait i dont get it...cool and cold? *no thats the play button... *zoo animals and stick heads *ewwwww your pants smell like your leg! *why is that guy humping my favorite pop? *do you charge for an empty cup that i put stuff in? wait can i charge you if i put stuff in it and give it back? *GASP! YOU J- WALKED?! OMG YOU BASTARD NOW WE'RE GONNA GET ARRESTED!!! *....TAG BLANKET CHAIR AND BELT CHAIR AND BELT...ROOF and kt and jme and stuff! tag blanket chair and belt chair and belt! *the mexican burn song *that bobby pin looks like a bug...*flick* it wont get off.. oh thats right its a bobby pin. * silence...and then all of a sudden...GOOD LORD!!! *YOU FOOOOOOOOOOL! *im english with an asian accent...wait i mean im english with an asian accent..wait did i just say that again? *whats the difference between and mexican and a bohemian... i dont know but thats kinda mean... *what does that mean? *looks it up in the dictionary...omg you are not allowed to say that! * 6 year old prostitutes in 15 years... *mommy why cant i reproduce like a flower? *kt i got lost going to ur house...oh its ok this is only ur 100th time over here. *     *weird smile*....i like to burn things... kt's mom: ok kt make sure jamie doesnt put paper on top of the fire... me after she leaves: can i see that paper...*throws a whole newspaper on top of the fire... oh nice and toasty.. lauren:MY HAIR'S ON FIRE!! suzy: my hot dog wont burn...but my bread will.. *hey looks its osamas black mama! *BRING ON THE PIXIE STIX!! *warm up dances in the rain.. * kt: im going to a theatre class...  me:ok... wait where are you going for summer school?  kt: i just told you me:you did? kt yea im going to a theatre class... me: oh thats right.. 5 MINUTES LATER... me: where are you going for summer school? *that one song... hey mama...blah blah blah blah blah blah hey mama blaha blaha blah aha blaha blaha *trying to do things in ballet and realizing we cant do it so we look at each other and realize we have no idea whats going on..
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi all once again i am in here typing. how joyful. anyways...last night i didnt sleep till like 5 (actually this morning) and it was kinda weird because everything in my room (other than my clock and my little night light..hee hee) was off so i had alot of time to think. its the 4th of july.... i wish i could spend it with my friends... but hey whatever you know my parents. theyd rather have me hang out with them.. because they're "hip" as they say. *shivers..lol. its not fair my brother got out of it because the bastard said he was tired... BS!! he totally left the house like a half hour after we left him. ah whatever im just mad because he thought of it first and im always stuck with my parents. yeah...you know sometimes i wish he would just teen-nap me and take me out with his friends... come on i'd be quiet. by the way anyone can come and kidnap me i really would just come with...lol. ok anyways back to my story. ok i lied.. im kinda mad at my mom...she says im fat..just because shes jealous that i eat everything and still look the way i do ...(its this little thing called skating you know? i do it alot...)hehe ok now REALLY im going back to my story. so my parents tell me that im not allowed to go anywhere and im like rawr ur gay! they only said that because they wanted to hang out with me. thats kind of sweet but still... i never hang out with my friends and this whole summer ive been going places with my parents and i need a break. so i have to tell lauren, suzy and kt that i cant go to ribfest with them and i was sad. But guess what my parents say...WE'RE GOING TO RIBFEST! im like...WTF?! couldnt i have just gone with my friends and like met you there? jeebus.. so i was angry and i went downstairs. i fell asleep for like 3 hours seeing that i fell asleep late this morning and we left for the ribfest at like 7:30ish (without my  -lying about being tired- brother) so we get in the parking lot and almost run over this kid.... my bad driving ASIAN parents...lol. we take the bus and im like freaking out because this little kid was like jumping on me and saying that i was his new hero...i was kinda confused but hey whats new? we finally get there and i like ran off the bus. ok all was great...soooooooooo many freaking people and sooooooooo much freaking food that we just kinda walked around everywhere. so we got some food and ate it and then washed our hands. i hate por-ta-potties!!!! i truly hate them. so i went to the bathroom and look down and i like screamed because there was like a little animal in the toilet so i freaked out and the person in the portapotty next to me was like....ARE YOU OK? i didnt even go for fear of little animals raping me. that was bad. ok so we walk around the amusement rides... and im running around like asking if i can ride stuff and they are wusses.. god they were screaming for the people on the "pharoah's fury" ride... so i didnt go on anything.. they're freaking scared of everything. especially my mom.so all of a sudden all the rides are off and its dark. the fireworks are going so we sit in some random street. Like literally  the street... it was so pretty...the fireworks lasted for a half hour and i loved it. ok now its time to run because everyone is running for the doors and im like freaking out. we walked pass the bus because my dad thought that there was another one in the front...he was wrong and i was right mwahahahaha! lol ok sorry. we drive home and i was expecting my mom to ask me if i pray again...shes weird like that. ok we get home and i make my dad coffee because he works at night and i like making coffee... i stole like alot and made ice coffee for myself...lol. ok he leaves and my brother comes back like an hour later...this was at like 11:26pm and all is great. he stole my coffee and gave it back when i yelled at him. now they went to mcDonalds because my brother was hungry because the bastard lied about being tired so he didnt have to go to ribfest..lol. after they left i called up my friend and left a message saying happy 4th and i was a little hyper so...um im sorry lol you know who you are. and now here i am...typing my whole story up and scratching a mosquito bite....damn mosquitoes.  how do you say mosquitoes...im weird and for some reason i say it and completely pronounce the "qu" lol. ok im finished with that. Who loves me? i love you so i really think i deserve your love because i think you deserve mine.. yup..ok ive got nothing to say. random message... i think im going out of town sometime at the end of this month...hmmm.. another random message... i like sparkly thongs so can someone buy me some more? i have like 4 but i like them. yet another random message... what do you get when you put laundry and detergent together? LAUNDRY DETERGENT!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jmesk8s2: watch me scream in like 5 seconds jmesk8s2: lets check jmesk8s2: 5 jmesk8s2: 4 jmesk8s2: 3 jmesk8s2: 2 jmesk8s2: 1 crazyblondie51: !!!!!!!!! jmesk8s2: ......*silence.... jmesk8s2: lol crazyblondie51: lol crazyblondie51: darn jmesk8s2: hahaha you were all hyped up for that one jmesk8s2: lol jmesk8s2: you had the whole exclamation point thing going on crazyblondie51: :-[ jmesk8s2: lol its ok i walked into a mirror ^haha nora we're officially retarded..   yeah...well that was all fun a didly..i have nothing else to say
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its kinda funny how my mom can make me feel worthless in a matter of 10 minutes or less
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i know im not the perfect daughter...i know im not the perfect child that stays home every night and studies her ass off...i know im not the best sister... i  freaking know ok? god... im sorry that im everything wrong in your life. and im sorry that i had to be your kid...  its not my fault that i grew up and i never felt right in this goddamn family. im always the worst one... the one who "acts out" to get attention. Im sorry that everywhere i go i can never feel like i fit. I turn to you expecting you...my own mother.. .to even try to stop my tears. but no youre the one that makes it worst. so thats why i dont like being home with you... thats why i HATE being your daughter... thats why sometimes i hate you. you tell me that i can tell you everything... that i shouldnt be afraid to talk to you...but look at when i try...all you do is yell. i cant talk to you if youre yelling. All i feel like i have are my friends... theyre the one things that dont judge me for everything...and they do see me for who i am.... unlike you. you are everything ive learned to try not to be... you are everything that makes me hurt myself. if you are asking why im not trying anymore.... its because of you. you wouldnt understand what kind of stress im in... to you i dont know what stress is.. but you dont know what my kind is. to feel like you dont belong...and feel like no one cares about you all the time....to feel like you cant succeed in anything you do..to feel like your own family doesnt even care... to feel like life is worthless and youd give it up if it wasnt for certain people...you wouldnt know what that was like. you dont know how sometimes i would wish that you would understand why i do half the things i do... you have no idea how much i wish that. this year alone so much has happened to me that no one would expect....that you wouldnt understand...yet you say you are a good mom... ok you provide things... thank you for that... but i am a human.. i have feelings. how am i supposed to open up to you if you knock me down everytime im actually happy? people tell me that i look sad alot and that i usually looked so happy before... well you dont know the difference. you look at me and my sad face would look happy to you.... or when i fall at skating all you ever do is yell at me... how is yelling supposed to help your daughter if shes crying and waiting for someone to hold her in their arms and tell her its alright to make mistakes? i feel like its not ok to make mistakes... its not ok... and thats a big flaw in my life..it should be ok... it should be. but its just...not. where is my mom that tells me that its ok... the one that was there when i had my first athsma attack... the one who hugged me because i was crying because i missed her... the one who talked to me and let me say what i needed to instead of hitting me with a board because she thought i slammed something too hard when i was angry? how else am i supposed to show how i feel if i cant even get mad without you getting mad at me? i cant get upset without you getting upset first when you yell at me... so this is my blog... something that youll never read because you cant use a computer...something youll never see because chances are ill never talk to you about any of it.. most people wouldnt care anyways... 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is the burn your hand song i made up when i burned it in the kitchen...it's sung to the mexican hat dance...  i burned i burned i burned my hand on hot water i burned i burned i burned my hand on hot water scalding your hand really burns i dont want to raise your concerns i put ice on the spot.. because burning your hand is real hot!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dont like movies with my mom. holy cow.. we went to see spiderman 2 and i had to go with her. We went at the 8:30 show because a show that was half an hour later...was too late.. ok so we get there and i buy the tickets and we go to get some seats. of course she was like...SIT THERE!! and i really didnt know where "there" was but she kept saying...THERE!! so i went to some random seat and she was like...NO NOT THERE I DONT WANT TO SIT THERE!!!!! SIT THERE!!!! so im really confused and people were looking at me weirdly. so i tell her to go where she wants to sit...so she grabs my arm and says.... THERE!! at this point im getting really annoyed with her so i just sit down on the stairs and let her complain. finally she showed me where "there" was and of course it had to be by some hot guys. i was so angry. you cant hit on people in front of your mom...its just not right. anyways...so we're sitting there and she tells me to get her popcorn... ok so i go get "us" some. i come back she grabs the popcorn and like ate 3/4 of the bag and asked if i wanted some. so i took a little and she says "jeeze did you have to eat the whole bag?" so i give her my part of the 3/4 and she just eats the whole thing. ok we watched the movie and she wouldnt shut up!!! like seriously she had something to say about every little freaking thing! OMG LOOK ITS SPIDERMAN!! OMG LOOK ITS THAT GIRL!! OMG LOOK!! i was just like...ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!so the movie finishes and we go home. out of nowhere she asks me if i pray at night...and im like...uh no. so like 10 minutes later, i start talking about something else and she cuts me off and goes...DO YOU PRAY? YOU REALLY SHOULD PRAY... YOU USED TO PRAY.. so im getting all pissed off at her and then we go inside and she complains about the dishes that my dad left and complains about me not doing dishes and not folding clothes...ITS NOT MY FAULT I WASNT FREAKING HOME MOST OF THE DAY AND COULDNT FOLD THE FREAKING CLOTHES!! ok so then my brother comes in and shes all being her damn investagative self... and asking...OH DID YOU GO TO THE MOVIE WITH US? YOU DIDNT WANT TO GO BY US? god! i didnt want to go with her! and we saw my brother when we were watching the movie and he like ran away...shooooooooot i would too! so im all pissed at my mom because she freaking ruined my night and all she does is complain about every living thing in the freaking world. she says i cant go anywhere tomorrow...WTF!! WTF DID I DO?!!! AHHHHHHH SHE MAKES ME ANGRY...  my little prayer... dear lord please bless my mommy, my daddy, my brother, and the rest of my family and friends. i love them all so much. Thank you for all my blessings and everything you've given me. Thank you also for this wonderful night that i was lucky to share with my mom. (please lord forgive that sarcasm and make me truly be thankful for tonight) I love you so much and thank you for this wonderful day in my life. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sarah, mallory, megan, and cory (and cassie last year..)are the names of the seniors on the teen team (jr classic.. same difference...)I've been on the Dazzler team for about 5 years and so many different things have changed over that time. We all grew up a little bit each year...whether it be new coaches, new programs, or even a new zamboni..we all changed. These seniors have been there through alot of it. I've always looked to them for help and always asked them stupid questions that i never understood, and they would always find a way to help me.I watch them on the ice and i feel so lucky to even get a chance to share the ice with people as talented and as amazing as them. They have been the most outstanding leaders, friends, and role models for me.I watch them and see that their friendship is always there...and it never seems to fade..and i guess i envy them for that much. they've always had each other.. and in my life the people always change and learn to move on without me. so why? why do i feel so inspired by them? because there's only a few times where i've found myself in a group of friends who love me. Though i'm not so close to them.. i can say that i do love them. Through many of my years they've been there for me...and to me that's all that counts. They have stood up for me when i couldn't stand up on my own and even made certain parts in my life the best that they could be.... for that much i thank them.i know that we've all been through so much together and throughout it all i have always cherished and cared about them.... as well as love them and i would be surprised if they knew that. believe me when i say...a team really makes life worth living because this one has for me... especially with them on the team. So thank you... to all of you. You've taught me so much. I know that there is still a full year of all of us together... but...time flies by so much faster than we'd know. So if any of them read this, i hope you know that you've changed my life and you'll always be loved by everyone...including me. thank you for some of the greatest times in my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its funny because i cant really stay angry at my brother for very long. I was angry because of my mom yesterday and because my brother opened the door and shoved it in my face again. so i was just pissed at people and my brother was like...awwwww jamie is PMSing? that never makes it any better when people say that. so i just ignored him and kept going...haha he just kept doing that all day until i started laughing and punched his arm. it was funny now that i think of it...i love him so much! i dont know what i would ever do without him... im stupid.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i was happy that you two got together.. i mean two of my best friends getting together? what more could i ask for. i know that this could possibly the hardest thing happening to you right now...but i know somehow you guys will work through it.   riza: you been my friend since 6th grade and for so long i felt as if i could turn to you. when you two got together it just made me smile... i have never seen you as happy as when you're with him. and in turn it made me happy...theres nothing that i ever wanted but to see my friends happy. there have been alot of hard times through this whole year but when doesnt life put those in? i love you very much till this day and it tears me up to see u hurting. so dont u ever forget that im here for you...i really am here. i promise.   rutter: ive known you for not even a year...for the first half of school we weren't that close at all but then suddenly we became friends and i considered you to be one of my best friends. you made one of the very special people in my life happy...and i thank you so much for that. not only that but you really made me feel special. even though we dont talk at all anymore...i still care about you. and i know ill always think of you when i can see the stars.  both of you have made a large impact in my life. and theres nothing more that i can do but offer myself as help if you ever need me... i love you...both of you
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah well yesterday was fun and so was this little part of today. its leah's bday and yaay...lol.and i carried a watermelon...(dont even bother asking)....im done. anyways...right now im watching dirty dancing and im just randomly thinking about stuff as usual. i guess it wouldnt be random if i do it all the time then i guess...blah whatever. you know i was just thinking about those friends that always have promises and say no matter what, that they would keep them. you all know that im a very trusting person and i know i trust people too easily....thats something i still have to learn. so dont mind me if i feel like i cant trust you...its really nothing personal but its just the fact that im so freaking tired of always trusting and no one else even seeing how much hurt...ah whatever i dont want to talk about that.  the only thing i miss is the fact that you dont look at me the same way anymore... im just like the person you passover or like one of those people that youd never think to look at twice. I was never looking for a special person...but in the end i really did find one... so me being me, i acted stupid and tried to change for you...tried to smile for you...tried to laugh for you...tried to make myself better and ended up hurting myself all for you. im not trying to say that its all your fault...but im just trying to get you to talk to me.....i just want you to really...talk...to me. Because everytime i hear your voice...the feeling i used to get... the feeling of knowing that my one of my closest friends really would always be there....is gone. its just not there....no matter how much i want it to be.  ah well im tired and i kinda left my friends so i think im gonna go now. bye 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>