<Blog>


<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lifes interesting now. certain events really scare me and make me worry about whatll happen next. my mom wont leave me at home by myself anymore cuz i had cammie over for about 4 hours on tuesday. at least i think it was tuesday...we were both sick, and her mom didnt know where she was.  HOURS LATER...  went to cammies earlier. had fun with her and preston, then annalise came, and we still had fun. cammie wished that by the end of the summer we would be able to tell each other that we loved each other. i dunno if ill be able to, cuz of the tally incident. but w/e, ill figure something out. listeing to soybomb rite now, sad cuz they broke up. in 24 hours ill b somewhere in idaho, sleeping in a stranger's house. well, at least i think ill be asleep. wouldnt count on it though. tomorrow'll be my last entry for at least a week. jeez its a 2 day drive to canada. hopefully itll b fun. ill miss cammie sooo much, it wont b fun. o well, canucks r cool. most of them anyways. mmm the LIVESTRONG braclet cammie's dad gave me smells good cuz cammie put perfume stuff on it. cant stop sniffing it lol. grrr im gonna miss her lots. as soon as i get bak, im gonna b moving. well, pretty soon afterwards anyways. i dunno what ill do if i cant see cammie every day. o god i dont wanna think about that. ill fall apart. i dont think she knows it but shes such a big part of me... ill cry at least once, im sure.
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The last few days have been pretty hectic. Cammie and me hit lots of rocks - big rocks - emotionally and now we're better. it was really tough cuz i think she loves me or something and doesnt want to say it, cuz she thinks i might not feel the same way. i cant say i blame her cuz from what happened with tally, its hard to say i love someone new. schools out finally, and i didnt beat bob up. goin to canada for a fuckin week on saturday, and its a two day drive just to get there. Staying in banff, alberta. goin with mckinley and stuff. i hope i dont get too bored. sounds boring. on the way bak i get to buy firecrackers and stuff from the indian reservation though, so that'll b fun. tubs of it. wow mckinley just reminded me he has one of my magic decks, so i hope my good cards are in there. ive been looking everywhere for them! im such a nerd, o well. its a fun game, really. i dont see why ppl have to look down upon ppl from doing stuff they like. w/e, doesnt matter to me. hopefully IHS wont hate too much. o god IHS is gonna b sooo lame. im not looking too forward to it. ill miss all the friends i guess i made at MMS, but i wanna start over. screwd up too many times.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ha yesterday was a fucked up trip. first i found out that cammie came home sick from camp, cuz she had another dizzy spell and stuff, then i hung out with her till like 10 in the evening, from about 2 in the afternoon. afterwards i got home and was supposed to call her, but she wasn't home yet, cuz i think either her mom lied to me and said she wasn't home, or her dad had pulled over to yell at her cuz she just ran out earlier that day. whatever is was, i had told cammie earlier that i would be at her house around 1 or something. but anyways, after i got home i called my mom, got in the shower, then went to shelby's. had  a  drink. just one. once that was done molly was totally wasted and we hadta escort her back to her room. meanwhile as all this is goin on, her mom is asleep on the couch. shes still there and its 2:45 am. so anyways, i talked to molly about her emotional issues for like...2 hours. i think i helped her, but im not sure. rite now shes asleep, hopefully forgetting all thats happened since she started drinking, specifically chase. she really loves that kid, and he doesnt acknowledge it at all. i feel sorry for her, because she has apologized multiple times for cheating on him while they were goin out, and he still doesnt talk to her, much less be nice to her. she said he called her "the biggest ho in the world" and some other nasty names. it almost seems like the tally incident with just reversed sexes. just what i needed. o well, it feels good to talk. and help her. she says shell miss me, and i think she will. unless all this has been just a drunk episode. thatd b kinda funny if it was, ya? pretty chaotic. im done for now. peace.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, now cammies gone. ill miss her so much. i just finished writing her email, and now i hafta wait an hour before i go down to mollys and drink my boxers off maybe, lol. i kinda doubt ill actually drink, but maybe i will. also just watched the grand finale to BgC2 of RvB, it was funny. codename dirtbag! omally made off with lopez through the teleporter and now all hell's broke loose. i wonder what happens next. no more episodes for a few months. hmm...i really dont know what to write. i spent all day today with cammie, and it was fun. we had a water fight, among other things. ie jumped on the tramp, ate stuff, listened to music, chilled, etc. it was fun. ill really miss her. i dont know what to write so ill either edit this later or who knows. peace.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cammie leaves tomorrow, and i move on tuesday. marches are still here, dunno when they leave. they kinda get annoying. so later im goin down to cammies again, actualy make that rite after im done typing this. i got a plan to do while cammies at camp, im gonna sneak out one night and help them raid stuff, then cammie an me will b together for a while at least. on friday im goin to the walkers cabin near Olympia so i wont get to see cammie before i go. ill hafta wait till monday! o well, at least ill get to see her again. i think im gonna stop taking my medicine cuz it makes it so i cant show any emotion. im always sure that i love cammie when i havent taken my medicine, but when i do take it im never sure. its really starting to bug me. but hopefully itll all be batter once i stop taking it. i really want to love her as much as she loves me. she sewed C-A-M-M-I-E into my sleeve end on my blacklabel jacket. and she stitched up the neck place thing. how sweet lol. ill be happy to see her as soon as she gets back. i cant say that i will miss her, but im sure i will. ive seen her every day this week. i gave her a stuffed koala bear thing which i thought was pretty ugly, but she acted like she liked it so, ya. at least she didnt make me feel stupid. we had a water fight today and afterwards she was worried that after this week i wouldnt love her anymore cuz we had been apart for a week. i reassured her that id still love her just as much, if not more, cuz i hadnt seen her for a week. i sure hope i still love her. really, ill feel so bad if i dont. i really dont wanna lose her. it was ruin me and her. im gonna go now, ill write more tomorrow. peace.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      walking a tightrope, ill tell ya. amy is convinced we made out, and we didnt. shes so dumb. i really dont like her at all. hate her in fact. i do realize i brought this on myself though. ill do what ive always done before, ignore it. cammie an me had a rough day today, but it all ended well. all because of a stupid ring. and avi. shes weird. hopefully i made an impression today that she didnt like. ha i "called her fat" once or twice, and i was gonna go up to her and call her the pillsbury dough-girl. man she woulda beat me up so bad. and her brother morgan was being a total bitch to me for a while. then he was shooting at me with his paintball gun and only CO2, leaving nice little white spots on my pants from frozen Co2, and i grabbed the end of the gun and just twisted it around. ha then he kinda stopped. he threw a ball at me, and hit me in the ass! what a freak. o well i didnt get really mad at him. grr really hate amy rite now though. shes really pissing me off. i love cammie more than she knows though, and i dont need amy there screwing it up. fuck im such a screw-up. o well, whats done it done. i didnt make out with her, and thats final. i didnt! i got my Darksteel forge in the mail while i was gone, and my mom was...not terribly pleased that i had used her CC again. lets just say  ninjas on fire  lol to quote  urlLink RvB . god im gonna miss cammie so much when i move. im gonna see if my mom will let her spend the night sometime. itd be so much fun. not like we'd do much, but i bet my parents think we would. they suspect too much. im done for now. peace out.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well im home. been home for a day now, but yesterday i got sidetracked when i was gonna write. cammie gets home today, and im thrilled to see her. really. ive missed her so much over the past week, its sad. i love her lots. i hope she likes the present i got her. necklace and a ring. still got fireworks to use, saving them for my new neighborhood. gotta make a good first impression, ya know? pissed my sister off a lot yesterday, and had a good time doing it. the march's are at my house now, and their mom offered me a job back on their home island, but i had to turn it down, on account that cammie gets home today. i coulda made like 70-80 bucks from it though. nice amount for just a days work i think. she was gonna pay me 10 bucks an hour. thatd a been nice. o well. hmm these march kids r bothering me. o well, one more day. ill survive. might goto nicks on account of severe boredom. he cut his hand on glass yesterday and probably lost lots o blood. what a retard, but we still love him lol. ill write tomorrow. peace.
    
</post>


</Blog>