<Blog>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its been almost 4 weeks, since sbihin nia na hindi na nia ko kailangan, that he had found someone better than me...na hindi nia na nga ko mahal, just like that...  ...but until now, hindi ako okay...  ang hirap magpretend na, there's nothing going on inside me,  na ang totoo umiiyak pa din ako sa gabi, na iniisip ko pa din kung iniisip nia ko... na sana bumalik na cia...  napilit kong mapaniwala ung iba, nakalimutan kong kumbinsihin ung sarili ko...  sobrang na-mimiss ko na cia...  
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i may force myself to forget you and escape i may forget the magic words i might forget to say i love you forget that i did love you i may loose my mind and my heart i might loose myself with confusions and frustrations i might loose you and then find you again i might know or would know,  i love you then and i love you still realizing i remain in love with you i might loose the chance of having you back i might loose the nights and days of being with you i might loose the chance of having what i possessed i might loose you but i want you to know i loved you for a moment i loved you for sometime in my past i loved you for a while i loved you, even if for the meantime, means forever in my heart even if promises turned into harsh words and curses even if all the love i have had and i should share means to be forgotten even if this love was stolen away from me even if love means separation, being brokenhearted, painfully because of you even if love means tears and despair even if love meant… …you’ll live in your present, while I still live in our past… 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don’t worry; this will be the last time…  Sending this was never easy for me. Particularly now, knowing that you may not even care what this letter is all about. Knowing that, at this point in time, you may not give a damn regarding what I feel. And it kills me to think that you’re much happier without me…but I’ll send it anyway, it’s hard to keep things hanging on, leaving stones unturned, as well as I don’t want regretting “what ifs” afterwards.  There are so many things that happened without specific reasons… and I presume you’ll be the biggest question unanswered in my life.  As I begin writing this, I look back late last year, when I experienced happiness I never knew would be possible. It was before my second semester, everything was laid back - nothing really to look forward to, until I heard the news about our reunion…                 I was ecstatic knowing that I’ll be seeing my long lost friends...     and believe it or not…specially you.  Before that day, I was so excited to text you after hearing that you’ve been sending messages to ma.fe, even though she told me that you’ve been asking her about… you know, courting her…, but what the heck! Reuniting with you even as a former classmate would be fine.  And so there it was, the big day arrived. To tell you honestly, I was so nervous at that time…why? I didn’t know either. I’ve been quiet the whole day, not just because I don’t fell well, but because all these years I never thought the feeling would be the same. However, aware that you like ma.fe, I ignored it…I just wanted to go back to where I am…maybe we’re really not meant to be.  But fate took its turn. Everything happened so fast. Surprisingly, I’ve found myself deeply falling in love with you. I’ve never been happier. I’m used to having you beside me… There were times that I have so many weights to carry on…at school, at home, but I don’t worry much, because I know that you’ll always be there. Walang Iwanan… We always worked things out and facing each problem seemed a lot easier having you around. Oftentimes, iniisip ko, mawala na silang lahat wag ka lang. Even in my wildest dream I never picture losing you, I thought what we’ve been through will be reason enough for us to stay strong and hold on… but I guess I was wrong.   Everything seems so perfect, or so I thought it was… I already set my mind and more than willing to spend my lifetime with you...no questions ask…you know that. We used to dream. And I know that visualizing my future with somebody else will not be as ideal if it won’t be you.  Until that day… I didn’t really see it coming.  I wasn’t, or rather, never prepared for that.  I assumed you loved me that much.  All throughout our relationship, I never thought another girl would ruin everything. You’ve been telling me before that it’s impossible.  Not to you. Not to us. And not now. I even thought that if we were going to part ways, I’d be the one to blame… You know what?, I’ve never been so insecure my entire life, after hearing all the things you’ve said. You’ve turned into someone else just like that.  I still remember that Sunday, our last break-up, you decided to end this because                             sabi mo,” nahihirapan ka na” ,I can’t help thinking, bakit ganon? bakit laging ikaw? di mo ba naisip na mas nasasaktan ako?… It’s hard to accept that kind of reality..  The pain has its own way of wounding your whole being. It’s hard to regain yourself …not after taking away something you’ve always asked for. Overreacting as you may think I am…but who cares?…it’s the truth.  It was never easy for me. I was so helpless.  Agony would be an understatement…it was hell.  I wasn’t ready to face the truth and give up.  Your memories keep haunting me and moving on seems impossible. For days I keep on crying…I keep thinking what went wrong...        I’m really devastated. I was so scared.  I can’t bear loosing you. I wanted to talk to you personally to patch up things, even as your friend, but you rejected me every time I tried… Still, I insist.  Until that incident in SM Manila… It strike me hard, big time! It was an eye-opener for me.             I have to save something for myself… at least my self-respect. And that was more than enough reason to let you go…sorry it took that long… I guess it’s really over then…   Now I know that some good things never last…  I decided to tell you all this because I don’t want to remain issues unsettled between us. Hating you will not help me forget.           I’ve realized it. Sure I’ll miss you. I’m missing you now, what more tomorrow and for the days to come, but it was so pathetic holding on to something that is not yours anymore. I was stupid to think that you’ll be coming back. But I guess it’s also my fault. I never stop on hoping that you’ll be back to your senses, but maybe it has to be this way…  I just hope that sooner or later I’ll understand it.  Telling you this has been hard for me. And I guess I should prepare myself for more. It would hurt me seeing you with someone else, but I don’t want to be selfish. I’ll let you grow and find what will really makes you happy. I may or may not regret giving you this letter but I know I would not regret telling you this...                           I loved you…I loved you even before. More than I expected, more than you know…I still consider you one of the best things that ever happened to me. Sana hindi na lang nagbago…                          if only I could turn back time...                                                                   Thank you for everything. Thank you for the good memories that are worth remembering.  I’m sorry for making such a big deal out of this.  I never imagined I’ll be seeing you again after four long years…whatever the reason, I’m glad it did.                                  I hope someday we’ll meet again...                                    As they say,only time will tell… 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don’t worry; this will be the last time…  Sending this was never easy for me. Particularly now, knowing that you may not even care what this letter is all about. Knowing that, at this point in time, you may not give a damn regarding what I feel. And it kills me to think that you’re much happier without me…but I’ll send it anyway, it’s hard to keep things hanging on, leaving stones unturned, as well as I don’t want regretting “what ifs” afterwards.  There are so many things that happened without specific reasons… and I presume you’ll be the biggest question unanswered in my life.  As I begin writing this, I look back late last year, when I experienced happiness I never knew would be possible. It was before my second semester, everything was laid back - nothing really to look forward to, until I heard the news about our reunion…                 I was ecstatic knowing that I’ll be seeing my long lost friends...  and believe it or not…specially you.  Before that day, I was so excited to text you after hearing that you’ve been sending messages to ma.fe, even though she told me that you’ve been asking her about… you know, courting her…, but what the heck! Reuniting with you even as a former classmate would be fine.  And so there it was, the big day arrived. To tell you honestly, I was so nervous at that time…why? I didn’t know either. I’ve been quiet the whole day, not just because I don’t fell well, but because all these years I never thought the feeling would be the same. However, aware that you like ma.fe, I ignored it…I just wanted to go back to where I am…maybe we’re really not meant to be.  But fate took its turn. Everything happened so fast. Surprisingly, I’ve found myself deeply falling in love with you. I’ve never been happier. I’m used to having you beside me… There were times that I have so many weights to carry on…at school, at home, but I don’t worry much, because I know that you’ll always be there. Walang Iwanan… We always worked things out and facing each problem seemed a lot easier having you around. Oftentimes, iniisip ko, mawala na silang lahat wag ka lang. Even in my wildest dream I never picture losing you, I thought what we’ve been through will be reason enough for us to stay strong and hold on… but I guess I was wrong.   Everything seems so perfect, or so I thought it was… I already set my mind and more than willing to spend my lifetime with you…no questions ask…you know that.                                   We used to dream.                                                      And I know that visualizing my future with somebody else will not be as ideal if it won’t be you.  Until that day… I didn’t really see it coming.  I wasn’t, or rather, never prepared for that.  I assumed you loved me that much.  All throughout our relationship, I never thought another girl would ruin everything. You’ve been telling me before that it’s impossible.  Not to you. Not to us. And not now. I even thought that if we were going to part ways, I’d be the one to blame… You know what?, I’ve never been so insecure my entire life, after hearing all the things you’ve said. You’ve turned into someone else just like that.  I still remember that Sunday, our last break-up, you decided to end this because sabi mo,” nahihirapan ka na” ,I can’t help thinking, bakit ganon? bakit laging ikaw? di mo ba naisip na mas nasasaktan ako?… It’s hard to accept that kind of reality..  The pain has its own way of wounding your whole being. It’s hard to regain yourself …not after taking away something you’ve always asked for. Overreacting as you may think I am…but who cares?…it’s the truth.  It was never easy for me. I was so helpless.  Agony would be an understatement…it was hell.  I wasn’t ready to face the truth and give up.  Your memories keep haunting me and moving on seems impossible. For days I keep on crying…I keep thinking what went wrong...          I’m really devastated. I was so scared.  I can’t bear loosing you. I wanted to talk to you personally to patch up things, even as your friend, but you rejected me every time I tried… Still, I insist.  Until that incident in SM Manila… It strike me hard, big time! It was an eye-opener for me.              I have to save something for myself… at least my self-respect.        And that was more than enough reason to let you go…                sorry it took that long… I guess it’s really over then…   Now I know that some good things never last…  I decided to tell you all this because I don’t want to remain issues unsettled between us. Hating you will not help me forget.             I’ve realized it. Sure I’ll miss you. I’m missing you now, what more tomorrow and for the days to come, but it was so pathetic holding on to something that is not yours anymore. I was stupid to think that you’ll be coming back. But I guess it’s also my fault. I never stop on hoping that you’ll be back to your senses, but maybe it has to be this way…  I just hope that sooner or later I’ll understand it.  Telling you this has been hard for me. And I guess I should prepare myself for more. It would hurt me seeing you with someone else, but I don’t want to be selfish. I’ll let you grow and find what will really makes you happy. I may or may not regret giving you this letter but I know I would not regret telling you this...I loved you…I loved you even before.  More than I expected, more than you know…                I still consider you one of the best things that ever happened to me. Sana hindi na lang nagbago…if only I could turn back time...          Thank you for everything. Thank you for the good memories that are worth remembering. Sorry for making such a big deal out of this.      I never imagined I’ll be seeing you again after four long years…whatever the reason,                                                 I’m glad it did.                                                      I hope someday we’ll meet again...                                     As they say, only time will tell…                                                      >Catherine 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      somebody said na if u love someone, set them free...gago b guamwa ng wisdom n 2...d nia b alm kung gano kahirap ung pinapagawa nia? hindi ko alm kung anong dapat kong maramdaman...  oo mahal na mahal ko p rin cia, khit ang dapat magalit ako sa kanya... khit ayaw nia na sakin, khit cguro...my mhal na ciang iba...  alm ko o.a. na, sbi nila kht respeto n lng sa sarili ko, khit un n lng...ngaun, un ung gnagwa ko...kya lng d nmn ako masaya...  bkit ganon??gnawa ko nmn lhat d b? hanggng ngaun iniicp ko pa rin kung anong nagawa ko 2 deserve this kind of pain...  hanggang ngaun, hinahanap ko pa din cia,hanggng ngaun...  ang hirap pla ng sobrang saya mo, then suddenly wala na... gus2 ko lng mlmn kung bkit...everything seems so perfect, im ready 2 spend my lifetime w/ him..no questions ask...i thought, kontento na cia, masaya na cia, kala ko lng pala...  ang hirap ng empty ka...sobra... ang hirap ma-miss ung isang taong wala nmn ng pakialam sau... ang hirap pag bumuo ka ng pangarap kasama cia, tapos d nmn pala ma22pad..  bkit ganon???  gus2 ko ciang sumbatan..gus2 kong pamukha sa knya na wala akong gnagawang masama sa knya para saktan ako ng gani2... gus2 ko maramdamn nia kung gano kasakit... i really, really hate him...  he was everything i've dream of...sana nanatili n lng ganon, hindi n lng nging reality...don cguro masaya p rin ako hanggang ngaun...kasama cia... 
    
</post>



</Blog>