<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so ive done it. ive entered the fabulous world of online journaling - baring my soul for the world to see...or something like that. i figure, i spend the majority of my time at work, with NOTHING to do, so i may as well give myself  something  to do. and ive been told by a certain someone (who shall not be referenced hereafter for the sake of my sanity) that i like to listen to myself talk. at least i have the guts to put myself out there, you yutz. god forbid YOU ever be vulnerable, lest someone realize you arent perfect. oh, wait. already did. "va te faire enculer, salope!" (as the french say)   speaking of france, dyl is there "a ce moment"! he called to say "ciao" the day before he left...how jealous am i? "tres." i asked for some Kinder Eggs, but if he had a nickel for every time someone has said, "bring me back some ________!" he could, well, spend them on some Kinder Eggs for "moi"!   anywho, im at work (bentley college, graduate school of business)...multitasking, if you will. that is, im writing a blog, eating a pop tart, occasionally getting up to shred bags and bags of documents, stuffing envelopes as the spirit moves me, and writing graduate certificate requirement summaries (DRSs) as colleen finishes creating student folders. thankfully i actually have something to keep me occupied today, mindless as it may be. yesterday was the worst, fully intended to quit. babs described it best: i hate feeling useless, especially when i am capable of ten times more than answering a damn phone.  apart from work, life is slowly improving. its the little things mostly, serving to keep my mind in a better place: dad gave me twenty bucks for gas (only perk of living at home), eric made me dinner last night (which i forgot to bring with me for lunch, doh), i got to see my cousin and her new baby (kyle brandon donahue-frey 6/22/04 7lbs. 15in.), and la piece de resistance: im friggin' psyched for tomorrow! rach will be down after work, just got an email from ventre saying she will likewise be down, talked to ky sunday who is scheduled to work but may be able to switch, havent managed to keep cait on the phone long enough (damn VT cell service) to find out if she has plans to come down...its all about having things to look forward to, particularly to be fortunate enough to surround yourself with wonderful people.  which makes me want to piss my pants at the thought of going to san diego in september. ventre, may i please borrow your gi-normous cojones? thanks.  all right, so i should do some more work, finish my grad school application/essay, and run home to my bed. so exhausted. cant be exhausted tomorrow...MUST...GET...WASTED...(no worries) perhaps i will sun myself during the day? does anyone know what skin cancer looks like? i think i may have it. but anyway. hi ho, hi ho, and all that shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so my app made it to PCOM, i have an admissions interview in two weeks, i have plane tickets and a rental car.  so what is this apprehension for??? on the one hand, im pumped to go out to SD and start this chapter, but on the other hand, reality reared its ugly head and slapped me with the possibility that i may not get into the program. in related news, my adorable 82 year-old great-aunt wrote me a check for "a couple hundred bucks to help with your trip", i love her. shes been staying at my house for a week now, such a difference between her life-perspective and that of my miserable uncle. she has the money (no husband, no kids), and she doesnt hesitate to share with the people she loves. she has a habit of taking my mum on cruises to places she wants to see before she dies ("ive already been there, no time to see it again!" i want to be in her position when im 82.  in the meantime, im at work, cursing my boss and hating my life. ive packaged another 50 graduation gifts...only 50 more to go, for a grand total of 400. im sorry, is this a grad school or a mail room? 'cuz for a minute there i forgot...id make one helluva disgruntled postman...=P at any rate, i actually have to get back to packaging before they realize i have managed to do as few as possible today... highlight of my day: lunch at demos with eric (greek salad, why you gots to be so yummy?)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      translation for the french-impaired = men. ive accepted that i will never understand how the male species can detach from emotion so effortlessly. there are wonderful exceptions of course, without whom i would be forced to convert to lesbianism. so thanks for keeping me from a world of vaginas. you know who you are. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      thursday (part of my weekend, i have fridays off):  - worked all day (see blog for 6/24) - scheduled an admissions interview in san diego for july 15 (ah! how crazy is that?) - decided it would be a good idea to haul ass up to VT to pick up caitlin (it was a fabulous idea, albeit impractical, spending 6 hours in the car = exhausting) - rolled into the 'ham and crashed at 2:30am  friday's adventures: - finished up my grad school app and essay - made an impromptu trip to the rmv in new beford (pronounced new beh-fud or simply new beige) - trekked out to hyannis for the show - cait and i came to the realization that we might not make it through said show without the aid of alcohol - kandy korner (of all places) to the rescue! the very confused kid at the ice cream counter sold us two tall glasses of milk - said milk was then doctored with kahlua from the trunk of my car (how shady are we?) - cue the hyannis sound - mary & cait = wasted by intermission. i think its a first in HS history to have audience members imbibing mid-performance (ventre and jo had pre-gamed prior to the show, but my guess is that thats fairly typical) - intermission lead the four of us to my car once again, this time to mix the mother of all midori sours, cleverly concealed in babs' nalgene bottle (yes, in addition to kahlua i keep midori and sour mix in my trunk...am i an alcoholic? perhaps.) - said midori got us through the second half of the show, after which we replenished our supply at the packie on the way to the house - cue the party/under-aged estrogen/drama/bullshit - massage party in the airconditioned upstairs with eric, cait, and vic - world record set for 5 person "spoon"  - sleep (finally)  saturday: - woke up too early - rolled up to fenway to catch the phillies/sox game - fucking incredible seats, as per usual when doug is in town - bought a new hat and a super cute t-shirt - sox lost, oh well - met doug at the hotel and had a lovely dinner at marche - home to  see my great-aunt and uncle - glass of wine and sat at the computer with my little kitty asleep in my lap - got cornered by my uncle (who is also my godfather...too bad i havent seen a card or gotten a phone call on my birthday in 8 years. nor did i get a phone call upon graduation from college, in part because of his money-grubbing bitch of a wife, and because he has the need to make everyone feel inferior) - he talked at me for an hour to let me know i was lazy and acupuncture was a load of shit and i should be going to medical school, but again im lazy and i wouldnt ever be called in the middle of the night to save a twelve-year-old girl who needed emergency acupuncture (hes a retired radiologist). so basically, without ever bothering to get to know me, he has determined that my life is worthless and wasted. good thing im not like him or i would have promptly told him that his wife married him for his money, he is not the father of her child, and that the airline he bought for her was likely purchased from another man she had been sleeping with. - fell asleep feeling shitty.  sunday: - im off to newport to a graduation party, details will not likely follow.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i wrote a blog about my weekend last night, finished it this morning and tried to post it...too bad the session had timed-out and i lost the whole thing.  sucky. if i feel ambitious enough to retype it all then i will. in the meantime:   im lost in my head been thinking all around i gotta find the off-ramp to my heart stoplights in a row when all i want is 'go' drop it into first and ill get home  its ok, im all right im just a little rough around the edges of this life play it cool, you can always follow breadcrumbs in a line when you are lost  little, little seeds grow into troubled trees a sorry, sorry sight between my ears i need to settle down and eat my troubled fruit the sweetness of the taste will do me good  its ok, im all right im just a little rough around the edges of this life play it cool, you can always follow breadcrumbs in a line when you are lost    ~ teitur 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah, so when i got to work this morning my boss tells me shes really sorry, but the woman i was temping for is coming back...ON TUESDAY. so all that bullshit that i put up with from randstad...needless.   life is just plain funny. i should really learn to take things less seriously, no one gets out alive anyway. on the other hand, i think im pretty damn good at coping with the little shit. its the big shit from which my issues stem.   surprisingly, i am coping fabulously with the thought of the impending interview in SD. yes, i might get in there and need to hurl out of nervousness, but honestly, im so excited i could pee my pants. but enough with the graphic bodily functions. BRING IT ON. leaving in 6 days (5 if you dont count today).  so ventre sent me this -   urlLink Security Alert  oy vey. im moving to someplace that terrorists have never heard of. like newton, ma. ranked the safest town in america by the Morgan Quitno Press's annual report. or perhaps the #2 town: amherst, ny. which is next town over from williamsville - eric's hometown. no wonder hes so nice =) anywho, its freezing in my office, so im going to run an errand that involves being outdoors...perhaps i will blog again later. im sure y'all are waiting in rapt anticipation...
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BabooRachl: let me know how it goes Auto response from Dr Bugg: lunch...and giving my two weeks notice. :-D happy day! Dr Bugg: well Dr Bugg: that sucked BabooRachl: why, oh no Dr Bugg: i called my rep at randstad to see if he could meet with me, which he couldnt, but we did talk and i told him that the commute is just too much BabooRachl: ok Dr Bugg: that it wasnt justifiable BabooRachl: right Dr Bugg: and he gave me shit about how he and bentley college made it very clear that they needed someone who could commit to august particularly until the last week, and i told him that i was fully prepared to commit, but unforeseen circumstances made it necessary for me to move home Dr Bugg: and he was like, "well what happened?" and so i told him my roommate threw a party while we were gone and the landlord kicked us all out... Dr Bugg: close enough to the truth  Dr Bugg: whatever Dr Bugg: hes going to call me back after he talks to his supervisor, once im out of work Dr Bugg: and sitting in traffic for 2 hours :-D BabooRachl: awesome BabooRachl: that's horrendous BabooRachl: but better than sitting in traffic for two hours Dr Bugg: yes, i understand that he wants look out for the interest of his customers, but if he doesnt look out for the interest of his talent, he cant have any customers Dr Bugg: (you are participating in my blog, btw...) BabooRachl: oh am i? BabooRachl: how? Dr Bugg: im typing to you and copying it to my blog BabooRachl: hi mindofmary BabooRachl: lolol BabooRachl: I can't believe that he's making you wait on this BabooRachl: i mean, technically, he can't keep you from quitting BabooRachl: can he? Dr Bugg: oh hell no Dr Bugg: he can waste his breath trying, but i still dont give a damn Dr Bugg: whats he going to do? Dr Bugg: tell my mother? Dr Bugg: keep me after school?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       People have the right to fly  And when it gets compromised  Their hearts say "Move along"  Their minds say "Gotcha heart"  Let's move it along  Let's move it along   And airports  See it all the time  With someone's last goodbye  Blends in with someone's sigh  Cause someone's coming home  In hand a single rose   And that's the way this wheel keeps working now  That's the way this wheel keeps working now  And I won't be the last  No I won't be the last,  To love her   And you can't build a house of leaves  And live like it's an evergreen  It's just a season thing  It's just this thing that seasons do   And that's the way this wheel keeps working now  That's the way this wheel keeps working now  And you won't be the first  No you won't be the first  To love me   You can find me, if you ever want to give  I'll be around the bend  I'll be around the bend  I'll be around,  I'll be around  And if you never stop when you wave goodbye  You just might find if you give it time  You will wave hello again  You just might wave hello again   And that's the way this wheel keeps working now  That's the way this wheel keeps working now   You can't love too much, one part of it   I believe that my life's gonna see  The love I give  Return to me  I believe that my life's gonna see  The love I give  Return to me  I believe that my life's gonna see  The love I give  Return to me    ~  John Mayer  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SHA LA LA LA (as repeatedly sung by Ed)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      holy chaos, batman! friday traffic was surprisingly light. both babs and ventre (w/angela) arrived on cape comparatively early. eric and i had a quickie dinner at friendlys (i highly recommend the cajun style chicken with jack and monterey cheeses topped with tomatoes...d-lish) before heading to the poptart-filled insanity that is the hyannis show. bonnie and alan miller recruited me to "handstamp", which proved to be hysterical. alan fires one-liners like ive never heard...most people walk away totally confused (and by most people, i mean poptarts.) friday's party was as equally retarded as last weekend, if not more so.   who are you and why are you here?  ~ fugly chick to rachel.   so are you friends with the guys? which ones are single?  ~ fugly chick to ventre. um, pardon? also, i wonder how emily (aka "face") would feel if she knew that she wasnt respected enough for anyone to actually call her by her name. shes a nice girl who just doesnt have a clue. i should stop by and see her at work (although i shudder at the thought of running into shelley-the-bitch). i would like to see lizzie, betty, dave, bill, and nick if they are still around. oh CLH how i miss your earning potential! (this time last summer i had banked roughly $5000, drop a 0 and thats whats in my account this summer)...was it worth it to have fucked up my knee? i still dont have an answer to that question, but my guess is that it wasnt...injury sucks.  lets see, what else happened this weekend...saturday brought a beautiful day at the beach with babs and katie (tim's girlfriend). its been almost a year since i had been to skanky bitch (skaket beach), jebas. will had a lemonade stand outside CLH, hes so damn adorable, too bad his mom and sister are miserable bitches. anywho...the water was delightful and lets be honest, there are few things in this world better than sun, sand, and onion rings. babs and i ended the day watching movies and cockroaches/napping/trying to figure out why the heck katie drove back and forth from sandwich to west yarmouth twice. the world may never know. i feel like there was more to this day, but i cant tell you for the life of me...babs, as youre reading this, let me know if you remember what the hell else we did.   sunday was a blur, slept in just b/c i could, eric and i had brunch at the mancake pan (oh boy!!!!!) for the best damn blueberry pancakes ever (side order of corned beef hash...drool), then it was off to dana's for her annual 4thofJuly BBQ...so much meat, so little time. after i had managed to shove as much food as humanly possible into my face (hahaha...face), it was a(n) (entirely needless) mad dash to p-town with babs and the boys, at which point we schlepped from the p-town theatre -> downtown and back (as they tried not to get arrested for singing without street permits). cue the HS "show":  by a show of hands, how many of you have seen us perform before?  ~ HS member to the audience  by a show of hands, how many of you have hooked up with a HS member in the past 3 days?  ~ the better question, i asked rachel...and apparently the same question discussed backstage during intermission.  in a word: pathetic. ive reached my breaking point as far as how much general indecency i can tolerate. yes, they are young. yes, they are still in the process of maturing. but were they absent the day they taught respect? for others? for oneself? anyone? anyone? bueller? after the show, we headed back to danas for good company and dessert (danas key lime pie is to die for)...did i mention that vic got pulled over? oops. pretty sure i was stuck behind a really, really old person when we passed that cop. 11pm rolled around and i was ready to pass out. so i did =)   monday was clean-the-house-because-its-just-too-damn-filthy day. to anyone going up the stairs at #6: be aware that micah polished them, and you risk breaking a leg (in the pain and agony sort of way). however, the floor and stove and dishes and basement and living room and (upstairs) bathroom  are all spotless (i drew the line at cleaning the downstairs bathroom)(or at least they were 24 hours ago)...hurray for teamwork, it only took a two hours and the place looked great. following our cleaning rampage, eric, vic and i set off for wareham to make copies of flyers, however, traffic was horrendous and it took forever. once we finally got over the bridge and to the exit, vic's car (that had been following mine westward) suddenly disappeared as we rounded the off-ramp...as eric and i circled the rotary a few times, he called to say that he had spun out but was ok (im amazed hes still brave enough to drive at this point). chez donahue afforded us a xerox machine and several tuna sandwiches. moving along, we caravaned back to falmouth for the show and then to friendlys for ice cream. ri-goddamn-diculously busy, poor waitstaff...3 parties of 6+ people at 10:30 = sucky. some white trash, obnoxious, idiots in the booth by the door began clapping loudly; chiming in was the booth next to me. at which point i left, along with the rest of my booth, so as not to be associated with such immaturity. again, its about respect. and some people just dont have any. eric and i were lucky enough to catch dinner at the friendlys in west yarmouth before they closed and i headed home.  presently: ive had a really fucking long day at work. on 4 hours sleep, no less. i fully intend to quit, unfortunately, michael (my rep at randstad) wasnt in today, so i had to schedule an appointment with him tomorrow to give him my two weeks. stupid. stupid. stupid. and im spent. T-1.25 hours. sorry it took so long to give you something to read babs ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      despite the hell i went through to get here, i may never leave...i was such a little kid getting off the plane! its gorgeous. period. the weather, the bay, the ocean, the mountains & hills, the lack of 93/95/128 traffic. and the people are just plain chill. i feel like im wearing a sign that says "hi, im an uptight east-coast bitch." =)&nbsp;   interview: went really well. have another scheduled with the president of the college wednesday via phone.   treatment: this morning. for free. holla. i feel so good. and they gave me a discounted prescription for a back xray from the orthopedic center next door. make sure my lumbar vertebrae are ok/not causing the pain in my legs.   apartments: looked at one in a very quiet gated community close to the school. somewhat in need of renovations, but for $375/mo i cant complain. laura offered it to me if i could let her know by sunday. oy. im also going to check out a few from the huge book my admissions officer reenie gave me. some by the bay/beach. some closer to school. we'll see.   phone: got a new one. hit it up.   calls: have a ton to make. so thats all, folks.   miss all of you on the east coast!!!! wish i could take you all out here =(&nbsp; come visit!! mu-ah!   ps. apologies for the gansta-esque qualities of this email. im just fired up, yo.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rachel (Babs) MacNamara - you are fabulous more than words can adequately describe. Thanks for just plain being born. =)  Joey Blum - despite all the chaos, you always manage to rise above. Thanks for being an inspiration.  Happy Birthday and all my love to you both. Wish I could be at your respective "there"s.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so its wendnesday, july 14th. and im leaving for san diego. and im ecstatic. and also im petrified. if i over-think this right now, it will result in complete disaster...  new topic:  teitur - paradise lounge - sunday, july 18th - 8pm - $12   caitlin, ventre, babs (if youre back from the cape already?), kyla (ditto/not going back to VT just yet; get a ride with cait and send your parents home), danes (if you wanna/arent busy), nello, kathy, jeff (if you read this), anyone else who might want to come with...  ok, leaving...oy vey.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - eric: for loving me despite myself - babs: for being my sanity and my strength as i sit here at work needing to cry - the little kid running laps on the track near bentley: for pretending to cross the finish line and doing a happy dance - ventre: for the comment "you suck, hope your peepee falls off" - dominic's: for a chocolate cannoli - stevie: for being on the radio at lunch - caitlin: for the "fearsome foursome" - san diego: for having a current temperature of 78 degrees, and opening its arms to me in less than 2 days - cort: for causing the mess that has propelled me toward being a stronger person, pursuing my academic/career goals, and trying to take better care of the people i love
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every thing about it. Most people from it.*   I want to run away to the opposite side of the country. I may very well do that, if all goes well on Thursday. But im realizing (slowly and with too many tears) that i cant run away from life. Moving solves my immediate issues: proximity to the constant reminders of things that hurt/the people im hurting in response, seeming lack of direction/sense of purpose....etc. But the long-term, deep-rooted issues will follow me to california.  And just like that, life interrupts. Stacks of shit piled on my desk...silver lining: only 1 more day of this crap.    *My apologies to those few new yorkers i actually give a crap about.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BabooRachl: i feel bad for tuna fish BabooRachl: because you never hear anyone putting fish after any other fish Dr Bugg: like swordfish fish? BabooRachl: lol BabooRachl: can I have a sturgeon fish filet? BabooRachl: no, it's just sturgeon Dr Bugg: lol BabooRachl: it's almost like people have to remind themselves that Tuna is a fish 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       the street light winds    through my cheap venetian blinds    the hip-hop beat    will not go to sleep     &nbsp;   so i step outside    and go stalking in the night    'cause i dont know what to do about my life     &nbsp;   so im watchin you sleep    right outside your window    inches away from sleepin with you    you dont even know it    watchin you sleep all night     &nbsp;   all day long    ive been sleepin like a log    i dream your face    through the window at your place     &nbsp;   i guess its wrong    but ive been lonely for so long    and i dont know what to do about my life     &nbsp;   so im watchin you sleep    right outside your window    inches away from sleepin with you    dreamin in the day   and    watchin you sleep all night     &nbsp;   i confess    i looked up your work address    it wasnt fate    that bumped into you that day     &nbsp;   but its still me    that holds your hand when your asleep    'cause you dont know what to do about your life     &nbsp;   so im watchin you sleep    right outside your window    inches away from sleepin with you    you dont even know it    watchin you sleep all night     &nbsp;   im watchin you sleep all night     &nbsp;   ~ bleu    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What's it been over a decade?   It still smarts like it was four minutes ago   We only influenced each other totally   We only bruised each other even more so       What are you my blood? You touch me like you are my blood   What are you my dad? You affect me like you are my dad       How long can a girl be shackled to you?   How long before my dignity is reclaimed?   How long can a girl stay haunted by you?   Soon I'll grow up and I won't even flinch at your name   Soon I'll grow up and I won't even flinch at your name       Where've you been? I heard you moved to my city   My brother saw you somewhere downtown   I'd be paralyzed if I ran into you   My tongue would seize up if we were to meet again       What are you my god? You touch me like you are my god   What are you my twin? You affect me like you are my twin       How long can a girl be tortured by you?   How long before my dignity is reclaimed?   And how long can a girl be haunted by you?   Soon I'll grow up and I won't even flinch at your name   Soon I'll grow up and I won't even flinch at your name       So here I am one room away from where I know you're standing   A well-intentioned man told me you just walked in   This man knows not of how this information has affected me   But he knows the colour of the car I just drove away in       What are you my kin? You touch me like you are my kin   What are you my air? You affect me like you are my air        How long can a girl be tortured by you?   How long before my dignity is reclaimed?   And how long can a girl be haunted by you?   Soon I'll grow up and I won't even flinch at your name   Soon I'll grow up and I won't even flinch at your name    ~ Alanis Morissette   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      urlLink Which Family Guy character are you?  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The following is a list of things my mum has always said, and things&nbsp;that i should start paying attention to:   there will always be people who are better and worse than you, so&nbsp;stop agonizing over your perceived shortcomings  if someone is talking about  you , it means they are giving someone  else  a rest  dont waste your time on anger  who cares what people think about you. the people who matter can be counted on one hand, two if youre really lucky  the best things in life, money cant buy  (I think she found it quicker than both "the best things in life are free", and "money cant buy happiness")   it wont hurt&nbsp;you to spend a half an hour to make someone happy  dont be mean to your sister. shes the only one who's been there your entire life and may someday be your only link to those memories  time to get up, hunny.  (5 minutes later) &nbsp;mary t, wake up.&nbsp; (10 minutes later)  mary,&nbsp;get up.  (15 minutes later, as the covers are ripped off)  right now, mary theresa.   that last one seems especially pertinent, considering&nbsp;its 6 am. oh yeah, and i havent slept yet.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So lately i havent felt motivated enough by anything in particular to compose an actual, honest to god, "heres my soul" kind of&nbsp;blog.  but at this moment i am compelled.  i dont know what changed or when.  but here goes.   first order of business: i was accepted to grad school. wahoo. no really im elated. its just the aforementioned lack of energy. i feel as though ive stalled for no reason whatsoever. im hoping to god that its not just because the new-ness has worn off and/or reality is hitting me that im leaving all that is comfort and familiarity in less than a month. and then i read my horoscope for today...     It may become apparent that what was so light and active yesterday is running into a few roadblocks today, dear Aries. It may seem as if you are suddenly heading straight into a brick wall with some of the projects you have been working on. Suddenly there is a more reserved tone to things and precious momentum may have been lost. Use this time to back off and reassess the wisdom of the direction you were going.    FUCKING GREAT. thank you msn astrology for reaffirming my fears.   which brings me to my second topic: im not usually a believer, but after this past monday night, beau has officially freaked me the hell out in terms of the supernatural. she read my palm(s). and erics. and arjuns. and recently babs. i have had no real conversation with beau. EVER. yet she was telling me things about my nature/past/family/demons that she had NO possible way of knowing. not your generic,&nbsp;omni-applicable&nbsp;"you have been unhappy" bullshit. specific, hardcore, holy crap, details. and if she was guessing, well then, that shes damn lucky. she was 98% accurate. and perhaps more so with eric. and at least that dead-on about arjun and rach. for anyone with an open mind to these sorts of things (a la&nbsp;"going in with no expectations"),&nbsp;i recommend her highly. preferably when shes not stuck with the clique. hey, i try to give everyone a fair shot, but sometimes people just instantly grate on your last nerve. and frankly, t2 is one of the irritating masses that seem to take over 6 morgan on any given friday. oh lord. stop me before i get on  that  topic. save it for a rainy day. when i have a lot more time to waste.   third: Public Service Announcement #158 - For the love of all that is holy =), please dont inquire as to the status of the relationship between eric and i.&nbsp;  there is no answer to such a question . it is downright confusing and complicated and ever-shifting.&nbsp;neither of us could give a cut and dry response. a pretty safe bottom line would be to say that we love each other very much and always will and want the best for each other. anything beyond that is speculation. some random-ass girl at the hyannis show seems to think we are back together. fine. lovely. discuss amongst yourselves. this has been a public service announcement, paid for by the "tiredoftryingtoexplain association".   fourth (and returning to issue #1): i just got confirmation of a gigantic private loan. only one of a few im sure...but we'll see how the fed. gov. treats me. fafsa how i loathe thee.&nbsp;not only do i need to pay for school, but for the cost of living.&nbsp;another excellent segue...   fifth: my non-existant apt. i finally heard back&nbsp;from the guys with the ultra-desirable apt between the bay and the ocean in mission beach. no dice. im unloved.&nbsp;second runner-up. (i see a tacky t-shirt slogan from my adolescence&nbsp;that reads&nbsp;"second is the first loser") fabulous.   ok, im drained. thats all ive got for now. the sox took a lot out of me tonight...i blame them for premature&nbsp;aging.   ill leave on a good note, hopefully it will take care of my sleep-karma. =)    Good night, sleep tight and pleasant dreams to you    Here's a wish and prayer that every dream comes true    And though it's always sweet sorrow to part    I know you'll always remain in my heart  Good night, sleep tight and pleasant dreams to you    Here's a wish and a prayer that every dream comes true    And now 'til we meet again  Adios, au revior, auf weidersehen.....good night.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://hyannissound.smugmug.com/gallery/179022/2/6751974   "Anything for $$$ Party"  2002 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      5/24 Lately, it may seem that you have been accumulating a lot of excess nervous tension and stress, dear Aries. Unfortunately, you won't be able to count on the people around you today to make it any better. In your relationship, for example, you may find that what your partner wants and what you want do not coincide. It may be time to think about doing something to reenergize your relationship. How about planning a weekend away, for just the two of you...  5/25 A very nice day is in store for you, dear Aries. People may seem more attentive to you and to your needs, and generally very pleasant to be around. You may not be used to this kind of treatment! As for you, you feel more outgoing and sociable than ever before. You could take advantage of the tolerant atmosphere of the day to meet people you may have been too afraid to even introduce yourself to. They will surely have some new things to teach you...  5/26 Some rather unusual events could cause you to feel discontented with your lifestyle and contemplating some rather major changes, dear Aries. Money matters might need attention, and this could prove to be frustrating. Outrageous ideas for improving your financial status could be popping into your mind. Make a list of your options, then wait a few days before actually making serious plans. This is NOT the day to start anything new, particularly with regard to major changes.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yes. so ive been in a foul mood. no. i dont  specifically  know why. i could give you a million reasons. looking at my recent posts, i realize ive been on a "list" kick. so im just going to roll with it. lets play with numbers this time to mix it up, shall we?     i hurt. like, everywhere. bruises. cuts. tailbone. muscles. places i didnt know i had places.  then throw in a ton of non-physical hurt. ego. heart. energy. general emotional state.  to elaborate on #2, my past, my parents, my "job", my impending move/lack of housing.  oh fuck this.     i dont even have the energy to rant. theres so much more shoved away inside my head/heart than this stupid list could even begin to describe. it will process on its own and ill start feeling better. most of it just needs time and distance. in the meantime, ill just make a more concerted effort to be cheery. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      two words: theme party. two more words: oy vey.  hs tp '04 recap:    micah - parKING (dd)  jim - KING midas (goldschlager)  victor - KING kong (banana rum)  cooper - elvis, the KING (lynchburg lemonade)  ed - KING of beers (budweiser)  eric - KING of spades (various alcohols, facilitated by a card game, naturally)  tim - KING of KINGS ie. God (non-alcoholic punch)  paul - burger KING (rum &amp; coke)  joe - KINGdom cum (love punch/sex on the beach)    the debauchery abounded. the poptarts annoyed. the cops busted. a good time was had by all. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Focus on the information coming your way today, dear Aries, and try not to get too emotional regarding the consequences of this information. More than likely, you will find that a neutral approach is the best in any situation you encounter. If you already have a strong preconceived notion of how things are going to be, you will fail to notice valuable nuances that are being presented to you at this time.    How do you know that i spent 20 minutes talking to the only decent one of my former roommates, who hesitated and then proceeded to fill me in on the past month and a half (most of which i had predicted from the outset)???  How do you know that i could only moderately refrain from joining in the bashing (ie. "get too emotional")??  How do you know that i tried desperately to maintain the morally higher ground (ie. "a neutral approach")??  And what "valuable nuances" did i miss (can timmy  pronounce  "nuances"?!)?? ARGH. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its bittersweet, this feeling im experiencing. i dont like that im relishing in the plight of others. but i cant lie. i do like that karma has struck. shes a bitch, isnt she? you got yours, 'enry 'iggins... and yet, beyond this self-righteous, self-serving affirmation, i truly feel sorry for you.  you sacrificed something of greater worth than you even realized. and for what? temporary, instant, and not-so-gratifying gratification? injury to all those involved?  you will be lonely, as long as you keep hurting the ones you are closest to. you will not achieve, as long as you keep settling for mediocrity. you will self-destruct, as long as you keep your lifestyle.  ive said all this - and then some - in our silly email war. but sometimes the truth isnt pretty, and you know where i stand on honesty.  maybe next time youll think first and act accordingly/appropriately. maybe, but i doubt it. at least not until you can look at yourself as objectively as introspection can be. so good luck with that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so its 2am and im sitting here thinking about my job. well, technically speaking, my ex-job...probably the shortest employment of my life. im not gonna lie, i rather enjoyed it. what other job lets you pretend youre hangin out at a club with your best friend and other high school acquaintances? i now find myself listening to the radio and stopping on songs i would normally have avoided, simply because i want to jump out of my car and dance. i think thats a good thing...except that my outlet for dancing is nonexistent. for the record (jim), i did not work as an "entertainer", but rather as a waitress. that notwithstanding, it did afford me the opportunity to stand around and dance  with myself  on any given night. i think it did a lot to lighten my mood. i dont know that  all  of those around me lately would agree, but whatever. i notice it, even in its smallest measurement.  and from that high, i come crashing down: just checked ventre's countdown...realizing how close i am to departure. wondering if anyone will come to say goodbye. i hope so.  14 days. still no place to live.  im pretty sure ive cried every day since my mum came home. and not likely to stop from here to the 22nd. shit. i hate second guessing. i can do this. i swear to god, i know i can do this. and i know i want to. its so damn exciting and scary all in the same breath. BREATH, mary. sometimes i forget how...just keep reminding me, please... 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I woke up early this mornin' around 4am   With the moon shinin' bright as headlights on the interstate   I pulled the covers over my head and tried to catch some sleep   But thoughts of us kept keepin' me awake   Ever since you found yourself in someone else's arms   I've been tryin' my best to get along   But that's OK   There's nothin' left to say, but      Take your records, take your freedom   Take your memories I don't need 'em   Take your space and take your reasons   But you'll think of me   And take your cap and leave my sweater   'Cause we have nothin' left to weather   In fact I feel a whole lot better   But you'll think of me, you'll think of me      I went out drivin', tryin' to clear my head   I tried to sweep out all the ruins that my emotions left   I guess I'm feelin' just a little tired of this   And all the baggage that seems to still exist   It seems the only blessing I have left to my name   Is not knowin' what we could have been   What we should have been      SoTake your records, take your freedom   Take your memories I don't need 'em   Take your space and take your reasons   But you'll think of me   And take your cap and leave my sweater   'Cause we have nothin' left to weather   In fact I feel a whole lot better   But you'll think of me      Someday I'm gonna run across your mind   Don't worry, I'll be fine   I'm gonna be alright   While you're sleepin' with your pride   Wishin' I could hold you tight   I'll be over you    And on with my life      So take your records, take your freedom   Take your memories I don't need 'em   And take your cap and leave my sweater   'Cause we have nothin' left to weather   In fact I feel a whole lot better   But you'll think of me      So take your records, take your freedom   Take your memories I don't need 'em   Take your space and all your reasons   But you'll think of me   And take your cap and leave my sweater   'Cause we've got nothin' left to weather   In fact I feel a whole lot better   But you'll think of me, you'll think of me, yeah      And you're gonna think of me   Oh someday baby, someday      ~ Keith Urban  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>