<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is some free association  urlLink fun  i just discovered via  urlLink trilia   1. Lounge ~ chaise 2. Photograph ~ black and whites by man ray 3. Catacomb ~ rome and skeletons and crying babies 4. Crucifix ~ jesus will protect me from dracula 5. Fire drill ~ quietly, single file outside on blacktop 6. Tube ~ toothpaste 7. Dropped ~ acid 8. LTD ~ Ford 9. Panther ~ Black 10. Formica ~ countertops i am sure someone in this absurd blog world has a rorschach dealie.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, it's almost over. my semi-perpetual, inescapable slavic страдание. i think it seems to always come around especially hard near my birthday. my appetite is gone, i could sleep all day, my eyes feel weird, like they are heavy lidded and squinty weird, like renee zellwegger's. but i think i am crawling out of the abyss. my poor dh. how he suffers with me and stays with me is to be commended highly. but no tears today, so major progress! this is beyond hormones, folks, so don't even suggest it. it isn't even that time anyway.  but good news: haley hasn't barffed since saturday night! After a $250 vet bill, they have told me she is fine and doesn't have diabetes, thank god. how could she? she's a mutt and extremely healthy. only pure breds get that weird s$@&. imo. mostly. but my  urlLink vet  people are awesome. i recommend them to all in east dallas.  hint for self-esteem boost: if you want to feel really good-looking and well-dressed, go to the sam's club in the land of gar. whoooo-eee. i felt like paris hilton or something.
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, i give up. you beat me. i will never learn coding. give me gui any day. this is what happens to you when you choose photography class over tandy 180s or whatever we had in the 7th grade in 1982. i was a major technophobe for a long time. now, i played my fair share of atari games and whatnot, but i never really was interested in trying to make the computer do things. i had a typewriter in college. i only knew two people who had macs. until now. i supposed i could try to learn, and i have figured out the super basics of html, but i will never be able to get this skin to look like how i really want unless i pay someone. i looked through tons of skins on other sites, but nothing really fit. or they didn't have all the features i wanted, or some didn't work and i had no idea how to fix them. so, we shall go with the blogger minima black for now, sans pics because i can't even get stupid hello to work.   it's around lunch time. i should go get something. i will probably treat myself to the delicioso chicken fajita salad at taco cabana. but i won't eat the shell. and i'll take off most of the sour cream. but i will definitely eat all the guac. and put extra pico and cilantro on it. yes, your slightly pudgy pollock is doing the low carb thing again. the way it's become overhyped in the media and our consumer culture in general is truly annoying. this plan  does  work, but you must totally change your eating habits for the  REST OF YOUR LIFE . You cannot go back to eating that whole loaf of rosemary bread at Macaroni Grill. it doesn't work that way, sadly. it creeps back. and you really need to work out at least 4 times a week. i'm writing this more for my own sake, i guess. the ukrainian women told me 10 years ago that pasta and bread will make you fat and i laughed at them. well, look at us now! 
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      let's see how this puppy works. why am i becomming obsessed by blogging? i can't program, i don't even turn on the computer on the weekends for the most part unless i need a map or have forgotten to buy someone a birthday present, which happens often. will i be able to figure out how to put a different template on this sucker? the plot shall unfold shortly.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, we just found out that the elderly lady's creepy grandson is...an ex-con! Yes, folks, he has been in jail and more than once. Once for stealing a car and for assualt. And whom did he assault? None other than HIS OWN MOTHER. He apparantly  broke her ribs  and also beat up his girlfriend. He has asked other neighbours for money and apparantly his grandmother, who lives with his mother, posted a sign on their door: No Cash. No Credit Cards. No Checks. DH got a 12 gauge shotgun. Can't seem to find rock salt. I feel so dirty having to buy a gun. Is that the weirdest? I don't feel more powerful or protected or secure. Just dirty. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the crying out loud, as Grandma Rita used to say, the creepiness continues. The flies have stopped, your Hutsulka solved that mystery. The floors and walls are a tad sticky from all the Helene Curtis spritz hairspray all over, but the bugs are no more. Last night I settled in to watch a movie on cable I had always wanted to see, mainly because when it came out, my mom forbade me to see it: Mommie Dearest. So I'm getting into it, loving the over the top acting and bad wigs, and the doorbell rings at 9:30pm. DH was already doing his Homer Simpson look by that time (in his bvd's and t-shirt), and I was reluctant to answer, but we have a lot of elderly people in our neighbourhood, so I thought maybe something was wrong and someone fell down or something. So all three of us (including Haley, the crazy lab mix) go to the door, DH asks who it is, and it's the grandson of one of our elderly neighbours. DH had loaned him the phone a month or so ago, I wasn't home at that time. DH says hold on, let me get dressed, and I open the door with Haley right next to me. But it's hard for a lab to look intimidating, especially this wimpy dog. I wanted her to growl, like she does with some strangers, but she just stood there with a dopey dog smile on and wagging her tail. So this guy is late 30s, early 40s, and starts rambling on about how his grandmother isn't home and is in Southlake and he got hit by a woman who had no insurance and his electrical system is all blinking and he drove around the corner and his headlight fell out and his wife is in the car, and well, Larry at PepBoys says he can fix it up for $9. I told him that we had no cash, sorry. But then DH goes and gets $9 out his wallet! This is the oldest freakin' story in the book! He said the "accident" was at Preston and LBJ. Well, what the hell is he doing all the way down in our neighborhood? And PepBoys closes at 9. I was pretty pissed at the DH. I don't want this crackhead coming back asking for more, or breaking into our house for that matter. It was hard for me to go to sleep last night. Then about an hour ago, the DH calls me and tells me he's taking the day off and going to get a shotgun, shells, and rock salt, a la Kill Bill vol. 2. I have never been a big fan of guns, but I am not opposed to this. I am so creeped out now. I am going to go talk to his grandmother and see what the deal is. See what her reaction is when I tell her was around asking for money. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had the strangest thing going on the past two evenings at our house. We had a bunch of flies buzzing around in the kitchen. Last night we came home from the Y and there must have been about 12 flies divebombing all over trying to eat and lay more maggots. We didn't want to use bugspray, so I used an old trick I used to do, spray those suckers with hairspray until they can't fly well and them smoosh em. So dh and I were running all over the kitchen, me spraying the flies and dh swatting them with the day's Dallas Morning News, still in the baggie. The dog flipped out, thought we were mad at her and went and hid in my closet. We had fly guts all over the cabinets and counters, so I started cleaning that up. We thought we were done. We gave puppy a treat, comforted her, she seemed to be placated. Then more flies started buzzing around. What the F? So the whole scene repeated itself. The dog flipped out again and ran for the hills, and we ended doing the worst postmodern dance routine ever in the kitchen trying to kill about 10 more flies. DH then said only half joking that this was starting to resemble Amityville Horror. That sent shivers up my spine. I then noticed that there were three little f)*&amp;ers sitting on a white towel on the dryer in the utility room. I made a note of this, but went back to chasing flies with fruit-smelling hairspray. We could not figure out where these were coming from. All the doors and windows were shut. We have huge gaps under our front and garage door, but there was nothing there. I went back into the utility room and looked behind the washer and dryer, and lo. There was a 4" diameter hole in the wall that went to the crawl space or the plumbing space in between the bathroom and the utility wall. I have no recollection of this hole ever being there. When we moved in, there was no washer or dryer in that space, but I sure don't remember there being a big hole cut in the wall. Very weird. Very  urlLink House of Blue Leaves . So dh put tape all over it, but we need to something permanent. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       subluminous         Sleep:: yum       Stats:: class from hell        Portfolio:: leather       Lipton:: tea       Telly:: England       Immigrate:: travel       Viable:: strong       Serene:: quiet       Mountain:: sierra nevada       Natalie:: Portman        
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, still no call from the software co. Still in limbo. I guess I'll be the aggressive go-getter mba type that I pretend to be and give 'em a jingle manana. I thought I wrote some kick-ass thank you letters too. I'm surprised to hear I haven't made the second cut. They probably think there is no way they can pay me as much as they think I should earn since I have an MBA (a real MBA from a full-time program, from a TOP 20 in the USA PROGRAM, I might add...), but they are wrong. The current place of rabota pales in terms of salary and bennies.      But that's neither here nor there. I love that phrase. Much better than saying some dumbass analogy or even a non-analogy and then adding "if you will" at the end and trying to sound smart. I noticed that this was quite the catch phrase for tv journalists covering Bush's Iraq War Part Deux. It drove me bonkers to hear that phrase everyday. "It's carpet bombing, if you will." Well, it either is or isn't. What if I WON'T? It was major pet peeve of mine. It seems to be disappearing in the vernacular lately, slava bogu (thank god, for you non ruso or uki speakers).      Went to  urlLink Kalachandji's  today for lunch with the boss immediately over me. It was pretty good, but it always kinda tastes the same. Not that I mind, but I couldn't eat that everyday. The soup was some kind of dahl and was pretty extraordinary though. This one hari krishna chick there is intriguing, not in a lesbian way or anything, please! She has been there since I started going there about 3-4 years ago. She is really thin, is white, always wears a sari, and has striking blue eyes. I heard her speaking with some guy there once in a language I knew was Slavic, but couldn't figure out what it was. I asked her and it turns out she's from Serbia. I found that so crazy. She always acts kinda stressed out and harried, so maybe this hari krishna thing isn't really the inner peace she was hoping for. But maybe she doesn't like wasting time waitressing. I'd rather be chanting. She must have come here some time ago. So once upon a time hari krishnas were dancing down the old cobblestoned and shellshocked streets of Belgrade in the early 1990s getting converts? OK, I'll dump this Orthodox/Catholic/Muslim thing, just get me the f outta Dodge, dude!     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dios mio. Already Friday! Had an interesting week. I interviewed for a position with a software company on Tuesday morning, pretty much to do the same thing I'm doing now, but possibly for $10k more a year. I should find out yea or nay soon. I'm nervous. I'm overqualified for the job, but that dengi is nice. Light a candle for me. The plusses: more money, new industry for me, same bennies, better 401(k),. The minuses: unknown devil, unknown workload, unknown bosses, possibly more travel.    I finally swam some laps yesterday. I was not having an easy time. I only did about 1.25 miles and it was a struggle. It's amazing how quickly I can lose my fitness level for swimming, but it comes back just as quickly. Ideally I'd like to swim 2x a week, but dh wants to do more gym work than that allows. We're going tonight and I'll do the bike and walking and weights.     What I really need to do is stop eating so much. I wish I didn't love food so much. We discovered a pretty good TexMex place. It's Mario and Alberto's on Preston. The menu said that the carne asada was filet mignon, and I, of course, said, yea right. Oh Dios Mio! It really was! It was the best carne asada I've ever had. The filet was probably sliced in half and then pounded thin, marinated in delectible spices, and then grilled so that it was actually medium. Now that takes some freakin skill to grill that thin filet like that. It was amazing. 4 stars. The decor of the place is ultra wacky. Nearly everything is pink. The walls are pink, the tablecloths are pink, the napkins are pink. Then there these huge mirrors along the walls with these enormous wrought iron crosses with votives burning in them. The ceiling was decorated with wrought iron lamps interspersed with baskets of gargantuan multi-colored paper flowers, with many being pink, of course, to match the walls and linens. I've never seen wrought iron and pink together. If you think it doesn't go together, you're right. I really don't think even Thom Felicia could make that look work.    welcome to dullsville  urlLink sublumina  of hutsulka's mushy noggin:    Nostalgia:: sad longing    Irreplaceable:: valuable    Odd:: strange    James Spader:: kinda cute. Find him cuter now than in the 1980s.    Flamboyant:: gay    Intense:: hyper    Simple:: life    Septic:: tank    Ton:: tonnage    Turkey:: stuffing          
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh, Friday. My first full week of using the Foxfire browser. It's ok, but for some reason I find it a little slower than IE and none of my radio players work, so I have to open my beloved 3wk in IE. I don't know why Real Player or Windows Media Player won't work in Firefox. I am still a bit of a technophobe/luddite, so I don't want to mess with anything too much. I just went to a celebration for two people in our company who have been there for 20 years. Apparantly one of them turned in her resignation yesterday. This person(A) is just fed up with her boss's(D) crap, I'm sure. My boss thought it made no sense, which I find totally incredulous. D would make A do personal stuff for her on company time and then tell her that she had to make up the time. You can only take so many years of that. I wouldn't have lasted more than a few months before the door would hit my ass on the way out. D nearly ran this company into the ground, imo. Her ego is just enormous. Regardless, A will be missed. She is indeed an angel.     So Martha  urlLink Martha  Martha got 5 months. Now, talk about a boss from hell, but I still love her magazine and show, and I think that the whole thing was a bitch hunt. The fact that the Feds with after her with such vehemence and vigor is pretty suspicious. Like most rich old white men in the Good Ole Boys Club haven't pulled much worse schemes and frauds? Talk about incredulous. Gotta stand up for my sister pollocks, too. But the latest headline said that MS Omniliving's stock was up on the news. Relief that it's over and it's mild? It sure is hard to picture her in prison garb amid all that ugly ass CMU and bolted down furniture. I wonder what the monthly Letter from Martha will read like? I heard some bit on NPR the other day about women who had been in prison discussing the various concoctions they made out of vending machine food, which including chips and ramen. One woman said that she kinda has cravings for her ramen recipes now that she is on the outside. Maybe Martha will come up with how to make the perfect Thanksgiving meal from Nutter Butters, Fritos, and shrimp flavoured ramen.     OK, hutsulka o-u-t. happy friday, y'all!     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      from  urlLink her    Crippling:: polio  Tough:: skin  Slinky::dress  Slogan::good to the last drop  Stuffed::shirt  Instructions::dull  Expletive::fuck  Cartoon::bugs bunny  Toddler::terrible 2  Insinuation::narrowed eyes  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good grief, work is BUSY. The phone has been ringing off the hook, which is good. Thought we were headed for the typical summer slowdown.   We survived the weekend with the stepmonster. If you think you know an annoying, know-it-all, trashy, stinky, stepmonster, you do not know M. She is the end all be all of hideousness. She chainsmokes and her teeth are yellow, has the worst taste in fashion imaginable, actually still wears banana clips in her hideous hair, and has her husband completely hoodwinked. So sad. She is so obnoxious, there are hardly words. I just sit back and pound a few Bass Ales and then tune her out. She is the authority on EVERYTHING. Nevermind she never went to college and can't hold a job for more than 2 years before she gets canned/laid off, most likely for being so bloody annoying. She told dh that he was stubborn and that when he had long hair, he should have had bangs and some layers. He blurted out, "And what?!?! Have a MULLET?!?!" She has also argued that the Titanic had been raised and was in the Smithsonian. What a dumbass. Well, we don't have to see them for another 4 months or so. Slava bogu.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy Birthday to me!  And to the other rad person born on this same day in 1970:  urlLink BECK ! If only I was blessed with his musical talent. hmmmmrgg. Seven years of piano lessons didn't do much. I wonder how much los padres blew on  that  failed endeavor. Well, I haven't posted about this to protect S's privacy, but I will soon be an auntie! I am so excited. She thinks it is a girl, which is awesome because the little girl clothes are so much cuter. Just like women's clothes are more interesting, I guess. I am thrilled, even though I think my parents are turning their eyes to me and wondering where their grandchild is. I have never felt particularly maternal, so I hope they don't get their hopes up too much. I'm probably sterile from living a few hundred kilometers from Kyiv for over 3 years. I joke. Many of my Ukrainian friends have had perfectly normal kids.   So we're going to  urlLink Bavarian Grill  tomorrow night so we can have some bieren. I don't like drinking on school nights. It makes Friday seem the longest day EVER when you have a hangover. Very excited. I love Jäger Schnitzel mit Spätzle and the little breads you get, especially this roll that has rock salt on it. Then the salad is to die for. So perfectly Central European with pickled beets, beans, tomatoes. yum. I highly recommend this restaurant.  I have received a lot of birthday greetings from the inlaws, from dh, from my ex, from the president of our company, and from one of the vp's. I work for a small company and I like the president, but I pretty much despise this vp. She is at another office and I don't report to her, thank God. She went and got a bunch of pre-printed cheesey ass cards and had her name imprinted on them and then had her poor admin assist mail it out to me. And the bitch didn't even sign it. She is such a political weasel it makes me puke. She almost destroyed this company with her overblown self-importance and ego, in my opinion. We are lucky that K took over the presidency from C so that she couldn't wield her influence anymore.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      freudian socks from  urlLink her     Resignation:: trepidation  Coupling:: flies  Grounded:: teenager  Habit:: smoking  Chainsaw:: massacre  Rental:: movie  Deleted:: file  Online personals:: cheesey  Penguin:: tuxedo  Offend:: indignant    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blow Job, I mean  urlLink Blow Out , just had its penultimate episode last night. Johnathon is such a tool and has the worst rug! Have you noticed how the cameraman subtly chops off his crown in interview scenes? Anyway, poor Kim. It's hard to believe she's put up with his crap for 2 years. She probably feels trapped, like she won't be able to get anywhere if she quits. This show hasn't been as intriguing as the Restaurant for some reason, but it will still be major summer tv doldrums when it's gone. I should really stop watching shite and read a freaking book.   Or take poor Haley to the  urlLink dog park . I am very interested in whether she will swim if not provoked. She is mostly Lab, but absolutely hates water. She hates rain, hates baths, and we spray water on her as punishment, which sends her running for the hills with her tail between her legs, cowering in the corner and sulking for several hours. But she has these massive paws with webbing in between her toes. If she sees other puppies swimming and retrieving, will some sort of instinct take over and make her leap into the lake? She finally can ride in the car and not barf, so I think a visit is soon in order.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The 4th is over, thank god. I don't know why, but I don't really like it. Now, I'm ultra happy for the day off and all and I am a pretty patriotic soul, although I am what is called a "liberal" these days, but I don't really like it. Maybe it's because I used to be really scared of loud noises when I was little or something. But it is gone and all we have to look forward to now is Labor Day. August is the longest month ever it seems.   We went to our first wedding as a married couple. Got a little sloshy and since the wedding was at civic building in Grapevine, there was a freaking cop there and we had to call a cab. We made the cab driver just drive a couple of miles and then drive back to our car. He started to get totally beligerant and I thought we were going to have to throw down with him, but it all worked out ok. What a hot head. It's not like we didn't have money to pay him and there's no way in hell we wanted him to actually drive us all the way back to Dallas. No injuries, no arrests. whew. We'll be better next time.   Then we just chilled on Sunday and made some steaks at the in-laws and were able to watch 6 fireworks displays on the horizon since we were in Rockwall. It was cool.  On Monday we joined the rest of America in our contribution to making  urlLink Spiderman 2  the highest grossing movie for a three day weekend. I liked it, but I wasn't gaga over it like everyone seems to be. There was so much computer animation in it. And then I didn't understand why his powers started to fade and then come back. And then I found out Kirsten Dunst's hair was a wig. I was kind of bummed about that for some reason. It seems like a cop out to not really dye your hair for the role.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the strange pub, warsaw 1997&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Brando just died. Finally shot with the  urlLink diamond bullet .
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ohhhh, cross your fingers for me that we will be told to go home early! OK, enough with improper capitalization. I will now start writing with capitals. I will not use any lame IM abbreviations either. They way bug.   Agenda for the weekend, nada mucho. Tonight I will go see J's new abode in Richardson while the DH goes to B's bachelor party. I told him I'm ok with the fact that they may go to a strip club, but he cannot have any lap dances or boobies in his mouth. Then tomorrow is B's wedding. I hope he's not hung over. Then the 4th with the inlaws.   I wish we were going to MN for the 4th. I love it at the Lake with the subpar fireworks show of my dad's hometown. The funniest thing is that everyone pretends that it's synchronized to corny music on the local am station. And every year, it's the same music in the same order, ending with that country song "Proud to be An American". I don't know who sings that because I don't know anything about country music except that most of it sucks. Except for Patsy Cline and Johnny Cash. Maybe I like the MN fete because it's always the same. I say that I love change and new things, but I think I love ritual as well. Maybe it's a Catholic thing, I don't know.   Russian word for the day: фейерверк fyerverk fireworks. Those are the Russian words I love. Just sort of a bastardization of another language's word.  English certainly loves doing that.  I doubt I'll write until next week. Rest the ole glazzies.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      stolen from  urlLink her     bold =i've seen it underline=i own it  steal it if you want, but add three movies to the bottom if you do.   01.  Trainspotting  02.  Shrek  03. M 04.  Dogma  05.  Strictly Ballroom  06.  The Princess Bride  07. Love Actually 08.   The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Rings   09.   The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers   10.  The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King  11.  Reservoir Dogs  12. Desperado 13.  Swordfish  14.   Kill Bill Vol. 1   15.  Donnie Darko  16. Spirited Away 17. Better Than Sex 18.  Sleepy Hollow  19.  Pirates of the Caribbean  20. The Eye 21.  Requiem for a Dream  22.  Dawn of the Dead The original.  23. The Pillow Book 24.  The Italian Job  25. The Goonies 26. Baseketball 27. The Spice Girls Movie (Spice World)  28. Army of Darkness 29.  The Color Purple  30. The Safety of Objects 31. Can't Hardly Wait 32.  Mystic Pizza  33. Finding Nemo 34.  Monsters Inc.  35.  Circle of Friends  36.  Mary Poppins  37.  The Bourne Identity  38.  Forrest Gump  39.  A Clockwork Orange  40. Kindergarten Cop 41. On The Line 42.  My Big Fat Greek Wedding  43. Final Destination 44. Sorority Boys 45. Urban Legend 46. Cheaper by the Dozen The original. 47.  Fierce Creatures  48. Dude, Where's My Car 49.  Ladyhawke  50.  Ghostbusters  51.  Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade  52.  Back to the Future  53. An Affair To Remember 54.  Somewhere In Time  55.  North By Northwest  56.  Moulin Rouge  57.  Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets  58.  The Wizard of Oz  59.  Zoolander  60. A Walk to Remember 61.  Chicago  62.   Vanilla Sky   63. The Sweetest Thing 64.  Don't Tell Mom the Babysitter's Dead  65.  The Nightmare Before Christmas  66. Chasing Amy 67.  Edward Scissorhands  68.  Adventures of Priscilla: Queen of the Desert  69.  Muriel's Wedding  70. Croupier 71.   Blade Runner   72.  Cruel Intentions  73. Ocean's Eleven 74.  Magnolia  75.   Fight Club   76.  Beauty and The Beast  77.  Much Ado About Nothing  78.  Dirty Dancing  79.  Gladiator  80.  Ever After  81.  Braveheart  82.  What Lies Beneath   83. Regarding Henry 84.  The Dark Crystal  85.   Star Wars   86.  The Birds  87.  Beaches  88.  Cujo  89. Maid In Manhattan 90. Labyrinth **DAVID BOWIE!! I know every word to this movie! ;) 91. Thoroughly Modern Millie 92. His Girl Friday 93.  Chocolat  94.  Independence Day  95. Singing in the Rain 96.  Big Fish  97. The Thomas Crown Affair 98.   The Matrix   is there anyone who hasn't see this?? 99.  Stargate  100.  A Hard Day's Night  101. About A Boy 102.  Jurassic Park  103.  Life of Brian  104.   Dune    105.  Help!  106.  Grease  107. Newsies 108.  Gone With The Wind  109.  School of Rock  110. TOMMY 111.  Yellow Submarine   112.  From Hell  113.  Benny & Joon  114. Amelie 115.  Bridget Jones' Diary  116.  Monty Python and the Holy Grail  117.  Heavenly Creatures  118. All About Eve 119.  The Outsiders  120.  Airplane!  121. The Sorcerer 122.  The Crying Game  123.  Hedwig and the Angry Inch  124. Slap Her, She's French 125.  Amadeus  126.  Tommy Boy  127.  Aladdin  128. How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days 129.   Snatch   130.  American History X  131. Jack and Sarah 132. Monkey Bone 133.  Rocky Horror Picture Show  134. Kate and Leopold 135.  Interview with the Vampire  136.  Underworld  137. Truly, Madly, Deeply 138. Tank Girl 139. Boondock Saints 140. Blow Dry 141.  Titanic  142.  Good Morning Vietnam  143.  Save the Last Dance  144.  Lost in Translation  145.  Willow  146. Legend 147. Van Helsing 148. Troy 149. Nine Girls and a Ghost 150.  A Knight's Tale  151.  Bill & Ted's Bogus Journey  152.  Beetlejuice  153.  E.T.  154.  Harry Potter and the Sorceror's Stone  155.  Spaceballs  156.  Young Frankenstein  157. Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind 158. American President 159. Bad Boys 160.  Pecker  161.   Pink Floyd: The Wall   161. X-Men 162. Sidewalks of New York 163.  The Children of Dune  164. Beyond Borders 165.  Life Is Beautiful  166.  Good Will Hunting  167.  Run Lola Run (Lola rennt)  168. Blazing saddles 169. Caligula 170. The Transporter 171. Better Off Dead 172.  The Abyss  173.  Almost Famous  174.  The Red Violin  175.  Contact   176. Stand and Deliver 177.  Clueless  178.  William Shakespeare's Romeo+Juliet  179.  Dangerous Liaisons  180. I Am Sam 181. The Usual Suspects 182.  U-571  183. Capricorn One 184.  The Little Shop of Horrors   185.  Die Hard  186.  The Flamingo Kid  187.  Night of the Comet  188. Point Break 189. First Power 190.  Smoke  191. Untamed Heart 192.  So I Married An Axe Murderer  193.  Pump Up The Volume  194.  Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon   adding: 195.   Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels   196.   Andrei Rublev   197.   Time Bandits  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Olympics are in full swing! Yippee! No, Phelps isn't doing what the media predicted, and YES, he  is  living up to expectations. If you don't know much about swimming, then you will believe all the media hype and absurd predictions. Yes, it would have been nice, but y'all have to realize that he is already the best swimmer in the US and that is a HUGE feat unto itself. He is also pretty well-rounded, swimming different strokes and different distances. The swimmers who are beating him specialize in one or two events and that's pretty much all they swim. And remember, this guy is only 19. Can you imagine what a powerhouse he will be in four years? Iam Thorpe really seems to be peaking NOW, not in Sydney, when he was target of all the hype and didn't sweep his events.    In other swimming news, Yana   Klochkova is moya tyolka! Slava Ukrainu!    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Sting:: Police   BMW:: tired brand of car   Jeremy:: Simmons   Audacious::obnoxious   Drag Queen:: dress and bad makeup   Title:: book   Stamp:: post office   Bad:: good   Snow White:: 7 Dwarves   Delegate:: tasks     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        One more day until the swimming begins! Needed distraction.  Ex-con update: saw him and crackhead girlfriend who has one leg (really) out in front of his mother's house yesterday and then saw him hop his mom's fence and go around back and start banging on the door. So we called the cops as we drove off to get some bbq. Came back, no sign of Ronnie or one-legged crackhead girlfriend or cops, so we don't know what happened. Still trying to get a hold of the DPD interactive policing guy for our part of the city, left 3 messages, no call back. Typical city employee. hrmmmphf. 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        opening ceremonies tomorrow! swimming starts saturday! yippee! 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dang it all. Now I'm having a PA flare. I had a bad feeling last night as I was trying to fall asleep. I get this weird pain, it's not super intense, but it's like it's eminating from the inside of my joints. Last night it was in my thumb, but now I am having major flares in my ring finger and knee. It sux. I am going to work out anyway. F it. I refuse to let this disease get in the way of my life. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We actually went mtn biking yesterday. It was the first ride since The Accident, so our first ride in over two years. We went to a super easy, but fun, the  urlLink LB Houston Trail,  which we always call California Crossing. This is a great trail for beginners or if you don't want anything too crazy. Decide fast whether you want to do the dips or not because the mosquitos are horrendous. I pray I don't freakin' get West Nile. I hope to get my skills back quickly. It felt pretty good to ride again.  I must send out my lament that Loehmann's on NW Highway has closed. I am so devasted. That was my favorite store. I liked it because the brands were so great and the sales were awesome and the store was a manageable size, unlike department stores. I am so sad. I have written emails to Loehmann's, but have heard no response. boo hoo. 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Michael Phelps pic o the day     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My  urlLink hometown  makes yahoo frontpage news! Not really the way we would want it, but I knew immediately it was the Auburn Dam. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No developments with our semi-resident ex-con, Ronnie. We did have an impromptu neighour powwow on Liz and Mike's lawn to discuss the situation at hand. He was apparantly in the vincinity a mere 15 minutes before we drove up, coming back from diiner. Nothing was resolved, but the consensus was the sooner he goes back to jail, the better, and if we can in any way expedite the inevitable, we are all willing to do so.  Let me go back to dinner. I want to publicize how delicious the fish and soups are at  urlLink Hurricane Grill  on Greenville. But I thought that was just a bar, you may say. Well, it is primarily, hence there is smoking there, but it's a well ventilated venue. This is the second time we have been there and we haven't tries the oysters, which are apparantly good, too bad I hate oysters. We have gotten the same things and both times were DELICIOUS: blacked catfish with a thick creamy sauce with artichoke hearts and shrimp in it and grilled snapper with bernaise sauce. They are to die for. So yummy. And you must try the crab bisque. It's not a typical pureed pink thin liquid. It's spicy and full of strands of crab meat. It's wonderful. Please go there and patronize the kitchen so they don't do away with the dinner menu.  At the HG some middleaged dude handed us a copy of some new free rag in Dallas called  urlLink Vain . Ripping off  urlLink Vice ? Dunno. Lame magazine, although it's a cool little size. Crappy printing, crappy layout, full of typical crappy Dallas stuff and pictures of fake blondes with fake boobies and all the latest hip places. And was frickin two month's old. Don't you  know  it's bad luck to read old horoscopes, dude? Went straight into the recycling bin. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        to make you feel that icy mint fresh sensation...your hutsulka and DH in Tahoe Christmas 2003. I miss the mountains. Can we grow some here? 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Testicles:: balls   Ribald:: huh? i'm not studying for the SAT, thank you   Auction:: gavel   Inch:: mile   Tony:: award   Phony:: people   Stool:: bar   Coyote:: howl   Cinderella:: dress   Battery:: duracell   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I definitely busted a gut last night watching QEFTSG when Kyan was giving garbageman Al a foot massage. What the hell?? That was completely hysterical. I bet Al will never hear the end of it from his fellow garbagemen. All their roles are being flip flopped around, except for Thom and Carson. Now the other three are telling him cultural stuff and poor Jai is sidelined again. They're edging in on his turf. He should break out some dance moves from West Side Story. I think he's even Puerto Rican.  These are  urlLink actual phobias : Euphobia: Fear of hearing good news Frigophobia: Fear of cold or cold things Geniophobia: Fear of chins Lutraphobia: Fear of otters Zemmiphobia: Fear of the great mole rat  People have got to be making these up. How often do you ever see otters or the great mole rat, for that matter?  I think the end of Western civilization draws nigh.  urlLink More phobias  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Michael Phelps is so awesome. This pic doesn't do him justice. There's a great pic of him in Time this week and 2 months ago in ESPN magazine that show his amazing body in the streamline position right after a turn or start and are taken underwater. I don't think he'll break Spitz's record, but I hope he kicks some Aussie ass in Athens. One of only two millionare swimmers. The other is Ian Thorpe. I agree with Phelp's sentiments that swimming should have more attention paid to it besides every four years. It's such a pure sport. I will be totally devastated as a fan if there are any doping scandals on the US team. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More on the neighbour's crazy ex-con son: One neighbour, H, an older lady who lives alone during the week and then goes to her other house in the country where her husband lives, is constantly bothered by Ronnie. She left for her other house on Saturday and Ronnie came over, knocked on the door, and then went snooping around back to see if she was home. This really pissed her off and she went and talked to his mother, who refuses to call the cops on him. But who can blame her, since he did break her freakin ribs once. So poor H is scared to death, and we are too, for that matter. DH called the cops and tried to file some kind of report so there is a legal record of this guy's "visits", but they said they can't really do anything other than step up patrols. Apparantly his own mother is so exasperated that she is considering putting up razor wire or an electric fence to keep him out of her yard. H also told us that he comes over at 6:30 in the morning and about 3 more times during the day. She said she also told his mother that the "boys" in the neighbourhood aren't going to put up with her son's BS, which mean the cops are going to be called at the very least. This is starting to get out of hand. It really pisses me off to not feel safe in my neighbourhood. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quite the unremarkable weekend. We went over the B and P's on Saturday and found out P is 6 months pregnant. Which we figured anyway. B told DH that they had some "big news" to share with us. Well, big news is either you're getting married or preggers. And they got married 4 weeks ago, so...I had no clue she was 6 months along! You couldn't really tell at the wedding at all. Granted, she did have a big poofy Cinderella dress as opposed to my garden drape-style dress, which I had to wear a freakin' corset under because it showed every imperfection. One very funny thing that happened when we were getting the new house tour is P's daughter (from previous relationship) A asked her mom, "Where are the kids?" We started laughing so hard and told her that our parents are wondering the same thing. This, of course, went over a 5 year old's head. DH got mad at me because I fell asleep at their house around midnight. I had maybe 4 beers, which is nothing for this beer-guzzling Pollack, but I think it's the new medicine I'm on. Last week I had 6 beers and fell asleep at midnight. I finally looked at the bottle yesterday and it said that DO NOT DRINK WITH THIS MEDICATION. WILL CAUSE DROWSINESS AND ENHANCE EFFECT. Damn, they sure don't lie. Well, on the upside, it'll keep me from drinking too many alcohol calories.   urlLink pretty disturbing  
    
</post>


</Blog>