<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to run away and live as a cattle rancher with a rough tough and deep man who will make love to me at the base of a canyon in the middle of nowhere while I scream his name fearlessly in the isolation.  We discover artchaelogical finds and he doesn't talk very much and we fight but its really sexy fighting cuz we always end up mauling each other hastily declothing one another and passing out in sheer exhaustion afterwards.    When we wake up we're silent and complacent and pretty much forgot about the whole fight and he makes poached eggs and we chew our food silently and surrendered.  It would be a nice weekend trip anyway...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kat walked into the church silently, looking around in the back for a seat and attempting to avoid notice.  She found a several pews in the corner, dimly lit and empty.  A large group of people her age had congregated in the mid back but though they were all talking and looking for people from the crowd, they seemed to look right through her.   This suited her.  Kat was not shy or anti social but today just felt like a day to be invisible.  Looking down and letting her hair cover her face, losing herslef in her own thoughts, she seemed to repel people and no one came over to say hi or sit with her.  It had been three months since she saw him last.  She had known a couple of his friends.  She saw them now, talking somberly with other people.  She felt no need to say hello.  She felt incredibly lonely, and that was how she wanted it.    Something felt wrong about the whole grand event.  The adults spoke as though they knew Chris.  They knew parts of Chris.  Girls sobbed in crowds.  They knew parts of Chris...  Three hundred people knew parts of Chris.  What were the missing parts?    I guess it doesn't matter how many friends you have.  You can still be terribly lonely.    Kat left the ceremony early, leaving a solid silver ring on his casket and disappearing through the doors.  When the crowd had said their final goodbyes, they filtered through the back doors into the bright afternoon sunlight.  The breeze carried the scent of cherry blossoms.  The trees swayed lazily.    Later a couple of people mentioned that they had seen Kat... and where had she gone?  But she left town.  She uprooted.  She had picked up and moved out and said all her goodbyes.  She was a road girl now.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ingrid gets to be famous.  INGRID.  Ingrid who doesn't want to be an actress...  Ingrid gets photoshoots and interviews and her face posted up all over NYC and I get to pealing skin on my fingernails, carpal tunnel from my job as a baker and another part in another show that has noble goals and dreams but absolutely no one in the audience and very little little pay.    I am not bitter I am just jealous as all hell.  I AM FUCKING JEALOUS!!!  JEALOUS!!! JEALOUS!!!  I know, its one of the deadly sins.  I am also gluttonous, greedy, rageful and sloth.    I am going to hell.  Oh well.     Ok- so chill.  breathe.    Reality.   I don't really know what I want to do with my life in many ways but I am heading to New York...  I am going to get an internship.  I will keep writing.  I will learn to be more aggressive.  I am a creative person and I will build a creative life however that may be and I will have my time in the sun as well.  Ingrid is famous, so what.  Her fame will last 10 minutes.  It is short lived and, honestly, I have no desire to be on a reality tv show anyway. Well maybe a little desire...  BUT it doesn't fit in with my longterm goal to be a professional actress.    I want a lot.  I may never get it, but I will find something on my journey and it will be worth it.    Besides.  ingrid always does things first.  Its kind of the pattern.  First Seattle, first to Europe, first to cocktail, first to be famous.    Do I want to be famous?  I want to be a little famous.  I want to have a reasonable income.  Famous doesn't make problems go away.  Famous doesn't make you talented.  Famous doesn't make you thin.  Famous is probably very interesting for awhile and then it becomes cumbersome or it fades away.  Thing is- and maybe its my nedd to feel perpetually jealous of everyone else around me BUT I wish I wasn't always telling stories about my sister.  I wish I had something interesting to say about myself.  And its not that I am not interesting.  I mean, I went to Europe too.  I have been in a number of plays.  I go on road trips and auditions and come from a large family.  But Ingrid just goes that extra wild risk taking step that makes her life appear, from the outside anyway, much more fucking fun.  But  I am young yet.  I am going to get a credit card and use it to finance my move to NYC and start to live a little.    Though I shall be responsible and I shall not accumulate unsalvageable debt.  Because I will get a cheap appartment.  I won't have the horrendousness that we call car.  I will live outside Manhattan.  I will commute and live in NYC all day.  I will temp.  I will tend bar.  I will intern at a good theater.  I will write and perform.  I will manage to let loose and have fun sans the influence of alcohol.  I will dare dare dare.  I will have hard times and I will blog about them and sound incredibly heroic...  I am learning something here.  I am learning a little everyday.  I will crawl out of this melancholy hole I found in the ground and I will resume the adventure.  Because, when i die.  I want someone to want to read my journals.  I want someone to be fascinated by me.  I want stories to continue to circulate about me years after I have passed through.  I want to inspire, amaze and be the reason someone else has the courage to crawl out of their own melancholy hole.    Just like my sister.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jaleh plays the piano... drolling out tunes from an earlier era.  I wonder what haze and world the composer was in when he created this music.  From what inner world did he bring this music?  The wind chimes jangle.  A breeze comes in through the window.  The sprinklers from the neigbors yard play against the beat of the music, german?  russian composer?  Did he sit at his piano on a summer morning and create this piece, slowly, earnestly, immersed and ignorant of all the world?  It seems like its own story, its own land...   And in the far far distance I hear the siren of a police car, someone is being pulled over and Jaleh gets to the darker part of the piece.    It is so beautiful.  I can't describe.  Oh what a shame to not have hearing, to not be able to hear these things...  These beautiful sounds...  The new song she plays reminds me of a mischevious child playing tag and hiding from his mom...  He is most definitely winning. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know that blankness that descends upon you the moment the alarm goes off, that brain drain from the glorious adventure or dream or peaceful whistful sleep you were having...  Suddenly the brain is low into the ground and you are with it, trying to climb yourself over the cliff of lovely unconsciousness.  Once you awake, its no better because you half want to fall asleep again and half desire to go on with your life.  There are few times when I burst out of bed with enthusiasm to greet the day.  What bullshit.  I'm going back to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have recently decided to change my blog host for a clean fresh slate and a little momeentary privacy to express myself.  I am Maiken.  Hi. My fondest wishes include avoiding everything I need to do so I can write down my fondest wishes.  I am an actress and singer in Seattle and I work two horribly boring, unchallenging, and underpaying though time consuming jobs in food service.   During these jobs i mostly day dream, consider the state of the worlds, the state of my world and what i must do about it.  unfortunately, getting from my head to the outside world is a little harder than it should be.  Currently I am looking for a waitress job where I can garner tips on a day time shift since I act in the evenings.  After I write this i will be printing out about a million resumes. I have about a million goals.  Someone, somewhere once told me that setting achievable goals and taking the steps to accomplish them equals happiness.  I hope so.  Occasionally I write stories and poems.  These relieve me, they prove to me that I am not all caught in a mind trap but that I do have an escape route via my imagination.  Imagination is very important, so is courage.  Power shifts and moves; one day its yours, the next day you think it is and the next it is completely vanished.  True power lies, I think, in your ability to imagine, and the bravery to grasp for your dreams.    This week has been a bit mad.  I am house sitting for a friend of mine in Seattle, which is good because that is where one of my jobs are.  It is also good because she has a cat which loves attention and there is truly nothing that soothes me more than the sound of a cat's purr under my petting hands.  Ok, well actually, I like to be massaged.  I enjoy sex, both events are soothing and stimulating.  But for the least amount of guilty pleasure, the cat is lovely.  She is a sweet black tan and white fuzzy cat.  She digs her claws into the pillow when I pet her and nuzzles into my arms.  Its blissful to be out of my parent's house, truly.  I love them.  They have been wonderful, but I just need my own space.  I need to be alone.  Diane's appartment is not elaborate.  They have little kitchen equipment.  Her boyffriend's paintings and posters serve as wallpaper and there are pictures everywhere of Diane and her friends and family.  There's a beautiful painting of Diane's eyes right next to the computer.    The second episode of Joe Schmo  came out this Tuesday.  I am not a reality tv show enthusiast but this is a good show, actually and well, you know, my sister is on it.  She is Jane , Ingrid  and she is beautiful and fabulous and a little too smart for her own good, fortunately or unfortunately.  I don't know what happens cuz my sister won't tell me but i THINK SHE IS GOING TO GET KICKED OFF NEXT tUESDAY.  I hope not.  Because if she does I will have nothing interesting to watch on TV.  Oh well, maybe I will read instead... Of course now everyone in the world knows and loves my sister and she has been doing a million interviews and talking to radio stations and all this is the perfect thing for her since its the exact fun kind of attention she thrives on.  OK- I am a little jealous, but mostly because she does such a great job of enjoying herself and maintaining her integrity under the gaze of the camera.  I find myself wondering if I would do so well, and I have to say, I don't like the actress who plays Cammie.  She seems bitchy and dumn and I question her acting choices.  Producers!  Hey!  No woman is that dum!  Sorry- I don't buy it.    And now for my job search.  I must look up several restaurants and places of employment.  My dream job?  Acting in Joe Schmo 3.  The Schmo must go on, and hey, I have had the experience of fooling my sister, who no one else seems capable of fooling... Nah...  I'd prefer to be in a film... or working on public radio, or writing my opinions for people to ponder...  Yes. Well, time to look for a waitress gig.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder if I am a human being at all.  I feel like a machine- a smart machine, but a cold cold machine.  Calculating, figuring, driving from one thing to the next.  I know I am being overdramatic- but this is one of those times when i am wondering why... what for?   Why am I stressed out all the time?  Why am I always one step behind.  I know.  I know that this isn't always true.  I have to get over the part of me that wants a drink- that needs a friend all the time, that dreams other people are happier and prettier and enjoying their lives so much more than I am.  I want to get out of this chain of events.  I am too stressed out to go on this interview.  i have enough to freakin' tackle.  I have a new job to start on Thursday.  I am house sitting for my parents.. I  am leaving a job I love for more pay.  I am living in Seattle- rampant with distractions.  I miss him so much.  I don't know if I did the right thing...  But if I call him up what will I say?  If I call him up, will I just be making him feel worse?   I ...  I did the right thing.  I did the right thing.    I can go on this interview.  I can give it a shot.  I can try.  I can try.  Better sleep.  I promised Heidi I would be in by 5am tomorrow.  Ella is making me crazy.  She can be so manipulative.  She gets stressed out and she makes me think Heidi is saying I am doing a bad job.  I am tired and everything feels plastic.  I am tired and I don't know what I want.  I want to sleep.  I am tired.  I will sleep.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      driving towards the horizon, trying to catch up with the sun, sinking below the line, the blue rocky mountain line, speeding over 80 trying to catch up with my mind a hundred miles ahead of me at all times.  There's answers in Montanna, I think, though I know nothing awaits me there, there's mystery in Montanna even if I know the end of the story even now.  One set of dashed lines is all that reigns me in as I pass over twqist into turns I leave behind.  Tumbleweed sticks to the grill of my car and it will stay there till it withers and is blown away by time.  driving towards the sun setting, the line that keeps just beyond my reach.... driving towards an answer to the speed speed speeding in my brain.  driving to catxh up with something from my past.  When I get there I can rest.  When I get there I can rest.  There's answers in the Dakotas, I think, though i know nothing awaits me there, there's mystery in the Dakotas the I've heard this story before.  driving past the lights of withering small towns, trying to find home past the place others make their homes of.  driving towards the moon so high and bright I just might catxh it, driving towards the looming dark horizon...  when I get there I can rest...  When I get there I will rest...  When I find it I will rest...  Have I found it, no not yet... not yet... not time to rest... not time to rest... will I find it- no time to think, no time to rest, better drive, keep on driving between those lines... stay between the lines.  Stay between the lines.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Frankly, I have been really lucky.  Really fucking lucky.  I have a family of fully limbed and living brothers and sisters.  My mother and father are living and breathing and care about me generation gap and all.  I have a dream and people who support me.  Somehow some of the most beutiul people in the world come in and out of my life.  I am lucky.   I am scared about the changes I am making in my life.  Breathing.  In.  Out.  I will be ok. Thankyou
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am turning fat.  I have been in denial long enough.  BUT, obviously, have gained ten pounds so now everything else in life is pointless.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to go to sleep and dream of a world much more imaginative and zen and purple than this.  Apparently, all the hippy children's stories still didn't prepare me for real life.  So you are just going to have to fucking deal with the fact that I still sleep with a stuffed animal, and no, it doesn't mean I don't know how to handle daaily fucking reality,  Roam , my white buffallo doll is just a symbol of the dream world I have to have to live this crazy life and be a normal human being outside my lovely bed...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I walked up to the fron of my Honda.  a car, gifted to me by my older and bolder sister.    it seemeed like a new world in a way.. at least a new agreement because there was no place to go but I-5 and all the other routes that intersected and I couldn't reconcile any other destination but as far away as possible...  Oh, I had taken planes but the lands I had found were television serials... not real like the trees and the flat lands and the brush that floated and tuck to my car...   It was time to leave and run far far away. to Mexico to a boat to India, New Zealand...  Paradise is travelling as far away from here as far awy can be...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Julie decided late on a January Saturday night, coming home from her late night work that she didn't believe in herself anymore, not even a bit.  She had read everry inspirational, motivational, biblical, spiritual workbook on how to love yourself and motivate yourself, and on that late Saturday half moon night, she made the decision.  " I don't fucking believ in myself and I don't know what I am doing"   her soul kind of cried, indignantly, " but what about your dreams, your feelings, your soul?  What about the time you got stitches in your right eye when the cute boy was chasing you and you fell or the time you painted in water colors or the racoon by the river where you criedc when you broke up with your boy friend? "  "No," she respnded, "it is merely a trick of the mind, an ardent desire for  romance and adventure, and the crushing impact of reality:  I am nothing.  I am nothing.  I ma nothing."  "Such thoughts are suicides made after and I dare you to be hopeful despite all reality!"  Her brain cried.  "Oh, worry not,"  she consoled,"  I am too much of a coward to slay myself.  My life will come to more than this sad thought.  If I would have the courage to take ills or slit my wrists, assuredly, I would have the courage to climb mountains first or become a circus freak or get a better job or love myslef or be alone or reach the moon"  "Worry not for my well being"  she said, " I come from a long line of outspoken and courageous women"  "I REFUSE TO BE LOST AMONG MY BEAUTIFUL SISTERS, FOR I AM ONE OF THEM!!!!!!"
     
    
</post>


</Blog>