<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I like stuff.  I wish I had money to buy lots of stuff.  But I dont.  Is stuff what makes people happy?  In my eyes if I had lots of stuff I think that i'd be happy, but people say that nice things or money isnt the key to happyness.  I dont know.  I mean I know I shouldnt keep buying name brand stuff, but if I dont then I feel like Im a outsider.  Tell me what you people think ok??     
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well last night was T's party.  It was a good time, I think.  I remember swiming and fireworks.  I also remember sleeping in cabe's car.  I'm sleepy so I will blog more later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Im out..............Im so sleepy.  Goodnight friends of Dlog's Blog. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I remember one time my friends and I took a ride to the Yale campus.  It was a trip in a half.  We met up with a friend I knew who goes to Yale.  That night I will never forget.  First off because she was the cutest little thing you ever hope to meet but second because it was the first "road trip" the group had ever taking.  Pete, J Juice, Alex, Cabe, and T Bomb.  T and Cabe were in another car and J, Alex and I were in one.  T was driving so we all were a little afraid of how that was going to turn out.   Anyways we were all fine intill we got into the city.  Yale chicks were walking around campus and Pete was looking for a taste.  I on the other hand was very nerves about meeting this "earth angel".  I kept looking back to see if Cabe and T were staying with us.  We got near the school and looked around for parking, nothing, not one spot was open, hey it was friday night and it was New Haven.  So Alex and I got out of the car and Juice looked around for a spot with T behind him.  I remember Al saying to me Tim (T Bomb, Tank, T bag, Tammy....etc.) is going to get lost, I thought so as well.  Alex and I walked over under the street sign (Chapel) and waited for the rest of the guys.  Meanwhile I gave Cindy (the girl I talked about) a call.  She was coming down in 10 mins she said.  It was damn cold.  I remember a man asked me if I can give him bus fear and a cig he said he had lost his wallet and he needed to get home, mostlikely he was lieing but i did it anyways.  Alittle after the bum walked away Alex and I saw Tank drive past us, we called for him but he didnt look.  "Shit there he goes, hes getting lost."  I remember Alex saying.  He did.  Joe and Pete came around the corner a couple of secs after T pasted.  Joe ended up paying 5 bucks to park in a lot and was upset.  Then Cindy Coco came across the street.  My chest began to feel warm in the winter cold.  I dont remember what we said at first but I remember a hug being made between us.  T never showed up.  The group had a bunch of theory's at what might have happened.  Funny ones at that.  You have to know Tank to understand why it is funny.  T of all people to get lost in the city. LOL.  Well we all went for pizza and then Cindy and I went to see her frineds a local ice cream shoppe they were hippies lol they were cool tho.  After that we went to her dorm.  A big frat party was going on and it looked sweet.  But I wanted to chill with Cindy.  We got up to her dorm and her temp roommate was there.  She was kinda cute I really cant remember.  But we chilled and played so gitty (guitar) and it was fun.  Then we went for some coffee at Star Bucks.  Joe wanted to go so he went to get the car while Coco and I stayed in Star Bucks.  A Bum was bugging some people at the table next to him but I gave him a smoke and he went away.  I dont no why I help bums.  Maybe because Im afraid of them.  Anyways Joe came and I had to say goodbye to the cutest.  We hugged and I got into the car.  We got lost on the way home and we didnt get back till one.  It was 11 when we left.  We yelled at each other and I screamed then got out of the car and puked.  I wasnt drinking I was just sick from the goddamn pizza, it sucked.  We got home.  The next day we called T.  He was mad.  So it goes.         
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So this is High School bullshit??  If I remember you called me at FIVE IN THE FUCKING A.M.!!  I was happy sleeping, dreaming of whatever I was dreaming about.  I told you we can hang later but no you had to call me back till I said come on over.  So it looks to me that somebody wanted something.  And if you say you wanted to hangout thats bull it was 5 A.M. mind you!!  I dont wanna talk about it I still like you and Dlog's Blog is a happy place so no yelling.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Whats up bloggsters?  Im just hangin' round downtown by myself and I had to much time to sit and thing about myself.  LOL So not much to report...I just ate din din, Im at my Aunt's house.  She lives in a 2 million dollar house.  When Im here I feel rich.  Someday I will have mad coin but not right now.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What a day!  I dug holes all day and moved 80 lb bags of concrete.  Fun, fun, fun.  I got there with five bucks and left with 237.  I should have a hell of a lot more but Im only getting 8 bucks a hour, which I might add blows balls.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WHAT THE HELL IS WITH EVERYBODY"S SODDEN OBSESSION WITH EMO??  Its pretty corny, if you are sad you are sad, you don't need to make a style out of it!  Making a style out of being sad just shows how materialistic we people of the great United States are. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Im up, Im up.  Its 6 in the morning and I wanna go back to bed.  But I got to go the workplace, WHICH SUCKS. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Im sleeping.  The AC was on in my room all day, so its like a icey relax pit........I cant wait....See you when the sun comes up over the hill.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello.  Its late and I have to go to work at 7:00.  That sucks, but I have a new computer in mind so I got to work hard for the money. Hmmmmm........ It's Summer!  Schools out.  Im afraid to go back there, most of my friends have graduated and I am all alone.....Well maybe that means I'll do good instead of partying all year.......JohnQ is going to NVCC so that means Ill still hang with him.  Thats a plus!  Keep it real JQ! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My 1st post of Dlog's Blog.  I hope you enjoy as my life is layed out for you. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got a new Apple ibook.  Its pretty sexy.  I can record my music for real, like a rockstar! LOL.  Im still working getting the grip of having a good computer thats mine. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Blogglovers.......Guess what?&nbsp; I fell for another girl.&nbsp; I always fall, Its dumb, I met this one girl and for like a week or two Im in love.&nbsp; I don't know what the story is.&nbsp; Well this weeks tasty pick is a girl from the far land of Colombia.&nbsp; Shes in town for a couple of weeks.&nbsp; You have to see her, she has the cutest little actsent.&nbsp; We were camping and she got scared of a Daddy long legs, so I killed it (Doug to the rescue) and she didn't know what is was so I said, "Daddy long legs."&nbsp; and shes like "Daydie Lang Legs" is was the cutes thing in the world.&nbsp; Well Im rebuilding my room.&nbsp; Im trying for total comfort for my last year of school.&nbsp; Cool Cool Cool.&nbsp; LAzy boy has these new rugs by Todd Oldham they are pretty cool.&nbsp;    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey Blog people what is going downtown?  Im not a single man anymore as of the day before yesterday.  Shes a cutey.  Well Ive been working and boy is it hard.  The day goes by kinda fast tho, not really.  Im sick og building goddamn decks.  But I need the coins so I work.  Im going to New York this weekend with my dad and my cuz is taking a hot girl, one of her friends.  To bad I got the old ball and chain (Just kiding babe).  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       She is tall, tan, long legs, nice rack, not to big not to small, soft, and smells fucking tasty.  I knew from the minute I saw her that I was going to get a lap dance from her.  I paid the man at the register and I entered a small room with about five chairs and nothing but black lights on.  I sat down in a chair against the far wall and looked up at the goddess before me.    “Hey, how are you?” said in a cute sexy voice.    “I’m….I’m good.” I said baffled by her beauty.  “Can I take your hat off?”  “Umm….I got a really bad haircut.” I blushed as I replied but the black lighting hid it.    “That’s okay sweetie, I’ll just turn it around.”   She proceeded to turn around my hat than turned around lowering her thong.  My eyes lit up as her ass slowly started to cheep closer and closer to my lap.  She sat down and started to move back a fourth, and believe you me that it was the best thing I have done in a while.  I was looking up at her in amazement, and then she turned around and put her chest in my face.  There I was sitting in a leather chair with my nose between to soft tits.  I was in fucking heaven.  As she did this she was rubbing my lap with her hands, I began to melt.  She smelled so fucking good, I never smelled such a wonderful smell in my life, and I could have stayed there forever and ever.  Time pasted and she finished up, she leaned up to give me a kiss on the cheek and she softly whispered, “thank you, my name is Meia.”   I was in love with a striper named Meia.  That’s fucking retarded.      
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       come crash into me, im game.  The song goes, "she will be loved."  To bad its not by me but some fat-headed army man, maybe if i shot women and children in Iraq she would like me.                                                  -Douglas J.  Boucher III                                                                                 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Hotplates have died.  It's a sad Juice and Cerbs are going away to school so I'm stuck without a band.  But my friend is starting to play bass and it looks like I might have a new band.   
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello.  Did you know Rick James died yesterday?  They say it was natural, lol I don't know about that.  I can quote Rick saying, "Cocaine is a hell of a drug."  Well I guess Dave Chappelle is out of a job, wait he still has R. Kelly.  T Bomb went to the Rush show tonight, he says it was, "a hell of a rush."  I myself am not a 'rush-head' but some stuff is okay.  People say that the Rush drummer is the best drummer in the world, HEY PEOPLE EVER HEAR OF KETH MOON?  T went with a girl from his work, good times.  Well tonight was okay for me, I went to Chili's with my cuz and her cuz.  Then we watched The Exorcist.  It's a okay movie but not a fav of mine.  School is coming up fast, my head is spinning.                             -Dougie B from way above the knee 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
              My name is Conway Peterson and I live in the upstairs room of, Goodies Spirits.  I guess it’s not all that bad I get the out of code beer for free, but it’s a small place.  I attend school at the college across the street, SSVC, Smith Sampson Valley College.  I’m very popular on campus because of all the free beer; all the parties are late at night so nobody can see the out of code date.  The chicks at SSVC are okay but you should see some of the prep school chicks that sneak out of the rich school down the road.  Mill Valley is a dry campus and parties are frowned upon, so horny schoolgirls with a pocketbook full of Daddy’s credit cards stop by.     
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My friend is going to the Rush show at the meadows, he is taking a hot girl.  WIll they have a good time?  I have a feeling that there is going to be alot of drugs at this Rush show.  T if you are reading, DO NOT EAT THE RED ACID!                   -Freddy Douglas 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Hey, don't knock masturbation. It's sex with someone I love." --Woody Allen in "Annie Hall"   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>