<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my whole week of exams is finally cuming to an end. alas, the damn oral is on friday after my econs paper. my chinese very poor leh. how? how to prepare for chinese oral? my exams ALL die man. confirm die. 30% of pormos, i dont want get retained!!!! i tik my maths have to drop liao, haiz, no future. can only balme myself lar. got one whole hol i chose to waste. well done. today someone get to go watch movie. so good. haiz. 4 days cannot see another someone. haiz. speak not the name man, or u shall die... i want to sae hi to someone.. but dont dare. later backfire i becum reputable for the wrong reasons in sr. today literature exam, difficult man other than otello section the rest game over. haiz. afternoon go play soccer again. duno y nowadays not so enthu abt soccer anymore... monday no school! youth day rite.. tik so. most prob they oso tk as marking day, no extra days of hol to earn.. nothing more to say. always outside got a lot of tngs in mind to add in my blog, but in front of comp only mind blank. just like maths paper lie tt. always do maths brain freeze..
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cheers. holland got into the semis. yeah. holland is packed with so many freaking good players. with big names like france, england and italy out, the competiition is for them to lose now. seriously portugal and czech republic are inferior when comparing the verious departments. portugal and czech defence are not exactly solid. ajen robben, vaart and meyde should not have much problems.... hahaha. now mtv got stella huang, wow, she is actually quite pretty. hmm. nice voice too. wonder y she not tt famous. haha. tml open sch liao. sch is nth to look forward to. exams and test spoil the mood. sch is suppose to be a fun learning place where u learn at ur own pace and not be forced to tk the a levels when it is time for it. obv human nature dont allow such a tng so alias here i m. exam tml leh. oi. hello? heard it? after econs paper on friday i can havoc! yes ar. haha. end quite early too. 9.45. great. quite sure someone would go library on thurs to return sometng...but i thurs no sch. haiz. sad. wad diff anyway, no chance one. toad trying for sometng high here......
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your soul is OPEN-MINDED. Although you do have strong opinions and make decisions, you never make them without thinking first of not only everything that is, but those that may not be as well. People trust that you'll willingly hear them out and understand when they tell you something, and you are well-liked for it. You are often the mediator in disputes and your desire to do what is right overcomes all else. You are an understanding and admirable soul.    urlLink   What Is Your Soul's Trait?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today woke up at 10, haiz got the troublesome pw at 12. hmm.... my revision is in a mess. should have took bus 8 to tpy, but chose to tk a bus to yck and transfer to mrt instead, bad choice, becum late. so sorry, reach there there all waiting for me. feltso bad! but as usual nv sae sorry. i suck. go jx house. wow, wonderful man. 23rd storey? nice view! well, me nv do the survey, wad  a member i m. forgot how to use microsoft excel, so cannot do collation. haiz. ended at ard 5.30, go popular get some stationery for mid yr then went home on bus 8. slept on bus, very tired. during pw oso half conscious. always like tt. nowadays tire very easily. jc very sian. go home eat dinner, chat, bathe then watch euro 2004. heartbreak man. england and france out, no more fun. italy and spain suffered shock exits even earlier. now left wad? holland? after tt ard 10 liao go did a bit of geog. die. how? a lot... always last minute one. same as o lvl, 3 hrs brk btwn papers then study. siao man. try not to last min nxt time yar. aiya, my blog very boring to read, not in high spirits now. now me toking to yi ling and derrick. haha. my chat pals... haha. i want to buy many many cds, but me bankrupt liao leh. cannot wait for friday exam over. happy! then after tt monday no sch yes ar... hahaha. anyway i fear the day need ask parents sign report book. how? sure fail. hope to pass ao maths... pray for miracle, typical bad student. fail cant tk anymore, nxt time uni got lesser choice. haiz. is this long? i wonder lets post it and see how it looks like
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Information  i   	   nathaniel is a restricted area. Authorised personel only     Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com       N     Normal       A     Amazing       T     Trustworthy       H     Healthy       A     Amazing       N     Naive       I     Intense       E     Explosive       L     Little       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com       How to make a nathaniel        Ingredients:   1 part pride  1 part crazyiness  5 parts ego        Method:  Stir together in a glass tumbler with a salted rim. Add a little cocktail umbrella and a dash of lovability        Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com               abalagarar Highway    Mt. Happiness    7      Study Hall    12      Tower of Commitment    60      Valley of Depression    115      Confusion Lane    392      Please Drive Carefully               Username:      urlLink Where are you on the highway of life?   From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com 
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3 more days mid yr exam starts. quite sure tt my gp exam cannot make it liao. ok. june holidays.. time flies. whoa. so far i only finish reading 1984, tt damn irrelevant to today's world book. congragulations. well done. so wad abt maths, geog, rest of lit, chinese? err....
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, so here goes my very 1st blog. nv imagine one day i will have an online diary to whine and crap to ok... lets see how this online diary of mine survives....
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was parents day. my mum go sch with me tk results. sorry mum if at some period i was rude.  Econs AO Lit ???? Geog F GP C6 AO chinese E8 AO Maths F9  i must start to work hard.... i dont wan to get retain. but easier said than done. i got concentration probs... easily distracted. nvtheless i will try. hahaha 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stay The Same by Joey McIntyre  Don't you ever wish You were someone else You were meant to be The way you are exactly Don't you ever say You don't like the way you are When you learn to love yourself You're better off by far And I hope you always stay the same 'Cause there's nothing 'bout you I would change I think that you could be Whatever you wanted to beIf you could realize All the dreams you have insideDon't be afraidIf you've got something to say Just open up your heart And let it show you the way  Don't you ever wish You were someone else You were meant to be The way you are exactly Don't you ever say You don't like the way you are When you learn to love yourselfYou're better off by far And I hope you always stay the same 'Cause there's nothing 'bout you I would change  Believe in yourself Reach down inside (ohh-oooh) The love you find will set you free Believe in yourself (ohh-oooh) You will come alive Have faith in what you do You'll make it through  Ohh-wooahh-ohh Heeeeeyyy  Don't you ever wish (ohhhhh yeah) You were someone else You were meant to be (you were meant to be) The way you are exactly Don't you ever say (Ohh-wooahh-ohh) You don't like the way you are When you learn to love yourself (love yourself) You're better off by far And I hope you always stay the same (stay the same) 'Cause there's nothing 'bout you I would change (change)  No, there's nothing 'bout you I would change . . .  Don't change . . . 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello.... today is the library investiture. today has been an eventful day for me. i have nv relished a leadership post, but after today i have to scold myself. it is fun... to see wad u plan cum to the real tng. well, the investiture was basicaally a success. got njc and acjc ppl cum to lend us their support. disappointed with our own sch ppl. a lot of librarians nv turn up. hows some came, so sweet of them. the cca grps did a bad job of sending representatives over. next time dont go theirs. i nv brg anytng for investiture other than blazer anf the long pants!!!! well and tie. need black shoes and white long sleeve shirt. i dont have!!!! today start off the day with othello. ms G is a great teacher. then gp... chacko is funny too. haha. then econs lecture. new lecturer making his debut. haha. good. after tt is econs test. with fingers crossed i went to class, lucky for me test cancelled.&nbsp;got to skip maths becos of investiture. set up tngs, carry table, plants, prepare the drinks. change into proper attire then had to go tk food frm the muslim stall. haha. 5.45 guest strted streaming in. ard 5.55 we strt? ya. everytng went smoothly... or rather say few bloopers lar. haha. great music and quite nice speeches. had to perform too, me duno the song man. haha. the tng ended around 6.45? i tik so. then got refreshments...  Now listening to fianl countdown very nice. i m very happy todae. sad on smtng i just found out too :( contradiction but nvm, generally today is one of the best days i have had in srjc. now the song is lost in motion... tt is fast. orietation song.. love the orietation, very nice. was very impressed with srjc at tt pt in time. now i m still quite happy lar. but of cuz sure got unhappy times rite.  tml is parents day. i m dead meat. i failed everytng. lets see wad happen. i m really lagging acdemically since young. maybe in other areas too man! haha, how dumb wad a failure.  11.11pm tata  
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today reach sch at 8.30, got a lvl chinese listening. haha. then got to see someone. after tt got lib meeting. and guess wad. one whole day. ended at 5.30 man. have to rush the proposal. no time!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! -_-! really have to be optimistic abt this investiture. the time it is allocated most prob ppl wont cum, they rather go home. 5.45pm? if it is me i rather go home. logistics not as scary as programs man. haha. still duno the positions yet. then yue ming hu has a face tt look like he will eat u up but he is quite ok on the whole use me as an example to convey a msg. dont ask wad is it. no harm intended so it is fine with me. havent buy my brave new world. haiz. how man. tml faster fly go buy. i really hate pop-out windows. extra. hu would go and read. waste time. sch sucks. should i drop maths? my timetable is overloaded. everyday until 5. other than lunch no free time. then now my lunch get taken over by library meeting, or either do hw. a lot of hw, like we tk one subj only then the teacher tot we very free. study so hard for wad. now maybe u tk phy, then next time u work as businessman u nv apply eventually forget. maths is even worse. wad for? a cert is safety? even if a cert is safety, for sci students be a doctor maybe can prevent u frm losing touch with ur subj when u grow up? if not u work as wad have u, most of the time will forget. singapore students have no childhood. none of the gp qns seems to target this type of qns.... log off 9.04pm....
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today sch as usual father fetch. u see life is mundane, it is a repeatition. today's best lesson was again miss g's the worse is AO maths. the inexperieced side of the teacher is to telling. wad to do, my sch dumping ground wad. go chinese lesson late on the pretext of helping my fren look for his tooth. haha. actually he had the freedom of fixing it back and taking it out at will, he nv ever lost it. haiz, when i m tired ar, i keep doing stupid tngs. it is embarrasing, but no one notice me one lar, so nvm.haha. wednesday is cca day. alas, library at 1315. one of the lib stuff leaving, so give us treat pizza hut and kfc in the comfort of m2-1 classroom. haha. lovely food. the exco promise BIG changes to the library. tell u lar, difficult. my sch budget, spend on many unnecessary tngs when other more appaling tngs cont to exhibit their beauty around my beloved sch compound. after tt went derrick hse for a while, tell me his mum not in. as usual lie again. haha. derrick! u r reading this! oh no... haha. derrick, fun man, i guessed ur password correctly. haha. hmm, wad else. how can a whole day account be so short. oh, because there are some tngs cannot sae. not tt as if u interested like tt but if the relevant parties read i duno wad will happen to me. anyway the concealed part is always good. nth bad. time: 0623pm. tata
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      todae.... woke up at 610 father fetch me to sch... haha. morning assembly was esp long and boring, the unvealing of the walss of hope. one word hope sum up the main idea of the principal's speech was was more or less crap and repitition. now just finish burning cyndi wang's song. more for my sis this type of music genre. never get back any papers today. haha. not bad huh. all as usual, 1st period PE, jogging all slack. then geog then bla bla bla. nv eat lunch man. hungry like hell. next time library meeting during lunch if can not goin to go anymore. i got no free periods, my whole timetable is pack frm the moment the 1st period strt right up to 5pm everyday! except friday. realised my lit utopian writing out of pt, big fat 0. fail liao. tired, tonite do hw finish can sleep already. haha. this sat listening compre, my lc pathetic. tt idiotic singh wan ask to get the damn bk as soon as possible. due to singh's intelligence or maybe not lar, maybe tt book got intro appendix + a few more pages of gold, the version he ask us to get is not exactly easy to get. today's best lesson was ms g's. worst as usual superintendent singh. not boring, but sux. ao maths got new teacher. not too bad better than the last 2? duno yet, time will tell. GP got relief teacher, haha. not bad oso. it is 6.40pm now. tata
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      todae go out around afternoon with derrick. go suntec city to jialan jialan then watch spiderman2. nice show, worth watching. after tt bought a music cd. if i m rich i can buy many more man. haiz. can buy all the games and cd i like. haiz. now very sian, tts y i m blogging here. tml is sch again. i hate sch, very boring. super way of distributing people into classes. not even balanced. seems only my class like tt, haiz.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today woke up at 7.45, got library meeting at 9. haha. library investiture is 3 wks frm now. general pubkic image of the library is distorted. hello, the services u get at the library are not god-sent. the books esp those binded ones dont form on their own. wad u want man, we r not slackers. after lib meeting went to heartland mall for lunch with weiqi, lawrence and dixie. eat BK, heard funny stories. haha. after tt go home tk 81, pass by so many places. finally reach tampines then flew home. reach home watch soccer... haha. repeat match btw portugal and spain. spain is lousy. greece in the final man. whoa. greece really have to thank their coach for his profound tactics and player management. in the greece team are virtually unknown players except nikopolidis, whu let in 6 goals against manU. haha. lets look at this, got ppl whining   Barce unhappy with Reds Manchester United were last night at the centre of a FIFA probe after Barcelona accused them of trying to nab Gerard Pique on the cheap. Barca are furious they have not received a penny in compensation and are demanding up to £3million for the centre-back, 17, who has agreed a five-year deal at Old Trafford. The Spaniards insist they are entitled to the sum as Pique has been at the club for seven years. And furious Barca president Joan Laporta revealed he had alerted FIFA about United’s handling of the affair. He claimed: “United have acted in a belligerent manner and failed to respect the effort some clubs make in bringing on young players.” Pique said: “Barca say I belong to them but I’m not a slave.” Staff reporter, The Sun  TOO BAD. TOO BAD U R LOUSIER THAN MANU, TOO BAD U CANNOT PERSUADE UR OWN PLAYER. SAD LAR. manU problem ar. 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hurray, my mid-yr exams finally over. all fail liao. haiz. today go to sch as usual, econs exam till abt 10+ then go someone hse play game then go oral. oral always brain freeze one, so wont do so well. after tt go someone hse again. same person. play ps2 watch him interrogate ppl for my benefit. hahahaha.  greece produce a big shock man. i must sae they are not a good team, but are tactically sound. but portugal got big phil, sd be able to lift the trophy. cheers portugal. tired. dont wan typa anymore............
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... now blooger allows you to change the time displayed in ur blog. cool. today, common test proper comes to an end. I still have a literature common test on thurs... staying in sch till very late on that day. 7.30pm....  Ok, common test. wad can i say. i m glad that i have kick the habit of not studying. but still not desirable content yet. all the tests study bits and pieces. nvm, as time goes by and with more perseverance i can study well and score well. haha, self-belief and reality always differs a lot, but just dont wan to get retain. already taking energy-consuming subj... arts is writing, reading. i have nv memerise tngs  till the day i enter jc.... as chacko said. if u study bits and pieces expect ur marks to have that form oso. bits and pieces marks? ohoh. (anway only  ppl reads my blog... trusted 3... haha....  manchester united my beloved soccer club begin their english premier league campaign on a sour note, losing to Chealsea by a goal. Not a very good tng that manU has no points to account for. but i m proud of my fav team... injury-hit but they work hard and were unlucky to lose. Do not noe y i have an affection for manU. they are not the best team, it would be arsenal. they are not the richest it would be chelsea, they are not exactly star-studded truout, tt would be real madrid. love man united.  really worried for my grades. only pass one a lvl, lit. yet to read bnw, must! if not i will end up failing my only a lvl pass and end up in jc1 again...  wonder if i can pass gp. chose "Spare the rod and spoil the child" Is this always true.... now was i type i have many points to tok abt... it is always the same old story, in the exam hall nth seems to cum to ur head..... guess many of our fellow students oso like tt.  today i slack a lot. tired i guess. must quickly get down to reading brave new world soon. wonder if it is a good read. i must find the true essence of utopian literature. i must like it, i must excel in it, since it is wad i have chose, rather unknowingly.  funny, nobody online.... blackout again? haha. tot exam over many ppl would be online. maybe they hanging out at the streets of orchard or havoc in some delusive place.  every lect i m damn lost. today econs make-up lect i duno a single shit of wad is bein taught. i just have to go in and tk down the notes blindly. seriously if the sch can consider the concentration span of a student it would help very much. but everyone has diff pace... so..... guess i m one of the slower ones.  tml got PE. i have to tk napfa test again. got bronze... but i cannot get silver... i got sicolsis... sit and reach barely pass... + a m as unfit as i can be... i cannot do standing broad jump. cannot do pull-up.... haiz.... soon i would have to go to ns-serve the nation they say, duty to the nation  i m bored so naturally no mood to type. anyway as u can see my blog contains nth constructive. anybody suffering frm insomnia is more than welcome to read my blog. i guarantee u fall asleep around the middle paragraph... 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I do not recall celebrating National Day earlier so many days before the actual event. haha. anyway, today no souvenir. so sad. was wondering wad sr would give esp after they gave QUITE nice stuff for the th anniversary. ok nvm abt tt. today performance was not bad. st was the rugby boys.... i tik it is a good way to start the ball rolling with such chants. then some ppl from 1s04 performed. haha, a teacher performed with them. she was wearing sch uni. haha. an eye opener. maybe one day all the teachers sd cum in sch uni and all the students in home clothes. then let them sit at the back of the LT and show slides on the transparency at a fast pace w/o switching off the front lights to make the words on the screen clearer. then talk in a way only ppl of ur own religion can make out wad it is. none other than iderjit singh. boring fellow. 1s04 performance was not too bad. got the guts to go on stage to perform in front of the whole sch is already wonderful. after tt is a dance forgot wads the class. but it was nice. then it was the indian cultural society, also dance, not nicer than the one b4 tho. the emcee is talented man.  after tt went off to the lib to slack. if got no pw i would have flew straight home and sleep. haiz. had to go all the way to spore national eye centre to do interview. the interview was quite ok but i dint have the chance to pose qns.... tml got pw meeting again. at tpy, very inconvenient. voiced out but nth changing i guess. all my fault for getting into a sch faraway, so the ppl there oso stay in places not near my home. in fact at the other end of spore. haiz. spore is not exactly great for sight seeing. travel for wad. no fun. can sleep. the doctor we interviewed share the same chinese name with my fren WH. haha. i m not saying there is anytng big abt tt. just saying for the sake of it.  my blog got no paragraph one. haha. so dumb.  today only 5mins of the performance i really enjoyed, other than tt sd have pon sch again.  next wk common test. hope i have the heart to study. studying is easy for many, but it is an uphill task for me. but i dont wan to flung either. so have to make myslef panick and find the true worth of studying since i chose a jc path..................................................  my ambition is to get a job tt can travelround the world. wanted to be a journalist, so almost went to poly do mass comm... but changed my mind. diploma cannot really give u such a job, have to further studies....  at one stage i actually plan to set up a series of big comp, supermarket chains, teenage-theme stalls but all this need capital. maybe can look for ward to business management if i ever get in to uni.  i wonder if i will work a profession i dont like becos i have no alternatives or becos it pays better. then, the true enjoyment of life is half gone. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today sch end early at 1.15pm. pon the house election tngy, waste time. went for badminton. enjoyed myself. nv realise tt today i can get to see the national day celebrations rehearsal. it sd be a great performance. wasted my class dont wan to perform in the end, actually i was oso reluctant... i m really XXXXXnised. haha. nv seen such a beautiful girl in my life.  now listening to eternal flame. boy long time nv listen to this all time great.. feeling miserable now. feeling weird, not due to someone but i tik i m sick. feeling bloated.  dont feel like going to sch tml. lit tutorials are torture. i have the right to pon rite? i mean i dont like wad the hell they wan... haiz. but sch is like tt dont like oso have to bear with it. so much for freedom.  today the time spent in the hall play badminton and watching the rehearsal is gotta be one of the best times i ever had.  manU beat PSV 1-0. not a great result. hope my fav team can exceed expectations and repeat their feat real soon. now listening to euro 2004 theme song. very nice. ty mr twh.  one of my frens quit sch liao. now my class left with 6 guys. already so bad and it is now worse. may u find happiness real soon in wadever u do to huever concerned. 
    
</post>


</Blog>