<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whahahahhahas.ive sorted things out with myself.=)
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      first and foremost. i would like to take this opportunity to thank dearest yuntian for causing me to trip on the stairs. and therefore causing my leg to be bruised. if i cannot walk for the rest of my life. i'll chop of your leg! waahahahhahahas. j.k la.how could i bear to! aniwae rites, todae was a not-so boring day. i repeat. NOT-SO boring. yups. but it was still rather boring lar.kinda slept during lit.its like totalli sucky. and during science. i was playing with shibin n kin phang.those horrible guys were throwing stuff on me. and they were like trying to hit me and things like that.horrible rite? hahas. i pity tanisha dude. having to sit next to me.wahahahhas.must be a torture.okaes.den ums.yea.evrything else was rather alright i must say.hees.went to JE after school.and we bumped into nicholas and i-kinda-forgot who. wasit alfred? ahh.wadeva. den nic was sooo farnie.he was telling us some lame jokes and things like that.oh my gosh im NEVER goin out with nicholas AGAIN.NEVER IN MY WHOLE LIFE! so diu lian.-.-.hahas.den i was playing black magic with him. and he never got the answer! lol! poor thing..awwwww.too bad.he owes me and yuntian a meal.YAY! wheeeheee. yea.guess tts bout all tt happened todae. oh ya. was there a blackout in sg sumwhere or sumthing? hahas.cuz it was kinda dark outside.yea.tmr got syf.im seriously gonna bring my discman n stuff.prolly gonna camp there e whole afternoon.dun wanna rot dude.hahas.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hees.went to church in the morn.was VERY tired can? but was alrite after that la.hahas. den ums.din do much todae.yupss.gonna have to do my hmwk.  [y]ou:if wad u said in ur blog is wad i tink it is. den im seriously dissapointed in ya.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      decided to start out on a new blog.kinda got sick of the old one and stuff.as its kinda messy larr.hees.yupss. so ums.im still working on it so...yea.gimme some time!
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wheeee.im officially fourteen years old! had a greaaat day larh. was really happy n stuff. hahas.guess ppl do care about me lar. inbox was flooded with sms-es todae. n had loadddds of prezzies.awww.so sweet rite?awwww. waited for shaun for FOUR hours. so that i could get photo. so stupid rite? argh! wahahahas.den went to fairfield carnival!! rawked larh.. like rawkked sooo much can?! saw sean n sum familar faces that apparently noes me n i dunno them but heck la. oh yar. the haunted house rawked!! n the guy who painted his face black is superrr duperrrrly CUTE.like CUTE. sean looks like shaun. hahas.tts wad alot of ppl told me! gosh. how can they look alike? but personality about there la.hahas. yeps. den went to town n went for major shopping spree. like spent my first hour in town n spent 100bucks.which is like uh...alot..cuz im supp to be broke.wahahahhas. yea. guides rawked too! yay! eunice, sherrilyn n liyi rawked larh! love them!! wahahahas. e sec1s were rather enthu todae. so quite happie n stuff lor. yups. gonna have church tmr!! wheeee! gonna be fun larh. yay.....! but cell's gonna split up so ya..kinda sadddd.but well...its a good thing.show tt we're growing!! 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      awwww.so touched man.got quite a number of ppl wish me happy burthday n give me prezzies already. n its still ilke two days more.gosh.so touched.-sobs-.yea.heees.the prezzies rawked totally.n wanna thank my cell grp N163 for evrything larh. sigh. gonna split liao.its a good thing la. but se bu de!! ahhhh! hees. todaes cell grp soooo rawked can!! gosh.lurved it loads.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      awwww.so touched man.got quite a number of ppl wish me happy burthday n give me prezzies already. n its still ilke two days more.gosh.so touched.-sobs-.yea.heees.the prezzies rawked totally.n wanna thank my cell grp N163 for evrything larh. sigh. gonna split liao.its a good thing la. but se bu de!! ahhhh! hees. todaes cell grp soooo rawked can!! gosh.lurved it loads.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      awwww.so touched man.got quite a number of ppl wish me happy burthday n give me prezzies already. n its still ilke two days more.gosh.so touched.-sobs-.yea.heees.the prezzies rawked totally.n wanna thank my cell grp N163 for evrything larh. sigh. gonna split liao.its a good thing la. but se bu de!! ahhhh! hees. todaes cell grp soooo rawked can!! gosh.lurved it loads.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmm.im home! lol. like superrr early todae. cuz gonna have cell group later n stuff. so nidta cum back n complete some of my hmwk n stuff.yepyeps.anihoos. todae was alrite.not very boring.hardly fell asleep except math as usual..=p.yup.went to collect tics from sean yest! gosh! scarrie....! lol. he's scary.yarh. bought 30dollars worth of tics. shaun better come lor. if not..i'll make him buy me present.ahahahhas.yup.den went to manda's hse to slackkkk.went home at bout 10 plus.wahahhaha. i sooo rawk. n i stepped on her dog poo!! eewwwwww!! totaly gross. hahas. yah. i guess tts bout all larh. lol. and yah. i forgive caiyue for irritaing moi.=p 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      =)) im almoz done with the presentation i deleted! hees. happy! aniwae. supp to go to e national stadium today. but decided not to go laz minute cuz had loadz n tons of stuff to do. boo-eys. wish i was there lar. kinda regret changing my mind now.=( anihoos.. sch was okae todae. i killed caiyue. irritating pest! AGRH! the guys are just soooo immature and assholes!!!! gosh. seriously..when will they learn to be more gentlemanly larh. sickening. tmr having combined cell meeting. yayS! weeee-o-weeeet! wahahhhahahas. u-noe-who's gonna be there. yay! wadevar. turdles. back to my project now. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      kaes.todae was alrite. went swimmin with yuntian. just got off the fone with shaun n yuntian. he still refuses to go out larh. n kept on askin me why i have no party. hahas. okae. aniwae. sean called me just now. so scary leh! gosh! yea. i was like kinda eager to put down. i guess he got shocked&nbsp;n stuff. mabbe he wanted to talk. aiyar. wadeva larh. gonna get tics frm tmr. ekkks! scarieeeee! wadevarr. hees.. b'dae's in FIVE days! wheeeeee! lol. aiyar. im like sooo dead larrr.boo-eys. haven really studied. went swimmin just now. had loadsss of fun!! hahas..=p aniwaes. im stressed! ahhhhhhhh! so much things to do. so little time. pressurised by evry1 to do evrythin! aniwae. gary rawks.lol.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whee. just got back frm church. my tiann! service rawkeddddd.its soo cool.there were breakdancers. this superr cool drama. and even a sound mixer. like those hip-hop stuff!! n guess wad. the tangible presence of God could be felt too.just really felt like crying. aniwae. i was a counselor..! cool eh? yea. but aniwaes. there were free hot dogs and ice cream fer all the new frens. ORANGE JULIUS HOTDOGS! argh! me n yuntian were like screaming when we realised that e hot dogs were frm orange julius. bam. i wish we were new too. hahas. then went to watch i-robot with josh mike n tash. n the show RAWKS! woooots. i give it 4 stars! rawks totalli. hees.          yesterday.  had the cultural potpourri thingy. its alrite i guess. shaun quek was soooo shuai... wahahhhahas. had to do ushering. so stupid. argh. church ushering's more fun. n the ppl are less unreasonable. so sickening the parents. they just refuse to budge when we ask them to move in so that can we can create more spac for others!! seiously sickening. got pissed off by them.yea.aniwae. me wenbing claudine n wenhui got lost on the express way. we wanted to walk back to school but we ended up walking along the expressway to ite!!! so scary! could have gotten killed by a car. seriously scary.was abit scared larh. hahas. was like telling Jesus. cannot let me die now. cannot. CANNOT! hahas. den this stupid lorry suddenly drove sooooo close to us! but luckily God's hand of protection was with us. hees. so i am here now. alive n kicking.=)den went to jurong east to get a bite..        &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There was once a man. He was a loyal and faithful christian, he trusted the lord in everthing he did. He walks on a beach and it represents his life, when he looks back, he always sees 2 sets of footprints. One was his.. and one was the lords. There was once when his world turned upside down.. his parents died.. he lost his job.. he got divorsed.. he was on the verge of commiting suicide.. As he looked back on the sand.. he only saw one set of footprints.. When everything was over and all was calm.. he talked to god.. asking god why he left him in a time of such trouble.&nbsp;God replied.."Those set of footprints were mine..I was carrying you throughout" .&nbsp;When the man heard this.. he broke down and cried.&nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im back frm cell! missed me rite? hees. cell rawked. timq's like farnie! so farnie kan? hahas, aniwae. there's gonna be weekend connection on sunday. altar call. heard it was greaaat. im excited! oh my gosh! ahhhhh! -screams!- okae. hahas. there's gonn be guides duty tmr. like argh! sarky. culdn't go to cell cuz of it n had to go for brother joseph's cell today. oh wells. better than nth. its the same in N163 or N233 aniwaes. hees. the song below this entry rawks! the lyrics are soooo meaningful. so touching n sad. gosh. anihoos. really hope my friends can go for sunday's service. its gonna be greaaat.! sigh. been rudder spiritually low n stuff. been blaming it on my sore throat. but guess it wasn't really cuz of it. realised there was sumthin else distracting me. yea. tts rite. its -him-. he's hindering my walk with God. okae. mabbe those reading my blog dun understand wad im talking bout. just ask me lar ir ur curious. well. tt's was a blog is for rite? to write bout how ur feeling. aniwae. yea. really pray that i'll have a breakthrough once more. if Jesus could do it once for me. i believe he'll do it again.faith.faith.faith.wheeeeeeeeeeeeeee. yeaaaaa.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        [worlds apart]-jars of clay  I am the only one to blame for this Somehow it all adds up the same Soaring on the wings of selfish pride I flew too high and like Icarus I collide With a world I try so hard to leave behind To rid myself of all but loveto give and die To turn away and not become Another nail to pierce the skin of one who loves more deeply than the oceans,more abundant than the tear Of a world embracing every heartache Can I be the one to sacrifice Or grip the spear and watch the blood and water flow To love you - take my world apart To need you - I am on my knees To love you - take my world apart To need you - broken on my knees All said and done I stand alone Amongst remains of a life I should not own It takes all I am to believe In the mercy that covers me Did you really have to die for me?All I am for all you are Because what I need and what I believe are worlds apart I look beyond the empty cross forgetting what my life has costand wipe away the crimson stains and dull the nails that still remain More and more I need you now,I owe you more each passing hour the battle between grace and pride I gave up not so long ago So steal my heart and take the pain and wash the feet and cleanse my pride take the selfish, take the weak,and all the things I cannot hide take the beauty, take my tearsthe sin-soaked heart and make it yours take my world all apart take it now, take it now and serve the ones that I despise speak the words I can't deny watch the world I used to love fall to dust and thrown away I look beyond the empty cross forgetting what my life has cost so wipe away the crimson stains and dull the nails that still remain so steal my heart and take the pain take the selfish, take the weak and all the things I cannot hide take the beauty, take my tears take my world apart, take my world apart I pray, I pray, I praytake my world apart    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       jus came home.i think todae was the slackiest day in school.hardly did anything at all. just slacked all the way. i guess like almost half of the school left halfway! 2o1 was left with only bout 18 of us.seriously stupid.hahas.they should just declare it a holdiday! waste of my precious time. i could have gone out with kaiming! with mike! and with josh! argh! oh wells. home nuw. hafta rush off again for cell grp later. hafta find time to go look fer sean too. sickening. grrrr. and yea. the guys in my class are seriously arghh!!! they always disturb n irritate me. feel like just punching them in the face! and im still not over the fact that i failed math!! ahhh. how could i fail math?!!?!? my gosh. sighhhhh. yeahs. guess tts bout it. i''l write more when im back from cell grp. hahahahas. dun miss me guys!     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just reached home. went to see e doc. gosh. my throat reallly hurts loads. =( aniwae. im in lurve with this no secrets song tt i heard off&nbsp; my sister's blog.&nbsp; yups. well. gonna have tuition later. n im sleepy. boo. im goin to her hse n slp! wahhahahas. oh.. todae me n yuntian did a badddd thing to sum1. lol. mwahahahahhas. wadevar..=p im lame. boo-eys........nth much todae. just tt the guys in my class are as irritating as ever. throwing stuffed toys at me and touching my things. argh! one day....i'll pluck off their puny lil heads!! hmph! grrrrrrr. sickenin rats.   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        [my 'so' called]friend called me. his voice still as angelic as ever.sigh. miss the old times when we would talk and night. listen to his horrible yet "makes my heart melt" voice&nbsp;as he sings.&nbsp; aniwae. asked him out larh. but he's having badminton. soooo. yea. tink gonna ask on sat again.oh wells. &nbsp; okae.hahas.back to business.i went town todae..sooo kool! haven been there for quite a while.last time i went there was two weeks ago.ahahahahahhahhahas.yea. so we walked..walked...n walked around..walked summore n walked. searching for my roxy pencilcase.but boohoooohooos.=(.culdn't find it larr! haiyoo. hahas.so i was kinda sad. n i felt sick. mabbe cuz i din get my pencil case.okae.tts lame larh wadevar. anihoos. kaiming kor is runinng todae!! but heats only larh. my darling kor's sooo pro. like its a duh- thing tt he'll win rite? wahahahahhas. like kor like mei. i lurve my kor!!! =) *hugs* okae. aniwae. hahas. enuff bout that. i need to include one more person in my previous entry. and that would be [drumrolls]&nbsp; GOD! yea. he rawks. changed me totally.turned my life around. i love him. alot. more than i would love anyone or anythin. okae. tts all for todae. the end. u can close the window now. i noe im lame. but i carn help it. in a good mood todae.wahahhahahahs. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        [some1 whom im close to. n always will be]   i miss the days. when we would talk for hours.i miss the times. when you would greet me with a cheerful smile. i miss the old you. the you i used to know. the you, i could just pour out evrything to. the one who cheer me up with just one word. the one i used to know. but..no matter who you are now. i'll remember you.. n you'll always be in my heart.  &nbsp;    [i'll never forget you. the impact you made in my life]   it has been so long since we have talked, i hope that things are still&nbsp; the same. hope that it will never change. cause wad we had can never be replaced. dun let it fade away. u made me believe i could do almost anything. stood right by me through the days and evrything. i'll remember you.and that's forever true,&nbsp;you're the one that i'll always miss. who would have thought it would be like this. i'll be with you, no matter what you're going thru. i promise you i wun forget the times we shared the days we cried. you'll always be the sun in my sky. even though we've gone seperate ways. if the day shud come when u nid sum1. you know that i'll be there. dun let there be a doubt in ur mind, cuz i'll remember you. it ended so soon.&nbsp;the impact you made in my heart, my life. you'll always be in my heart. no matter what. i cannot deny it. i still haven't forgotten you.=) thank you...    [january&nbsp;2 2003]i will not forget you..[april 22 2003]    &nbsp;    [someone..]   i have had enough of your games. the riddles that u have left me to solve. thank you for evrything. the sweet memories. the precious gifts u left me. the movies. the nice messages. thank you... its been already almost a year. its hard to forget you. but i just have to let go. maybe you're just not the one. you're causing too much hurt, pain and sorrow. you're not the same anymore. i hope you'll change. but i guess im gonna erase you completely. i never dreamt it'll end like this. wells.. i guess this is it. bye. that's all.&nbsp;  &nbsp;    [my darling kors]  geez. just wanna thank you guys fer standing by me thru the up n downs in my life. really learnt how to treasure all of you. although i have not really talked to some of them [especially tim] but u've really changed my life. really wanna thank God for having such caring n wonderful kors like you, who are sooo willing to just give up some of your time just to talk to me. although i may not seem interested, u ppl have really made a difference. thanks..=D  &nbsp;    [n of cuz..yuntian]  hees. ur the greastest bestest fren one could ever have. one that i can talk to about anithing and you would just understand. its so easy talking to you. one that i can just share all my time with. though we pms each other evry now and then. we just laugh it off a few minutes later. although we have only been very close recently, it feels like ur a long lost fren tt i've never known. i dunno how to put it into words. ur like the greatest fren one could have  [friends.forever]  ....thank you..=)  &nbsp;  hees. wells. just realised how this ppl here have changed my life.was reading a fren's blog, when i realised that i just needed to show i really treasure this ppl here.=)   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      went to church todae. was greaat. hees. message was.   -solid-   anihoos. yea. den went fer bible study. tuition. blah blah and all e usual stuff lar. celebrated jeremy &amp; sista ping ying's burthdae.heez. had loadz of fun. yups. den went outta with joshua n yuntian after that. went to watch MEAN GURLSS. RAWKS TOTALLY. yea. den yuntian left first. so i walked around with joshua fer awhile....yea. he got me my   birthday   present!! [e happy house duck tt i wanted!!!!!!] &nbsp;n we talked bout sum stuff larh.lol.yups. den yea. accompanied my bro to e fish shop.n i tink i have just fallen in   lurveee   with fishes. i tink they're cute.hahas.all thanks to jonathan's and my brother's influence.sigh. = p  . wadevarrr. n my throat hurts reallll bad.=(. gonna see a doc tmr. boo-eys. wahhahahahhas.yeahhhh.   [thirteen]   more days. = p   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  wenbing.eewen.huimin[guides]    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          my church! soooo rawks!      hees.made it myself.=p         me.minz.   &nbsp;&nbsp;      tash.nic.jeff.me.[at bintan]    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  skittles.=p      me.minz.eewen.yuntian   okaes. i guess tts all im gonna load in. kinda got sick of it. will take more pics when i can. wahahahahs.rite now.my&nbsp;head's like gonna split. really having a   baddd   headache! argh. wells. went to school in dah mornin. cuz of yuntian. see, im   nice   after all.wahahhas. yea, den went to school. n stoned in class. n gort scolded. den culdn't take it animore. so went home. so here i am now. hahas.wells.my head's still throbbing. really hurts.boo-eys. but aniwae. yea.nice lil yuntian brought my hmwk back for me n gave it to me. so nice rite? yea yea. wadevar. im really sad lei. cuz&nbsp;of dis stupid   fever   den cannot go prayer meeting. sigh. n to think i was looking forward&nbsp;to it. really glad my mom allowed me to go.&nbsp;&nbsp;budden now. im down with a fever n carn&nbsp;go..hahas. wells.&nbsp;pray i ged well soon! hahas. pray tt nxt week got prayer meeting! i wanna go. reaallll&nbsp;bad.yeaps.&nbsp;haven finished our project yet. reallll dead man. shucks.&nbsp;aiyar. who care larh. burhdae's in   [FIFTEEN]   days. hahas.hints!!!  &nbsp;   &nbsp;  &nbsp;            
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wells. school was totally boring.was like falling asleep during mr choy's lesson. hahas but by God's grace. i managed to understand the lesson in the end. its serious chimology! hahas.yea. den after that went for prayer meeting. it was fantabulous! really felt the presence of God come upon me as i prayed for Nanhua. just felt the warmth n encouragement from God. like he put his hands around me. and just gave me the encouragement. just took a step of faith n prayed in front of so many people. [burden for revival.]yea. tommorrow got overnight praying meeting. really wanna go! its from 11pm to 5.30am. but have school on saturday morning. so i guess i'll be staying till one only.yea. asked my dad if i could go already. he said alright. but mom wasn;t too happy bout it. well. just hafta pray harder then. gonna try asking her again later! yea. hahas. =p
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hees.just came back frm e bible thingy. n it rawked like dunno wad. message was wunnerful. hahs.took a cab back with yuntian.lol. went to singapore poly to go meet meng ching b4 goin. n guess who i saw? SEAN TAY. "lucky" punk huh? hahas. its his gd fortune tt he saw me kae. lol. yarh. tt ass larh. sickening toot. n ums. wahahhahahaha. i actualli waited for meng ching for 40 mins. see how patient i am.==x lol. yeah. den she was like "sorry sorry" long story larh. lazy to type it outta here. n she treated me to KFC.lol! yea. thx lar. sigh. tmr having hist test. sooo dead.=( boo.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okae.testtesttests coming up. so stressed. really hafta do well. sigh. cannot fail my cheena if not i hafta drop to express.=(.im seriously broke.like ZERO this month.im serious.so yarh.believing in God that he will provide with e finances.chinese test coming up tomorrow.and have churchwide bible seminar. haven settled e ministry thing with sister py. hope can settle by tmr.den dun hafta worry bout it anymore.hmmms.kkinda feeling werid this few days. heard loadz of stories. oh wells. sigh. yea. guess tts it. nidta go study nuw. turdles.=) smilezz
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okae.im still not sure when's my science test. arghh.wadeva lar! ahahas.geez. yeahs. i studied a teeeny bit todae.which is counted as good already! n i did art lor.hahahahhahaas. den yupss.meng cheng called. den we were talking bout sum stuff. gosh. N163 sooo rawks! oh yea! this sundae is ice-cream and hotdog weekend at church! who wants to come? hahas. feel free to ask me kaes? lol. yea. listening to ps. kong sermons todae again. so farnie okae! oh my gosh. he sooo rawks! lol. wahahhahas. yeah. hmmms.tts bout all tt happened todae lor. geez. my hair's not tt bad after all larh. whahhahahahhahs. yeah.  kinda lurvinn it nuw. yepps. sigh. fould out loads of stuff bout well you-noe-who. well. im so glad. so so so glad its over. hahas. yeahs. yay! yurpps. tts bout it.turdles.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my precious sleep.i spent most of day in school today sleeping. o never slept so much in class before! was really tired kaes.hahas.my eyes were like closing and before i knew it, i drifted off into dreamland.hahas.i din get caught though.wahahhahahas.oh wells. yeah.todae after school went to yuntian's hse to cut my hair.hahas.it sarks larhhhhhh.hahas.den went to church! n it rawkkkkked like dunnowad. but i had a fever. i was seriously sick okae.ahahas.eugene was soooo nice to lend me his jacket.but it was sooo big! i could seriously swim in it.hahas.so sweet.awwww.yups.the bible study was seriously greaat okae.it was like sooo WOW! yurps.i nid to math now.toodles
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahahahhas.kinda gone nuts bout spiderman n stuff? lol.rawks kae? hahas.watched it todae with lucille n yuntian.wahhahas.so nice kae? yups.so proud of myself todae.i spent only like 15 bucks! so..wow rite? wahhahas.mabbe one of e reasons is.IM BROKE! boohoo.oh ya.n roxy got new wallet.so pretty kae! pretty pretty wallet!! argh. aniwae.yarh.tmr after sch gotta like rush to church or sumthin litat.fun!lol! lurve it like sooo totali man! wahhahahahs. wells.yea.havent exactly finished my hmwk.but oh wells.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whheeee.really high todae man.lol.im so glad i took it well.din ged depressed over it.kinda surprised over myself too.tot i would like get very sad n stuff.but i didn't! wahahahahahas. i can actualli tease him bout it.like sooo wow? and guess wad.the ice between us finally broke.i guess we're toking now. wells.yea.i want to keep it this way.geez.had SYF todae.it was not so boring larh.hahas.this time the time seemed to pass veryvery quickly.finall learnt to appreciate nanhua.lol.guess god put me in there for a reason and i should not be complainging so much about my school.hees. other schools got sum weird noodle fer their dinner but we, nanhuarians got KFC! wooohoo! rawks dude! hahas. and ums..yea. sundae again tmR!! -cheers- funfunfunfunfun! yups.guess tts it.wanna watch teevee nuw.turdles!
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just watch the nine'o clock show on channel eight. rawks totally.soo in love with that show. awwwww. wenhui[chen han wei guy] is sooo friggin sweet. soooooo sweet and nice to kaixin. damn. im getting jealous. wadeva. hahas. but really la.soo sweet. okaes. hahas. umsss. todae's test was alrite i guess? wrote crapp. hope i do well. sigh. screwed chinese. really really did. lucky i din use the screw driver todae. wahhahahas. aniwaes i wore contacts after sch. since ive been really lazy to put them on evry mornin.  heeees. but wadevaaaaaaaaa. i'll wear it more often next time.. too lazy.=p den went to bras basah or howevar u spell it. lol. to get our art materials. yupss. guess tts bout it. sigh. english paper tmr. n WENHUI rawkss! gosh. n chen hanwei's rather cute too. awww. hees. till next time, tudles. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wheeee. church was simply greaaaaaaaaat! no better word to describe it. it rawkss! superrr totally crowded. whole place was packed. even all the staircases and ppl had to sit on e floor!! wahahhahas. soo cool larh. yeaps. food fair was alrite. den went to go get glitter tatoo. hahas. had loads of funnn! lol. had parade of ministry too. lol. saw tim1 dancin when it was the indian outraeach part. lol. so darn farnie. i was practically staring at him instead of the stage. wahahhhahahs. yeaps. gary n his couz louis came.hahas. COOL! yeah. den dan n carlos mite be coming next week!! yays!! awhahhahahas. so cool eh? hope cas can come n bingn clauds. esp mabel n estella too. ahahhahas.a nehoos. yeap. guess tts about it? nid to go start mugging for exams tmr. wahahhahhahhas- 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh wells. to all those hurting/sad/depressed ppl out there. especially those that i noe. im always there for     [y]ou guys. and so is God yea? boo. makes me sad to see evry1 sad n hurt n stuff. argh. so much i want to say to y'all. aniwae. yea. hope y'all noe wad i mean. okae. first things first. woke up early to study den went for cell grp with E316. at lucas's place.hahas. sooo kool! hees. N163 first cell grp meeting as a multiplied cell. yays! soo fun larh. evry1 there's soooo farnie n crappish.aniwaes. den went back with clara n serene. n here i am. muggin again. but nth's going in. so yar. hope i do well. sighhh! church tmr. 15th aniversary. lol. FUN!. gary and his cousin cummin along.!! kewl larh. gary so solidddd. already bringing frens to church. kewll ehs. =p ooo.  carlos said he'll be cummin ti church nxt week! yay! so "on" leh. mwahahhahas. n i tink almost 10 ppl say tt me n yuntian look alike lorr. like wthh-! hahahas. yar. n im serious. ALOT of ppl.i dun look like her rite? do i???=x oh no. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yays. finally got my contacts!!! wahahhas. finally.after suchhh a long wait!! lol. yeps. todae was alright. not tt boring todae. hahas. im so hardworking kae! damn guai in sch todae. early in the morn. Beannie lim made my day. caught me for my attire. but hey! im a good gurl. so she had nth to book me about. lol. she checked if i folded my skirt but i din.=p so no pink form.no detention. den she not happie ask me to lift my hair up let her see my ears. but too bad for her. i wore earsticks todae..=p so nth for her to book too. wahahhas. xia suay eh? too bad. im just soooo friggin guai.=) yups. ate alort todae. gosh. gonna seriously grow fat. wahahhahas. oh no- aniwaes. yea. nid to go soon larh. hafta stardee.=(((( common tests on mondae. freaaak! 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      umms. todae was sucky. day ended rather quickly. mabbe cuz i was busy with stuff but after PE lessons i started feeling sick. yea. head was throbbin n stuff. so was weirdly quiet during assembly. hehe. sorry yuntian. wasn't feeling well so just din feel like talking much. yup. feeling better now. awwww. i feel so guilty. freak. shud have just returned the VCDs. aniwaes......... i need to study now lar. boo...examss!! eeeek. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so im finally done with the project. -yays- hahas. now to concentrate on studyin. poo. hees. have twenty hours to do this week. bwahahhhas. but i can do it!! yeah!! =p. umms. mission impossible was greaaat! but i tink that around the world in dunno how many minutes was more fun! but yeah.. enjoyed myself. n i got cooked. wahahhahas. nvm larh. at least it wasn't as bad as the time we went to bintan. ahahhas. ummmms. im studying now. so guai yea? caught the JT disease. wahhahahas. gosh. im sooo gonna study like siao after todae. carn slack animore. really wanna go for prayer meeting too. hahas. i realised why i forgot my password. evrything happens for a reason. now that my old account is gone. n all my contacts lost. not much distraction already. gonna concentrate on studying and glorifying God now. mugmugmugmugmugmugmug. the mugging has begun... boooooo 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      add me now! at  urlLink jaslynn_teo_@hotmail.com  [i friggin forgot my old password. but dun delete my old acc yet. cuz i mite remember it suddenly.hahas]   freak.forgot my password! argh. anihoos.im in N163 still. yeaH! whahahhas.kaes.serviec was greattt! n gary came again. tmr got mission impossible. really hope he can come too. whahhahahahahs. ummmmmms. yeah. tts all i guess. kinda depressed now cuz i forgot my password! argh!!! sobbs. all my pretty n shuai contacts all lost...eeks.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okae. today's the   last cell grp   meeting. sigh. hahas. gettin depressed..=x anihoos. goin outa to study later. n den for cell grp. boohoo.! wadevar.i dun rally have much to say at the moment. so yea. i'll update later.   [wth! fine.  if u choose not to believe me. its your own problem. well. i dun talk about evrything and evryone on my blog. i can choose wad i want to write. its   MINE  . since u say so.. den i have nothing else to add. i wouldn't be bothered to read ur blog if i din care.] 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys.im home   earlly   todae.big achievement.hahas.had a half day. den went to jurong point. was seriously crapppp!!! did nth in sch but watched e stupid performance. but wadeva. at least   he   sat behind me. he's so   gorgeous  ! awwwww! supper cute. but wadevaar. who cares.we're frens now. hahahahahhahas. at least we talk more now. a   BIG   improvement. kkaes.enuff bout   him  . went to jp to walk. cuz culdn't eat since me n yt were fasting..so ya. n ums.athmosphere was weird la. -confused- wadeva. yea. bought   eewen's   present. got the idea out of   aaron's   present..not really complete yet tho. but once it is. i''ll take a picture n show y'all.ahahhas.hope it turns out well. n we borrowed like 4 vcds. gonna have a marathon tonite dude! gonna stock up on potato chips n chocs. GOSH! im soooooooooo in lurveee with chocs! gosh. especiall   M&amp;Ms  . ummmmmmmm.yummie! wahahhahas.wadevar....!! tmr's cell grp's   last   meeting. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whheeeee.wahahhas.have been pms-ing lately.opps.hahas.anihoos.yea. cuz kinda busy n sum irritating ppl jus cum seem to understand it. wadevarrr. yay. i skipped sch todae n yest. had this options trading seminar. sooo totally rawked! like cost 5k!!! hahas but anihoos. it was fun larh. my dad's giving me $$ to go n play with the options. lol. if i make $$$ im seriously gonna get myself that laptop pc and and my darlink hp!!!! hahas. so nice..yea wadevar. cell grp's multiplying soon. sat's gonna be the last meetin. its a good thing. but still kinda sad. so yea. happy tears.(*=.okae.im crappin shit la. kinda messed up now.hahahahhahahhas. alrite. nid to study. friggin exam's cummin n i have like 10 more study hours to fulfil.eeekkk!!!!  [seriously. i have my piorities. yea. so if u cant understand den let's just drop the whole subject. so sick n tired of giving in to u. if ur not happy about it den too bad la. cuz God's always first. den sch work. i have my own life and i do treasure you. if u don believe me. den its ur own prob. y dun u just stop being so selfish n think about how others feel first. you're not that perfect after all. so ya. do some soul searhcin.]  [it'll seriously help if u stop talking about tt guy.] 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my burthdae sooooo [  RAWKED  ]. lurve evry1 for making tt day superrrrr special. wanna thank like tons of ppl larh!!!  yuntian, N163, kaiming, gary kwek, lixuan, cuitian, mom, dad, godmom, wenbing, jermaine, jeff,mabel,adelene, jt[not the one frm 2/1], sean tay, gary goh, zhen feng, jingjie, tanisha, chin huimin, tay huimin, another huimin[dunno surname], yuting, nik, tash, angeline, mengching, sheng wei, jeremy, amanda, yuzhi, dallan, qian wen, funshen, jansen, kaibin. wenyang, estella, sihao, jillian, daniel, eve, leon and his bro.dun ask me why but ya.n a few more who i kinda forgot . bu hu cares. u guys rawk larh! made my day!!!! had loads of pretty prezzies. both big n small. wahahhas. n sum that hafta be censored. lol. but they allll rawks. n of cuz i wanna thank GOD. for giving me the best present...lurve u guys alorrrrrrrt......!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! aniwaes. yea. gonna forget my unhappy memories. and my birthday resolution  [to spark revival in NH.]  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [those memories. keep flashing back. go away...GO AWAY!!]  todae's service was greaaat! rev. mike cowell came to speak to us n it was simmply grreaaat! had massive deliverence sia! rawksss! just started weeping suddenly. really. presence of god was like WOAH! culdn't stop. tried to. but i just carried on. gosh. really felt soo much better after that. God's seriously amazing. those who experience deliverence were simply changed. he prophesized about many ppl. really rreally powerful.aniwaes. gary came -cheers-. wahhahhahas. yarh. service sooo rawks.  [im getting kinda jealous of you. sigh. wad's happening.]  [those memories.] 
    
</post>


</Blog>