<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. At least 2 people in this world love you so much they would die for you.  2. At least 15 people in this world love you in some way.  3. The only reason anyone would ever hate you is because they want to be just like you.  4. A smile from you can bring happiness to anyone, even if they don't like you.  5. Every night, SOMEONE thinks about you before they go to sleep.  6. You mean the world to someone.  7. If not for you, someone may not be living.  8. You are special and unique.  9. Someone that you don't even know exists, loves you.  10. When you make the biggest mistake ever, something good comes from it.  11. When you think the world has turned its back on you, take a look: you most likely turned your back on the world.  12. When you think you have no chance of getting what you want, you probably won't get it, but if you believe in yourself, probably, sooner or later, you will get it.  13. Always remember the compliments you received. Forget about the rude remarks.  14. Always tell someone how you feel about them; you will feel much better when they know.  15. If you have a great friend, take the time to let them know that they are great.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - A group of jellyfish is known as a smack.  - The French eat an average of 200 million frogs each year.  - Your body gives off enough heat in 30 minutes to bring a half gallon of water to a boil.  - sheep snore.  - In the 1500s, England's Queen Elizabeth 1 outlawed wife beating after 10pm.  - According to Pickle Packers International, the crunch of a pickle should be audible from 10 paces.  - Number of grooves etched into U.S. dimes: 118. Into U.S. quarters: 119.  - In 1912 the Archbishop of Paris declared dancing the tango a sin.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - British left Waffles on Falkland Islands  - Shot off Women's Leg Helps Nicklaus to 66  - Plane too Close to Ground, Crash Probe Told  - Juvenile Court To Try Shooting Defendant  - Stolen Painting Found by Tree  - Bomb Hit by Library  - After Detour to California Shuttle Returns to Earth  - Boy Declared Dead, Revives as Family Protests  - Dead Coyote Found in Bronx Launches Search for Its Mate  - Childbirth is Big Step to Parenthood  - 42 Percent of all Murdered Women are Killed by the Same Man  - National Hunting Group Targeting Women  - Fire Officials Grilled Over Kerosene Heaters  - Police Can't Stop Gambling  - Ablitity to Swim May Save Children From Drowning  - Low Wages Said Key to Poverty  - Youth Hit by Car Riding Bicycle  - Hostage-Taker Kills Self; Police Shoot Each Other  - Testicle Cargo Seized  - Check With Doctors Before Getting Sick  - Police Kill Youth in Effort to Stop His Suicide Attempt  - Intern Gets Taste of Govenment  - Convicted S&L Chief Donated to University  - Parking Lot Floods When Man Bursts  - U.S. Ships Headed to Somalia  - U.S. Advice: Keep Drinking Water from Sewage  - Suicides Asked to Reconsider  - Cold Wave Linked to Temperatures  - New Autos Hit 5 Million  - Gators to Face Seminoles with Peters Out  - Study: Dead Patients Usually Not Saved 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - At a Budapest hotel: " All rooms not denounced be twelve o' clock will be paid for twicely."  - In a Swiss mountain inn: " Special today - no ice cream."  - At a Vienna hotel: " In case of fire, do your utmost to alarm the hotel porter."  - In a Moscow hotel room: " If this is your first visit to the USSR, you are welcome to it."  - At a Budapest zoo: " Please do not feed the animals. if you have any suitable food, give it to the guard on duty."  - In a tailor shop in Rhodes: " Order your summer suit. Because is big rush we will execute customers in strict order."  - A laundry in Rome: " Ladies, leave your clothes here and spend the afternoon having a good time."  - In a Czech tourist agency: " Take one of our horse-driven city tours - we guarantee no miscarriages."  - A doctor's office in Rome: " Specialist in women and other diseases."  - At a Hong Kong dentist: " Teeth extracted by the latest Methodists."  - At a Swedish furrier: " Fur coats made for ladies from their own skin."  - In a Hong Kong supermarket: " For your convenience, we recommend courteous, efficient self-service."  - At a Norwegian cocktail lounge: " Ladies are requested no to have children in the bar."  - On a Viennese restaurant menu: " Fried milk, children sandwiches, roast cattle, and boiled sheep."  - At a Tokyo bar: " Special cocktails for the ladies with nuts."
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - Aglet: the covering on the end of a shoelace.  - Phosphenes: the lights you see when you close your eyes hard.  - Kick or Punt: the indentation at the bottom of wine bottles.  - Harp: the metal hoop that supports a lampshade.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      " The other night I ate at a real nice family restaurant. Every table had an argument going."  " Whenever I hear about a 'peacekeeping force,' I wonder: If they're so interested in peace, why do they use force?"  " McDonald's 'breakfast under a dollar' accually costs much more than that. You have to factor in the cost of coronary bypass surgery."  " There is something refreshingly ironic about people lying on the beach contracting skin cancer in an attempt to acquire a purely illusory appearance of good health, while germ-laden medical waste washes up on the sand all around them."  " Honesty may be the best policy, but it's important to remember that apparently, by elimination, dishonesty is the second-best policy."  " Who says life is sacred- God? Hey,if you read your history, God is one of the leading causes of death."  " Most people work just hard enough not to get fired and get paid just enough money not to quit."
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - Been Nowhere, Done Nothing  - I have no idea what im doing out of bed.  - Consciousness: That annoying time between naps  - Suburbia: Where they tear down trees and name streets after them  - Support bacteria: It's the only culture some people have  - The gene pool could use a little chlorine  - So you're a feminist... Isn't that cute!  - Men are from earth. Women are from earth. Deal with it.  - The more you complain, the longer God lets you live.  - Warning: Dates in calander are closer than they appear.  - Age is a very high price to pay for maturity.  - The older you get, the better you realize you were.  - Time is what keeps things from happening all at once.  - We have enough youth, how about a fountain of smart?  - Your kid may be an honor student but you're still an idiot.  - Dyslexics have more fnu.  - I doubt, therefore I might be  - Forget about world peace - visualize using your turn signal!  - My reality check just bounced.  - No sense in being pessimistic - It wouldn't work anyway  - I used to be indecisive; now im not sure.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      " Anytime I see something screech across a room and latch onto someone's neck, and the guy screams and tries to get it off, I have to laugh, because what is that thing." - Jack Handey  " If they ever come up with a swashbuckling school, I think one of the courses should be laughing, then jumping off something." - Jack Handey  " A good way to threaten somebody is to light a stick of dymamite. Then you call the guy and hold the burning fuse up to the phone. 'Hear that?' you say, 'Thats dynamite, baby.'" - Jack Handey  " Whenever I see an old lady slip and fall on a wet sidewalk, my first instinct is to laugh. But then I think, what if I was an ant, and she fell on me. Then it wouldn't seem quite so funny." - Jack Handey  " Probably the earliest flyswatters were nothing more than some sort of striking surface attached to the end of a long stick." - Jack Handey  " If you ever fall off the Sears Tower, just go real limp, because maybe you'll look like a dummy and people will try to catch you because, hey, free dummy." - Jack Handey
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      " When life is too easy for us, we must beware or we may not be ready to meet the blows which sooner or later come to everyone, rich or poor." - Eleanor Roosevelt  " Those who find ugly meanings in beautiful things are corrupt without being charming. This is a fault. Those who find beautiful meanings in beautiful things are cultivated. For these there is hope." - Oscar Wilde  " Speech was given to man to disguise his thoughts." - Charles Maurice de Talleyrand-Perigord  " The things you refuse to meet today always come back at you later on, usually under circumstances which make the decision twice as difficult as it originally was." - Eleanor Roosevelt  " When you want what you've never had, you must do what you've never done." - Unknown  " Your beliefs become your thoughts. Your thoughts become your words. Your words become your actions. Your actions become your habits. Your habits become your values. Your values become your destiny." - Mahatma Gandhi  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>