<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's the start of something good....  The vast reality sighs in the night, weighs an ambivalant ray of light. A secret fortress in a forest of blight. A shimmering dove trapped from its flight.  Haunted to insanity, the distance remains A copasetic bloke who follies disdain. Silence inseminates all the sense he's entertained in solace he waits and forsakes the game.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since matricide is the killer of hope, it's ok to pop pills everyday to cope.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...Ok...so I can't create a blog about poetry w/o posting one. This is a tiny little poem I wrote the other day. Not quite sure if it's finished or not. Not quite sure if I'm moved to add to it or not. It's called 7's. Here goes...   I wanted to keep a piece of you So I started crossing my 7's Now each one is a pennance dedicated to you. Evil Spaniard.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ....so this is my first blog, EVER! I am at work creating this thing and sipping Lady Gray Tea. It's an "elegant tea, lightly scented with bergamot and other citrus flavors." Quite tastey, mmm. I am dedicated to begin writing poetry/songs again. I had a huge writing block and didn't write for maybe 3yrs. It's quite sad because it's the only way I can communicate my feelings. While it may not make sense to anybody else, it makes perfect sense to me. The words are coming to me again. I'm going to post my writings, new and old. Please feel free to post comments, thoughts, questions and your own poetry/songs or anything else you have homebrewed that you would like to share....
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drink, it makes a man it makes me happy it treats me blurry  Sip, to the last drop look me in the eye pin me against a wall  Move, just for awhile to take me in you look funny  Regrets, come later your in the now and i am way beyond  Find, hands in wrong places an unknow source a dreamer's nightmare
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sleep the day away in your abbreviated conscience gutter thoughts bring you to anneurism to glaze me over wet your lips  it takes all my courage to let your eyes in your a novel creature stinging at my soul my feet start to burn when you roam  hurry home to your pathetic life dribble in and glitter the floor your metal eyes gone silver settle in because there's no one home whimper to gain control scream aloud eyes shut tight, my sulky pearl.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why does it pail me so hard? sink into the miniscule slither into the bell jar creep in my open window J, you should have been there you should be here to make it OK. J, you like to bullshit you will never let it go away.  I'm glad your not lying in a ditch somewhere these are the reasons she says she'll never understand i'm already there. J, you should be here but u don't want me to be OK J, your such bullshit but i'm tax deductible.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      with every loud tick, I wait standing alone accepting the chill the eccentric rush invades me through the villain's voice glued with my wonder its beautiful when he's dressed in the night its tortuous to be hung in the clouds confuse me, delude me....every word you breathe.  and with your transparent heart never let them see the real thing clearly the string i've got you on is frayed one little step my way could solve the whole thing its arduous to have mannerisms so cherry its satisfying to see ice trickle from your eyes erase me, complicate me....every thought you make.  heaven is a thing you want to be you smell like a god and your'e smoking it in dream aloud until the nightmares are your reality trip up the backstairs, slide down the canvas wall its inviting to have your halo circle my throat it's electric when your poison injects and i peel you. torment me, envoke me....every step you break.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not quite sure what substance inspired this...  In the evening you start to run beats you with the butt of a gun holds you down and inject you with a venom that turns you blue you gasp for air as you start tripping and blood is the wine your now sipping constantly he screams the description of what's moving in your direction  and you swear he'll never tie you down but you fear he'll put you in the ground  yellow elephants stampede town runs a killer whale down purple cream cheese at dawn grows a black asphalt lawn.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's so sweet orange kisses succulent juices from all the fleshy parts you taste so sweet my orange man  don't say all the things you say they're not at all what i want to hear don't force me to be that way what you need me for still isn't clear  it's so queer purple plaything no conversations from all the fleshy parts you taste the bite my purple diamond  don't feel all the things you feel they're not at all what i want to touch don't try to break the seal what you need me for is too much.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      poem #21, book 1  Shattered, battered, defeated & torn we are one, blood relations, it's sworn caught up in the madness you've provoked lays a limp body & the hands that've choked tears fall, producing the river at your feet it swirls in the blood, makes the red ocean complete and there sitting quite still is the one to blame we'll judge him, torment him and crucify him we'll beat him to make him confess this sin and what we do is no more holy than he for we aren't as precious as we seemed to be.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is poem #14, book #1 - translation = written about 5 yrs ago.  I walk in the room the bitterness swallows me. i stand in the doorway, and your ghosts encircle me. In the deepest dungeon of your heart I am imprisoned there.  I know the cold air that falls off your skin is true. Your hurt, your pain, your misery, you keep it hidden deep within you. It controls your every move your every breathe, your every desire. And to the deepest corners of your mind You are imprisoned there. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      another something old.......  Tonight we're taking a walk into the abyss of nothing. shimmery stars light up nothing hall and when we look around, we stare at nothing at all. searching around what have we found? happiness in nothingness go crazy in the nothing and stand on your head sometimes i'd rather be in here than where my soul's dead. i'm awake and set free when the nothing touches me. all my thoughts become clear when the nothing appears.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is about a guy i loved...  So I broke my heart in one too many words and more or less I killed the part that's so hard to find.  and if you are still alive, I'll hold you very firm. Without a pushing hand, pull me from the clouds. The air is thin and hard to gauge.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so again, not sure if it's done or not. just wrote it about 10mins ago....  Surgical impulses infect the wound I'm driven to the center of forgiveness Simple as it seems, ties too tight can be broken and modern day crises invoke emotion. simplify the quest for inertia science incriminates every man blind. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      life is a moving target, we can't all be sharp shooters. some of us are in training hitting innocent bystanders.  some of us are quick to the draw, and miss it. some of us are second guessers, and miss it.  some of us are lucky enough to be standing on a street corner minding one's own business when it's frantically running from someone else and crashes into us.  then it gets up, dusts off. life can do that. it runs on touching, affecting, infecting, harming everyone  life is the disease we are all dying from. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the dealing has been offered, the bar has been lowered, the signing has been penned, the I's dotted, the t's crossed the X marked my seal embossed the wax hardened the label written the badge sewn into my skin the suit's pressed the case is briefed the air soured the nylon's controlled my heart hardened my soul sold I am drowned by the anvil overboard. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>