<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I think the role that I will play here seems a lot clearer.  I will be a language arts teacher in the school that is on the grounds.  The school is called "Think City" isn't that kinda cute?  Anyways it is really intense.   Compared to the other staff members we are a little secluded, lots of extra meetings and we miss out on a lot of group meetings.  I have to create lesson plans and decorate my classroom, which seems exciting for some but not for me.  I lack in the creative juice department.  Maybe I could learn a thing or two from Lauren and Amanda.  I'm not sure if I said this earlier but the children are not here, they will get here Monday.  I'll start teaching Tuesday.  As of right now I'm not super duper excited.  I think the lesson plans I freaking me out.  I'm sure that I will feel better as time goes by, all the other staff members are very supportive. Within the next couple of days I will find out which developmental group I will be working with.  I will then live in the cabin with that group the whole summer.  They will be considered my group but I will only be with them at night.  I will be in the school for the entire day.    I hope everyone is well!!!
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I made it here to New Hampshire!!  It feels like I have been talking about coming here forever and I am finally here!!!!  Everything is hilly and green.  Today all the staff arrives and orientation doesn't begin until tonight.  It is a bit awkward because some people know others from years past and others do not know anyone.  I can compare it to the first day of freshman year in college.  I'm sure it will get better after days pass.  The camp is HUGE, it is on 200 acres of land and a water front.  As far as I know the residents do not come until next Monday so within the next week I have training and orientation.  My cell phone is not working out here so if you need to reach me call 603-478-2040 and my ext. is 379 (don't I sound important?) I won't answer but you can leave a message.  That is all for now, I hope everyone is doing well!!  
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this is definitely not like anything I would do but I feel it is a good idea.  I'm not much of a technology savvy person but this is a great way for ya'll to know what is going on with me while I'm in New Hampshire and then _____________________(fill in the blank).    I'll get everyone up to speed for those of you I have not talked to in a while.  I just moved home from Carbondale, which I miss.  I was home for about three days and then spent a week at Nazareth Farm (West Virginia), for an interview.  It was wonderful and they offered me a volunteer position to begin after New Hampshire.  I'm not sure what I'm going to do, I have to see what happens in New Hampshire.  I'm hopeful and excited about the future. I leave for NH Monday early morning I struggling with packing, how do I pack for two months and fly?    Well I guess this about all for now. I hope you enjoy!!  "You must do the thing you think you cannot do"   -Eleanor Roosevelt
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks for all of your suggestions!! Well I just found out that I do not mind teaching. Isn't that exciting!? The thing that stresses me out is not having enough time to lesson plan. I feel torn between spending me time with my group and creating good lesson plans. I had a very nice day off. We stayed in a wonderful bed and breakfast. In the morning we had blueberry pancakes and hot blueberry tea. I loved every minute of it! I can't believe all the changes all of my friends have gone through since I have been gone. It is hard for me to imagine all of you guys leaving Carbondale and starting your real lives!! Good luck with the moves ladies!!    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is very hard for me to deal with outside issues here in NH.&nbsp; All of my time and energy is devoted to school and the girls.&nbsp; When I get a second to stop and think, usually the two minutes before I go to bed, I realize that I have a life out of Wediko.&nbsp;&nbsp; I feel very disconnected&nbsp;with what is going on&nbsp;with all of the important people in my life.&nbsp; I'm very thankful for everyone who has wrote me letters, left me a voice mail or a comment.&nbsp; I'm sorry that I hardly respond, it is really hard.&nbsp;  I went to an information meeting the other night&nbsp;on the year round program I think I was more focused on keeping my eyes open.&nbsp; The program is all year (obviously)&nbsp;here in New Hampshire.&nbsp; I would not have to be a teacher so that is a plus, although I'm used to teaching now!&nbsp; I received a memo the other day telling me when I could sign up for an interview, I forget that&nbsp;I do not have&nbsp;a job after this.&nbsp; It's hard for me to think what I am going to do 10 minutes from now!&nbsp; So I&nbsp;don' t know what to&nbsp;do, I guess I should see what it's about.&nbsp; the Boston jobs have not been advertised yet.&nbsp; I feel very confused with what&nbsp; I want to do when I grow up!!&nbsp; I'm taking suggestions!! hahahah  Well I wish I had more time to write to everyone individually but the time is just not there and I do feel bad.&nbsp; I'm sending everyone love, hug kisses and positive energy.   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well three weeks down three more to go (with the kids).&nbsp; Today is visitors day.&nbsp; All the kids have their friends, family members, etc. come and check out the setting.&nbsp; I have to stay in my classroom all day.&nbsp; I'm really excited to meet my students visitors.&nbsp; Some of the kids here do not have anyone to come and visit so they get to go off setting and play.&nbsp; It is sad to think that no one would come and visit them while they are away.  Sometime I get very frustrated working with the children because of the behavior they exhibit.&nbsp; I&nbsp;then&nbsp;remind myself of the things that these children have gone through.&nbsp; It&nbsp;is just unreal.&nbsp; I don't think my bad days are even comparable to&nbsp;their bad days.&nbsp;  Nothing is really new or exciting.&nbsp; Just taking one day at a time.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well my first day off came and went.&nbsp; It could have been the fastest 24 hours of my life.&nbsp; It was really interesting to get off setting for a little while.&nbsp; I wish it was a little more relaxing but it is kind of hard with four other people to accommodate.&nbsp; We all went to Keene, New Hampshire, it is a cute little town.&nbsp; We all ate a lot and did our laundry.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm pretty tired right now and want to go to bed but my group has supervision tonight.&nbsp; That means once the girls are in bed we sneak out of the cabin for two hours.&nbsp; We don't really sneak, staff from other groups come over and&nbsp;watch our girls&nbsp;for us.&nbsp;  The setting is crazier then ever due to Sunday being visitors day.&nbsp; I have herd that after visitors day, they all seem to calm down.  Teaching is still going alright.&nbsp; The girls in my cabin have started giving me a hard time about not being around during the day.&nbsp; I'm not sure they realize that I'm not on break all day.&nbsp; I do feel bad about it because I wish I could be with them more.&nbsp; I'm just the key person for them to take their anger out on right now, I hope it ends soon!!&nbsp;  I love and miss you all!!!&nbsp;  My cell phone was in roam Friday do&nbsp;I didn't call anyone, sorry!!&nbsp; I hope to have better luck this time!!   
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In eight more hours&nbsp; I will have my first 24 hours off, my first day in three weeks!!&nbsp;&nbsp; I can't wait.&nbsp; Well things are better around here, I'm not sure the situation is changing, I believe I am changing to adapt to the situation.&nbsp; Since I made that realization, things are going better.&nbsp; If the quote, "That which doesn't kill you makes you stronger," who know what will happen&nbsp;when I finished?!?!?!&nbsp; Teaching is going better, I have started to read several books with different classes and that makes lesson planning a bit easier.&nbsp; Well I really have to go.&nbsp; Thanks to everyone who has sent mail, care packages and comments!!&nbsp; They really inspire me and keep me going!!!&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I know my entries have become few and far between because that is how my breaks are here.  This is like nothing I ever thought it would be.  I will tell you all more about it when I get back, it is just too much to write about.   My girls got here Monday.  They are 17-18 emotional disturbed female.  They are a handful.  I am challenged every second of every day in the classroom and with my girls.  I feel the need to set it straight, this is not a camp, camp here is considered a four letter word.  This is a hospital in the woods with camp activities.  I really did like the idea of being at camp, well I still like the idea but it is not true. Teaching is alright, I have a wonderful co-teacher.  I don't love it but I guess I'll survive.  As of right now I do not want to become a teacher.  I'm sorry that I have been down in the entries it is just a challenging time for me right now.  I'm also sorry for not calling anyone, ever you Mom and Dad, there just isn't any time!  Well I hope everyone is well, tomorrow is another day!! 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We just had a really intense speaker tonight that talked about diversity.  It was really thought provoking.  We are all just dealing with the after shock of it all. It is just frustrating to hear people piss, moan and cry about how unjust the world is and then go back to living their ordinary lives the next day!!!! On a lighter note I got my developmental group the other day.  I will be working with the oldest girls group, 16-18 year olds.  I feel it will be a challenging and growing experience.   Think City is going a lot better.  I got my classroom today and started to organize things.  I'm really tired and worn out all the time. Thank you all for the encouraging comments, they really do help.
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Birthday Dad!!!  Well I have huge news for everyone.  I am going to take a job here in New Hampshire.  I will sign my contract this afternoon.  The position I will be taking is an assistant clinical supervisor.  I'm nervous about supervising but they will train and support me.  They are used to getting novice supervisors.  I'm full of a range of emotions.  I nervous about starting a real job, sad because I'll be away from my friends and family but happy I have this opportunity.  This job will be a lot less intense then the summer job.  I WILL be able to keep in better contact with everyone.  So the job starts Aug. 30 so I will be home for a week before I come back here.  Other news is that I was bit on the arm yesterday by one of my students.  It hurt really bad and I still have his little teeth marks on my arm.  He would not let go.  It was an interesting situation.  I was trying to get him to sit back in his seat, then he started to draw of me and as I went to get the marker out of his hand, he latched on to me.  Two other staff were helping me get him off , he finally let go after about 2 minutes.  He aplopgized and made me two I'm sorry cards, he was back in class today and was fine.   All the kids are storming again (did they ever stop?!?! just kidding) termination is really hard on them.  Tomorrow is my last day teaching!  I can't believe it is over!!  Another funny story; the other day one of my students told me her father was in the Hall of Fame, I thought she was lying turns out her father is Dennis Eckersley.  Isn't that interesting!?  "The best way to find yourself, is to lose yourself in the service of others" - Ghandi 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it is hard to believe that the summer program is almost finished!!  It is interesting because some of the kids are starting to terminate and we are trying to keep our heads in the game.  I have one more full week of Think City!!  It will be nice not to lesson plan anymore but I'm sure I'll miss my students.  I had an interview on Tuesday for the year round program.  I feel that it went well.  I applied for a different position and it would be less intense environment.  I wasn't sure if staying in New Hampshire was the best idea for me but after talking to my Mom I feel better.  So I'm not sure what will happen with that, I'll keep everyone posted!!  I hope everyone is doing well, Happy August!!! Thanks for all the support!! 
    
</post>


</Blog>