<Blog>


<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        First of all, I have to apologize for my poor English writing, but it was something that I would love to share with all the Red Sox fans. I know people would probably tell me: "it’s your own fault going to Yankee Stadium all by yourself with Red Sox T-shirt", but when does going to a baseball game become a dangerous thing?    It was almost a month ago, but for me, it was like yesterday.   On June 30 th , I, a 25 years old girl Red Sox fan who doesn’t speak too much English (imported from Asia), was molested in Yankees Stadium.   It’s hard for me to describe how much I like baseball, but I certainly love it much enough that I would take a trip down to New York and support my team. But, I also try to give respect for the home team (Yankees) since I’d like to receive some respect from their fans as well.  When the game started, I was really focused watching every single pitch, and even though I was surrounded by a huge number of Yankees fans, they found me interesting because I was probably the only Red Sox fan in the whole section, I was there ALONE, and, I am a SHE. The guy next to me tried to make a conversation, I don’t know if it because he found me cute, or simply because he had never seen any girl doing score sheet during the game. But we discussed some major league baseball rules and how it’s different with the ones in Asia. He was nice and said: "too bad that you are a Sox Fan!" "Well, but we all love baseball!" I laughed. (His girlfriend was sitting right next to him, and eyeballed me for a while.)   I don’t remember when, but people started yelling, "Boston Suck!", "1918!", "Masssssholeeee!" next to my ear. The kid sitting near by made a funny face at me, I smiled back, and pretend I don’t understand English.   During the game, people sometimes poked at me, because I had my Pokey Reese T-shirt on. "Your guy just missed it!", "Your guy is no better than Jeter!"…. "Well, at least he tried to catch it. It’s a good try though!", I replied. Still, I smiled at the old folks sitting behind me even though they did enjoy poking at my Pokey T-shirt so much. I was prepared to receive all those nasty yelling, and I had no problem taking some poking.   There were 4 guys wearing pinstripe jersey (let’s call them "pinstripe 4-some") sitting right in front of me. It was PAINFUL sitting around them. They made fun of me probably every 10 seconds and tried to convince me to root for the Yankees simply because I am Asian and they’ve got Matsui and how Boston is a racist city. "I like Matsui, but I just like Red Sox much more." I tried to calm down and reply something nice and reasonable. I put my focus back to the game, and that’s what I’m paying my tickets for.   After the 7 th  inning, people started to get crazy – and "pinstripe 4-some" were just started to lose their sanity and targeting at me. Any nasty yelling could happen to a Red Sox fan, I received them all. Still, I know it’s would just be dumb if I yell at them back, so I simply replied: "Whatever… I don’t really speak English just like Hideki Matsui…". I guess they got really mad after hearing that.   Whenever any of the Red Sox players got strikeout, they turned back, looked at me, grabbed my score sheet and force me to write down a "K" in my score sheet. "Do you know how to write K?" They laughed, and kept saying "Go HOME! Asia or Boston, EITHER ONE! We don’t want you massholes here!"   I was a bit sad, not really because all the mistreated, simply because our bullpen sort of blew up the game. But still, I wanted to see the game, I would love to support them up till the last minute. And I thought the situation was not too bad – other than the "poking", no physical contact were made.   When the Quan-Go-Mo (a stupid abbreviation of Quantrill, Gordon and Mariano made by Michael Kay @YESNetwork) showed up, the crowd went wild. Whenever the Yankees fans cheering for their team, the pinstripe 4-some turned back, pulled me off my chair and grabbed my hand, forcing me to give them a "high five".    I started to get upset and told them not to touch me.    Apparently, they became the one who don’t speak English, and they even tried to pull me over to their seat. One of the guys was grabbing my arm and another guy had both his hands on my face squeezing my cheeks.   That hurt, and my rosy cheeks almost turned purple and slightly bruised.  I was shocked. I tried so hard to push them away and it did not really work. Finally, I started yelling, "Don’t touch me! Get your hands off me!!".   However, nobody could really hear me at that time. The stadium was loud with all the cheering sound, and everyone was standing up at that time. The people around me did not try to stop them (pinstripe 4-some were pretty big), the security were too far away and did not sense it….   I would like to believe that the people did not see what happened, rather than "whatever, she’s a Red Sox fan…"   I was the "Yankees Stadium Private Entertainment Girl" for a while till I finally found my way out. I felt bad for the kids sitting around me because they witnessed the whole molestation. The kid looked at me with sympathy…   I knew the "pinstripe 4-some" would not easily just let me go, and I needed to get out of my seat as soon as possible. It’s not easy since I was so stuck in my seat (right in the middle) and I waited till someone behind me made a space for me to pass.   I was dumb – because I ran into the restroom to wipe up the running nose and tearing eyes before running to the security. Later, the security told me they could not catch them, and asked me why I did not tell them immediately when it happened.   I was too tired and exhausted to do anything else other than crying, and couldn’t even say a decent sentence in English.   It was not a pleasant experience, and it’s even more difficult for me to write about it. But still, I know I have to do it because the games are coming again this weekend, and what happened to me last month might happen again to any female – if they are Yankees fans.   My friends, it’s just a baseball game, and we all go to the park because we all like baseball – no matter which team you root for. It does take a lot of courage going to Fenway Park if you are an Yankee Fan, and vice versa.   I just hope, whatever happened to me would never happen again in any baseball park. And please, if you see some helpless Yankees fans in Fenway, do not hesitate to help them out – I really wished I had some help from the Yankee fans at that time.   &nbsp;  Despite all these, I would still go back to Yankees Stadium this September and support my favorite team.   &nbsp;  Let’s Go Red Sox!   &nbsp;  -A Red Sox fan @ Medford but actually imported from Taiwan   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's such a good game today starting by our baby  urlLink Bronson Arroyo :   &nbsp;     12 Strike Out in 7 innings !&nbsp;   
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I had  urlLink PULP  in my CD Player running for the whole day.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I used to starve myself not having lunch during my teen years, and I could save up my lunch money to get CDs. More than 400 CDs lying somewhere in my tiny room in Taipei, and my dad had to make a mini-database organizing them.&nbsp; Some of those CDs are really crappy music, after it felled off the bullitinboard. However, some CDs you would just keep listening to it even years later.  &nbsp;   urlLink Different Class  is definitely one of them.  I got that CD almost 10 years ago, and now, it still sound fresh to me, and stroked me even more.&nbsp; Good music with deep thought should always be cherished, and it a good thing that PULP never comprised (like Oasis and Blur) and still kept moving.&nbsp;  &nbsp;   urlLink Common People  and  urlLink Disco 2000  are probably the most popular songs within the album -- other than the fresh tone and rhythm, what hidden in the song is the&nbsp;really witty but also ironic.&nbsp; With the most unique British voice since David Bowie, Jarvis Cocker mixed all the experimental elements and distinguished PULP from any other Britpop&nbsp; bands.&nbsp;  &nbsp;   That was 10 years ago? Oh GOD! I feel I'm old now.....  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Red Sox Game LIVE on THE BIG SCREEN in HIGH DEFINITION!  &nbsp; &nbsp; Check out this link, it's just SO COOL! &nbsp; I don't know if you could get beer and Fenway Frank in the theater, but still, 5 bucks per ticket is pretty good of a deal!&nbsp; But hopefully we could YELL in the theater.&nbsp;&nbsp; :) &nbsp; Anyone with a car interested in going to catch a game in Showcase?  &nbsp; &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  Nixon: It's dirty pool      Reading this news made me almost have my dinner flying out toward the monitor.   WHAT A RIDICULOUS LEAGUE. No wonder no one likes   urlLink  Bud Selig   !         "Commissioner Bud Selig is the dark lord of Major League Baseball. He tried to kill two teams last fall, and this summer he has sworn not to give into the player's union, even if that means provoking a season-ending player's strike. Fans, reporters, and players hate him. Even other owners hate him. Clearly, the man must be a genius."&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    --- David Propson in flakmagazine.com (2002)      &nbsp;  Oh man... Maybe Nixon could come with another commercial with   urlLink  Pine Sol   &nbsp;--       I use Pine Sol to remove Pine Tar!!!             
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is such a great article, however, I could only find the translated version in  urlLink Traditional Chinese  and  urlLink Simplified Chinese  .   The author of this article, Nahoko Takato, a 34 year-old volunteer worker, helped street children on the streets of Baghdad.         "Even though I was abducted, I don't hate Iraq. I will come to Iraq again,"    "I had to endure unpleasant things. But I cannot hate the Iraqi people," a teary Takato told an Aljazeera reporter.      As everyone knows, the Japanese Prime Minister Junichiro Koizumi made such response:    "A great number of government officials made efforts to rescue them when they were in captivity. How can they say such a thing? I want them to think about their circumstances."    This whole incident just became like a rolling snow ball and the conservative Japanese society started to view these hostages as the shame of Japan.  urlLink The New York Times  had a very good article about this issue.     When the doctor told Ms. Takato she had done good work in Iraq, she cried convulsively and said,  "But I've done wrong, haven't I?"      What Ms. Takato did is absolutely courageous and admirable.  I might have commit harakiri myself if I were her. Instead of hiding in the safe zone, she chose to stand up, and wrote what she had experienced in Iraq, and share it with the world.     我感覺到自己的肉體雖然沒有被那些拿著武器的伊拉克人活活燒死，但是我的心卻被沒有武器的日本給燒死了。  Even though I survived from the armed Iraqi forces, but my heart was murdered by the unarmed Japan.     I wish I had time and much better English skills to translate what I read in  urlLink here . This is not a story about Takato, it was a FACT telling you how beautiful human nature is -- even for the angry Iraqi people.    This is an amazing news (I won't use the word "story" since it's MUCH MORE than one). Hopefully they would translate it into English soon. If you know me in person, I'd love to do oral translation anytime.     Tell me, what we could do to help people get the courage of putting down their arms?   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh MY GOD, I was SHOCKED when reading this on  urlLink New York Post . No wonder it could never be as good as  urlLink New York Times !      urlLink New York Post Dating Game     We're looking for attractive, single guys and girls to take part in a new dating game for the New York Post's Sunday edition.   Please see http://www.nypost.com/dating for information and registration.      Show some class, please!  This is not  MTV channel with ink !      
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning, I was trying to save some of my old writing (in Chinese). And I think it might be a good idea to keep them in another  urlLink chinese blog .   Those are REAL stories happened to me, and whenever I read them, everything is still so vivid. The actual story line is way better than the Korean love Drama -- it's those "Madison Bridge" kind of love that you could remember that for the rest of your life.    I am glad that I was in love, and the greatest part is that someone loved me more than anything else in the world.    If you ever chatted w/ me through IM or use Yahoo account, Namisy would be one of my common handling.  I used to use the English name Daisy and his name is Namhoon -- we always shared two account together: Namisy and Dahoon.   I used to think about deleting all namisy accounts since we were not together anymore, but I realize that was part of me already.  Without him, I would never be the same as who I am right now.      Looking at the sky will bring me back the thought of you  --- although things will never be the same without you.     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I read this old email from a friend in 1998.  Reading it again 6 years later, I somehow realize what she meant.     If someone's success makes you slight, uneasy, or critical, examine what's behind you reaction. You are not diminished when others succeed.Your life is not a competition with them.  If your dreams fall apart, sweep up the pieces and save them. Sliver of hope can be found in the debris of shattered dreams.      I am thankful that I had this chance reading it again at this moment. It meant a lot to me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Sox is doing great this week playing at Fenway Park, and I do feel the same way getting back to Boston – the place I would consider as my second hometown.   One of the biggest connections of Taiwan and Boston might be “baseball”. I might keep the image of the “perfect Asian-lady” preparing tons of food and being a “man’s bitch” the Super Bowl, but when it comes to Red Sox and Chinese Taipei Baseball team, I am turning into those crazy fans jumping, yelling and non-stop cursing in front of the screen.       Reading " urlLink Leaving the Past Behind " reminded me about my first baseball experience.     Growing up as the only kid in the family, I did not really have chance to know anything about baseball.  urlLink Barcelona Olympics 1992  was pretty much the year getting me into baseball, because that year, our Chinese Taipei won the silver in baseball.   I remember at that time, I was so not literate in baseball. The commentary guys on TV were actually horrible, but I learned my way to understand the rules. Just like most of the girls, I got into baseball simply because my patriotism, and also because I was IN LOVE with one of the pitcher.   After the wonderful summer Olympics, I started to “listen” to the major league broadcast (well, we did not have cable at that time because my dearest dad did not want me to get distracted from STUDYING HARD). I could not distinguish from strikes to balls, and could only picture those in my imaginative mind.   However, I was young, and it’s so easy to kill a kid’s mind by disappointing them. The overwhelmingly gambling scandal just extinguish my growing fire through the only professional sport I like.   I was indifferent toward baseball for around 10 years, and almost forget all the basic for baseball.   On my 25th birthday (Oct. 8th 2003), I was at home having dinner with my housemates. I turned on the TV after the dessert and there was the first ALCS game on TV. Wakefield vs. Mussina in Yankees Stadium with a big homer by Ortiz – that was my very first Red Sox game. Have you ever had that “love at the first sight”? That’s what happened to me with the Red Sox.   It’s a team with “teamality” – they are proud of the history, talent but somehow just get screwed up for being lazy or unfocus. Under the pressure of curse, they still believe in themselves and never give up. That’s the spirit of a team, and that’s the spirit you would find in me. Professional sports  urlLink isn’t just ALL ABOUT WINNING  – that’s another thing I realized through the Red Sox. Pokey Reese, my favorite player in the team, shows how much he enjoys being there every single moment. Most of the players over emphasize how much money they could get from the club house, or how many CY Young, Gold Gloves they could get, but they forget the most important thing: the spirits! Even though we also have greedy “show me the money” players and whining babies in the Sox, but overall, it’s a team doesn’t need BALCO to build up their muscles, or outrageous money to build up more diamond toilets in their houses. Most of all, they have the most fantastic fans in the world – and I am really proud to be one of them.   Also, this year our National baseball team is going to play the  urlLink Athens 2004 Olympics , and hopefully this would rekindled more young spirits towards baseball.     It’s not just about winning, it’s about the spirit!    Here are some Taiwanese Baseball References:   urlLink Teams investing in Taiwan: Dodgers, Mariners among those building relationships    urlLink Taiwan: a home for second careers 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Passion  and  urlLink Compassion      This title is sort of funny – I’m sitting somewhere at  urlLink Starbucks  while the guy sitting right next to me is studying his  urlLink GRE  verbal.     In the past couple of months, I’m really sensitive to the word “passion”. Finding someone you really like having a profile on " urlLink passion.com  (aka.  urlLink Adultfriendfinder.com )" could be one of the unpleasant a girl could endure – which could be worse if you love him.   People suppose to have passion to everything – towards life, work, family, people, and of course, some lust. Maybe due to the image I tried to maintain, or maybe because of the cultural background of traditional and conservative Taiwanese family, I was angry about the whole “ urlLink passion.com ”. I did not realize what was wrong with it, and simply just spend my energy cursing the people there, including the one I love (yes, it was that bad, I love him and I could not find any reason why I love him).   Sexually frustration and self-denial could be the reason. It is never easy for me to keep this innocent image and totally let go during the “bed time”. Or, it just that I haven’t found anyone trustworthy and could totally let me forget about anything but lust in bed. Maybe deep deep deep down, I am a faithful  urlLink Catholic  girl, and always feel guilty about it.   However, God is always gracious, and it comes with  urlLink compromised solution  – human anatomy that is. If I am not comfortable with myself, how could I be comfortable with my significant other? And I really should stop that “innocent Asian girl” image since it not ME, it’s someone expected me to be. Still, I do not know how could the  urlLink “big one”  gonna think, but I’ll pray and ask him what to do. Time is different, and I’m 25 years old single female who has her crazy hormone moments from time to time (Amen, sisters!), and it's so hard to resist the outside temptation in this crazy world. I was not born like this, but the chauvinistic cultural background converted me into this “Japanese pron star innocent look” kind of behavior. You would know what I am talking about if you ever seen one of those.   So, I decided that I need to know myself a lot more (in every way) and I need to be VERY HAPPY of who I am and just simply BE MYSELF without worrying what would other people think. If people around me really love me, they would love me no matter what I do (within a reasonable range).   Sunday, I had my routinely date with Father John Unni at  urlLink St. Cecilia , and every single words he said just rocked my world. Compassion is the topic for today. It was not easy for us to admit that we did things wrong, and it’s even harder for a priest to admit it to a group of Catholic people during the mass. Even  urlLink the most beloved priest like him , has his tired and indifferent moment and forgot to help our neighbors.   To give compassion, reaching out to the world, passion and self-loving should be the first step. Just like I mentioned before, if I am not comfortable with myself, how am I going to establish a relationship with people? Being comfortable with yourself doesn’t mean to dress yourself up with nice name brand outfit or decorate yourself with fancy degrees or getting good physical image, it all happened in your mind. ( urlLink Phone booth  is actually a really good movie talking about this topic).   Despite the frustrated relationship with boys, I am still so loved by the people around me. I always have the courage to be so open up and TRY to love our neighbors – because I have the strongest support from God, my family and friends. However, I am far from being a compassionate person. Do you always help people out whenever you see the needed? I ignore them whenever I am tired, in a bad mood or in a hurry, and sometimes I am just scared to be different from everyone else. There is still part of me not happy with myself and holding me back.    Is it why God sent me this most impossible man for me to love and made me learn? The picture is getting clear and I do discover more and more about myself and started to accept for who I really am.   And you know what?  I think  I really like myself !    Thanks to thy Lord! (Right at this moment, Starbucks is playing some song “you are raising me high”!)   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Sell tomatoes to throw at Wally whenever he does some asinine antic. - Jason, Weston  (from Boston Globe)  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I first see this website, I was like... HA!  This is so "Yankees".  Check out the so called "Smart Networking" school list -- almost MOST OF THEM are so called "my parents need to pay $40K a year" kind of schools.  Well, maybe not really for the European ones (maybe 40K Euro instead, German/French ones are free - except business schools). But what's interesting was why would people think their schools are the "MOST SELECTIVE" colleges and universities?   Do these "elites" really need to distinct themselves from others to prove that they TRULY are the "A-List" type of people?  I am not being bitter or whatever because my school is also in that "MOST SELECTIVE" school list -- which I found it really dumb.  This site had a good intention for alumni networking, but it advertised in a wrong way.  First of all, if you want to gain membership and make money, you have to target at the right customer.  And now here comes the problem -- how many power net-surfers would register in this site if their schools were/weren't in the "LIST"?  And how many of them will be willing to pay for the membership?  Of course you could think this way that since all these kids went to really expensive school would probably willing to pay more, but here comes another question -- how many of them would possibly become unique user of this site?  (Okay, I am not really making any sense here, but if you really want to know what I mean, email me and I'll draw a graph to make you understand.)     NOT even mention that site is user-unfriendly and super "exclusive" in every single ways.    Internet suppose to break the barrier, but  urlLink Smart Networking  fielded up this "glass ceiling".      COUNTRY CLUB on the net, that would be it!      
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Love is a game. Easy to start. Hard to finish.   The first time I watched it, I was still in high school and knew nothing about love.   Now, I'm 25 years old, about the same age as the main characters in the film -- and of course, I do see this film much more different than before.   Other than the Alice in Chains & Soundgarden playing LIVE in the film and the background of Seattle Grunge (featuring Pearl Jam and my beloved REM), the whole twenty-something stories seems to be part of my life.  By changing a location, the whole Janet wondering calling Cliff or not scene happened in my apartment almost every single day (even though now I have no such a problem anymore).  The weird hand-shaking scene of Linda and Steve when Linda getting off the ship from Alaska happened to me not a long time ago in Manhattan.    I am not sure if I truely am a girl or not, because playing "GAMES" is just not my thing. I follow my heart and try to be as open up as possible -- which constantly lead me to be hurt from time to time.  Plus, dealing a guy coming from a totally different culture is another thing I need to adjust.  Maybe I am too used to "maintaining" this "perfect Asian girl" image and sometimes forget who I really am.    Looking back at my past relationships, did they really love me or they just loved my "image" instead?     There is one of my favorite scene that the plastic surgeon Bill Pullman was telling Bridget Fonda that she is perfect and she does not need to get breasts enlargement -- he should like who you are.  It sounds simple, but it does not sound that pleasant to most women.    Are you his Miss Right or just Miss Maybe?      Other than Love, stress from work is another point of the film.  Some of character in the film having multi-jobs at the same time and also need to face the loan and job searching problem.      Perfect timing for me to watch this movie, I guess.     
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Red Sox and St. Patrick's Day    urlLink Red Sox vs Yankees @ Fenway Park (4/18/2004)   A special experience in Fenway bleacher section.    urlLink Top 10 reasons the Red Sox are better than the Yankees -- Detail explaination in Chinese    urlLink Behind the Enemy Lines (a Red Sox fans gathering in Manhattan) Part 1    urlLink Behind the Enemy Lines (a Red Sox fans gathering in Manhattan) Part 2    urlLink Green Red Sox Jersey Part 1 -- Ugly GREEN JERSEY    urlLink Green Red Sox Jersey Part 2 -- funny conversation in the store    All of those were from PTT.CC, a traditional Chinese BBS.  Some of the things are really funny, and I might try to translate them sometime later.    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ESPN.com - MLB - Neyer: Fenway Park vs. Yankee Stadium    urlLink Times stands still at Fenway    urlLink Stadium mystique makes up for mistakes   Recently I've heard about comparisons of Fenway Park and Yankee Stadium -- from public transportation, food, hotdogs, restrooms and $$$.  As a "Fenway Faithful", I enjoy every single game at Fenway Park, no matter how the final scores are.  I just found this article interesting because it actually reflected a small part of my thoughts -- just a small part.  However, what I like about Fenway ths most is that it provide all the statistic numbers on its huge big screen instead just putting some stupid player pictures and ads all over the ballpark.  After every single pitches, the "FLEET BOARD" would actually tell you the pitching speed, type (fast ball, change-ups...etc), strike percentage and ERA.  I remember I went to see the game on 5/30/2004 in Fenway with SEA Mariners and Raul Ibanez hitted a homerun from Keith Foulke.  Right after that HR, Foulk's ERA increased from 0.8?? to 1.2?, and the number just kept slowly going down after Keith back to his tough state.    Oh well, if you are truely a baseball fan and know something about math, you would probably enjoy reading those numbers as much as I do.    WELCOME to FENWAY PARK!  :)    urlLink ESPN Page2's Ballpark Grades   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I thought Barry Zito was the hottest pitcher in MLB, but I totally changed my mind after my short conversation with  urlLink Lenny DiNardo .   There were some great stories about the batting practice of the Red Sox in Yankees Stadium -- mostly pitchers. Pedro, Schilling, K Foulke and A. Embree: I was lucky enough to see them THAT close with some short conversation -- sometimes it's good to be a female baseball fan.  :)    I will write something more maybe after I finish my draft of thesis first.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's interesting why would I put these 2 movies together. There is a connection between the two -- George Bush Jr.  The Day After Tomorrow is a movie about global warming -- which easily reminds everyone the "Kyoto Protocol".  In 1997, this agreement was signed by Clinton government, EU members and Japan in order to combate with global warming.  However, in 2001, President Bush rejected this agreement simply because he thought it unfair on the United States, as it leaves out developing countries.    But, who is  urlLink the world's biggest carbon dioxide polluters ?   Maybe that's why before this film released, NASA sent an internal memo stating that no employees were allowed to comment on this movie.  And another trivia part of the movies is that the director actually insisted that the vice president in the film needed to be physically resemble to Dick Cheney.    As for Fahrenheit 9/11, I don't think I need to mention too much about the Anti-Bush part (since everyone knows about it). Still, there are some other background of this film people should know.   Michael Moore actually interviewed Nicholas Berg (I believe everyone knows who he is). I think Moore showed some heart by removing the sector from the documentary. I always think his work "over-ambitious" and trying to hard to sell his version of story -- even though he indeed is a great story teller (aka director).   Maybe a lot of you knew about the SciFi book  urlLink Fahrenheit 451 , and Ray Bradbury's claim for Moore's appropriating the title.  According to Moore's spokesman: "Mr. Bradbury’s work has been an inspiration to all of us involved in this film, but when you watch this film you will see the fact that the title reflects the facts that the movie explores, the very real life events before, around and after 9/11."  "Fahrenheit 451 is the temperature at which paper burns,” while Moore’s subtitle is that “Fahrenheit 9/11 is the temperature at which freedom burns."    However, Fahrenheit 451 was also adapted into film in 1966 (directed by François Truffaut).  Fahrenheit 451, 2001: A Space Odyssey (1968, directed by Stanley Kubrick) and Alphaville (1965, directed by Jean-Luc Godard) are the classics among all SciFi films.  There is also another interesting story about Fahrenheit 451. Ray Bradbury wrote the original manuscript of "Fahrenheit 451" on a rented typewriter which made the novel really easy to read due to the rent of the typewriter.     Alright.. enough crap about movies.   Hopefully I'll get to watch Before Sunset soon.  :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is this famous quote in this film:  Hub: Sometimes the things that may or may not be true are the things a man needs to believe in the most. That people are basically good; that honor, courage, and virtue mean everything; that power and money, money and power mean nothing; that good always triumphs over evil; and I want you to remember this, that love... true love never dies. You remember that, boy. You remember that. Doesn't matter if it's true or not. You see, a man should believe in those things, because those are the things worth believing in.    This is a simple movie with 3 great actors: Michael Caine, Robert Duvall and Haley Joel Osment.  It might looked odd but an amazing team telling you this story full of hope and joy.  This is not a difficult film but light flavor and meaningful.   Just like the title of this blog: Every Ordinary Life is Extraordinary.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Boston Red Sox VS San Diego Padres 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Drink a lot of coffee before I go to sleep, so I can dream fast.     I still remember when I was in  urlLink National Chiao Tung University  , there was this Jim Jarmusch's film called "Night on Earth (1991)" .    Simple cinematography with hidden images, contrast and theatrical conversations are always the symbol of Jim Jarmusch.  It was pretty much the same for movie "Coffee and cigarettes".    Imagine Tom Waits and Iggy Pop sitting down in a diner in California, talking about the coffee in IHOP, RZA and GZA of the Wu-Tang Clan and Bill Murray having tea/coffee,  urlLink the White Stripes'  Jack and Meg White doing some engineering experiments while having cigs in a coffee shop right next to the machine "Cigarettes 9", and Cate Blanchett plays both herself and her jealous cousin Shelby. The short pieces of this film is deep, somehow with some hidden sadness and slightly sense of humor.  It did reflect a whole part of the reality in an ironical way.  All those short films are independent, but somehow has connection other than 2 addicted elements: coffee and cigarettes.   Another thing you might want to pay attention to the film is the contrast of the color (even though it's purely black and white). However, there is much more hidden in every single scene -- every coffee cups, spoons sugar jars, cigarettes... everything had its own implied messages.  One thing I found the most interesting is the part for "twins", where Steve Buscemi and Cinque and Joie Lee (Spike Lee's siblings) -- during the entire conversation, the coffee table was a complete chaos and kept reflecting the inner mind of the two twins. Even though they are twins with same style of clothes, shoes and haircut, they are very different personality-wise.  Joie always had the black coffee and rolled her own cigs while Cinque always had it with sugar and milk, and had the cigs from the pack. Racial problem is hidden in this "Twin" short film as well -- ironical enough having Cinque Lee and Joie Lee to participate in this great contrast of "Elvis Twin" image. Also, I was wondering in "Twins" segment, where did the coffee pot went and how did Joie got her coffee refilled?    It's really a great and fun movie of Jim Jarmusch.  I think I might have to watch "Nights on Earth" again.      Cigarettes and Coffee, Man... That's a combination.    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       G. Bush Jr. is the smartest US President,  Osama Bin Laden deserves Nobel Peace Prize,  William Hung is the best singer,   Paris Hilton is a virgin,   Winter in Boston is warm,   Yankees is the greatest baseball team,   Francona is the best manager,   and I am a fucking genius!   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I always told people that I went to "Traffic School" as undergrad i Taiwan. The word "Chiao-Tung" means "traffic" in Chinese Mandraine, however, for some people, it's a name of proud and great memories.  It was known as the "paradise" for girls, since  urlLink NCTU (National Chiao Tung University)  is such an engineering/science oriented school, and the male/female ratio is 7:1 - which means, I could pretty much date 7 different boys when I was in undergrad. Also, in the previous decades, NCTU alumni had worked in the industrial park, pushing Taiwan into the competitive market of semiconductors, electronics and computers. Acer group, UMC, Micronix, Santak, TSMC, D-Link, Synnex...etc, more than half of them were founded by NCTU alumni. It is also known as the nerdiest school in Taiwan, and all graduates easily get tons of job oppertunities before graduation. Even if you graduate as an Enlgish major,  ANY  NCTU students at least have the skills working as MIS, even for girls.  Before getting into college, I could not even type. But right now, I guess I could still easily get a MIS job if I do not ask too much $$$ (worked in internet/media start up for 2 years). I guess I did learn a lot in NCTU (except chemistry, which was my major).         Yesterday, I got one song through the internet, and the title is " urlLink NCTUer ". I was reading the background of the song, and realize the composer of the song was one of my ex sweet heart. I still remember the days...whenever he saw a piano available, he would just sat down and played music and made some songs for me. He was a genius, and he still IS.  I don't remember why I broke up with him -- he was everything I ever asked for: very good looking, similar family background, political point of view, same hobbies (movies, music, politics, internet, writing, art...). And not only he loved me, his parents loved me too.  Yesterday was the first time I felt for his music -- maybe that could explain why we never worked out years ago. Years later, his music is getting much more mature. I am glad that he finally made his decision giving up his computer science degree and embraced the true passion in his life -- compose. He was born for that.     One day, he will shine like a star.     Download "NCTUer"  urlLink mp3 ,  urlLink music video     交大人           作詞:  薛衣珊    作曲: 薛衣珊 何嘉駒  交大人秉持拓荒者精神    用歡笑和淚水締造奇蹟 展翅飛翔未來無邊無際    釋放能量一定天下無敵  交大人擁有不服輸勇氣    堅持夢想要實踐的韌性 放眼世界努力絕不遲疑    交大聲名遠播所向披靡  不畏現實推擠   肩並肩走下去 交你我的心       就更加堅定  就算不可思議    仍執著追求真理 緊握信念            大步邁進  交大人擁有不服輸勇氣    堅持夢想要實踐的韌性 放眼世界努力絕不遲疑    交大聲名遠播所向披靡  人生難免總會經歷些不如意        若能視其為生命的洗禮 讓明天的陽光為你我點燃希望    勝利屬於～ＮＣＴＵ～            
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         DO NOT CLICK ON THE HYPERLINKS  
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Nomah was kidnapped!   I was laughing so hard when I read this news. Where was that store again? Broadway in Somerville? Haha... isn't that the one next to the  urlLink Pinis Pizza  and  urlLink the Wangs Fast Food ?  But Nomah is gone. *sigh*.... I'll write a bit more about the trade a little later, BUT.... I was reading on some  urlLink Taiwanese Red Sox Forum , and one Taiwanese kid from UCLA ( urlLink Dodgers  fan because of  urlLink Chin-Feng Chen ) was saying:  The RedSox Clubhouse people are chicken. After the deal was done, they just went on vacation and let some "part-time assistant" or "secretary" holding the press conference....  Alright. This kid totally beat me. THEO, a "part-time assistant"? I was laughing so hard and almost fell out of my chair, AGAIN! I guess you don't really need a JD degree to be an assistant, right?  HEY! But  urlLink Paul DePodesta  isn't that much older than  urlLink Theo Epstein  (like a year older)? Aren't they both young, good looking, talented advocates of  urlLink MONEYBALL ?  Talking about Theo, I've seen Theo in person one time in Fenway. He was talking to some people while standing RIGHT NEXT TO ME on  urlLink 7/24/2004  (Saturday afternoon game with MFY plus an awesome fight).  I was thinking, who is this punk wearing a black jacket without the lable and acting like an expert -- must be some chicken MFY fans doesn't dare to wear their pinestripe Jerseys. Theo was standing right next to me for like 15 mins. I looked at this face, he looked really familiar, but I just could not remember who he was. After processing though all the hotties database, I just realized he was THE ONE, THE ONLY, THE HOTTEST DUDE in bean town: young, SUPER HANDSOME, educated, and he's Red Sox's GM! Plus, he got the chance going to Schilling's place during thanksgiving and wash their dishes! How HOT could that be!     MmmmMmmm... THAT'S my man. :)      As soon as I realize who he was, he got into the field and walking into the GREEN MONSTER.      =(           
     

    
</post>


<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       當初的故事，寫到了上一篇就停了下來。 這些文字一直儲存在我的電腦當中，偶爾拿出來翻一翻重新回味。  我覺得自己真的是幸運的，故事中的男主角 -- 南勳   他真的很愛我....  我之前對於自己 being judgemental over Korean people 不了解其中的原因， 但是我開始瞭解自己對於這段感情的無奈，因為國籍不同的無奈。 其實，我一直很嫉妒韓國女生，因為他們有著我永遠無法擁有的東西：韓國國籍  曾經，我是他在世界上最珍愛的人，他願意為了我放棄任何的一切，但是我不能就這樣讓他放棄自己的前途跟家庭。他也曾是我世界的全部，但是他愛我，所以他解除我桎梏住自己的枷鎖，放我飛向屬於我的天空--因為他瞭解我，他知道我是天空中的翔鷹，而不是願意關在籠子裡面的白文鳥。   我不知道他在世界的哪一個角落，但是我真心的祝福他。 因為他，我可以坦然的跟人說： Yes, I have been loved, deeply been loved.      
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       話說我跟 Namhoon  因為沒有地方待，只能寄宿在 Maggie 她     的公寓，雖然 Maggie 並沒有給我啥好臉色看，但是有個棲身     之處、最愛的人又在身邊，我已別無所求了。                                                                              由於房子是新的，裡面所有的家具都沒有，就連廚房都陽春到     只有一個冰箱、流理臺、一個附烤箱的美式瓦斯爐....           看到我跟我男朋友兩個人，不知道是我們兩個太幸福了，還是     她對 Namhoon念念不忘，只要我們三個人在一起，她就會跑過     來把我摟得緊緊的（Namhoon 根本不讓她碰他）；當然，我的     他看在眼中，非常的不是滋味，我跟他好不容易可以在一起，     望著眼前的我，他卻連我的手也牽不到....雖然如此，我跟       Namhoon 也盡量順著她的意思去做，只希望不要冷落到她。                                                                  每次出去外面吃飯，總是去吃她想要吃的；而她，總是拉著我     男友，講著一些我不懂的『柏克萊術語』，往往，她拉著他講     她的，我只能坐在一邊保持沈默，而他，總是偷偷的在桌子下，   把我的手握的緊緊的，不敢讓她發現....她總是喜歡去韓國餐     廳，要 Namhoon幫她點他覺得最好吃的東西，而我，不但看不     懂韓文，對於用英文寫的韓國菜單更是一點 idea 也沒有，看    著他辛苦的應付著 Maggie 不甚合理的請求，我除了心疼，還    是心疼；雖然自己往往被冷落，也不忍心苛責他。這樣一頓飯    下來，吃掉的錢並不算少，而他，除了要付我們兩個人的錢以    外，也要付她的份....                                                                                                她在幾個月前吧，被男友拋棄，一個 caltech的大陸人。她被    甩的原因，是因為她根本不讓她男友碰她，連牽手她都她都覺    得太親密了....她總是喜歡在我不在時，問我男朋友跟如何才    能讓男孩子覺得她 sexy & hot ，如何去交男朋友，還要求他    教她談戀愛所需要知道的『技巧』。                                                                                    一晚，她硬是要 Namhoon  寫信去給她的前任男友，說服他回    到她身邊（雖然我男友根本不知道那個男的是何方神聖）....    我男友答應了，但是她卻要求要他當場在她面前發 e-mail 給    那男的；他為難的看了看我，我點了點頭，也想幫幫她的忙....  就這樣，我跟他合力寫了一封我倆都覺得不錯的信，沒想到，    信還沒寄出去，她很不高興的把所有東西 delete 掉、甩了頭，  走回她房間，並且很大力的把門帶上....大家都知道她真正不    高興的原因....                                                                                                      善體人意的他，起身要去安慰她，同時徵求我的同意。拜託！    他是我的男朋友耶，為什麼要這樣委屈自己，讓自己的男朋友      去安慰其他的女人？可是，我也不忍心就這樣放她一個人躲在      房間裡面難過，我有 namhoon在我身邊，已經很幸福了！          於是，我拿了盒衛生紙給他，要他帶進去....                                                                                他一進去那房間，我就後悔了....他去安慰別的女人，那誰又      來安慰我？那女人會不會藉這個機會想把他佔為己有？想著想      著，難過到只能抱著棉被哭....十幾分鐘，就像十幾個小時一      樣難熬；當房間的門一打開，我看到面無表情的他，立刻衝到      我身邊，把我抱的緊緊的，告訴我他好想我，心裡面全是我....    我雖然心疼自己，更心疼我的他。緊抓著身旁的他，我告訴自      己，絕對不會讓你再去安慰其他人了....                                                                                                                                                
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                                標題  她的告白....                                            時間  Fri Nov 27 02:39:53 1998                                來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                      ─────────────────────────────  我早就察覺她了！                                                                                                      那女人一見到我，就不給我啥好臉色看，劈頭第一句話就是：     『I was really wasting me time！』一說完，甩頭就走....     那時候，我唯一能做的，只能跟她道歉（雖然這根本不是我的     錯）。妳們一定很難想像我做出這樣的事情，低聲下氣的跟這     樣一個女人道歉；在那同時，我家 Namhoon則是想盡辦法跟她     聊天，逗她開心....                                                                                                    之後，在我跟 Namhoon  去領行李的時候，有一段時間可以獨     處，我發現事情的不對勁，便問他到底在我到達之前發生了什     麼事？原來，在我下飛機之前，她還希望，能夠把 Namhoon       搶到她身邊....原來的我，已經很疲累了，聽到這些，真的是     差一點吐血....不過那無所謂，真的！打從我一下飛機看到他，   我就知道他是我的，跑也跑不掉。趁著這個小小的空檔，跟他     依偎在一起，真的感覺到那種幸福，也覺得 Maggie 真的很可     憐，跟我們比起來....                                                                                                  他對我說，只要我們三個人在一起，他就必須要多注意，不能     讓 Maggie 有任何一點點被冷落的感覺；因為，他不希望 Maggie  對我有嫌惡的感覺....就這樣，我們三人行的日子就這樣展開。                                                              當天晚上，等到 Maggie 回房間之後，他才跟我說，當他看到     我走出登機門的時候，他真的好開心，好感動我千里迢迢從南     加州趕回來，祇是為了他....講著講著，我發現他的眼眶是紅     紅的....                                                    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                                    標題  越走越漫長....                                        時間  Fri Nov 27 01:59:35 1998                              來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                    ────────────────────────────  除了上述的難題之外，似乎所有的倒楣事都會發生在我身上....     在機場的路上，車子一路塞塞塞，塞到機場的時候已經四點多了，   我五點半的飛機，照理說在怎麼樣也是來得及....                                                                              到了機場的櫃臺，應該要 check in 了，該繳的一百塊美金罰款     也應該要交了；可是櫃臺的小姐對我說：『你怎麼把你原來的班     機改了，你下午五點半的班機已經被 canceled 掉了，如果我還     是要回去的話，只能改搭下午六點半的飛機。』                                                                                我聽到時，當場差一點昏倒....我要怎樣才能聯絡到我的他啊？     我的班機被 canceled 掉，那我的他會不會留在機場等我？想到     這邊，心裡真的是很慌亂，身上只有一個 Maggie 的電話號碼，     打電話過去，他們卻都在學校，沒有人接電話....在這個時候，     Diana 是唯一可以靠的支助....雖然心中充滿著憂慮，我還是決     定要搭六點半的飛機。我相信他會在機場等我的....                                                                            畢竟他已經找了我二十年了不是嗎？                                                                                          時間似乎越過越慢，鬧烘烘的機場，看到了許多台灣、大陸來的       觀光客，Diana 很好心的請了我喝杯 starbucks  的 Frappuccino     Mocha 冰咖啡，甜甜的喝在心裡，謝謝有這樣的一個好友總是支       持著我....望著機場航班表，當天的飛機大概有三分之一被取消       自己不禁又擔心，該不會六點半這一班飛機也被取消了吧？我那       一天雖然帶衰，也沒衰到那種程度；只是應該要六點半起飛的飛       機，硬是到了快要七點才讓我們登機。就這樣，Diana 一路下來       不停的鼓勵我、支持我，就連那個時候，也堅持陪我到最後一分       鐘，登機前她叮嚀我，要我千萬小心，如果 Namhoon  沒有在機       場出現的話，就搭飛機回去找她沒有關係....就這樣，帶著好友       的祝福，我搭上了飛機去追尋我的幸福....                                                                                                                                                       飛機上塞了滿滿的人，到了座位上，發現一個金髮小妞正翹著她       的二娘腿大剌剌的坐在我的位子；跟她講了一下，她要求要跟我       換位子（我的位子是靠窗），反正自己心裡已經煩的要死，換個       座位也無所謂；沒想到身邊坐的竟然是一個宇宙無敵超級大胖子，     小小的飛機座位被他塞的滿滿的，看了真的有點噁心....=(           只希望飛機快快起飛，趕快讓我回到他身邊。當天，『莫非定律』     在我身上真是屢試不爽，不知道啥原因，我那班臭飛機就是飛不       起來，等到引擎開始啟動時，早就過了八點了（我本來六點半就       可以到的）。班機取消、飛機不爽飛，升天之後又慢的像小鳥飛，     這也就算了；就連空中小姐送飲料時，也自動的把我跳過去....     :(                                                                                                                     好不容易降落在舊金山機場了，我的小心肝反而噗通噗通的跳個     不停，不知道他是不是在登機門那頭等著我....步出登機門，只     看到黑壓壓的一大群人；突然看到站在角落的他，雖然他沒有任     何表示，臉上掛了一抹微笑，一看到我，只把我手上的手提袋搶     去，拉了我就走....這時我才發現，在不遠處的座位上，坐著表     情有夠難看的 Maggie 。我立刻察覺，something happened....                                                                   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                                    標題  難題.....                                             時間  Thu Nov 26 21:52:20 1998                              來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                    ────────────────────────────  回去找他的路，並不是那樣的好走，不但不好走，還相當的坎坷。                                                                    碰到的第一個問題，就是機票的問題。由於我在台灣的老嗎，並沒     有給我很多錢在身上，當初要到 LA 時，我買舊金山跟洛杉磯的來     回機票只要美金一百多塊，也就是說，一張機票大概只要五十塊錢。   可是因為我要回去找他，回程的時間就要提前，原來的機票也要改     期，改期還要交將近一百塊美金的罰款....原本身上已經沒啥錢了，   只好咬著牙，把身上僅存的旅行支票用掉了。Diana 也相當的有義     氣，在我去舊金山前，為了不要讓我花太多的錢，決定帶我去一些     不會很花錢的地方玩；像去海邊看加州穿 speedo 的陽光少年跟比     基尼美女，開車到處兜風....到了晚上，我們就到超市買些簡便的     食物，兩個小女生，就這樣打理每天的三餐，也算是複習以前高中     家政課吧！                                                                                                                    第二個問題：我老媽....                                         我娘在 LA 的朋友不少，之前，我媽的友人們就不停的要我去住他     們家，如果我就這樣回去找我家的 Namhoon，那我要怎樣向我爸媽     交代？更何況，我爸媽對韓國人的印象很○○ＸＸ，我根本不能讓     他們知道我在美國交了男朋友....於是，我找了我其他在 berkeley    的台灣朋友們幫忙，讓我爸媽以為我回 berkeley 是跟我其他的台     灣朋友一起，請他們放心，並且婉拒我媽朋友們的邀約....                                                                          第三個問題，也是全部最嚴重的問題：Namhoon 跟我並沒有地方住！   也就是說，當學期結束要搬離宿舍時，他根本就沒有地方住，那也     就是為什麼當他送我到機場之後，就跟我失去聯絡的最主要原因。     不過，之後他就先寄宿在一個朋友的公寓裡。他的那個朋友，我也     認識，台灣人，是個女生，Maggie....而且，很喜歡我的 Namhoon....                                                                那個女生的公寓，非常的貴，一個月大概要七百多塊美金，而且是     好不容易才找到的；由於公寓很貴，而且蠻大的，我男友就暫時住     在客廳，，幫她分攤一半的房租，同時也幫忙她搬家（她暑假時也     跟我們一樣住在宿舍）。由於公寓是新租的，還沒有接電話線，也     無法上網路....附近由於是住宅區，要找公共電話，可能要走個一     兩公里才行，交通也非常不方便....雖然高速公路就在旁邊，但是     沒車的我們也是沒輒。                                                                                                          即使我到了舊金山機場，接機也是一個很大的問題....               Namhoon 必須拜託 Maggie 開車送他到機場接我。當然，對我而言，   想到自己的男朋友，跟另一個女人住在一起，雖然他睡客廳、Maggie   睡寢室，心裡那股濃濃的醋意還是酸的讓自己吃不消....              開玩笑，我漂漂海牛的男朋友怎可淪落到這種地步，說什麼我也要    『宣布主權』，讓那女的一點機會也沒有....=(                                                                                  就這樣，換帖的 Diana  開著那台十幾歲的二手車，送我到了到處    挖的坑坑疤疤的洛杉磯機場，and i am on my way to my love....                                                                  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                                    標題  Diana's answer machine                                時間  Thu Nov 26 02:59:00 1998                              來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                    ────────────────────────────  暑假在 LA 的日子，真的能用一個『難』字形容......   一到當地，就立刻跟他失去了聯絡，心裡真的很怕，怕   他就像斷了線的風箏一般，永遠也沒辦法回到我身邊...  更怕我們的關係，就像我以前所謂的 summer fever 一   樣，來得快，去得更快。第二天晚上，終於，在電話答   錄機上聽到了他的留言....（美國的答錄機，你可以在   別的地方打電話回家 and check your message ）                                                          當我一聽到他的留言，眼淚就像決堤一般流個不停，因   為我發現我錯了，我不應該懷疑他，應該對我們兩個有   信心才對。當天晚上，善體人意的 Diana  立刻決定，   第二天就帶我回到她 Irvine 的公寓，只為了要讓我接   到他的電話。在那兩天，真可以說是我長這麼大以來最   焦慮不安的 48 小時。在那段時間之中，自己幾乎只能   用『行屍走肉』來形容我。那時候，根本不知道什麼較   快樂，強烈的相思與寂寞充斥著，伴隨的是莫名其妙的   眼淚。                                                                                                當我接到他電話的一剎那，我笑了，同時相思的眼淚又     不爭氣的滴了下來。他說想我想到快要瘋掉了，而我，     一邊哭一邊跟他說我要回去找他....只要我在美國，就     應該要跟他在一起，他也一邊哽咽的要我趕快回到他身     邊。                                                                                                      可是實際上，要我回柏克萊找他，真的是很難。或許是     被愛沖昏頭了吧，我也不知哪裡來的勇氣，毅然決然的     決定回去找他。                                                                                             
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                                    標題  離別的第一天....                                      時間  Thu Nov 12 02:12:34 1998                              來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                    ─────────────────────────────────  剛下飛機，眼眶還紅紅的我，真的是非常的懊悔，嫌嫌沒事      幹嘛飛到 LA 過著寄人籬下的日子，同時還得忍受相思之苦....  一下飛機，我立刻做了決定，只要他開口，我一定立刻飛回      他的身邊；只要我在美國一天，我就想黏在他身邊....                                                                    到了機場，Diana 還沒有出現，大概還在塞車的路上吧？        孤單的站在人來人往的洛杉磯機場，心裡，想的全是他：不      知道他現在好不好？回到宿舍了沒？會不會在回去的路上就暈倒了？                                                                                                            心裡面千頭萬續，不如直接打電話到宿舍去找他....            電話響了幾聲之後，他的室友接起電話；他，還沒回到宿舍....  心裡一急，也是無能為力，一邊擔心他那還未交出去的報告，    也擔心他的安危....只能交代他的室友要好好照顧他，並且      幫他處理一下搬家的事情....                                                                等到 Diana來接我時，已經是一個多小時之後的事情了。        他很開心的帶我到處晃，還帶我去很高級的電影院看了『 The Mask of Zorro 』。愛電影的我，在戲院當中幾度落淚，   不是電影令人感動，是因為我心中只有他一個人....           思念他的情緒已經淹沒了我整個腦海，眼前的每一個景象，     都會讓我想起他....                                                                                                看完電影之後，本來要去 Diana 在 UC Irvine 附近的公寓，   可是她臨時決定要回到 upland 的家；而我，當然只能跟著     她走....雖然我留給我家南勳的，是我們在 Irvine 的電話     號碼。當晚，我在 upland 焦急的很，深怕他打電話找不到     我；我們也 check  過了 Irvine 公寓的電話答錄機，他也     沒有留下任何 message，email也一封都沒有收到....          我不禁擔心：他是不是就這樣不要我了？！                                                                              
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                                  標題  短暫的離別                                          時間  Sat Nov  7 22:44:36 1998                            來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                  ───────────────────────────  從正式決定跟他在一起，到暑期課程結束大概只剩兩個禮拜，        期末報告截止前，他陪我讀書，甚至幫我改我 paper的文法，        而他的 paper呢？ he didn't care that much 因為他覺得我        在他生命中，才是最重要的  =)                                  可是對於大一到現在，在柏克萊成績 straight A 的他來說，        要他拿一個 B，簡直比登天還難....                                                                                            由於在學期的最後一天，我必須到 LA 去找我高中同學 (Diana)      機票很久以前就買好了，要呆在我同學那邊兩個禮拜，而那天，      也是他 paper  的 due day，可是他大概還有一半尚未為完成。      前一晚，他跟我說，他會在天亮之前寫完，並且送我去機場。        眼看著要來接我去機場的車子已到了宿舍門口，他還在掙扎猶        豫要不要送我去機場，當場我一氣，踢了他一腳，並且問他：        Which one is more important, me or that god damn paper？                                                                    他毫不猶豫的推了我上車，並且把門關上。你覺得他有沒有上車咧？                                                                  嗯....當然是有的啦！  =)                                         在車上，我不禁有點後悔，硬是要他多陪我去機場的那幾個小時。      對於他整夜沒睡，心裡更是心疼....他對我說，他也狠想早一          點完成他的 paper，可是整個晚上，他心裡想的都是我，滿腦          子都是我，面對著螢幕，一個字都榨不出來....                                                                                      由於開車的司機，是我在美國的老闆，所以我們都是用筆談的....      怕被我老闆聽到，我們會不好意思  =P                              我一面心疼他的累，一邊也想質問他為什麼剛剛不決定送我去機場？    他告訴我，他希望我能夠在去機場的路上睡一下（因為我前一          晚整理行李，也是整夜沒睡）。很好笑吧！不過，我知道他是說        真的，依他疼我的程度....他寧願自己很辛苦很辛苦，也不希          望我不快樂。                                                                                                                    到了機場，匆匆跟老闆到聲謝，便跟親愛的他，拎著我的行囊去        check in。由於他整夜沒睡，整個人很虛弱，加上身上又沒錢，        我急忙在機場點了些食物，強迫他吃下去，順便把身上的旅行換        成現金，塞了 20 塊美金給他，怕他沒錢要走路回去....                                                                              不知為何，時間過得特別快，馬上就到登機的時間了。我，一直        抱著他，哭著跟他說我不要去 LA 了，而他，只能輕輕的摸著我        的頭，要我去 LA 之後，開心的玩，不要想他，have a good time....  雖然他的眼睛當時也是紅紅的，抱我也是抱的緊緊的  =~~~             最後，航空公司的登機門關上了（就是要飛了的意思啦！），他           一急，就跑去跟櫃臺說他的女朋友還在這邊（當時我已經哭的跟           tweety bird 一樣了），於是，我就成了那班飛機上，最後一個           登機的乘客。當然啦！一上機，飛機就馬上啟動引擎，離我那親           愛的越來越遠....                                                                                                                      在去機場的路上，他寫下一段話給我，並且要我上了飛機之後才           看。我噙著眼淚，打開我的背包，看到了這一段文字：                                                                                       Daisy:                                                                                                                                  Remember that our story is just beginning, and we're not        saying goodbye.                                                                                                                          Let's make memories in which both of us realize the secret         of what is really important in Life.  Like you said, I am          always yours -- just one flight away too--                                                                                               Looking at the sky will bring me back the thought of you        --- although things will never be the same without you.                                                                                  I love you & see you soon                                                                                            Namhoon  南勳                                                                                                                                         ------                                                                                                                                                                                                看完之後，我不禁哭得更大聲（也沒有很大聲啦，只是被旁邊的老太太發現而以）。機上的空中小姐，問我是不是需要幫忙？而我，只是點點頭，跟胖胖的聯合航空空姐要了些衛生紙。她就給了我一大疊....                                                                                                               
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                            標題  告白....                                      時間  Sat Nov  7 21:37:21 1998                      來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                            ────────────────────────────  快樂的時間總是過得特別快，當天晚上我還有一個 party  要參加，       由於是另一個好朋友的生日宴會，他也不認識，所以他也不能陪我去。     眼看著時間就要到了，匆匆喝完 unfinished 的義大利汽水，             一面跟他漫步於傍晚的柏克萊陽光下....                                                                                                  回到宿舍（他跟我住同一棟樓），朋友們早就動身去 party了，只留       下一個地址，要我速速前往。宿舍的餐廳馬上就要關了，他也不顧自       己有沒有錢吃晚飯（宿舍餐廳的飯前包括在宿舍費裡，不吃白不吃），     在加上他那天錢包裡面已經沒錢（他差一點連剛剛 italian soda 的       錢都付不出來），可是他依然堅持要送我去開 party的那個餐聽，理       由只因為，他不希望我一個孤獨的走在柏克萊嬉擾的路上....              在路上，一直很想牽著他的手，一路跟著他，有種前所未有的安全感.                                                                     到了目的地，望著他，我一點都不想踏進去；他不想讓我孤獨的一路       走來，我又何嘗希望他孤單的走回宿舍？在 party上，所有的朋友都       看的出來我心中的幸福....=)  整個晚上，心裡想的全是他....                                                                              當晚，我高中同學 Diana  和她朋友從 LA 開車上 berkeley 找我，       這是許久之前就預計好的，所以 party一結束，我必須先把我同學安      頓好，帶她們到處晃晃，陪他們聊天....現在想想，對她們真的是有      點抱歉，因為當初，心裡面只有他，無論我在做什麼事情.....      actually, it's still the same right now, even during the exam....                                                                   好不容易，我同學累了想休息，我趁機跑去找他，希望他還沒睡著.    那一個晚上，他跟我說他什麼東西都沒吃，想吃也吃不下，因為沒心情. 當天晚上，我們就到外面的交誼廳聊天，聊些啥我已將完全不記得了， 而且，當晚我們就決定在一起了；雖然應該要告白，我們卻什麼也沒說，很自然，一切就是那樣自然的發生了....                                                                                    但隨之而來的，是一連串的驚嚇。他把他過去的一切，通通告訴我，      對於他的坦承，我真的是的嚇了一大跳，可是對於他的過去，我不知      道自己能不能承受。但是，愛就愛了吧！                                                                                                誰說愛是需要理由的，他以前在感情生活中曾經浪蕩過，那又如何？      那是因為我還沒出現在他的生命當中。                                                                                                  而今，有我的出現，我想，他也應該會定下來了....                                                                                        
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                              標題  第一次的驥動......                              時間  Sat Nov  7 19:15:42 1998                        來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                              ──────────────────────────────  那天在 computer center  打著 american study 的報告, 恰巧, 不知道是不是故意的, 向來慣用 pc 的他,                       居然跑到我旁邊的那台 MAC, 在我身邊用著那台不聽話的蘋果....                                                                          說也奇怪, 就在那個時候, berkeley 連外的網路全部不通,             整個學校都是這樣喔....望著動也不動的電腦, 我跟他便聊了起來....    我跟他之前就認識了, 只是一直沒有機會深入了解對方,                 結果一聊, 就深深的被他吸引, 望著他 netscape 的前一個畫面,         網址是在哈佛, 瞄了一眼, 上面有他的名字, 再一看,                   原來那個網址是全美大學生的物理競試, 而他是全美第七名....          (他成績這樣好,為啥我現在這麼笨 :(   )                                                                   過了幾天, 我們就出去約會了....雖然說是約會, 也只不過              是一起去 coffee shop  喝杯 italian soda,  我最愛的                peach + lime flavor                                   約會的內容, 曾被我美國的室友罵過 "白爛" 我們有一半的              時間在討論原子跟粒子的繞核運動, 還有宇宙擴張論....                很不錯吧!                                                          不知道為什麼, 跟他在一起, 他總是給我一種很輕鬆, 很自在的感覺.... 當時, 我在 Strada Coffee shop 用了很多的餐巾紙,  and i told him i really like napkins..... 根據他現在的說法, 他就是從那個時候開始愛上我的  =)                                                                            不過我們還沒在一起就是了....                                           
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (南勳在我心)                              標題  when will i see you again?                      時間  Mon Nov  2 18:58:23 1998                        來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                              ─────────────────────────  真的好想不顧一切，買張機票飛到他身邊，                                  讓他養我一輩子......                                                                                                                            今天他哭著問我, when will I see you again？                             講到我們兩個人都只能抱著電話流眼淚....                                                                                                          以前聽過一個台大的女生，為了她的男朋友，放棄了 MIT的入學許可，因為她說：『生命中沒有 MIT固然很可惜，但是沒有他，生命就太乏味了....』                                                                                                                現在，真的是沒有讀書的心情.....                                         那種整個人不是自己的感覺，唉.....要怎麼說咧？                                                                                                   就像我曾經對嘉淇說過：錢用光了，可以再賺；學分被當了，還可以再重修；但是，如果我這樣就讓他從我生命當中消失，我永遠永遠都不會原諒我自己！                                                                        很多事情，都可以重來；對於這一段感情....真的....                        雖然我們的爸媽都反對，而且又相隔了半個地球，                     我們依舊堅持要走這一條路；因為這是我們唯一的路....                                                             Hmm...講一講心裡的話，去讀一點書好了.....                   總不能每一科都被當，即使被當，也要有五十分咧！                                                                           
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (吃泡菜戒電影)                          標題  睡很少                                        時間  Thu Oct 15 04:32:30 1998                      來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                            ─────────────────────────────  三點的時候我家憶青還沒睡，叫我趕快去睡覺....                  那時的我，正在打著鍵盤跟地球另外一端的他， 靠著那一個一個打出來的英文字母，告訴他今天發生的事.... 講了一個小時，越講越想他.... 兩年，還有兩年我才可以長久的跟他在一起。                                                                                  下午的時候，居然收到了美國那邊學校的 admission form，        想起上週回家跟爸媽討論著要不要就此放棄交大的時候，           看著年紀越來越大的父母，第一次覺得他們真的老了......                                                                      我永遠記得爸爸當初對我說的話：『我們就只有你一個女兒，       對你也真的沒什麼要求，只希望你未來的日子能夠過得快樂。       今天，他們真的真的很不放心讓我一個人隻身去找他，而放棄       了我現有的一切....爸爸媽媽只希望你能夠在我們身邊待這最       後的兩年；如果兩年之後你們兩個還在一起，我們也會很高興       你們兩個有很好的結果....』                                                                                                有這樣的爸媽、我家的 Namhoon、還有許多身邊關心我的人....     現在才發現自己其實是很幸福的。                                                                                        有時常常在想，自己那麼辛苦是為了什麼？                     看看周遭為我付出那麼多的人，就算在怎樣辛苦，也不及他們     的千萬分之一......快樂過我的每一天，也就是他們最大的喜     悅吧！                                                                                                                清晨四點半，所有的一切都是值得的....                        
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       作者  Daisy (吃泡菜戒電影)                               標題  二十歲的感言....                                               時間  Thu Oct  8 23:29:07 1998                                       來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                             ──────────────────────────────── 首先，先謝謝婉婷的蛋糕，還有她那郭口黏的學妹....                                                                                           二十歲了，是個該替自己負責的年齡，（想想，年底就可以投票了....）    人過了二十歲，就已經不再是青少年了，以前，我們做錯許多事情，都可以以自己年紀還小當作擋箭牌，以後，無論在法律上，人情世故上，都必須以一個大人的角度來面對所有的問題....                          過了二十個年頭，到底我學到了些什麼，我又得到了些什麼？             生命當中一項順遂的我，無論是求學、讀書、或是各個方面，都有貴人相助，使我能夠從小學 → 明星國中 → 北一女 → 交大。這一路順遂的走過，從未絆倒過的我，根本不知道什麼叫『失敗』，也正因為沒有失敗過，自己並不知道到底我要的是什麼？                                                                       1998年，對我來說是絕對不平凡的一年；我在這一年即將邁入二十歲，行使第一次公民投票權，生命中第一次被當，第一次如此接近死亡邊緣，第一次出面控訴他人，第一次申請學校被拒......太多太多的第一次，發生在這短短的 365天....                                                                                                                 因為自己上學期被當，導致父母親的不諒解，甚至到全盤的不信任，想來也可笑，自己都二十歲了，要不要讀書還要父母在後面拿著藤條逼嗎？自己活該吧！以前總是站在金字塔頂端的我，也會有跌下來的一天......                                                                              認識他算是我這一年當中相當幸運的事情吧！                                  對他，我只有四個字：『無怨無悔』....生命當中，從未真正渴求過什麼，唯有他，真正激起我對人生的熱情。那種真真切切的感覺，以及回國時那種錐心刺骨的痛，自己以為從來沒有機會瞭解過。跟他分開之後，雖然天天寫信、打電話，但是一種『似乎缺少了什麼』的感覺，卻不時的襲上心頭。為了別讓自己想太多，我決定要以書本和他填滿我的生命....可是每當自己在夜闌人靜時寫著報告，那種思念他的孤寂感一來，自己就寂寞的掉眼淚.... 往往用長途電話跟在地球另一半的他哭訴，而他，就在電話另一頭陪我一起掉眼淚....             唉，現在心裡真的很煩很煩，『化學』這條路，似乎走錯了......                相較於他在課業上面的表現，我不禁反觀我的大學生活，在這過去的兩年裡面，我究竟學到了些什麼？摸摸良心，我回答不出個所以然....大部分的學分是拿到了，可是大部分的東西，卻似乎沒有學到。教授上課上的不是很好，分數打的頗低，出席率低，平常看書時間少......這種種都是學不好的原因之一....  唉呀！越唸越煩，明天還要烤高分子.....煩哪....                                                                                                  發發牢騷吧！不要理我....                                                  I am no teenager anymore...  :(  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        作者  toto (                       )                      標題  海牛...                                                                 時間  Mon Mar 23 23:37:35 1998                                                來源  交大應化 ─ 蔚藍海                                                     ─────────────────────────────                                                                                  送妳兩段話...                                                                                                                                               If someone's success makes you slight,                                        uneasy, or critical, examine what's behind                                      you reaction. You are not diminished when                                      others succeed. Your life is not a                                             competition with them.                                                                                                                                                                                                                    If your dreams fall apart, sweep up the                                        pieces and save them. Sliver of hope can                                       be found in the debris of shattered dreams.                                                                                                                                                                                             ==  六年過後再度看到這篇文章 心中的感觸特別深刻吧..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       這個是我三個月之前寫的，今天特別翻了出來，把他正式放在這邊。   昨天不知道哪裡來的勇氣以及機會，我把心裡面所有的想法告訴他：就像我跟他認識的方法一樣，我用IM完成了這項任務。  I love him: and I love him so much that I don't want to let him down. But I did, and I screwed up this time.  第一次自己那麼坦承那麼赤裸的面對自己愛的人，我一點防備的能力也沒有； 但是我有主的關照，家人與摯友的關懷來治療我這個受傷的心。  昨天過後，這場夢應該算是結束了吧！宣綺，妳也該醒醒了....     再會了  我的葡萄牙情人  早在許久之前，早在我發現你的缺點之時，  我已經愛上了你.....   但是，隨之而來的，是一波又一波對你感情的依賴與眷戀。  我這艘小小的船，在驚濤駭浪中總是險些被吞噬，  我努力的克服困難駛向你，冒著翻船的危險，一次又一次的前進，  但你始終無法給我一個在愛情海中的停泊港。   由今天簡短的對話，我更瞭解你了。  你心中早已擠滿了你所有的權力、慾望與自己的享樂；  渺小如我，也無法在你那自以為寬闊的港灣找到一個小小的空間。  我想，我依然是愛你的。  我不怨你、我也不恨你，但是我知道自己得在船沈沒之前把你忘掉。  就把過去的幾個月當作是一場夢吧，只是一場淒美的夢。   今天晚上，我決定要擁抱悲傷，  但是當早晨太陽出現之時，我將會去尋找另外一個屬於我的港口。    再會了，我的葡萄牙情人！  也許  在看到紅襪隊比賽的的時候會想到同是襪迷的你  也許  在聽 Chicane Saltwater  時會想起你閃爍的綠眼睛  也許  在吃rice pudding的時候會想起你那光滑柔細的額頭  也許  在經過康州的時候會有想要衝去 Stamford 找你的衝動    But after all, it's just a dream:  it started after ALCS 2003, and ended after the first Red Sox Game 2004.  It's a dream I would never forget,  but a dream I am trying to forget.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       就是剛剛....  我的 Verizon 手機叮叮噹噹的響個不停 checking my caller ID, 看來是用電話卡打的，本來以為是老媽繼續打電話來囉唆。 機械式的接起電話喊了一聲 hello....  對方是個男生 過了五秒鐘之後，才發現那個是我再也熟悉不過的聲音了  韓國人從韓國打了個越洋電話給我 是那麼熟悉的聲音、清柔的語調，聽了聽他的聲音，他還是一樣沒有變。  他曾經對我說過，他絕對不會變....    兩年多過了，他的確沒變，但是我卻已經變了。 我還是一樣討厭 Lee Sang Ah，那個從高中就對他死纏爛打的韓國妹，聽南勳說他們兩個在交往，我也一點都不意外，只是直覺告訴我，他們兩個不合適。聽起南勳講到 Sang Ah，他似乎一點開心的感覺都沒有，他甚至還跟我說 they would not work out....   (我覺得我會這麼一般性的討厭韓國女生，Lee Sang Ah應該是很主要的原因。)  我太瞭解他了 即使兩年完全沒聯絡，我還是這世界上最瞭解他的人。After talking to him for just 2 minutes, I could tell 他一點都不快樂.....  講了將近一個小時，彷彿回到了以前跟他遠距離的日子。可是，我的心早就不在他的身上了：一部份給了葡萄牙人，另外一部份早就已經死了.....    掛上電話，我對他的那份感情也 100% 的放了下來；我家上演的韓劇，也總算可以劃上句點了。    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>