<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      TELSTRA IP PLATFORM EVOLUTION is an infrastructure project aimed at consolidating and extending Telstra’s Australian market leadership in the provision of IP services, through continued technology leadership and excellence.  As Telstra moves into a new era of IP Solutions, where applications such as IP based Telephony, Conferencing and Messaging are expected to emerge into “prime time”, the continued evolution of our IP platform infrastructure is fundamental to ensuring our customers continue to be provided the best possible IP solution experience both within Australia, and globally.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There are two types of DSL access into IPWAN:  1. Dynamic Access 2. Fixed Access  Dynamic access currently uses ADSL in the local access network and consistent with the above naming, each session requires authentication/logging on.   The data throughput characteristics of dynamic DSL services are based upon customer sessions "contending" for bandwidth with variable throughput based upon the degree of contention at any particular point in time.  Telstra examples of this type of service:  - Big Pond Broadband - Hyperconnect - Telstra Wholesale Layer 2 ADSL - Telstra Wholesale Layer 3 ADSL - IPWAN/ADSL - Connect IP DSL  Fixed access currently uses G.SHDSL in the local access network with each service provided a fixed connection via a virtual circuit.  The data throughout characteristics are analogous to FR/ATM in that each circuit connection has a committed data throughput rate (CIR) and a burst, non committed component (Excess Information Rate/EIR).  Telstra examples of this type of service:  - Business DSL - IPWAN/Bus DSL - Connect IP Business DSL 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello young&nbsp;Sarah, Yesterdays Hero's&nbsp;ten tips for skiing survival are as follows (in no particular order of importance).  &nbsp;  Many are bad weather tips which I think is important, storms even hit the lower slopes hard sometimes.&nbsp;   1.&nbsp;Glossary of Terms:  &nbsp;  On-Piste: Skiing on groomed runs  Off-Piste: Skiing outside of groomed areas (not recommended and over-rated)  Post-Piste: From lift close to sleep, ie. 4.30pm to 4.30am  Pre-Piste: Wakeup to lift opening  T-Bar: Unnatural looking lift and typically the hardest to ride, you put the lift behind your deriere and ski uphill. Chairs are easier.  Thredbo Fiver: $50 note (This will become clear when you buy food)  Schuss: Ski or snowboard with elegance  &nbsp;  2. There is no such things as: i) Weather too bad to ski in, ii) A hangover too bad to ski with,&nbsp;iii)&nbsp;A gay ski instructor&nbsp;  &nbsp;  3. Always have a  second pair of gloves . Wet hands are uncomfortable and although it does not get really cold in Australia, chilled hands can get a bit nasty.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  4.  Always wear goggles  and never take them off when on-piste to de-fog/clean, they will get worse. The best way to defog is to schuss off somewhere and let those cute little holes at the top of the visor do their stuff (and give you an icecream headache at the same time).&nbsp;  &nbsp;  5. When you pull up for lunch,  put your gloves near a heater if there is one . Do not do this with your socks as these little babies really get smelly. even after a couple of hours.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  6. Eat pasta, sausages and/or sauerkraut.  Avoid Pies .&nbsp;Try not to drink alcohol until afternoon stop where I suggest either a gluwein or  my favourite,   Jagermeister with a beer chaser . The&nbsp;"Yogi" is a great warmer/heartstarter and gives you some "Euro cred" in the drinks stakes whilst all the other ponces drink Peppermint Schnapps.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  7. When you get back to the lodge, have a maximum two beers.  Never have three beers  as the combination of willing men offering to massage your feet, a warm fire and sleep inducing alcohol&nbsp;may mean you do not leave the lodge. Whatever you do, leave the lodge, the nightlife is fabulous and always better than staying at the lodge where the two beer party animals end up in bed by 9pm.  &nbsp;  8.&nbsp; Get lessons , preferably early. Its a real hassle to get down the hill to a 11.30am lesson and you get hungry. 9am lessons are great with the instructor also getting you to the front of the lift lines which can be long first thing.  &nbsp;  Ask the instructor how to get on and off the lift (there are no stupid questions, particularly when you start off).&nbsp;I have never snowboarded but T-Bar lifts look hard. If you have to get a T-Bar, get on with an experienced boarder/skiier,  not another beginner .  &nbsp;  9.  Ski with someone . If you have to ski alone, stay to groomed runs and keep the solo stuff for good weather conditions only. Bad weather can hit the low slopes and I have seen people run into&nbsp;trees only 100metres from the bottom  &nbsp;  If you get hurt or lost, stay where you and if you can, plant your board standing up in the snow above where you are. If on groomed runs, someone should be there in a second. If lost off piste, plant the board and stay where you are for at least 10mins to see if anyone comes. The ski patrol do a run last run of the day and generally look around for stranded&nbsp;skiers. If on piste, you will have no problems here.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  10. If you are on a chairlift and it stops,  do not jump off , no matter how close it looks, I have seen broken legs from this.  &nbsp;  11.  Stick with it , your first lesson will focus on how to get up, the second on how to stop. You will wonder what all the fuss is about but try not to pull the pin early, as the stories&nbsp;are told post piste, you will wish you stuck it out  &nbsp;  Have a great time Sarah, my tips are not meant to be negative/scary, just helpful. Remember to phone a friend if you get stuck.    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>