<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      right now i feel like im gonna SCREAM!!! and i have no idea why or how i came to feel this way.. but i am extremely close to just getting up and leaving my house and just taking a very long walk... possibly to south hill.. or penn yan.. i just dont feel like beaing at my house right now.. and i dont wanna come back.. and i cant stop shaking and its freaking me out.. i just feel super pissed off..for no reason..and i wanna just get out of this place!!! i havent had ANYTHING today.... no sugar, no caffeine... nothing  and im gonna try to stay in my house before i go and do sumthing very stupid...  mood: AHHHHHHHH!!!!! music: the crazy voices inside my head telling me to leave!!
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yea..today was very slow, but it wasnt too dull... i woke up and slumped around the house for a while, then i called heather and we were talkin about nothing (being the random ADD victims that we are) lol, and we somehow got on the subject of what the "nickelodeon slime" was made out of..and she said it was pudding?..anyway i havent had pudding before so i went to her house and we made pudding..and we were eating it..and got bored...and then she said it looked like a frog..............riiight...anyway, ignoring heather's issues, (just kiddin bud!) we saw the domino's guy pull up in the parking lot right below her balcony..so we obviously tried to cover his car in pudding..but we didnt really have much luck, so we covered the walls in pudding instead, and then we stuck paper to them. as u can tell...me and heather have problems..but thats alright b/c with our constant rambling about random subject, we never have a dull moment!  u remind me of the babe....what babe? the babe with the power....what power? the power of voodoo....who do? you do....do what? remind me of the babe!  mood: completely stupid (and random!) music: weezer-the sweater song
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HAVE SERIOUS THRILL ISSUES!  heh heh heh heh...im soo hyper right now and very tired (once again) because i got up at 6 am this mornin to go to darien lake and i just got back at 10! but it was fun becuase i did the bungee freefall thing with marcy and this really cute guy ;-) and i rode the superman 4 times....and it broke down cuz somebody dropped a camera into the chain! and the guy in front of me in line looked EXACTLY like jesus! (no shit)and it was really funny but since i am really delirious right now, thats all im gonna post..so g'night to all mood: spaced out music: in the shadows-(all thanks to tuck!)
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow... it is early in the morning..(for me) and im feelin emo, lol, so bear with me..  over the past 3 or 4 days I've been to numerous parties, slept over at numerous houses..(with barely any sleep) and completely abused caffeine substances till they no longer work for me...and yet i continue to go to bonfires and parties..why?..Because its summer and i promised myself that i would have a fun time ---promise..broken--- right now im feeling extremely depressed..(but nothing sum music wont help me fix) and listening to muse, and basically anything that will just make me zone out so i dont have to think about shit.   i finally realized a few nights ago at a friends' house...that nobody really knows me at all..they only know what they see..and what they interpret from my actions..but nobody watches all the time..and nobody can see my all the time..and they only know maybe 1/10 of the real me...and i think that is what im so stressed about...but im trying to fix that..and so far, not much luck, except ive made a few new friends on the way, and i feel that they will (hopefully) stick by me for a while.  music:AFI-silver and cold mood:'frozen in time'
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      howdy to all!.. ok..today i actually have to get off my lazy ass and do sumthing...  a-find sum money b-try to find a way to get to ranks and get strawberry milk and jolt for danilelle...::dont ask:: c-uh..i forgot what 'c' was supposed to be...but ill just say that its to find a ride to "dylan's" house.  im feeling kinda hyper today....and im listening to one of my favorite bands in the whole wide world!..DAFT PUNK!..and if u have never heard them...u definately need to stop what u r doing right now and go listen to them on launch.com or albinoblacksheep.com or sumthing! one of the greatest songs from them-'around the world'..and 'work it'! yea so better get a start on those 'goals' that i hafta do...(cuz everyone knows how lazy i am!) --off to find $!--
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        friday, feburary 23, the year 2034 at 9:00 pm at tom wahl's    BE THERE or prepare to feel my wrath.  today i have been not as lazy as i thought i would be. i went to heathers to watch the butterfly effect for about 2 hours.... (and i didnt even get to see the ending!!) and then her mom gave me a ride home....scary scary-lol    and then i sat around the house randomly watching tv and making more brownies.. oh yea .. i actually cleaned up my downstairs living room (obviously for "sucking-up" purposes)  mood: crazy music: DADA- blue girl  
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          this or that?     music or books:  music     family or love:  love     im's or calls or talking in person:  IM's     news or music videos:  music videos     MTV or Fuse:  fuse     VH1 or MTV2:  mtv2     writing or drawing:  drawing     talking or listening:  listening     shy or loud:  shy     long life or long love:  long life     cats or dogs:  dogs     rap or rock:  rock     sleep or awake:  awake     close or far:  close      Bands: this or that     yellowcard or bright eyes:  yellowcard     something corporate or lostprophets:  something corporate     blink 182 or green day:  green day     rancid or suicide machines:  suicide machines     rufio or thrice:  thrice     senses fail or story of the year:  story of the year     the early november or the starting line:  the starting line     brand new or taking back sunday:  taking back sunday     new found glory or good charlotte:  NFG     mxpx or allister:  mxpx     mest or matchbook romance:  matchbook romance     fall out boy or dynamite boy:  fallout boy     the used or the ataris:  ataris!     simple plan or gob:  simple plan     motion city soundtrack or sugarcult:  sugarcult     dropkick murpheys or flogging molly:  dropkick murphys      in guys (or girls)     blue eyes or brown eyes:  blue eyes     brown hair or blonde hair:  dont matter     short hair or long hair:  short     smile or frown:  smile     intelligence or popularity:  intelligence     rap or rock:  rock     great smile or pretty eyes:  a smile can brighten anyone's day     tall or short:  taller than me obviously     school sports or just sports:  just sports     fat or skinny or average:  average     outgoing or shy:  outgoing     writes or talks:  talks      anything     sky or grass:  grass     full or empty:  full     blank or too full:  blank     days or months:  days     concerts or plays:  concerts     coffee or cappichino:  coffee     vanilla or chocolate:  chocolate     7 or 13:  13     livejournal or insanejournal:  insanejournal?     now or the future:  now     past or future:  past     trees or flowers:  trees     roses or carnations:  carnations dont have thorns     cars or trucks:  cars     stars or stripes:  stars     pen or pencil:  pencil     marker or colored pencils:  colored pencil..for texture     seeing or hearing:  seeing     smiling or grinning:  smiling     dancing or singing:  dancing     ice cream or candy:  ice cream     roller coasters or water rides:  roller coasters     guitar or bass:  guitar     drums or bass:  drums     drums or guitar:  guitar     love or hate:  love     radio or cds:  radio     sci- fi or comedy:  comedy     home or somwhere else:  somewhere else     romance or horror:  horror     boxes or cartons:  boxes     blankets or pillows:  pillows     garbage or keepsakes:  keepsakes     bracelets or necklaces:  bracelets     earrings or rings:  rings     bath or shower:  shower     keeping thoughts in head or sharing them:  sharing them     tv or radio:  radio     tv or computer:  computer     choir or band:  band     smoking or drinking:  drinking     beer or wine:  beer     strawberry or blue berry:  blueberry     blinking or eyes wide open:  eyes wide open     forgetting memories or preserving them:  preserving them     halloween or easter:  halloween     christmas or birthday:  birthday     memorial day or labor day:  memorial day     hometown band or far out band:  hoetown band     violin or keyboard:  keyboard     left out or left behind:  left behind     you move or best friend moves:  best friend moves     town or country:  country     sitting or standing:  sitting     loving or learning:  loving      urlLink that or this  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   urlLink Get paid to take surveys!  
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Boys:  secure     Girls:  best buds     Friends:  the greatest     Love:  best feelin in the world     Farm Noises:  moo?     People Having Sex:  kinky     Bouncy Balls:  boingy boingy     Someone Lying to Your Face:  ::slap::     Getting Dumped by Someone Ugly:  oh no u didnt     Family:  fucked up..but wouldnt trade 'em     A Person Who You Didn't Really Like, But Who Commited Suicide:  damn that still sucks     A Dare to Make Out with Someone Ugly:  YOU make out with him!     Milk:  does a body good!     Your Best Friend Liking the Same Person:  i love competition     Shaving Your Legs, and Cutting Yourself:  shows im still livin     The First Song You and Your Ex Danced To:  some song by nickelback i think     A Dog Humping You:  i stay within my own species thanks     Someone Talking Behind Your Back, Who You Don't Even Know:  u talk shit... i bitch slap ya     A Scar From Cutting:  ...no comment     The Circus:  kinda boring     Touching The Face of the Person You Love:  awww     Laying Under The Stars.. By Yourself:  calming     Writing in a Notebook:  expressing my feeling best     Someone Telling You to Your Face, That It Was Over:  it sucks..but its admirable     Your Fish Dying:  toilet heaven for nemo     Your Favorite Shoes, Getting Ripped:  :'(       tear     Dancing With Your Crush, Before They Know You Like Them:  at least it isnt a 'pity favor'     Hearing Your Favorite Song:  SHUT UP..GOTTA LISTEN!     Seeing Your Favorite Movie:  SHUT UP..GOTTA WATCH!     Talking to a Really Hott Teacher:  is there extra credit?     Getting Your Driver's Permit:  hell yea..speed demon!     Hugging Your Mom After a Fight:  that'll never happen     Telling Someone, You Love Them, Without Meaning It:  i'd never do that     Hearing That a Friend Died:  here comes the suicidal thoughts...     Hearing That This Quiz is Over:  already?      urlLink What emotion comes to mind, when you hear..  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   urlLink Get paid to take surveys!  
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       friday!!!....isnt that supposed to mean that there will be excitement today? oh well.. i guess my excitement was delayed cuz i am still bored. i did get up and go to get groceries with my mom (well i was kinda forced to, or else i wouldnt have been able to go to seabreeze or the warped tour!) --short entry-- mood: devious music: DADA- blue girl  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       mood: cant complain music: THE CLASH-english civil war  alright, time for an actual entry.... today was alright.. not one of the best days but it was ok.&nbsp; everywhere i look people are having relationship problems and this is one of those times where i am thankful to be single! so far i am still lookin for someone to take to the warped tour...sorry paul :-( again..im wide awake..and barely anyone is online.. but thats alright becuase lately i have been able to be entertained.. i recently found my songs that i wrote last year, and i have been workin on a tune for them... (even tho im not having much luck) o well.. its still a work in progress  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Randomness! what would you rather be?     corn or beef?:  corn     jelly or peanut butter:  peanut butter     coke or pepsi?:  pepsi     PS2 or a DVD player?:  ps2     the ruler of antarctica or the ruler of the island tom hanks got stuck on?:  the island&nbsp;     a childs toy, or a sex toy?:  sex toy?     water coulour paints or acrylics?:  acrylics     a toothbrush or mouthwash?:  toothbrush     a tissue or a nose hair trimmer?:  tissue     infinately awake or infinately paralized:  awake     a cup or the drink?:  the drink     without friends or without money?:  without money     britney spears or dee snider?:  whats the difference?? lol     a can of tuna or a q tip?:  radio      urlLink random either or  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       True or False     TRUE is BLUE. FALSE is RED.  &nbsp;   01. I have never kissed someone of the same sex.   02. I see a therapist.   03. I'm the youngest child.   04. I am drawn to things associated with sadness.   05. I love my gauged earrings.   06. I wear black eyeliner every day.    07. I am extremely influenced by kindness.    08. I love to write, even though I think I suck at it.    09. I can't live without lipgloss.     10. I’m probably emotionally scarred.   11. I lived in Tahoe.   12. I spend money I have.    13. I'll be in college for over 4 years.   14. I love designer handbags.    15. I’ve had a concussion before.   16. I’m not good with confrontation.   17. I loved the Backstreet Boys   18. I have more than a couple horrible memories.    19. I'm addicted to Degrassi.    20. I’m spiritual… but not religious.   21. My first kiss was unexpected.   22. I start school on Jan 4th or 5th.   23. I love taking pictures.    24. I hate girls who are fake.     25. I can be mean when I want to.    26. When I allow myself to get close to people, I get very attached.  27. I am bisexual.   28. I have way too many pairs of shoes.   29. I've seen She’s All That at least 50 times.   30. I dress how I feel that day.   31. I love Charmed.   32. Sometimes I cry for almost no reason.   33. I hate when people are ridiculously late.    34. I procrastinate.  35. Winter is my favorite season.   36. I have too many clothes for my closet/dresser.&nbsp;    37. I love to sleep.    38. I wish I was smarter.    39. I believe that it is wrong to be gay. 40. I have a lot drama    41. No one really knows me.   42. I love my hair.   43. I sometimes fight with my parents.    44. I am passionate about my interests.   45. I have had the chicken pox.   46. I’m a hopeless romantic.   47. I feel empty sometimes.    48. I am/was most likely clinically depressed at a point in my life.    49. I am addicted to coffee.    50. I am very outgoing.     51. Christmas is my favorite holiday.    52. I CAN BE VERY INSECURE.   53. I don't notice it, but I'm told I'm very softspoken.    54. I hate ignorant people.     55. I love my laptop.   56. I love guys that play the guitar.    57. I state the obvious.   58. I'm a happy person.   59. I’m extremely mellow.   60. I contemplate suicide.   61. I hate cleaning my room.    62. I tend to get jealous.   63. I like to play video games.   64. I love John Mayer.   65. I get more upset when I see an animal hurt than a person.  66. I'm a vegetarian/vegan/don't eat beef.   67. I don't like to study for tests.   68. I am too forgiving.   70. I have a good sense of direction.   71. I love school.   72. I’ve played a musical instrument for more than&nbsp;4 years.  73. I tend to feel inadequate.   74. I love kisses on the forehead.    75. I love the color blue.   76. I don't sew.   77. I am not addicted to drugs.   78. I wear contacts.    79. PRESIDENT BUSH IS A COMPLETE AND UTTER MORON.  80. I become stressed easily.   81. I don't take criticism well. At all.   82. Conformity is stupid.   83. Chris Carrabba is one of the sexiest men alive.&nbsp;&nbsp;   84. So is Conor from Bright Eyes. (never seen him)   85. I love my family.    86. I don't mind getting shots.   87. I am a perfectionist when it comes to certain things.   88. I always wanted to learn to play the drums.   89. I can be too hard on myself.    90. I’m probably going to have premarital sex. 91. I don’t like my nose.  92. I am very religious.    93. I still act like a little kid.   94. I am ridiculously indecisive.   95. I believe in a higher power or some form of an afterlife.   96. I love music.   97. I’m in love.??   98. I have problems letting go of people.    99. I tend to think with my heart more than my head.   100. I don’t really like ice cream.  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Either Or ...     sneakers or sandals?:  sneakers     loud or quiet?:  LOUD     soft or rough?:  rough     boys or girls?:  boys     cats or dogs?:  dogs     jeans or sweats?:  jeans     tv or computer?:  computer     punk or prep?:  punk     goth or anti-label?:  anti-label     pepsi or coke?:  pepsi     market basket or stop & shop?:  stop &amp; shop     the simpsons or family guy?:  ouch...thats a tough one     shower or bath?:  shower     rain or sunshine?:  sunshine     summer or winter?:  summer     school or summer break?:  summer break     cold or hot?:  hot     chocolate or vanilla?:  chocolate     thong or granny panties?:  thong     boxers or briefs?:  boxers     kiss or hug?:  kiss     pool or ocean?:  pool     dolfins or sharks?:  dolphins     cake or pie?:  cake     make love or have sex?:  make sex and have love     dead or alive?:  dead     love or lust?:  love     prude or whore?:  wouldnt wanna be a whore...     rock or pop?:  rock     rap or r&b?:  rap     classical or country?:  country     water or milk?:  milk does a body good     bruises or cuts?:  cuts     happy or sad?:  happy     lie or truth?:  truth     silence or music?:  music     marilyn manson or mandy moore?:  marilyn manson     lick or suck?:  lick     oral sex or sex?:  uhhh     contacts or glasses?:  i have neither     radio or cd?:  cd     knives or razors?:  knives     monday or friday?:  friday     plane or train?:  plane     hyper or tired?:  hyper     pleasure or pain?:  pleasure     fast dance or slow dance?:  fast dance     rave or tea party?:  rave     fantasy or realistic?:  fantasy     horror or romance (movies)?:  horror     action or drama (movies)?:  action     phone or instant messanger?:  IM     pencil or pen?:  pen     college or high school?:  high school     pizza or pasta?:  pizza     seafood or meat?:  meat     this or that?:  that     hard candy or soft candy?:  hard     sour or sweet?:  sweet     blind or deaf?:  deaf     up or down?:  up     walk or sprint?:  walk     yes or no?:  no?     fast or slow?:  fast     rollercoaster or merry-go-round?:  rollercoaster     hello or goodbye?:  hello     big or small?:  big     skaters or thugs?:  skaters     cinnamin or mint?:  cinnamin     mom or dad?:  dad     silver or gold?:  silver     yes or no?:  didnt i already answer that     fat or skinny?:  skinny     nike or adidas?:  adidas     soda or pop?:  soda     tall or short?:  SHORT     friends or eniemies?:  friends     with tounge or without (kiss)?:  without     chevy or ford?:  chevy     sing or scream?:  scream     guitar or drums?:  drums     skimpy or covering (clothes)?:  covering..but skimpy is fun sumtimes     waterbed or springy matteress?:  waterbed!!!     health or wealth?:  health     left or right?:  right     ass or boobs?:  ass     moan or silent?:  moan     whips or chains?:  whips ;-)      urlLink This Or That ...  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today... Could've been better. That's all I have to say, I tried to dye my hair and get it the way I wanted.. But it didn't do barely anything at all. I also wanted to make brownies again today.. But there were no more. On the bright side-I did find my old songs that I wrote.. And I actually put forth some initiative to figure out the tune for them.&nbsp;   mood: awake (amazingly) music: THE CLASH-london calling   
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       alright...today i woke up....and thats it.&nbsp; okay, no big achievments there, but i did manage to stay awake at least!&nbsp;&nbsp; im partly excited because today is the last day that my hair is my normal hair color.. and then after that it will be....different..and you will just have to see it for urself.. not really anything too different.. but it will deffinately be darker.  im quite bored right now and i want to go somewhere.. but if i snuck out the only place i could go would be to heather's house.. and she would get in trouble.. so i guess im stuck at home... oh joy.  and once again im wide awake and im bored and not really depressed...but somewhat down.  mood: stagnant music: silver and cold-AFI  damnit i wish i could put smileys in here...... :-/  also i have a new sn...if u care enough and if u want it..im the one i have now  
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       again...running on empty--the cause?--> heather's house! lol, dont get me wrong... everytime i go there we have mad fun.. but again.. an all-nighter..included with sneakin out and runnin in the middle of main street in the pouring rain (and dodging cops as they patrol the area for curfew breakers!) so very very sneaky!    all i have had today to eat, included mass amounts of sugar.. and that is not good when you havent had sleep because you get depressed - and i guess that means i have had a little bit too much sugar.    right now i feel a) alone b) tired c) scattered    and obviously depressed. but since its late at night i guess i'll just have to sit in my room and have a trillion thoughts rush through my head.. (thinkin sucks)   o well..what doesnt kill me will make me stronger...   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        im still having second thoughts about the party that i might have... because if people are going to be spending the night.. and im going to invite my friends... alot of my friends dont get along with my other friends... and that it the worst position to be in. nobody should ever have to choose sides between friends... its horrible.&nbsp; that is why im thinking of just cancelling the party even before it has a set date..   i just cant figure out what to do... i cant just say "ok sorry -name-, you cant come to my party cuz certain people dont like you!"  i kno that if someone told me that i wouldnt like it very much.  mood: stuck in the middle music:fiona apple-criminal    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       cant think of a title for this entry, because i cant really think at all.... and lately i have been feeling not exactly depressed.. but definately not myself. its really confusing. ever since i came back from vacation it felt as if everything had changed.. i havent talked to the people that i once spent hours with on the phone... i havent really hung out with any of my friends since i came back.... its kinda like my luck is all gone... and i feel that nobody understands.     all i really wanna do right now is talk to some of my closest friends...(and have them get along) but everytime i call them or try to get ahold of them.. i have no luck... so i guess im just supposed to sit here in my boring house..and wait for something to happen because everytime i try to make plans.. nobody is there...   and im all by my lonesome... once again... which i guess isnt that bad...  ive gotten used to it over the years...     mood: empty..and alone music: fever for the flava-hot action cop&nbsp; &&nbsp;&nbsp; sweetness-jimmy eat world  
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       today was fun...i was in my pjs still.... and i slept till noon (or around then.) only because i stayed up until 6am..the i had to get off cuz my step-dad was waking up.  and right now i am EXTREMELY and utterly bored.... so i am watching fuse (which is the greatest station in the world-might i add!) and i am talkin to select few people online.. (meaning heather and mike) :-P  so since i cant think of anything else to say.. ill just leave you to have fun and read the rest of my journal..since nobody really reads it anyone.  
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          you bored?:  yup     Name?:  shortshit     Age?:  15     DOB?:  9-29-88     Fav color?:  pink     movie?:  save the last dance     song?:  either "volcano-damien rice" or "not like the other girls-rasmus"     Band?:  the rasmus and green day     food?:  mostly anythin but seafood     whos your fav person?:  gotta say sausage     would you spend your life with them if you could?:  maybe     would you do anything for that person?:  uhmm...maybe not anything lol     do you think your in love with that person?:  i gotta love him..but not in love with him hahaha...     what song would you sing to that person?:  "im my life" - the rasmus     would you really embarrass your self for them?:  i do that anyways haha     suicide good or bad?:  bad     money?:  i have none     poetry?:  i write sum     do you like jokes?:  i have a great sense of humor     are you a joke?:  i am a joker* at sum time..but not a joke     do you think your ugly?:  no     do you love being ugly?:  im not ugly     do you love yourself?:  im deffinatly not self absorbed!     you like drugs?:  no     smoke?:  no     drink?:  uh..no comment?     rock on party hard or peace &amp; love?:  HELL YEAH!!!      urlLink death by self &amp; love  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Bands Vs Bands      Pick the best, dir dir     Nirvana or Blind Melon:  blind melon     Bad Religion or Dead Kennedys:  bad religion     AFI or Story of the year:  ouch..i love both     Pennywise or Bad Religion:  bad religion     Sex pistols or The Clash:  CLASH     Strokes or Vines:  vines     Slipknot or hatebreed:  hatebreed     Disturbed or KoRn:  disturbed     Van Halen or Led Zeppelin:  ZEPPELIN!     Alice in Chains or Pearl Jam:  pearl jam     Hootie and the Blowfish or Goo goo Dolls:  hootie and the blowfish     R.E.M or Smashing Pumpkins:  uhh...i like both..but prolly R.E.M.     The Cure or David Bowie:  the cure     Guttermouth or NoFx:  guttermouth     Soundgarden or Audioslave:  soundgarden     powerman 5000 or Adema:  ADMEA BABY     NIN or Orgy:  orgy     3 doors down or 3 days grace:  3 doors down     Sublime or No Doubt:  no doubt     Wheatus or Distorted penguins:  wheatus     Good Charlotte or Simple Plan:  simple plan     Rancid or Pulley:  rancid     Staind or Filter:  staind     the distillers or death by stero:  the distillers     dropkick murphys or transplants:  dropkick murphys     seether or evenscene:  evanesence...but i like a lil seether too     cold or coldplay:  coldplay     Greenday or Blink-182:  green day     papa roach or drowning pool:  drowning pool     Metallica or Limp bizkit:  metallica     a perfect circle or Tool:  tool     stone sour or godsmack:  godsmack     The Casualties or The Misfits:  the misfits     Brand New or Yellowcard:  yellowcard     The Ramones or The Doors:  doors!     Millencolin or Tiger Army:  tiger army     Lagwagon or Less Than Jake:  less than jake     Maroon 5 or New Found Glory:  NFG     Anthrax or dimmu borgir:  anthrax     Ac/Dc or KISS:  even tho i have a tongue like gene simmons..im goin with AC/DC&nbsp; lol     Journey or Eagles:  eagles     Something Corporate or Dashboard Confessionals:  dashboard confessional     all american rejects or alien ant farm:  all american rejects      urlLink Bands Vs Bands/  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           *Write the first thing that you think of when you see the word.*      It can be anything: people, items, views, stories, etc.     Thunder:  clap     Pop:  rocks     Rock:  and roll!     Sweet:  DUDE!     Bliss:  miss bliss was a bitch     Kiss:  me     Finger:  I HAVE 10!     Figure:  go figure     Me:  spunky     Love:  is seen as just a word..but not to me     Sex:  id think it would be fun...but i wouldnt know :-D     Male:  willy the one-eyed wonder worm!....jk     Amphibian:  horny-toed lizard? idk      .:Tell the world how you really feel:.     What is love?:  love is when u dread the moments that u are away from the person u love     Can it really be shared?:  of course     Is sex love?:  no...its a pleasure..u dont need to have sex to show love     Is it bliss?:  sure     How does it make you feel to love?:  amazing     Can it be undone?:  i guess...     Have you ever felt it?:  all the time...just on differnt levels     Is love regrettable?:  no      urlLink .:Love:.  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          A:  acrobat     B:  basketball     C:  cool friends of mine     D:  dork!     E:  evanescance     F:  fuck off     G:  grace!     H:  howdy!     I:  i love eveyone and enyone..just depends how much     J:  just kidding..means nuthing     K:  kicking is fun..but not me anymore     L:  luscious lexi! i L-L-L- LOVE YA!     M:  mooo     N:  nobody knows the real me     O:  only cool people are losers..     P:  plt!     Q:  quilt?     R:  railroad tracks are fun to walk on     S:  SHORTSHIT!     T:  tucker fucker!     U:  umbrellas!...mine was broken :-(     V:  va-va-va-va-vulnerable!     W:  walker!!...also known as "sausage"     X:  xavier is not a common name     Y:  "Y" can mean 'lick my clit' --right lex?? lol     Z:  zooma ...wtf     #:  my number? 3965878! haha      urlLink Songs A-Z  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           a n g e r&nbsp; section.     do you have a quick temper?:  not usually     what do you do when you're mad?:  flip out&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; hehe     what's the worst thing you've done when you were mad?:  broke the garage windows     if you can take back time, would you have never done this?:  no...i cut my hand     ever made anyone cry when you were mad?:  no     ever psyhically hurt someone when you were mad?:  yes     do you curse when you're mad?:  o yea      c r y i n g&nbsp; section.     when was the last time you really cried your heart out?:  a few days ago     ever cried yourself to sleep?:  yup     ever cried on your friend's shoulder?:  no... they usually arent there when i need them     ever cried over the opposite sex?:  yea...what a waste     do you cry when you get an injury?:  not usually     do certain songs make you cry?&nbsp; which ones.:  yes...sum rasmus songs     can you make yourself cry?:  if i think really hard about sum stuff      p a i n&nbsp; section.     what's the hardest thing you've ever had to go through?:  moving from house to house..and a divorce     what's the worst thing you've done to yourself?:  cut     what's the worst thing you've done to somenbody else?:  punched them     ever had a painful break up?:  no     what about the old 'pain for pleasure'?:  sometimes     how depressed can you get?:  u dont wanna kno     do you inflict pain on yourself?:  i dont feel the pain      h a p p y&nbsp; section.     are you normally a happy person?:  yes     what can make you happy?:  my friends     do you wish you were happier?:  yes..but with my friends..i cant get any happier     what makes you the happiest?:  being with all my friends and none of them fight     is being happy overrated?:  of course not     what about being with your friends, does that make you happy?:  well DUH!     can music make you happy?:  yes      l o v e&nbsp; section.     how many times have you had your heart broken?:  not that many     do you still have feelings for any of your old significant others?:  no     have you ever loved someone so much, that you'd die for them?:  yes     did you ever love a guy, tell them that, and only got 'thanks' as a reply?:  yes     ever loved someone so much, it hurt and made you cry?:  yes     has anyone besides your friends and family ever said 'i love you' to you?:  not even my friends to that :-(     ever stopped a relationship because they didn't say 'i love you'?:  no      h a t e&nbsp; section.     who do you actually hate?:  i dont hate anyone anymore..i strongly dislike     ever made a hit list?:  yes..i still have it     have you ever been on a hit list?:  not that i know of     are you a mean bully?:  i hope not     do you hate any one that breaks your heart?:  no     do you hate George Bush?:  i change that first hate question...yes i hate george!     George Bush is so overrated...:  idk bout that...but he sure is a dumbass      s e l f - e s t e e m&nbsp; section.     is your self-esteem extremely low?:  not anymore     do you believe in yourself?:  yes     when people say they think you are pretty, do you deny you are?:  i dont think i am..but its nice that they think that     are you one of those idiots that think they are ugly, dumb, and fat?:  no     ever wanted to kill yourself because you thought you weren't good enough?:  i did..     are you happy with who are you?:  i am now     do you wish you can be someone else?:  if i did.. its only for a day      urlLink an emotion survey.  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          do you cry to your music?:  yes     have promise rings?:  no     Like the think rimmed black glasses?:  yes     black hair?:  yes     dressy shirts?:  yes     favorite song?:  not like the other girls-the rasmus!     write sad poems?:  yes     Have had your heart broken?:  yes     are you over it yet?:  yes     do think everyone is out to make your like depressing?:  no     straight edge?:       tough or weak?:  tough      one or the other...     dashboard confessional or thursday?:  dashboard confessional     single or taken?:  single     black or white?:  im white....but i love 'em both!     pink or purple?:  now..pink.....purple is old     fight with your boyfriend or fight with your best friend?:  fights make friends stronger     fight with your mom or fight with your dad?:  mom...i never fight with my daddy     acceptace or rejected?:  rejected..but thats fine with me     peace or violence?:  peace     knife or gun?:  knife-my friends kno what i mean     short hair long hair?:  short      opposite sex...     have a boyfriend/girlfriend?:  dont have one     would you do anything for them?:  if i did.. i prolly might     do you love them?:  i love 99% of the ppl i know     were you friends first?:       what do you love most about them?:        movies and music...     see the butterfly effect?:  nope     did you like it?:  how would i kno     did Courtney Love kill Kurt?:  deffinately!..shes such a ditz     what was he to you?:  quiet..but an amazing artist...he was too good for her     ever like the grunge?:  of course     still do?:  yea     like The GOONIES?:  ONE EYED WILLY!!!&nbsp;     who is worse, britney or christina?:  britney...christina is not a ditz-really     have a idol?:  yes..but i am a leader...not a follower     who is it?:  my daddy      life sucks, right?....     hate the radio?:  i love the radio...and it loves me..sumtimes     wear alot of bracelets?:  hell yea     parents hate your music?:  yup     think your pointless sometimes?:  sumtimes     ever think about commiting suicide?:  o yea     who or what holds you back if so?:  my friends     feel pressured?:  i used to     school sucks?:  besides the social life..yes     wish all the people there would die?:  of course not      ender..     think life will get better?:  life can always get better     is music always there?:  all the time     have friends?:  if i didnt.. i wouldnt be here     have a family?:  yea.. i love the redneck side more tho     believe in god..or a higher being?:  i guess u could say that     believe in the devil?:  i do for fun&nbsp;     would you give up anything to stay who you are?:  yes     don't change...life does suck but if you stay who you are,you will be fine:  i believe that...but many ppl dont      urlLink emo  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       omg it feels amazing to be back home! i have been so depressed since i left.. even though i usually enjoy being in texas.. it wasnt the same this time..&nbsp; the whole family is running around and everything is hectic, my cousins marriage is falling apart :-(&nbsp; and i didnt get to see everybody.. but the important thing is that i am home and i am happy now. and i can definately say that i wont be flying for a while... the first plane was cancelled (after sitting 6 hours in the airport) then we had to stay at a hotel in syracuse and leave at 3 am for a 7am flight.. (that was delayed) then we had to go to newark.. where the pilot was missing...which also happened at detroit...except..the whole crew was in baltimore...  so we had to wait 3 hours for the crew to get there.. then the pilot got airsick (go figure) and then.. we had to circle the rochester airport because the airforce guard was there and it was closed...(goddamn government)  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY! its raingin sooo hard at my house..and baker park is completely flooded..again.. and later all im going to do is run around town and jump in puddles! haha.. call me crazy but i dont care.. cuz its fun.. and if u think im weird for it.. then u should try it urself.. its GREAT! yea well i gotta go find a really big puddle! :-D
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow.. i havent posted in a while.. but i think i needed a lil break.. over the last few days.. i noticed that i havent been acting quite like myself.. and now i realize that this summer has helped me re-evaluate who i am.  and from now on, im going to stop trying, to be 'myself' because i found out that, to become the  true  me.. i dont need to try, and i guess that was what i was afriad of.. if my friends would be scared of the  'real'  me, since all they have seen, is what i believe to be the true me, but it wasnt.  from now on.. im going to show my  true  colors, wether anyone likes them or not.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      over the weekend i went to south hill for camping and a 3 day-long party. also 2 shoeboxes full of fireworks! (anyone can obviously say that i had fun over the weekend!)  and i got to see my whole disfuntional family (oo fun...) and i found out my cousin is 6 months pregnant.. and shes.. i think a year and a half younger than me.. (which i think is hilarious.. because me and my dad were betting on what age she would get knocked up..{which is horrible i know..but soo much fun!} and i was closer..i guess 15..my dad guessed 17) and i won about 20 dollars! heh heh heh!  but other than the psycho freaks that are actually dangling form my lightning-struck family tree.. it was fun.  i also brought home the tent.. so over the summer theres gonna be BLASH some night!!! hahaha  mood: hyper music: devil in jersey city-coheed and cambria
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok..im home alone.. and i have brand new speakers... and i figured out how to work my music player... (evil laugh) muah ha ha ha ha ha! yea.. so basically everyone on my block can hear my music.. and the soccer players in baker park are dancing and its very funny.. and also today want very good for me.. i got bitched at by someone elses mom.. (dont ask) and i went to ppl's houses and they ditched me      :-(    not cool. so ive been sitting here just waiting for something to happen.. or someone to just randomly visit my house.. (HASNT HAPPENED YET!) GRR.. yea.. im frustrated  mood: frustrated... and extremely bored music: hoobastank-out of control
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yea... my mom and steve's anniversary today.. (big whoop!) sure im happy for them.... kinda.. but all it means to me is that i have the whole day off since they will be gone to dinner and all that fun stuff.. so i could go set the town ablaze and they'd have no idea.. but thats the fun part! :-D yea.. and as of last night.. i can add another tally mark to the list of mental breakdowns.. i have no idea what its from.. but im determined to find out, and also thanks a ton heather for bein there! i dunno what i wouldve done.. at least i got to talk to someone (face to face and not on the retarded computer) but thanks for that.. and i also listened to that one song...it helped! lol  mood: awake...ish music: take me out-franz ferdinand
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       today started out as a pretty fun day..... i was with sarah palmer...and then i was hangin with alli and dan.... anway....things came up... and certain plans were broken...then more things came up...and as of now... my summer is now a piece of shit.... all i truly want right now... is someone to just be here with me and tell me that everything will be alright and that i will be okay....    unfortunately, i dont have anyone that lives close enough that could do that at the moment...and that might be the reason why i am not okay right now...  all i want right now is just to feel normal....and not like some freak that needs to be watched over as if i am some psycho killer  honestly..........i just wanna cry  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        mood: sad music: memory-sugarcult  i got back from heather's house, once again. and even though we didnt sneak out, we didnt meet anyone, and we didnt burn anything (at least this time around)...we still manage to act like total rejects. and i enjoy every minute of it! there are too many random and inside jokes that i probably wouldnt be able to fit them all in here. when i came back from the fun time at heather's... (i am never bored at ur house bud! lol)...i got some news...that i wasnt so thrilled to get, but there's nothing i can do about it. my friend -nameless- apparently ditched me to go to someone's house (who they dont like) to see their significant other. and it is a big deal to me at least.. because they dropped out of plans that we had for a long long time...and now it is too late to fix it--at least they could give me some notice!--but this person made a 'deal' with their parental...that if they went to 'so-and-so's house..that they would give up the plans they made with me...and i didnt know this.         ..................UNFAIR!                i know for a fact that if i did that to them...i would be bitched at and a fight would emerge and i wouldnt hear the end of it....but since i just dont care anymore...im just not going to say anything...because in the last few days, even though it hasnt REALLY seemed it--i have other friends that like me for who i am...and dont get mad at me when i dont act how they want me to act. and i realized this and i am thankful. so to those who know who i am talking about...those friends who wont leave my side......thank you and i love you.   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        oooookay... This weekend was not the most exciting, but at least I had something to do: -find paint for my room -move ALL the furniture in my room and CLEAN IT! (amazingly) -went to the arts festival on the lakefront-which was awesome by the way -visit deranged family on South Hill-they should be on jerry Springer! -and last, bowling!-(lowest score buys lunch!)  and not to mention repeating conversations on how corrupt and evil my uncle is and how the whole family hates him...And amazingly-my dad actually and finally told me that he had been hiding his pot addiction--even the I already knew about it before he moved. Now he says hes clean and im hoping that he doesn't start up again--as for my cousin, I hope he can get his act together before his girlfriend wakes up and realizes that she's second compared to his addiction.  im still tryin to figure out a date for the party...cuz it has (once again) been cancelled cuz barely anyone can go--so now im just waiting for the warped tour, and then maybe after that ill find a nice day to camp and throw it then... i still might have a few friends over on the 13th just for fun tho... (whats the worst thing that could happen? ::wink::)  mood: mischievous (heh heh heh) music: A Perfect Circle- 'weak and powerless'   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        today was pretty fun, i didnt just sit at home again, i got paint for my room (yay) and i also got together wit heather! SHE'S MY CHEESEBOIGER! lol. anyway we were bored so we made a cult--and we are now randominians..and we study the ways of randomism with all the other random people.....[yes, it is screwed up, just dont ask questions] anyway.. we started to recruit people to be randominian and in order to convert, they have to stand in pudding..and drink mountain dew which is being poured off of a balcony into their mouths.  and to convert people me and heather (the leaders) fly to peoples windows and throw pudding cups at them-(as opposed to the mormons walking door to door giving out pamphlets and reading from their bibles). and we are still deciding on this.. but our "god" is going to be Tyson....(the lead singer of the All American Rejects-for anyone who is clueless about who that is) so far we have 3 people willing to convert..and one person who is a randominian in practice (R.I.P.)  not to mention the speedy bike ride (in the rain) to pauls house. and runnin around his giant house with him, pat and heather....for the record...this kid has the hugest house that i have even seen.....and that is ALOT of places to hide when you dont wanna get caught!!  ::wink wink cough cough nudge nudge:: u kno wat im talkin about! lol     mood: dorky, slutty music: pretty girl (the way)-sugarcult   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       once again i spent another fun-filled night at heathers, which ended up with sneaking out (like we have done everytime so far..) and walking around the block and in the middle of main street in PJ's. amazing times! even though there was no mountain dew or sugar-filled kool-aid... we managed to stay up for while.. then we actually slept! (that's a first!!!) did i mention throwing burning pencils off the balcony? that was amazing.       ::sigh:: never a dull moment on heather's balcony!!! ;-)      mood: renewed music: sugarcult-pretty girl (  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           >:  shortshit      >:  american?      >:  i wish i could travel back in time      >:  bahamas      >:  uh...no clue      >:  yes      >:  yes      >:  yes      >:  kinda      >:  alt. rock and punk rock      >:  maybe...      >:  yes      >:  a few      >:  kinda      urlLink Cemetary Spirits  brought to you by  urlLink BZOINK!   urlLink  EmotionDump   - 100% Anonymous Emotions and Confessions  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       **HAVE YOU EVER...** Cussed someone out: o yea Thought about suicide: yup Stayed up for 24 hours: more than that Gotten drunk: mmhmm Gone a day w/out eating: prolly Talked on the phone all night: hell yea Been in bed w/the opposite sex: no Smoked: no Made prank calls: hehe yes Been in love: yes Slept all day: yes Killed someone: ...............no? ;-) Been out of the country: yes Told a guy/girl you loved them: yes If yes, did you mean it?: yes Ever gone skinny dipping: yes Kissed someone you didn't know: yea Thought you were going crazy: were? Eatened someone: no Done anything sexual with a member of the same sex: no Asked out a member of the opposite sex: yes   Four things you can't live without: 1. my friends 2. my health 3. my music 4. my dad   Four things that never fail to cheer you up: 1. my friends 2. music 3. dances 4. parties   Five tv shows you liked when you were a little kid: 1. gary the happy pirate 2. power rangers (the old shows...not the new shitty version) 3. salute your shorts 4. doug 5. hey dude   5 songs people should give a listen to: 1. volcano-by Damien Rice 2. blue girl- by DADA 3. anything by green day 4. kennedy-by Kill Hannah 5. gotta say ozzy osbourne  
    
</post>


</Blog>