<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently a friend of mine had come back to his native land from his stay abroad for the first time. He landed down at Trivandrum airport. When he reached out he saw a queue of beggars standing in perfect order receiving the travelers.&nbsp; My friend after searching for long found a ‘2’ rupee coin and dropped it in for one of them. Shot came the reply  “Sir, don’t you have a dirham”.  On visual scanning my friend finds that the plate in the beggar’s procession only had cents, pennies, fils…….in them. Yo! that is display at the POS!!!   My friend says he was surprised on the awareness these people had…….. they knew the flight schedule, the currencies on float in those countries and&nbsp; of course the exchange rates…….What would we call that - &nbsp;market awareness / targeting / demographic knowledge?   There is something here to learn from, for all the management students &amp; practicing managers………..   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Banks  borrow money and lend it to the needful. The spread between the borrowing and lending rates is their income. Of course there are other revenue generating businesses that banks cater to.   “Borrow money”  – The public entrusts the surplus cash with them to the banks locking it into different products that have varying liquidity. In return, expects interest income for the deposits. This is the  liability  side of the bank – the bank has to repay on demand.   “Lend”  – The bank finds customers and appraise their credit worthiness to give loans to them. This is the  asset  side.   ONE:  We have GTB on whom moratorium was declared by the RBI  and it had created concerns amongst the public who have their deposits with the bank. What would we say? – that the bank was careless in lending to the markets and failed in its risk management. What would have happened if the merger with Oriental Bank of Comm. was not put forward by RBI and had the bank went bankrupt? Depositors would get max. one lakh per account in one name by way insurance. Above that money would have just vanished. Earnings of years of hard work down the drains. The result……. Protests, agitations, suicides and what not…….. We should be happy that did not happen due to the intervention of RBI.   TWO:  We see borrowers across the country committing suicides because they are not able to repay the loans taken. We also see cases of suicide just because banks denied loans. The result….. politicians and social interest groups asking the debts to be written off…… state govt.s asking central govt. to give concessions/relief…….  Ultimately, who would carry the losses on the balance sheet…….    In my opinion, whoever is asking to write off / give relief is setting bad example to the future borrowers…..  you borrow and then you need not pay back (this syndrome is very contagious!!!)  ….. the ultimate dream…..ha! ha! banks should be in the business of charity and not banking!!! in that case, we could be better off printing money on our own – it takes off the procedural difficulties……..   Where did the govt. fail?  (1) the guidelines should have prescribed mandatory insurance for loans disbursed in socially sensitive sector. (2) the govt. should have taken the initiative to develop infrastructure in the agriculture sector uplifting it to international standards and forget about differential rates for lending to the agricultural sector. (3)instead of talking of reservations the politicians and the govt should work towards creating equal grounds for basic individual growth and the rest should be left to merit (give them the level playing field and stop discrimination)   The questions:  Do we want our banks to lend for free and in turn go bankrupt? Whom would you side with; the borrower - who cannot not repay or the depositor – whose bank shut shop?  (I express my sympathies to all affected – the families who have lost lives, the depositors who are struck up not able to withdraw and the banks who got ransacked)  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Firstly, I should keep aside my pride in being a ‘MALLU’ / ‘MALABARI’….. &nbsp;The Outlook dt. July 12, 2004 cover story had thrown light on the ‘Kerala’s shining numbers and the darkness they conceal’…….  It was very unfortunate that a student committed suicide due to the fact that she couldn’t afford her hostel fees. This incident has created havoc across the state. Student bodies who were not concerned when she did not turn up in her classes for about an year or so have raised their voices now…….. the state has declared a one week holiday for all educational institutions…….. Students by their inherent attitude should be happy……   In five days, 17 vehicles were set to fire, 30 destroyed and 39 state owned buses were ransacked…….. the agitating mob also took care of 9 Govt. offices and 14 banks….. Also people have got physically hurt…… arrests have been made…… cases were registered……If we were to estimate the damages and related losses it would run into crores of Indian Rupees. Where does this come from?   From the taxes, from insurance claims etc. Ultimately who bears the cost? The common man…… are we not destroying our own wealth in a way….. are we not becoming reasons for increase in tax rates…….. are we not boosting inflation……..   the economy has its own earning and spending cycle…….. it collects from us and spends on us……..   what is the reason for all this? Ugly self-motivated politics and politicians…….. self-centered student leaders (who want to come to the limelight)………   Some questions to the brains behind the havoc………. Have they ensured that the grants for economically backward students reach the needy and are not exploited by the mighty? While I was in college I have seen guys who come from well-to-do families claiming these benefits and enjoying.   Shouldn’t the society play a larger role in preventing all this……….they should ostracize the violence creators at the family level, at the institution level, at the social circles……   We always speak of innovation in today’s world………. Doesn’t the ALL LITERATE keralites have innovative ways to deal with such issues…….. what we need is solutions rather than more problems………  A question for thought -- What can we do to prevent ‘Kerala – God’s own Country’ turning into hell? 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FM’s revisit to the numbers on Turnover Tax was given a thumps up by the traders with the markets regaining volume. The bond traders have been fully exempt and for day traders and arbitrageurs it has been lowered to 1.5 basis points against the earlier 15 basis points. Also for trading in F &amp; O it has been reduced to one basis point.   Going forward, it should be a positive year for the Indian markets if the global cues, such as, the impending oil shock and hardening of federal rates doesn’t make considerable impact. The abolishment of tax on LTCG and with the reduction in STCG rates to 10% the capital markets are to benefit.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My dearest …  It feels like I will spent my entire life trying to forget you.&nbsp; You were my only real true love.&nbsp; The one person I loved more than anything in the world.&nbsp; There is no reason to fool myself anymore.&nbsp; I loved you from the first moment I laid eyes on you and I have ever since.   When I look back and remember how young and carefree we were, it brings a smile to my face.&nbsp; All the joy and wonder of being in love that we shared with other.&nbsp; How our lives have changed since then.&nbsp; Our lives took different directions.&nbsp; Yet after all this time, you are still my one “true” love.&nbsp; I have finally had to admit that to myself.&nbsp;   You don’t have to say anything or do anything.&nbsp; I just wanted you to know that no matter what happens in this life, I will always hold a special place for you in my heart.&nbsp; It’s true… it is better to have loved and lost, than to never to have loved at all.&nbsp; I am happy that I knew true love, for it is from that love that I have my most cherished memories.&nbsp;   From now to eternity, you’ll be in my heart every moment of every day.&nbsp; Thinking of you makes me happy and for as long as I live, I will never stop dreaming of a reunion for our two hearts.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;  This policy by Automobile manufactures has already come into being. Still I put this into words because as customers, we have been beneficiaries for some time now. Major companies have imposed this on their dealer service stations and in their authorized service centers.  &nbsp;   The   “this”   mentioned above : &nbsp;The different jobs or tasks are broken down into basic units and listed out to form an exhaustive listing of the jobs that need to done on vehicles. Against each task, the required man-hours are noted. Depending on the class of the city where the service station is located per hour wage is prescribed. So the customers are only billed for the jobs done and the customer is able to clearly see the benefit that arises out of the transparency that was not there earlier.  &nbsp;   Now the other side : Service stations bend this route when the vehicle is brought in for accident repair. Here they make an entry in the job card as just “Accident Repair” and they bill you as they wish. The ways this could be tackled are :   1.&nbsp; The customer should ask the workshop to list the tasks to perform on the job card. This of course will not be entertained by the service staff.  2.&nbsp;&nbsp; The automobile companies should give directives to the all service centers that accident repairs should also be treated at par as others by listing the jobs required. It is difficult to have job charts for denting and part-painting jobs. Maybe automobile companies can take tips from insurance companies on how they make estimates for repairs on claims to formulate such charts.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;  Products offered by insurance companies are different permutations and combinations of the basic two products, namely, the  Pure Term  and the  Pure Endowment  plans. An addition would be the pure market/ unit linked  plans.  &nbsp;  Plain facts: Firstly, in endowment products every company invests around 85% in Govt. securities and other prescribed instruments as laid down by the act. The rest 15% funds managed by the company will not be sufficient enough to make significant difference in rate of return on investments. Everybody plays in the same market and therefore every other player will mostly offer almost the same kind of returns.  &nbsp;  Secondly, the expenses of investments through insurance policies are very high. Expenses in the first year up to 40% and 7.5%, 7.5% in the succeeding years and after that up to 5% every year during the term of the policy.  &nbsp;  Thirdly, the liquidity offered is very low and in most cases is limited to the loan that can be availed limited by the surrender value.  &nbsp;  Fourth, as investments, there are mutual fund plans available suitable for every individual considering the risk he/she is willing to take. The asset management costs annually are limited to 2.5% by the regulatory body.  &nbsp;  Five, the policyholder cannot shift to other options available as the contract is normally a long one where he /she invests regularly for 10, 15, 20, 30 ……years.  &nbsp;  Market/unit linked products: &nbsp;Insurance companies have claimed providing yearly returns of 35% etc in the last year. But, what are they benchmarked against?? At the same time the BSE Sensex and NSE Nifty had given above 80%. And outperforming mutual funds had given 150%.  &nbsp;    Insurance is a MUST for every individual  . We need to be insured for at least 10 to 30 times our annual earning potential. Review your policies – does it give you adequate cover on life??&nbsp; Are you insured till the age 60? Who are we to blame? Yourselves or the Insurance advisors/agents who sells only policies that has huge premiums for short terms? Have you fallen for promises offering 10%, 12%, 15%, 20%...... returns on your investments?  &nbsp;   Don’t mix insurance and investments …………… Don’t fall prey for number games given through illustrations or sales material…………&nbsp;&nbsp; have realistic expectations……… also understand the ‘power of compounding’ before you make long term investment commitments.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Turnover tax of 0.15% suggested in the budget speech on July 8, 2004   It is well known fact the speculators and arbitrageurs provide liquidity and depth to the market. With the implementation of technology by way of online trading systems, the markets have gained volume tremendously over the years and transaction costs have come down. Today, the total brokerage per leg of transaction varies between 0.02 to 0.10% for intra-day trading for clients dealing with established broking houses. And for delivery based transactions the clients are usually charged up to 0.5%.   The traders can negotiate with his broker for a lower brokerage promising higher turnover. Usually for good traders the brokerage for day trading and derivatives is at the lower end of 0.02 to 0.03%. With the introduction of transaction tax (only for buy transactions) the expenses for the trader increases by 3.5 times to 4.75 times per leg on averaging out the tax between buy and sell transactions.   No other proposal in the budget 2004-05 has such an impact on traders dealing in any other goods and commodities markets. Unlike other trades, dealing in capital markets carries the inherent equal risk of making losses just as profits.   As the FM had asked for alternate plans, I have a suggestion:   Instead of the turnover tax, is it not better if the traders can pay another 8% of brokerage paid in addition to the 8% Service tax as turnover tax (or give it another convenient name). This way the effective increase in cost would just be 8% instead of 350% to 475% increase.   This suggestion if implemented would be acceptable to both the traders and brokers but would not result in the budgeted Rupees 3500 – 5000 Cr. collection.       
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      “In addition  to the statutaory warning, Singapore is going to put pictures of carcinogenic lungs and bleeding brains on cigarette packets to dissuade people from smoking.” consequence reminding pictures in what ever form should put off people from taking that always needed STRESS reliving puff.......  why does everybody wait for the regulatory authorities to sentence the ban, when they themselves know what is good & bad for health……  say, you spend Rs. 20 – 50 per day on smoking; annually, i.e., Rs. 7,300 – 18,250/-……. For the same amount payable as premium annually, an average healthy person aged 30 can get insured for Rs. 32 lakhs to 80 lakhs (10 year policy)…… that way at least smokers can prevent from dying in debt…….  somkers think of spending at least half the amount spend on cigar on life insurance...... (suggestion: insure for the longest term. The least you should be insured till the age of 60)   [This was initially posted as a comment for the blog ‘Who writes the statutory warnings...’written by karzarkin]
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       the GOLDEN rule in driving :- I am the king on the road, let others take the necessary precautions to prevent crashing into me........... follow this an you become a perfect driver on Indian roads......   awareness of the law is just the prerequisite for getting the driving license........ learn it.... forget it....... drive on..... the GOLDEN rule is all that is required.......   if you learn to always enjoy your drives, it is the ultimate - you have learned to harness stress......    CAUTION : applicable only to driving on Indian roads  [This was initially posted as a comment for the blog ‘Driving Through Life’ written by karzarkin] 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Extract from the Reuters report published in The Sun (UK based daily) dt. XX/XX/XXXX ......   SSS a.k.a SO-SHU-SHE SECRET SERVICE   An organized secret service agency at par with the likes of CIA, MOSSAD, Scotland Yard, KGB (extinct now) have sprung up during the last 28 years. The agency is known as SSS in international intelligence parlance. Now SSS is famous for its network across the global and is headed by the daughter of a silent scientist based in India. The agency was born on the same day as its founder chairperson.   The chairperson still wishes to remain anonymous even after the establishment has grown leaps and bounds.  The organizational hierarchy is simple with the following major functional departments: Baby Engineering, Adolescent Engineering, Teenage Engineering, Pre-production Engineering, On-production Engineering, Post-production Engineering, Baby Sitting (Post-production) Engineering, Production Preventive Maintenance/ Engineering, Production Predictive Maintenance/ Engineering, Breakdown/Abortive Maintenance/ Engineering. The different departments were floated separately as SBU’s as life stages progressed (not necessarily in the same order as listed above). Going ahead the chairperson also visualizes the new departments – Production RE-engineering, Production RE-RE-engineering…… It is reported that 90% of the revenues of SSS comes from a big separate department christened “Protective Engineering”. This dept. takes up contracts worth billions of USD from well known personalities like Lolita(herself a spy), Monica (of US white house fame), The Clintons for their daughter, Tony Blair on his wife. Name it and you find the WHO’S – WHO on SSS clientele.   In a forward looking statement the chairperson said “SSS plans to increase its revenue from the latest innovative department – The  Permission  for Production Dept. to around 50% of the total revenues so as to spread the risks associated with concentrating only on Protective Engineering. The likes of Microsoft, Oracle and IBM call this AUTHORIZATION for OPEN CODE software in their industry.  Tracing back to traditional Indian literature, permission is referred to as ‘after shaadi’.    The network has been established from the contacts that were developed, trained and retained form childhood days of the chairperson. The peculiar elderly nature of the chairperson has a charisma that has bought millions of people of the fairer sex to find a confidant in the chairperson. This is a network working beyond explanations cited by management principles or controls; a power greater than the dictators and religious leaders. “Time” magazine has devoted the last cover page to a masked face symbolizing the chairperson of SSS. It also states that person behind the mask is the most powerful individual with exorbitant control on humans with 46.7% of world population under control.   SSS contracts expire under the condition when the first party comes to “THE RIGHT SENSES”. A statement indicative of this from the chairperson: “I REALLY THANK GOD THAT THEY HAD THE RIGHT SENSES TO MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION AT THE RIGHT TIME WITHOUT MY PROTECTIVE ARM AROUND THEM”  An extended life time protection is given for a nominal fee.  The authoring of two books namely “Management of Preventive Production” and “Steps to Effective Production” published by Penguin books has been traced to anonymous chairperson of SSS. The first book was published while spending time in India on a secret mission for a rubber based roll-up product producing company. And the second one is derived from true-life experience coupled with secondary data from text books of Production Engineering. Effective “Management” skills have come up with the practice of theory in the management school campus.    Retired network agents (who were there during the text book learning period) say that the chairperson had sought help from the opposite people for practical labs to clear examinations. ‘Only experience could be gained’ since a major virus attack caused networks to crash for a short period. The cause was attributed to use of unauthorized software on hardware. After three years licensed software was purchased and implementation took place about three years before. Till date the licensed software is reported to function properly. Extreme testing measures were adhered to before purchase. Before this software was ordered SSS had full intentions for purchasing another software from a different vendor. During the finalization stage the software company backed off (as an after-effect of the bac-off, the chairperson even missed some important examinations) stating that SSS had used pirated versions before, though SSS stated in the press release that the asking rate was high. Simultaneous use of pirated software has not been reported but was suspected based on history. Past is past. Even when the world was  blind , ears were still functioning.    HELP! HELP! HELP! OOH!  AAH!  OUCH! (read Iodex adline) cried at times. And the  'crazy barbarian' (man) responded by dropping droplets of help which kept the survival of human evolution. (This para is from the yet to released ‘An Autobiography’ of the founder)   Dare not!!! SSS is a mighty force to reckon with………    [This was written for fun in replying to a mail from a classmate of mine....... Thanks SO-SHU-SHE...... This is my first blog..... My friend 'karzarkin' asked me to post it as a blog.]
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A piece of creativity
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.sebi.gov.in/Index.jsp?contentDisp=SubSection&sec_id=81&amp;sub_sec_id=81   Given is the link to a section on the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI – the capital market regulator in India) website which puts up ‘Reports for public comments’ before the guidelines are formulated based on those reports.  Here we are progressing towards a scenario where we will vote for all motions to be passed for governing the state. A step towards fulfillment of true democracy – ‘by the people’…..  I foresee a scenario wherein people also get the right to vote for ousting their elected representatives anytime before the end of their 5 year term if they are bad at their job without the high costs associated for re-elections…..that I think would be E-governance to the core…..  any suggestions? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>