<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    My pink shoez!! 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    My guera Veronyka showin me love 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Mario showin me luvin!!  

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Das My Benny Boo 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Some glamour picture i took about 3 months or so ago.. 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Das Me~!! 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Im not just a pretty face ya kno.. 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    victor kissin lani 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Das Fabian!! 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Fabian lovin Lani 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Lani givin lovin to Fabian 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    my lil cousin, me n fabian 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Victor & Lani 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Lani *again* 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Me 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Las 4 Amigas 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Elsie,Angie,Lizette,Alexa,Jazmine,Lani 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink       

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   pix of friends family special people ne one really. jus so you may know who im talkin bout. 

						
</post>


<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im not sure how i feel about Fabian. I mean i know i like him. i like him alot. but there is this thing about me i know he wont trust just because i told him that i lied to him about one thing. me n victor breaking up. i told him we broke up a while ago when we had only broken up about a week ago. but that shouldnt be a reason why he cant trust me. but yesterday he told me he really likes me too but that he is not sure if he wants to go out with me either because it'll be weird going to different schools and wondering what each other is doing. at least he was honest with me and told me that he wouldnt trust himself cuz he is really flirty (which yea he is) and that he is also a jealous person (which i already noticed about him). but he told me he would like the fact that he could call me his girl. which he already does sometimes when im with him. which i have no problem with. im single. another thing is i dont think he likes having me over at his house cuz alot of the guys over there check me out and all that. not that he's an insecure person jus jealous i guess. but he's the one im with when im over there. so he shouldnt worry which afterwards he probably doesnt...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Victor confuses me so much. He claims on how much he misses me but yet he goes out and parties all the time (all the stuff i wanted to do while we were going out. like go to juarez) and then last night he went to juarez and was in the get low contest and won. he didnt even invite me wtf.. and today he invites me. im like oh ok yea invite me when its just going to be me n you. how bout no! tonite im going with cortez and i guess i'll just have to find a place to stay the night cuz i told my mom that i was staying the night at jazmine's house. but yea so im not sure what we are doing tonite but im gonna have more fun than victor did last night. oh and he tries to tell me that he didnt dance then later tells me he was in the get low contest.. rrright. and then he tells me that he didnt drink either. i really just dont care anymore. this is another reason why i dont want to get back together with him. but whatever. it doesnt matter anymore. 
     
    
</post>


<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well well well today the plans actually went the way they were supposed to. we went to wet n wild and afterwards jus kinda kicked it. Wet n wild wasnt all that bad. we got 3 free tickets so katie only had to pay for hers but i paid for her tube and all that. OMG they had a males finest body contest!!! =0 wow haha there were 2 guys that just had my eyes locked on them. and even victor knew it but shiit i didnt care. one goes to canutillo i guess cuz david and victor knew him and he came in 2nd place and another was sum guy in blue shorts. i swear if i wasnt there with victor i soo would have gotten his number. oh yea and i saw sum punk like when we got there to the crowd and he reminded me and looked soo much like jacob my ex. i was like aaw cuz like i was there with jacob a couple of summers ago and i just thought about him. I'll call him up later on tonite. but anyways yea and i saw some people i had gone to school with in las cruces. jus saw old and new people. always the same cuties that work there. im tellin ya one day ima go with a whole buncha girls n get numbers n shiit lol. oh well one day.. but hey at least today's plans went right. afterward we went to taco bell and got food came back and ate here at my house. we dropped off katie at vanessa's house then came back to my house well stupid ass me left my keys inside lol so we had to wait for my mom n aaron to get home so they could open the door so i could give victor his money. but yea we just sat there listening to music. *memories* but yea they already left so i guess im outyz.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well last night plans got ruined AGAIN!! what else is new.. man well we were supposed to go to juarez. it was gonna be me victor david and katie. david and katie didnt go with us so victor didnt want to go. instead he wanted to go to club ice and i knew it was gonna be closed on saturday but he didnt think so so we went. and guess what... it was CLOSED. thas what i told him but whatever. so we were gonna go eat at chico's tacos but he wasnt hungry so i didnt get to eat there.. another plan ruined. so we drove to the east side and i told him to go to tinsletown so we could go see what movies were playin. well we ended up staying there and watching white chics. pretty cool movie. its actually hilarious. but yea after that i had already told my mom i was gonna stay the night at jazmine's house cuz i thought i was gonna go get drunk in juarez. so yea i had to stay at victors house so we went n picked up my medicine from my house and then we went to victors house. well victor and i both stayed in his bed but when he tried to do something with me i was strong and i told him no. im not just going to give in and all that for anyone. even victor. its just something i want to keep for myself right now. dont get me wrong.. there will be some exeptions. i know there will be cuz more than likely im gonna do it. but yea today we are supposed to go to wet n wild but now i serious doubt that we are even going to do that. cuz they cant find rene but oh well. if i dont go with victor i'll go with katie n have jus as much fun. .... damn it cortez never called last night. i wanted to go dancing with him but guess not.. i should have figured he wasnt gonna call.. he never does. well im outyz.. ยง
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yesterday i went to the mall with originaly just jacob. well it ended up being me, jakey, jeremy, chris, jei n jina. i bought one of the ruffle skirts. its black really cute from agaci 2. and then we jus kinda kicked it for a while. i saw that stupid bitch angela(lilly's friend). but i was being really really nice. i said hi to audrey and lillie. yess i did say hi to lillie. but anyways. i also saw yvette and the other angela *rene's girl*. who else did i see.. oh yea leo. he's still the coolest guy in the world. his girlfriend is really lucky. well after the mall jei came over for a while then after she got picked up cortez and ray came over. they stayed til bout 1.45 in the morning lol n then they finally left. i had to kick em out wit a broom ya know what im saying haha. nah jus playing. but idk in a way its cool being single. im going back to my old life of having all sorts of friends and going out and doing stuff with them. and having people coming to my house at all sorts of hours lol. the one thing thats back that i didnt miss.. the phone never stops ringing man!!! im like aaaaaaaaaaahhh but the same time its all good cuz i feel loved like people want to talk to Lani!! wahooO0o0. hehe well anyways thass all for now.. i'll write tomorrow or tonite. latez
     
    
</post>


</Blog>