<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm just sitting here thinking about how good God is to me. He's become a Friend to me. One that cares about every tiny detail in my life.   It still amazes me that despite all that I've done in my life, and I've done some horrible things, He still loves me and wants to call me 'friend'.   All the times I've cursed him... All the times I've cursed others... All the times I've made decisions based on my own selfish desires... All the times I've rejected Him... All the times I've ignored Him... All the times I've walked away from Him... All the times I've neglected my relationship with Him...  It's all in the past, and despite all that I've done, He wants to have a relationship with me. He loves me so much...   I never really give that enough thought, honestly. The God of the Universe... Maker of all that we see and all that we don't see... The One whose spoken words formed it all... He who transcends time, space, and everything else we don't know about... He cares enough for me, that He robed Himself in flesh, lived life as a lowly man, and died a horrible death ending on a cross suspended in mid air... for me. Not only did He do all that, He did it because my own sins required it. He took my place. I drove the nails into his hands. I am the reason He hung there...   What love... What undeserved Love!    No one shows greater love than when he lays down his life for his friends .  You are my friends  if you do what I command you. I do not call you servants anymore, because a servant does not know what his master is doing.  But I have called you friends, because I have made known to you everything that I have heard from my Father .  You have not chosen me, but I have chosen you . I have appointed you to go and produce fruit that will last, so that whatever you ask the Father in my name, he will give it to you.  ( John 15:13-16 ISV )  Thank you Jesus, for calling me Friend! I love you Lord!  
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Reymah   One of the best Christian discussion and Web-Zine sites on the net.  Run by my friend Nate (n8), and dedicated to the lifting up the Name of Jesus, and edifying His people.
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My wife, DeAuna, and I on our Wedding Day&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I figured it was time to join the rest of the world in their pursuit of blogs.   Here's my very first entry...   Blog blog blog.  Done for now.  :)  
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really have no&nbsp;affection for politics, or politicians. I love the men and women in politics, but I don't like their ways.   The DNC has been going on in Boston for a few days, and last night Kerry took the stage and delivered his 'most important speech of his life' as one news commentator mentioned. Gimme a break... he's said the same things everyone running for president has said throughout the ages. It was a yawn-fest. I'm sure I'll feel the same about W's speech coming up in the RNC, in NY. They simply say what people want to hear and change their words according to public opinion of what is 'hot' today.   Reminds me of what the scriptures say about&nbsp;'a doubleminded man'...&nbsp;he's unstable in all his ways.   Politics leaves a bad taste in my mouth.  Last night, watching the events unfold at the DNC, and seeing all those people cheering for this guy Kerry, like he was their savior or something... made me a little queezy. They're putting all their hope in this guy and he's just a man... a man who can't make up his mind where he stands or what he thinks... he'll say whatever they want to hear... whatever will get him elected.   So many 'religious' leaders throw their support behind W. I don't understand it. He's no winner either. He's got as many problems as Kerry... I can't even find an Independant that I like, not like there'd be a snowball's chance in the hot place that an Independant would ever win the Presidency...   Why... do we do that? Why do we point to a man and say "Behold... our deliverer", when he's just a man, as frail and faulted as the next guy?   They're all a mess. We're all a mess.  None of these boys and girls will ever be able to fix America's woes. Only Jesus can. Politics isn't our solution... Jesus is. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just realized it's been quite a few days since I posted my last entry. I figured I'd catch y'all up to date on the situaitons that have transpired in the past few weeks.   Saturday, the 24th of July, was a bittersweet day. I went out the the S.M.A.R.T. (Supervision and Monitoring for Alcohol-Related Treatment) Program by myself to minister out there, after a few months' absence. It'd been awhile since I went, but I had determined that after Panama, I'd start going again.   I'm glad I did. I preached about God's Love. A message entitled "You did this for me?". I didn't write it, but it said what I felt I needed to tell those folks.   Before I went, I was told one girl there, named Natisha, wanted to get baptized. So, after I preached to the men (they have segregated services), I went outside to&nbsp;baptize Natisha.&nbsp;I went over&nbsp;the meaning of baptism&nbsp;with her again, to ensure it's what she wanted to do. She was still up for it, so&nbsp;she went under the water in the name of Jesus. She came up out of the water&nbsp;weeping and thanking God. After they saw this, 4 other ladies that were gathered around to watch,&nbsp;wanted to&nbsp;get baptized as well. They'd all been coming to services and they all knew the importance of baptism, so they all went under the water, one by one. It was awesome! And it confirmed to me that I needed to start coming out regularly again.   Staruday evening, Dee and I got word that her surrogate Grandfather, Johnny Jones,&nbsp;had passed from this life and that the Funeral was Monday. We made the decision to drive to Marshall, TX to be with the family. We left Sunday morning.   The Funeral was beautiful. Sad, but beautiful. Johnny was loved so much, and although I never really knew the man all that well, it appears that he loved people as much as they loved him.   Tuesday morning, we left to come back to Austin. We drive&nbsp;US 79 most of the way, and on the way back, coming up on Rockdale, TX, our car began to make tapping noises from under the hood. I knew it was bad, but I pushed it to Round Rock (about an hour) to my mechanic. We rented a car from that point so we could make it home.   We got word yesterday that the car threw a rod, and obviously the negine needed to be replaced or rebuilt. Neither of which is an&nbsp;option since we're broke, and the amount it would cost to do either would&nbsp;be well in excess of what the car is worth.   God's in control! We're believing&nbsp;for His hand to work in the situation!   He's good...   all the time  !&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy y'all!  We got back safe and sound on the 15th. I took a few days off from Blogging to rest up and recover.  &nbsp; Today is my first day back to work and here I am ready to post a new blog. &nbsp; I guess I'll start by just saying that the trip to Panama was a big time eye-opener.  Most of those people have absolutely nothing we consider valuable. They live in cinder block buildings with tin roofs, and share their homes with the geckos and the insects.  &nbsp; Their churches are just like their homes. Spartan and very modest... and the same geckos live in their churches.  &nbsp; One thing this trip has taught me is humility... the kind of&nbsp;humility that brings gratefulness.  &nbsp; These people had nothing, but they had God so they had   Everything  . Sure it's like a sauna in their churches, but they don't care. That doesn't matter to them. They're there to worship God... not to be comfortable.  &nbsp; Imagine what we could do if we had that attitude... If nothing mattered to us, except having God and worshiping Him... imagine what could happen. 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will be my last blog entry for awhile. Tomorrow, my wife and I will be leaving Austin heading to Panama with a group of folks from our church on a missions trip.  We'll be there 'til the 15th of this month.  God bless ya! I'm looking forward to all that God has in store for us there!   If you pray, please pray for us. 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    After our vows... From left to right: Dee's Aunt, Pastor Johnson, Dee, me, and my friend Steve. &nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My wife and I while we were dating...&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Exodus 3:13-14 ESV    Then Moses said to God, "If I come to the people of Israel and say to them, 'The God of your fathers has sent me to you,' and they ask me, 'What is his name?' what shall I say to them?"  (14)  God said to Moses, "I AM WHO I AM." And he said, "Say this to the people of Israel, 'I AM has sent me to you.'"   John 8:56-59 ESV   Your father Abraham rejoiced that he would see my day. He saw it and was glad."   (57)  So the Jews said to him, "You are not yet fifty years old, and have you seen Abraham?"  (58)  Jesus said to them,  "Truly, truly, I say to you, before Abraham was,  I am ."   (59)  So they picked up stones to throw at him, but Jesus hid himself and went out of the temple.  When God called Moses to lead Israel out of Egypt, Moses didn't know His name. He just knew Him by His title, "God". When God decided to reveal His name to Moses, He chose some very interesting words...  "I am who I am"... The words used in the original Hebrew text of that account in Exodus open that statement up  well beyond  the attempt to convey it in simple English terms of "I am who I am". The phrase in Hebrew gives the picture of "I am all that I am" In other words... "I am, and always have been and always will be, whatever you need me to be. I am all sufficient, and not lacking anything. I  AM ... I exist... I live and give life." In order to make it easier for the Israelites, God simply told Moses to tell them "I AM" has sent me. That should have been enough for them to understand who God really was.  Unfortunately it wasn't. They grumbled in the desert after He led them out of Egypt through the miracle of the dry land at the bottom of the Red Sea. Many of them died in unbelief... Many of them were swallowed up by the ground, bitten by deadly snakes, killed by their enemies... all because they forgot God... Not necessarily forgot about Him, but forgot Who He was. "I AM"... "Your provider. Your God. Your Father. Your Deliverer. Your Supporter. Your Defender. Your Shelter. Your Friend. Your Helper. Your Shield. Your Rear Guard..." They forgot Who He was... Why? Because they hardened their hearts, and did not continually put themselves into remembrance of all that He had done for them.   They forgot Who He was... and because of that, they perished. None of the original generation that was brought out of Egypt by God's mighty hand was allowed to enter into the Promised Land, except Joshua and Caleb because they did not doubt God. Without remembering Who God is... We too will suffer the way they did.    In the account I posted above in John, Jesus was speaking with some folks that were  very  familiar with the  term  God used to describe Himself... "I AM". As a matter of fact, they knew the phrase so well that when He did use it in reference to Himself, they picked up stones to kill Him, as they considered it blasphemy. By using it, He was telling them that He was God in the flesh.   They knew the term "I AM", but did they know what it really meant? We know the term "I AM", but do we really believe it? Do we honestly realize what Jesus is saying by calling Himself "I AM"?   These people in John 8 also perished... Even though they were living in 'The Promised Land' that was given to them centuries earlier, they missed the True Promised Land... Of Life, and that more abundantly, because they refused to recognize who God is... They refused to hearken unto His voice. They hardened their hearts against Him and against His voice...    Let us always remember who Jesus  IS  ...and never harden ourselves to His voice! 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A tangent off the theme of yesterday is the friendship of God.   He's my friend. Think about that.  GOD , as in - ya know - "the Almighty One",  is my friend . He's my friend. He hears me when I talk to him. He listens. He not only listens, he's interested in what I say.   Think about that for a little while and let it sink into your skull. If you're like me, that can take awhile due to the thickness of the skull. Seriously, think about it. God, who set all things in motion, is my friend.   I can talk to him about anything, and he doesn't say "Sorry, I don't have time for this", or "I'm sorry, I'm too Holy to listen to your babbling, you insect" (like some of his 'children' do). We can talk to God about anything that concerns us and he's not too busy to listen. He says, "Tell me what's on your heart. Talk to me. I love you. I want you. You matter to me."  I'm not only grateful for   his   friendship, I'm also grateful for the friendship of the people he's placed in my pathway. I'm grateful to him for their friendship as well.    "Then the LORD God said, 'It is not good that the man should be alone; I will make him a helper fit for him.'"   Genesis 2:18 ESV  God made Adam in God's image to be his friend, but Adam had seen that all the animals had someone that acted like them, thought like them, looked like them, as a companion. God saw Adam's heart and knew he needed a friend too.   God gave Adam a companion. Someone like him... a friend to call his own.   God knows it's not good to be alone, so he sends us friends to love us, challenge us, make us laugh, make us cry, strengthen us when we're weak, correct us when we're wrong... all because he loves us.   He's my Daddy... and my Friend!  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm overwhelmed by a spirit of thankfulness.  I'm so thankful that the Lord is in my life. I'm so thankful that He cares for me. I'm so thankful for all of the things He's done for me, my wife and my family. I'm so thankful that He sent me to Christian Life Church. I'm so thankful for a pastor who loves God and loves people. I'm so thankful for a church that does the same, and reaches out to the hurting and the confused. I'm so thankful that God doesn't give up on me, even when I give up on myself.   I'm so thankful that Jesus came to make me free. I'm so thankful that He chooses to dwell with me and in me by His Spirit. I'm so thankful for the price He paid to win me.  Thank you, Lord... for being so good... all the time. 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep.  It's me Lord... I need to change.  I'm the problem, not the solution. I'm the one with wrong motives. I'm the one with sutff in my mind and heart that doesn't belong there. I'm the one that has to have the attitude adjustment. I'm the one in the need of prayer.  It's me, Lord... I need to change.  I'm the one that needs to get his heart right. I'm the one that has to repent. I'm the one who's gone astray... again. I'm the one that's chased rainbows instead of Righteousness. I'm the one with the pipe dream. I'm the idolater. I'm the wretch.  It's me Lord... I need to change.  Save me from myself, Jesus. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Something that bugs me a great deal is a person who finds the negative in everything and hammers it over and over again. People that tear things down and rip stuff apart all for the sake of them being right and showing the rest of us how right they are... and how wrong we are. People like that irk me...  Especially people that call themselves Christians. I'm not questioning their walk with God, but I am questioning their actions. I don't appreciate those actions...  People who thrive on contention have problems spiritually in my opinion... 
    
</post>


</Blog>