<Blog>


<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bugs is standing on Elmer's head, rubbing the hair tonic in really good with his big, rubbery bunny feet.  The hair starts to grow.  Elmer, observing developments in a hand mirror, is elated.  Petals pop forth.  No! That wasn't hair tonic, it was fertilizer! The kind that grows flowers on scalps! Now Elmer is very, very angry and reaches into the back of his shirt, where he has been keeping his musket the whole time.  How clever of him to have armed himself for his barber's appointment.  But I know what's coming.  In the next thirty seconds, Bugs will momentarily baffle him by dashing out of the scene, returning dressed as a girl (a girl bunny, though), and giving Elmer flowers and candy, thus wowing Elmer and causing him to present Bugs with a wedding ring, which in turn will inspire Bugs to don wedding regalia.  Bugs and Elmer will find a minister and say their vows, but Bugs will carry Elmer up a stairway to their honeymoon suite, which of course will not be a suite at all but just a door leading into empty space.  Bugs, lifting Elmer over the threshold, will then drop him to a nasty and violent death, which is really not very fair treatment for a guy who has just made a serious commitment to you despite the obvious hurdles involved in an interspecies marriage between a homosexual gun nut and a transvestite anthropomorphic rodent who barely know eachother, at least within the context of this cartoon.  That's marriage for you, folks.  Who needs it?
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past 2 hours I've been trying to fight off the thoughts.  The thoughts of wanting to binge again.  FUCK.  I really thought I was all recovered and I've finally lost almost all the weight from the stupid disorder but for the past week, everything's come back... I've been slightly able to fight it off though but it comes when I'm under stress... I can't think of anything wrong right now.   I probably don't even make any sense.  Something that did bother me today though was when my uncle came over.  He was like "Sarah, lose the eye makeup."  For some reason that bothered the hell out of me.  I like it, so accept it.  I just hate it when people comment on how others look.    I wish someone was at least around.  I don't like being alone right now.
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Spell your name backwards: haras *Date of birth: February 21, 1987 *Male or female?: Female *Astrological sign: Pisces *Nicknames: Hutch, Sasa *Occupation: Possibly Starbucks, CDplus or Stella's Cafe (applying to all 3 within the week) *Height: 5'9" *Hair color: Brunette *Eye color: Milk chocolate brown *Where were you born?: Winnipeg, MB, Canada  *Where do you reside now?: Winnipeg *Pets: The most adorable golden retriever ever... Chessie.  I'd also love to get a black cat. *Shoe size: 8 and a half or 9 depending on the shoe *Righty or lefty?: Usually left is the preferred one but I'm ambidextrous  Last Person Who.. *Spent the night at your house: Rhea *You shared a drink with: I honestly can't remember. I haven't for a while. *You went to the movies with: Mum and Kate to see The Terminal *You went to the mall with: Rhea and Megan *Yelled at you: No one yells at me!  Well actually probably Yemi but that's just cause her voice in general is a yell *Sent you an e-mail: Liz *Said they were going to kill you: People threaten me daily?   Friends Stuff  *Best friend(s) of the same sex: Rhea, Megan, Amia, Nessa, Kate, Tess *Best friend of the opposite sex: Sean *Person you've been friends with the longest: Katie *How many friends do you have on your buddy list?: 44  love/dating  *Have you ever been in love?: Yeah *How many people have you said "I love you" to (Besides family and friends)?: 2 *How many people have you been in love with?: 2 *Have you ever kissed someone of the same sex?: Yeah *How many people have you dated?: 7 *What do you look for in a guy/girl?: individuality, passion, creativity, hopeless romance, subtle flaws, quirks *Do you have a bf/gf?: *nods* *smiles* **What do you like most about your bf/gf?: he's very clever, passionate, and I think what I like most is that no matter what, he sticks to and stands up for his beliefs.  I really admire him for that. *Do you like someone right now?: Honestly, what do you think? *Do you believe in love at first sight?: Lust at first sight for sure but not love. *Do you remember your first love?: Yeah I do.  *Do you believe in fate?: To an extent.  I believe that the people you meet in life... you meet for a reason but it's up to you to figure out what the reason is and make things happen for yourself.  *Do you believe in soul mates?: Yeah. **If so do you believe you'll ever find yours?: *nods* *big smile*  Favorites  *Color: Bright pink and bright green *Food: Caesar salad, shapgetti =) *Song: Currently it's "Pharaoh's Daughter" by the Secret Machines *TV Show: South Park *School subject: Art & English *Radio station: Power 97 sometimes... I hardly listen to it though *Movie: Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind or The Royal Tenenbaums *Pair of shoes: My pink and black Converse sneakers *Potato chip: I don't like them at all *Drink: Vanilla coke, coke *Holiday: Christmas *Perfume/cologne: The coconut or the cocoa stuff I have from The Body Shop *Pizza topping: Veggie *Jello flavor: Not a fan of jello *Lunch meat: Chicken breast slices  *Board game: Clue, Snakes & Ladders *Cereal: Honey-nut Cheerios *Dessert: Date bars! *Disney character: Wylie Coyote *Clothing store: Le Chateau *Magazine: FILTER magazine *Salad Dressing: Ranch *Thing to do on the weekend: Movies, shopping, going to shows, driving around, hanging out *Season: Summer and/or autumn *sport: Snowboarding, running *person to talk to online: Sean   This or That   *Doughnuts/bagels: Bagels *Day/night: Night *Wicked witch of the east/wicked witch of the west: I can't stand The Wizard of Oz!  *Heaven/hell: Neither exist, thank you =P *Coffee/tea: Vanille latte  *Hamburgers/hotdogs: Hamburgers but I honestly like both *Rap/rock: Rock, for sure *Britney/Christina: Britney  *Swiss cheese/American cheese: American *Nike/Adidas: Ugh, neither *McDonalds/Taco Bell: McDonalds *Sweet/sour: Sweet *Hot/cold: Hot, I hate the cold *Winter/summer: SUMMER *Spring/fall: FALL *Operas/plays: Plays, I can't stand opera *Read/watch tv: I enjoy both *Cd's/tapes: CD's for sure *Dvd's/vhs: DVDs *Old/new: depends on what we're talking about! *Shorts/skirts: Skirts.  I hate shorts *pink/red: Pink *Colored pictures/black and white photos: Black and white usually but colored looks good for different photos... all depends *Meat/vegetables: Both, together.  *Mexican food/chinese food: Mexican! *Scary movies/comedies: Comedies, but most "scary" movies are comedies anyway *Bikinis/one piece bathing suits: Bikinis *Sandals/tennis: tennis shoes *Dogs/cats: Dogs but I like black cats *Unicorns/fairies: Unicorns *Water/land: Land *Sugar/spice: I enjoy both *Black/white: Black as in the color, we aren't talking race here *Ribbons/bows: ribbons! *Chicken/beef: chicken *Colored christmas lights/regular white xmas lights: I like white lights with green ones thrown in every so often *Cars/trucks: cars! *Austin Powers/James Bond: Austin Powers *Popcorn/pretzels: Popcorn   Have You Ever..  *Mooned anyone?: No =( *Been on a diet?: Yes, the don't eat and over-exercise one.  *Been to a foreign country?: England! *Broken a bone?: Nope but I've done many dangerous things... I'm invincible!  *Swallowed a tooth / cap / filling?: Nope *Swear at a teacher?: Yes but I don't think they could hear me *Ever gotten in a fight?: *nods* *Dated a teacher?: No =P *Laughed so hard you peed your pants?: Don't think so, lol.  I've laughed so hard I cried though *Gone skinny dipping?: Yep *Told a little white lie?: seriously, who hasn't? *Told a secret you swore not to tell: no  What were you doing.. *1 MINUTE AGO: eating fresh grapefruit pieces that mum got *1 HOUR AGO: Looking at the movie times for King Arthur on Wednesday *1 DAY AGO: getting ready to go to the gym *1 WEEK AGO: I don't remember!  *thinks hard* *1 YEAR AGO: I was in England at this point... I would have been in London right now.    Stoner Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm Sean's and he's mine.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday, I went to the Red River Ex with Amia, Megan and Rhea.  It's a big carnival/amusement park that comes every summer for about 2 weeks and the last time I went was about 6 years ago so I was really excited about it.  We went on EVERY one of the crazy rides... oh God it was fabulous.  There was this one called the Space Roller and I'm not going to try to explain this ride because I've already attempted to three times and it just doesn't work with text.  I had a hard enough time trying to explain it to my mum where I could TALK and use hand movements so this will get me nowhere.  I will just say though that it was the most insane and ridiculous ride ever and I went on it twice!  Yay.  Three things I learned while being there: 1. DO NOT buy Deluxe Candy Apples.  I bought the one with Smarties becuse hey, it looked tasty but I was very wrong.  The apple WAS somewhere deep in there but it was covered in this red, sugar candy coating stuff that was hard and plastic-like and I felt like I was trying to chew glass.  I ended up throwing it away because it was just too messy.  2. When carnies try to sweet talk you, they're really trying to just get you to pay for their game... I knew that before but last night really proved to me that.  3. I'm in love with Sam Roberts.  Hehe.  Okay not LOVE but he and his band put on such an amazing show.  He's much better live than on the album and I think that says a lot right there. Oh and look, here he is:     So all in all, it was a great day despite the horrible mosquitos and the heat.  Oh man it was hot out.  Today, I slept in till noon which was nice because I had no sleep the previous night due to my mind just not shutting up.  I'm going to make the most of these beautiful summer days before I start working, so it will include sleeping in, watching cartoons whilst I have breakfast, hanging out with people in the afternoons and possibly seeing movies as well as record shopping.  Yay!  I saw The Terminal today. The good: Tom Hanks, as always, was brilliant.  I just love him. Stanley Tucci was also good.  He's always good as the bad guy.  The bad: Catherine Zeta Jones was terrible.  I found that she and Tom Hanks had no chemistry whatsoever and her attempt at an American accent was just over the top.  The storyline was lame and didn't really go anywhere.  Overall: It sucked and isn't even worth renting.  Canada Day tomorrow!!  I'll be going to see the fireworks!  WOOH!
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Which 1990's Subculture Do You Belong To?   [Another Quiz by  Kris  @  couplandesque.net ]        Which Band Should You Be In?  by  urlLink  couplandesque        Your Name           Band Name    Blur       Role    Keyboardist      Trademark    Hating P2P File Sharing       Love Interest    The Vocalist              Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like doing current Top 5's.  BANDS/MUSICIANS 1. The Secret Machines  2. Radiohead 3. The Strokes 4. Led Zeppelin 5. Metric  SONGS  1. The Secret Machines- "Nowhere Again" 2. Sam Roberts- "Hard Road" 3. Led Zeppelin- "When the Levee Breaks" 4. The Cure- "Anniversary" 5. The Killers- "Somebody Told Me"  ALBUMS  1. The Secret Machines'  Now Here is Nowhere  2. The Honorary Title's  Anything Else but the Truth  3. The Cure's  The Cure  4. The Royal Tenenbaums  Soundtrack  5. Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind  Soundtrack   MOVIES  1. The Royal Tenenbaums 2. Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind 3. Donnie Darko 4. Dodgeball 5. South Park: The Movie  NOSTALGIA 1. My Little Pony: The Movie 2. Rainbow Brite and the Star Stealer 3. The Care Bears Movie 4. Care Bears Movie 2: A New Generation 5. The Last Unicorn  ANTICIPATED MOVIES 1. Garden State 2. Anchorman 3. King Arthur 4. Napoleon Dynamite 5. The Spongebob Squarepants Movie  ACTORS/ACTRESSES 1. Owen Wilson 2. Ben Stiller 3. Keira Knightley 4. Will Ferrell 5. Jake Gyllenhaal  BOOKS 1. Love Monkey by Kyle Smith 2. Sex, Drugs, and Cocoa Puffs: A Low Culture Manifesto by Chuck Klosterman 3. High Fidelity by Nick Hornby 4. The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger 5. Can You Keep a Secret? by Sophie Kinsella
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Secret Machines –  Now Here is Nowhere      	You know those three-or-so seconds right as you're falling asleep when you're completely oblivious to what's going on?  You don't realize you've fallen asleep until you wake up the next morning?  This is essentially what this album does.  As soon as you press the play button, it takes you on a psychedelic journey that you only realize you've been on when the last song stops.  It's like waking up suddenly when the alarm goes off in the morning.  The only difference, unlike sleep, is you can go back to the beginning right away and go again.  In other words, this is a complete mindfuck of an album.  	The Secret Machines have been compared to rock Gods: Led Zeppelin and Pink Floyd to name the main two.  While I can see some very vague similarities, there definitely aren't any that really stand out.  Pink Floyd began that "sonic landscape" sound; that haunting, progressive beauty.  And I think that if anything, TSM are similar but only in that sense.  In certain tracks, two in particular: "Leaves Are Gone" as well as "Pharaoh's Daughter", one can hear a certain quality that resembles Pink Floyd... mostly in the guitars as well as the melodic, space-out sounds.  It made me think OF Floyd but it definitely didn't make me think this IS Floyd.  There's a distinct difference.    	Track 5- "The Road Leads Where It's Led" is slightly touching-the-surface-of-Zeppelin but other than that, there are no similarities at all except possibly when vocalist Brandon Curtis sings.  His voice is't so much suggestive of Robert Plant, but rather it works a similar character in certain songs and key moments on the album.  	One thing I want to mention about this album is that it isn't exactly consistent throughout.  That's not exactly a bad thing in this case though.  While other well-known albums such as Radiohead's  Ok Computer  or Pink Floyd's  The Wall  sustain similar sounds throughout, this sounds different with each song.  I happen to love it and it definitely keeps me interested (wouldn’t normally with just any band but these guys make inconsistency perfectly all right.)	  Overall, this is an excellent album.  I can honestly say it's one of the best of the year; definitely my favorite so far and I can’t see a better album possibly coming out before the year-end.  It's such a good balance between dreamy soundscapes and at the same time, rocking you to the point where you're breathless and amazed.  These guys bring back passion and they bring back power to an age where packaged radio crap is doing so well (WHY?).   So please, dear reader, if you're into catchy drum beats, dark guitar riffs, desperate-almost-haunting and hypnotic vocals, buy  Now Here is Nowhere ...  as soon as you can.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Billy Corgan 1967-2004 says: as far as im concerned Billy Corgan 1967-2004 says: you havent died if you can remember it Billy Corgan 1967-2004 says: becuase thats just silly
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever act on your first instinct only to realize that once you can't take it back, you've made a mistake?  That's happened to me twice in the past 24 hours.  You'd think I'd learn after the first time.  I basically hurt one person that actually cared about me... only because I cared about them and for some reason, I was uncomfortable with that.  Fuck I don't even know what I'm talking about really.  My own thoughts don't make any sense to me sometimes.  The other was Aaron.  I KNOW.  It was for the best... I keep trying to tell myself that.  I couldn't just go out with him tonight because we had these plans 2 fucking months ago.  He was all upset but really, I haven't seen him in weeks, did he really expect us to go to this movie together?  He got all pissy about it but, even when we were together, he fucking FORGOT about our plans to go see Dodgeball opening day.  I don't regret telling him I wasn't going with him tonight.  I'm glad I didn't go.  I just always hate it when I upset people.  It's just the way I am.  I don't like knowing he was pissed off at me, even though I don't fucking care.   I don't even know why I'm wasting my thoughts on this.  It's stupid.  Anyway, after suffering a mind-circus with all this, I went out anyway with Kate, Megan and Rhea and we all saw King Arthur (yes, my second time) and it was just as good as when I saw it two nights ago... hehe.  I really like going to movie theatres; especially the one at Grant Park... it's so classic looking and if you go on Friday or Saturday nights, it's so crowded.  Ah, love it.  I'm not even upset about earlier anymore, I feel kind of at peace just in this moment.  I personally think it has something to do with Sean.       It has everything to do with Sean.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Mean lil fellow, arn't you?    urlLink   What Monty Python Character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HOLY ABSOLUTE SHIT!  This movie is incredible.  Fuck.  It surpasses any expectations I had and throws them strongly through the roof.  Seriously.  For me, it tops The Lord of the Rings.  My reasons are that firstly, the bond between the seven knights is undescribable.  You can see it in their eyes, in the way they speak to eachother, their actions, their bravery and their loyalty towards one another.  It's amazing and it really touched me.  That alone made the movie.  My two most favorite knights: Galahad and Lancelot.     I read some really mixed reviews on this movie and yes, some things were a bit off.  For example, there were crossbows.. many of them... yet, they really weren't invented for another 100 or so years after the time period this story takes place in.  Guinevere wasn't as much as a wench in the movie as she is in the myth.  Then again, it IS only a myth and therefore there are various ways to represent it and different takes on it.  Lancelot: There is a large number of lonely men out there.  Guinevere: Don't worry, I won't let them rape you.  Incredible!
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paralysed Lips of Ashes Synchronised Blue vein crashes  Touching you inside  Idolised Black Eyes fading You and I Connection failing  I drill down inside
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So I'm seeing this movie tonight.  I cannot contain my excitement!  I'll be sure to write up my review of it either later tonight or tomorrow.  The thing with it though is, I have very high expectations and I've been reading various reviews of it and well... it's said to be very full of itself.  And that it's good but could be better.  BLAH!  I'll see it for myself and then I'll make up my mind.  I really hope it doesn't disappoint though, I've been looking forward to it since January.  This movie looks really, really good:   You know when a song hits you so hard it gives you goosebumps?  Well music does that for me as well as movies... the preview for this movie did it.  It looks really interesting and though I'm not the biggest fan of Will Smith, he seems to have done a good job.  So we'll see!  HMV still haven't called... it's only been two days though... *calm* Oh well.  It they don't call this week, I'll apply to some other record stores... and possibly a couple cafes.    Yesterday, I got Porcupine Tree's  In Absentia  in the mail off of amazon.  This album is truly incredible.  They take progressive rock to a new level.  I found out about them through liking Opeth and I can see some similarities... but definitely more differences.  Anyway, I want to write a lot more about this album but I'm lazy, I only woke up 20 minutes ago (1:30 pm) and I'm still dead.  later.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Rotation:        Set my alarm for 10:30 this morning so I could have some breakfast and head over to the gym for noon.  I had a great workout; I love the feeling when I'm all done.  It's refreshing in a sense.  I saw Kristen there which was cool because I haven't seen her in a while.  She told me how grad went and now she's working at the cafe bookstore I love to go to.  I can't wait until I graduate next year, I really can't.  Tonight I'm going to see Spiderman 2 around 10.  Oh how I love late showings of movies. 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Favorite Songs Currently...  Pixies / Gauge Away Pixies / Cactus Manic Street Preachers / IfwhiteAmericatoldthetruthforonedayitsworldwouldfallapart The Postal Service / Such Great Heights Frou Frou / Let Go     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I go in to apply at HMV today.  I hand my resume to the guy at the desk... feeling all good and confident and then he says he's going to ask me just a couple questions.  I had completely forgotten that they do that sometimes when you hand in a resume so I'm slightly flustered all of a sudden but I'm keeping my cool.  He asks when I'm available.  Easy stuff.  Full-time until September and after that part-time.  Great.  One down.  Next question... "what kind of music do you like?" Fuck!  Seriously.  I could list of 1092127893 bands that I love, and I could go into great detail as to why I love each and every one of them.  But do I say that?  No.  It's awkward and it really doesn't help me that this guy is fucking gorgeous.  So I'm stumbling over words.  Great.  But I do say my favorite band is Radiohead.  Thank god I remember Radiohead.  He asks me, "Old Radiohead or new Radiohead?" And so I tell him I like everything after their first album.  He asks me why not the first one?  And if he asked me NOW, I would have said because it was their first attempt at recording an album, they didn't know what they were doing, and it really shows in the album.  Did I say that though?  NO.  You know what I said?  "Because it's... crap, really." He laughed and said something along the lines of "Yeah, I agree, *nods* good."  Eh... maybe he'll like that I have a sense of humor?  I failed to mention Pink Floyd, Led Zep, Secret machines, how I love the indie rock scene in NYC.  UGH.  Well, they'll keep my resume on file for 6 months.  I really hope I get it.  Who knows?    On the plus side, I bought bright green Converse sneakers today.  One more to add to my... soon-to-be collection.  I now have two pairs.  They're fucking brilliant, those shoes.  I feel good today... food-wise.  I just feel really confident about myself.  I like how I look.  Things are okay.  I just have bad days every so often, still.  I really think I'll be okay though.  How much of a genius is Will Ferrell?  Seriously.  I love that guy.  God DOES exist and his real name is WILL FERRELL.  He goes by God because it just sounds so powerful.  "God" is Will Ferrell's stage name.
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        np-   When the Levee Breaks /  Led Zeppelin     &nbsp;   So here I am.&nbsp; I've just had such a great workout at the gym.&nbsp; I'm just happy at how much better I've been doing for the past few months.&nbsp; I really feel like I've recovered and it feels overwhelming but at the same time, absolutely great.&nbsp; I remember back in January actually feeling scared of living without an eating disorder; as if it was part of me and no matter how much I wanted to let it go, at the same time I wanted it to stay with me.&nbsp; I've overcomed that though and despite a couple setbacks, I'm really doing&nbsp;well.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   What's also great is I actually enjoy eating again.&nbsp; I remember about two summers ago,&nbsp;I was counting all my calories, watching everything I ate, recording all my exercising and weighing myself like 15 times&nbsp;a day.&nbsp; I was obsessed with it.&nbsp; Now, I weigh myself maybe once every couple months out of curiosity and I just eat when I feel like it and what I want... just in moderation of course.&nbsp; I never thought I'd EVER get here but I am.&nbsp; Oh man.&nbsp; =)     &nbsp;   I love going to the gym in the evening.&nbsp; It's more peaceful at night compared to the morning when everybody seems to go.&nbsp; I like the atmosphere better at night.&nbsp; You know what though?&nbsp; If you asked me last year if I was a night or day person, I would say a day person without a doubt.&nbsp; Now, for sure, I'm a night person.&nbsp; Although, I can handle both if I must... like now, since I'm working.&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;   I do have a point... and now I'll get to it.&nbsp; I was looking through a photo album today of my aunt's wedding back in 1980.&nbsp; She hasn't changed!&nbsp; She never changes one bit... physically I mean.&nbsp;&nbsp;She's always had the same hairstyle, the same style of clothing, the same way she does her makeup, etc.&nbsp; Some of my close friends... who I've known for years, haven't changed either in my eyes.&nbsp; Whereas others most certainly have... and myself included.&nbsp; I change DRAMATICALLY each year.&nbsp; I'm not sure why exactly but it's just the way I am.&nbsp; I think I've come more into my own this year though... who knows what I'll be like next year but I'm pretty sure I won't change too much.&nbsp; It's because I can honestly say I like myself now.&nbsp; In previous years, there's always been something missing; a certain aspect of individuality maybe?&nbsp; Just certain things not exactly MISSING... just hadn't developed yet.&nbsp; I really feel like my own, strange person now.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   Albums in Rotation:    Smashing Pumpkins'  Adore     Led Zeppelin's  IV     Pixies'  Surfer Rosa     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What can I say? I just love doing questionaires like this. Thank you Keith!   thirteen random things you like:  1. Bright pink  2. Neon &amp; bright green  3. Photographs of people and more specifically; bands and artists.  4. Galahad in King Arthur  5. My Little Pony  6. Rainbow Brite  7. Going on crazy rides at amusement parks  8. Cartman  9. Summer nights  10. Thunder &amp; lightning storms  11. My dog, Chessie  12. Black cats  13. Record shopping and/or clothes shopping    twelve movies:  1. Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind  2. The Royal Tenenbaums  3. Donnie Darko  4. Starsky &amp; Hutch  5. Zoolander  6. Shakespeare in Love  7. King Arthur  8. Amelie  9. The Notebook  10. South Park: Bigger, Longer and Uncut  11. Monty Python &amp; the Holy Grail  12. Anchorman    eleven good bands/artists:  1. Radiohead  2. Secret Machines  3. Pixies  4. Porcupine Tree  5. The Strokes  6. The Beatles  7. Metric  8. Muse  9. The Doors  10. Led Zeppelin  11. Pink Floyd    ten things about you:  1. I prefer to drink using a couple straws... usually 3, actually.  2. I'm ambidextrous.  3. I think that if you can find true love, then everything eventually falls into place.  4. Someday, I want to go into outer space.  5. I love the smell of crisp burning-of-leaves outside... it's the best in Autumn. I just like the smokey scent.  6. I play the drums, piano, bass and the guitar.  7. I love anything retro (old childhood toys, pins, vinyl, etc.)  8. I collect vinyl records and CDs.  9. I look for the characteristcs in people that make them an individual.  10. I hate it when one puts on an act for me. First of all, you ruin number 9 and second of all, what's the bloody point? You can't hide forever so you might as well start trying to be more comfortable with yourself now. Besides, you're boring if you look or act like everybody else.    nine good friends:  1. Sean  2. Megan  3. Amia  4. Rhea  5. Vanessa  6. Tess  7. Dave  8. Jared  9. Kate   eight favorite foods/drinks:  1. Sundae Smarties  2. Diet Vanilla Coke  3. Starbucks Mocha Lite Frappucino (sp? I can never spell that word!)  4. Caesar salad  5. Carrot cake  6. Date bars  7. Apples  8. Spaghetti or shapgetti as known to the cool crowd. That's right... =D    seven things you wear daily:  1. My silver chain-like necklace with a small heart in the center  2. My pearl necklaces  3. A watch  4. A hair elastic on my wrist  5. Eyeliner/mascara  6. Cocoa or Coconut scented body lotion  7. Clothes, obviously, sometimes a skirt but usually my vintage faded jeans that I love and some sort of retro/unique looking/colorful top    six things that annoy you:  1. Liars  2. Hypocrites  3. Hilary Duff  4. People who like Good Charlotte  5. People who like Good Charlotte and THEN claim that they are punk. If you say that, it means you know nothing of punk culture or its history and basically, just die now... thanks.  6. Closed minds   five things you touch everyday:  1. My toothbrush  2. My cocoa scented body lotion  3. My dog  4. The computer mouse/keyboard  5. My running shoes   four shows you watch:  1. South Park  2. Sex and the City  3. Family Guy  4. The O.C.    three celebrities you have a crush on:  1. Hugh Dancy  2. Ryan Gosling  3. Nick Valensi (One of The Strokes' guitarists)    two people on myspace that you have kissed:  myspace? Oook... what is that?   one person you could spend the rest of your life with:  Like you even need to ask.  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           I saw this tonight. OH MY GOD! BRILLIANT! Seriously, it's that kind of comedy you just love Will Ferrell for. It's absolutely hilarious... and it's full of surprises but I won't give those away. ;) Anyway, that's all I'll say about it because what else can you really say about something like this? It's fucking great. Go see it.   I realized something today. Galahad... in King Arthur... my favorite... is played by Hugh Dancy... one of my favorite actors... and I didn't even know. How stupid could I have been? I didn't recognize him! Look:      Both of him! But to me, looks like two different people. Gah! Oh well, now that I KNOW, I see it... but I didn't see it in the movie. Jesus. I like him so much though. =)   Um, that's all for now I suppose. I start work tomorrow... I haven't even started and I'm already kind of dreading it but at least I can listen to music all day and I'll make some money. Hooray.   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I stole this from Keith, *big sneaky smile*   Name: Sarah  Nickname: Hutch, if anything  Birthday: February 21, 1987  Birthplace: Winnipeg, MB, Canada   =Now=  Current mood: Energetic  Current music: Porcupine Tree / Blackest Eyes  Current taste: Starbucks Mocha Lite Frap  Current hair: Straight, too long, must cut it  Current clothes: my track sweats and a pink shirt (I just woke up... it's 1:30.. heh)  Current annoyance: I woke up too late again. My sleeping schedule is WHACKED.  Current smell: Mocha  Current thing I ought to be doing: I should be just finished lunch and already gone to the gym... but, alas, no. I'll go for a jog outside instead today.  Current windows open: This, and Bolt  Current desktop picture: The "I have love for you" picture from explodingdog.com  Current favorite band: hmm... probably Pixies or Secret Machines  Current book: Slaughterhouse Five by Kurt Vonnegut  Current cd in stereo: The Killers / Hot Fuss  Current crush: My boyfriend (and Hugh Dancy)  Current favorite celeb: Actress- Kiera Knightley, Actor- HUGH DANCY    =Do I=  Smoke? No  Do drugs?: No, but I'd try mushrooms  Have sex?: Yes  Give oral sex?: ditto  Receive oral sex?: see above  Have a dream that keeps coming back?: I've had repetitive dreams, sure.  Remember your first love?: yes  Still love him/her?: No  Read the newspaper?: yeah, when something catches my eye  Have any gay or lesbian friends?: if I do, I'm unaware of it.  Believe in miracles?: Not really no.  Believe it's possible to remain faithful forever?: Of course  Consider yourself tolerant of others?: Yeah for sure. I'm laid back and patient with others.  Consider love a mistake?: No!  Like the taste of alcohol?: Yeah  Have a favorite candy?: I love Sundae Smarties  Believe in astrology?: To a point. I've read descriptions of Pisces and it's right on the money.  Believe in magic?: I like to believe in it. =)  Believe in god?: No  Have any pets: Chessie, my little golden retriever  Go to or plan to go to college: Yeah, as soon as I'm done grade 12  Have any piercings?: No but I want some... I will eventually  Have any tattoos?: I want on on the back of my left shoulder and another on my left hip bone... we will see  Hate yourself: Sometimes  Have an obsession?: Music  Have a secret crush? If I did, it would be a secret, so I don't see why you're asking  Do they know yet?: Again, if a secret, of course not.  Have a best friend?: I have a group of really close friends... I don't like having one best friend  Wish on stars?: Yep  Care about looks?: Yes of course   =Love life=  First crush: Rory back in grade 4  Single or attached?: Attached  Ever been in love?: yes  Do you believe in love at first sight?: No  Do you believe in "the one?": Yeah  Describe your ideal significant other: passionate, romantic, intelligent/clever/witty, goofy, tall &amp; skinny, good taste in music... am I asking too much? One would think! But I've already found him.   =Juicy stuff=  Have you ever played a game that required removal of clothing?: No  Have you ever been intoxicated?: *nods*  Favorite place to be kissed?: lips  Have you ever been caught "doing something?": Almost.  Are you a tease?: Only in a joking way  Shy to make the first move?: Kind of   --APPEARANCE:--  Hair: brunette, long, straight unless I don't straighten it... in which case, wavy  Eyes: milk chocolate brown  Height: 5'9"   --LAST THING YOU:--  Bought: A ticket to King Arthur for the second time  Ate &amp; Drank: A Starbucks lite mocha frap, a banana and a WW bagel  Read: Teen Vogue  Watched on tv: The Best of Will Ferrell on SNL Vol. 2   --EITHER / OR:--  club or houseparty: Both!  beer or cider: I've never tried cider so my answer is not fair  drinks or shots: shots  cats or dogs: I'm a cat/dog person... a dat.. or a cog... either way. I like both  single or taken: taken  pen or pencil: Pen  gloves or mittens: Gloves  food or candy: Food  cassette or cd: CD  coke or pepsi: Coke  this or that: a little bit of both   --LAST PERSON YOU--  talked to: Kate  hugged: Dad  instant messaged: Katie  kissed: Aaron   --WHERE DO YOU--  eat: in the basement or the computer room usually  cry: No specific place...  wish you were: in England again.   --RANDOM QUESTIONS--  What's on your bedside table?: My stereo, random CDs, a glass of water with three pink straws in it, my wallet, a photo of Sean in one of those holder things, some papers with random things on them  What do you eat when you raid the fridge late at night?: diet coke, fruit, yogurt  What is your secret guaranteed weeping movie?: I get tears in my eyes when there's a really happy ending... or something happens that's really moving  If you could have plastic surgery, what would you have done?: Nothing  What is your biggest fear?: not accomplishing my dreams, clowns  What feature are you most insecure about?: Probably my feet, I fucking hate them but whatever  Do you ever have to beg?: Sometimes, I'm pretty good  Are you a pyromaniac?: no!  Do you have too many love interests?: no, just 1  Crushes? haha, yeah probably. I see way too many good looking guys.  Do you know anyone famous?: *nods*... ok well not KNOW, I've met a few  Describe your bed: red sheets, black comforter, red &amp; white pillows, comfy-ish  Spontaneous or plain?: Spontaneous  Do you know how to play poker?: Yes and I'm good.  What do you carry with you at all times?: my purse with all my buttons on it... includes my wallet, sunglasses, etc  How do you drive?: I tend to speed... 50 is fucking slow and I usually drive at 60 in a 50 zone... it's horrible. But I do my best.  What do you miss most about being little?: not having to worry about the future, not having any problmes, playing with toys, being able to play stupid games like House without being embarrassed, watching Disney movies and thinking they were real  Are you happy with your given name?: I guess. It's so common though. Blah.  How much money would it take to get you to give up the Internet for one year?: eek. A LOT.  What color is your bedroom?: Black &amp; white  What was the last song you were listening to?: Like Spinning Plates (LIVE) / Radiohead  Have you ever been in a play?: Yes  Who are your best friends?: Rhea and Megan  Do you talk a lot?: I can at times... if it's something I know a lot about  Do you like yourself and believe in yourself?: yes  Do you think you're cute?: sure  Do poor, homeless, or starving people sometimes annoy you? No  Do you consider yourself to be a nice person?: yeah, I'm super nice most of the time  What is the first thing you think when you see two gay guys or lesbians holding hands?: It's just like seeing any couple hold hands... I just think "aww" and move on.  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past few weeks or so, I've been feeling really nostalgic and today I decided to look up all my old, most favorite, Disney movies... ah, the memories. =)  Someday, I want to watch all of these again.  Yep.  I sure will.               I also just want to say that despite the few REALLY LAME parts (with the two of them as elderly people... bad acting... lame dialogue), the parts of the movie with them younger made me melt and I absolutely love it.  Especially Ryan Gosling.   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Sahara Hotnights; check them out.&nbsp; Like... now.&nbsp; Do it.&nbsp; DO IT.          urlLink     urlLink http://www.saharahotnights.com          And watch the video for "Hot Night Crash."     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       GOT PAID TODAY!     &nbsp;   Yes!     &nbsp;   Half of it goes to savings, the other half... CDs!&nbsp;     &nbsp;   To buy List:    Girls Can Tell / Spoon    Hopes & Fears / Keane    Tyrannosaurus Hives / The Hives    Jennie Bomb / Sahara Hotnights &nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;   That is all.&nbsp; I'm off.&nbsp; I have some stuff to write about on here that I've been thinking about for the past few days but I can't be bothered right now.&nbsp; Tomorrow is my parents' anniversary and then the next day is my grandparents' one so this is the weekend (like every other year) where we all get together and go to this beautiful restaurant called Tavern in the Park.&nbsp; I'm excited.     &nbsp;     Idioteque is fucking beautiful.       &nbsp;   Later.    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I like Massive Attack right now.&nbsp; I've always been into them but lately even moreso.&nbsp; I think it has something to do with the fact that Kate's always playing  Mezzanine,  hmm?     &nbsp;   I don't like them THAT much though... in fact, I'm slightly bored with most of my CDs right now.&nbsp; I need something new and exciting.&nbsp;   Secret Machines   were doing it for me for quite a while (and still are), I won't ever get sick of them, they're just incredible.&nbsp; Period.&nbsp; But, I need something new still.&nbsp; I feel like I'm in a music-rut... ever had one of those?&nbsp; Somebody recommend a band.&nbsp; NOW!&nbsp;Please?     &nbsp;   I really appreciate and have a lot of respect for GOOD rock journalism.&nbsp; I've found that with magazines such as Spin or Rolling Stone; the articles are repetitive and lack creativity and quirkiness; two characteristics I NEED when reading an article (especially about a band/artist) or else I just get bored after the first paragraph and move on.&nbsp; What I love about&nbsp;  Filter   is that the journalism is intelligent, quirky, funny and not to mention- you can really tell the writer has enjoyed writing the article.&nbsp; The magazine talks mostly about music (CD reviews, getting to know certain bands, feature articles, photography) and they always discuss two films (usually an&nbsp;interview with the director).&nbsp; They've talked about    Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind, Coffee & Cigarettes, Garden State, Before Sunset, The Saddest Music in the World   ... etc.&nbsp; In other words: Fucking good stuff.     &nbsp;   Just some of my favorite parts from articles I've read in the magazine:    [From   Getting to know   The Veils article in issue 11]      &nbsp;&nbsp;  What's most troubling about music at the moment, owing to its being co-opted by lunkheads and milksops, is that the poetry is virtually gone.&nbsp; Not "poetry" poetry (God help us), but the sense that music has the ability to present itself in both an Expressionist and esoteric manner at once.&nbsp; Rather, we're forced to endure nu-metal oafs and emo whiners ranting on with a mind-boggling lack of complexity, plaintive-but-simplistic singer-songwriter whimpering and, worst of all, rappers going on about their dicks.&nbsp; It's enough to make one pray for Cole Porter's resurrection.       &nbsp;&nbsp; Times like these don't bode well for the likes of the Veils, another in a great tradition of emotionally grandiose British pop bands.&nbsp; In fact, 19-year-old ex-pat Aussie singer/guitarist Finn Andrews may be American music fans' worst nightmare: whip-thin, a bit fey, too well-spoken, and far too philosophical for his age.&nbsp; His T-shirt should bear the words, "Ask me about my tortured soul." (His bandmates' T-shirts could read, "I'm with introspective," the proverbial arrow pointing directly at their singer.)...  
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was really getting sick of the ol' pink design so I changed it.&nbsp; I'm liking this a whole lot more indeed. *nods*  &nbsp;     I'm going to order&nbsp;My Litte Pony: The Movie on DVD so I can watch it and&nbsp;be filled with memories&nbsp;from back when I'd watch it almost every day.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  So... today I went to the gym in the morning... oh man was it a hard day.&nbsp; I'm not sure why but I just felt totally exhausted.&nbsp; I'm not exactly looking forward to work tomorrow either... oh well.&nbsp; I'll look forward to tomorrow night.&nbsp; I'm going out with Kate (my sister) and another Kate.&nbsp; Confusing.  &nbsp;  Also, yesterday, I got a haircut... I'm still debating whether or not I actually like it though... we'll give it a few days.&nbsp; I might post a picture on here or on Bolt... we will see.  &nbsp;  I, Robot absolutely sucks by the way.&nbsp; It was just as bad as Spiderman 2.&nbsp; Not to mention the shameless advertising for Converse sneakers!&nbsp; There's this one part in the movie where Will Smith gets a shoebox, he opens it, close-up of the Converse logo and he says "my 2004 vintage converse!"&nbsp; And there are two more times in the movie when another characters asks him what's up with his SHOES.&nbsp; MY GOD.&nbsp; That alone ruined it.&nbsp; Yeah, I like Converse but I don't need it shoved into my face like that.&nbsp; I know that these days, movies do that... but couldn't they have made it more subtle?&nbsp; Then again, I don't like it when it's subtle either, but you don't&nbsp;see other characters ASK what they're drinking when someone's drinking a Coke or something.&nbsp; It just shows it with the logo facing the camera.&nbsp; I wouldn't have minded so much if they just showed us the shoes rather than make reference to them three fucking times.  &nbsp;  Oh, and the movie itself... predictable, but had a good message I suppose.&nbsp; The point was to say we, as humans, can think emotionally; which often over-rules logic.   Doesn't make up for the rest of it.   Some art I've really been into lately: (thank you to taramcpherson.com)    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        THE BEST LED ZEPPELIN SONGS      Over the Hills and Far Away   Going to California   When the Levee Breaks   Misty Mountain Top   Immigrant Song   Tangerine   Black Dog   The Battle of Evermore   Trampled Under Foot   Houses of the Holy   Friends   Ten Years Gone   Kashmir     THE BEST RADIOHEAD SONGS      Idioteque   Optimistic   Like Spinning Plates (Live)   How to Disappear Completely   Exit Music (for a film)   Street Spirit (fade out)   Lucky   Climbing Up the Walls   My Iron Lung   There There   Pyramid Song   Subterranean Homesick Alien   Packt Like Sardines In a Crushd Tin Box   Talk Show Host   You and Whose Army   True Love Waits   Airbag   A Reminder   Polyethylene   Punchdrunk Lovesick Singalong             
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So I'm sitting here, enjoying my favorite Mocha Frap. from Starbucks.&nbsp; I'm amazed that the new Lighter/less fat ones taste even better.&nbsp; My mum bought lots of organic fruit today and so I'm also having some of the freshly picked blueberries she got.&nbsp; They taste SO much better than the ones we normally buy from a place like Safeway.&nbsp; She also bought Date cake (my favorite dessert, ever) for tomorrow night when my aunt and uncle come over for dinner and it's homemade so when you look at the ingredients... it's simply dates, granola and cinnamon and not a whole bunch of other crap like it would have if you bought it from some grocery store.&nbsp; When you want to buy organic foods though, it's so much more expensive.&nbsp; So you have to pay more for something healthier.&nbsp; That whole system is fucked.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   Work went all right today.&nbsp; We were off at 3 which was nice.&nbsp; The great thing is that I get to listen to music all day.&nbsp; The ones we listened to were The Strokes  Is This It,  Sahara Hotnights  Jennie Bomb,  The Hives  Tyrannosaurus Hives,  Panurge  Throw Down the Reins,  Massive Attack  Mezzanine,  Blur  Think Tank  and a bit off of Keane  Hopes and Fears.&nbsp;  Keane's album is okay... I know people are saying they're similar to bands like Coldplay and Travis but really, I'm sorry to say it, they sound like a poppy British boyband to me.&nbsp; Well, maybe that's kind of harsh.&nbsp; The first song was catchy but meh... I don't know... it didn't blow me away or anything.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   There's this song, "Teardrop" on  Mezzanine  that is one of the most beautiful songs I've ever heard in my life.&nbsp; Everytime I hear it, I picture Sean and I walking down a street, holding hands and just smiling at eachother every so often... that song brings that image to my head, I'm not sure why, it just does.&nbsp; Another absolutely beautiful song is "Sweet Song" off of  Think Tank.&nbsp;  It's one of my favorite Blur songs.     &nbsp;   I was so hoping to go see a movie tonight but it turns out that out of all the movies playing:&nbsp;A) I've already seen it once or twice even,&nbsp;B) It looks like crap or C) I've seen it, it was crap, and I wouldn't see it again SO, no movie tonight.&nbsp; I might walk down to ABE's with Kate for dinner though.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   All right, so apparently, every person in this world has at least&nbsp;one other person who looks like them.&nbsp; Now, what if we all have somebody else who thinks just like us?&nbsp; There are bodies timed to give out at the very same second.&nbsp; Thousands.&nbsp; I don't see why there can't be minds also.&nbsp; But, when your body gives out, you die... and when your mind gives out, you die (they just call it  suicide.)      &nbsp;   Hm.&nbsp; Random thought brought to you by Sarah.&nbsp; Reading over that, it doesn't make much sense, and I'm not sure where I was going with it either.&nbsp; *shrug*     &nbsp;    urlLink  This band   &nbsp; is really awesome.&nbsp; Think happy-indie-pop that makes you feel all good and happy.&nbsp; Not to mention the percussion is a girl tap dancing!        &nbsp;   That's all for now I think.  &nbsp;      
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wooh!  I've just ordered    Razorlight's    album online so I can get the original copy that was released in Britain back in June. Apparently the American version comes out here on the 17th but it has a different cover and that pisses me off. Since the band's British, I just want to order it from England... I'm just picky that way sometimes. Can I just say how awesome they are though? Jesus Christ. I can't stop listening to    "Golden Touch"    and that's a problem because I don't want to get sick of it. I think I'll stop listening until the album gets here. Yes. *nods*  Ha.  Like I'll follow through with that.  Well, we just ordered pizza so that should be here soon, and then I'm off to the gym. Nothing else to report except that I've realized a few things about my personality that I need to fix, thanks to you (and you know who you are). I feel good knowing that you can help me become a better person.  This is fucking cool:    Later. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm sitting here on my lunchbreak at work.  *looks around* Well this is fun.  Friday is payday though so I'm looking forward to that.  Let's see... I had a pretty good long weekend.  Yesterday, went to Kelsey's for dinner.  The day before, I saw The Village.  That movie has such crazy reviews; the people I know who've seen it either love it or hate it really.  I love it.  I really do.  The overall message of the whole thing is beautiful.  And the character, Ivy, was wonderful.  She'd be the kind of person I'd want as a good friend in my life.  She was blind but the way she acted it was like she was a blind person who could see... but could see the world just in a different way than the rest of us.  Overall, there were some incredibly lame parts where I couldn't contain my laughter and really, at those points, I was thinking that the movie sucked.  Then the end comes and everything turned around and what I thought was lame actually wasn't lame at all.  That's all I can say really.  I don't want to ruin it for any of those who actually read this.     I'm going to edit this and write more when I get home.  Later.
    
</post>


</Blog>