<Blog>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally not late for sch... hehe... today got Culture and Communications module... sianZz... change of the groupings... sianZz... dun wanna change... okay lo... really nth to write leh... oh ya... tml, guitar prac and band prac clash... how? go for which one??? haiZz... mi sianZz... how? how? tell mi leh... 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiZ... today i am late for sch... the stupid dog 's lesson... wa lao... den the prob so doff... dunno wad inductive and deductive.... so diffcult... den the VB test was like hell... nv learn stuff came out, mi gong gong... found out Floorball got to go this friday, den my whole week everyday not free... lolZz... so stress la... den after the test liaoz rush to Wind Symphony... got new score... dunno wat sheep graze blar blar lo... den so diffcult... flute melody... luckily mi second... or else the band will hav no melody.... lolZz... got an expert beside mi... so stress... cannot play the semi quaver thingie... aiyo... so after that i borrowed my instrument home lo... den when i reached home, den realise like no time to practice lo... Waste energy to bring home flute.... den now got black out... wat kinda rotten day is this... so damn hot so tired cant slp... wat did i do to my life man! so cham!haiZzz... =(
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiZzz... today sch reopen... c my poly frens again... hee! quite ok la... lots of fren going to Np sch reopen today... all of them say so sianz...hee... erm.. wonder they can use msn messenger in sch anot...(hmmm)... nvm... back to my blog... today so sianz lo... basic science... wanna die le... learn abt wad dissipation and stuff leh... HELP!!! so diffcult nv learn the topic in sch sch... it's abt the concentration and erm... blar blar la... aiyo... just finish writing the Reflection Journal... so long... hope tt tml my Congnitive n prob solving fag will change... stupid DOG!!! LOLzZZ pple in my class will noe y la... Oh Ya, tml got the Visual Basic understanding test... aiyo... Cham le la...OmG! tml still have Rp Wind Symphony... 5.30pm to 8.30pm... i m gonna be so tired!!!oh! now havta go study le... haiZz... so tired...  ---> Every obstacle presents an opportunity to improve our condition. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Erm... hihi... my first day of this blog... dunno wad to write... all thks to my frens blog page attracted mi to start ‘blogging’ too! Erm... basically, nth much to write la... today nv went anywhere... so tok abt yesterday, I went to the Vb thingie... the senior was a great helper... veri friendly n everything... den after cleafing my doubts n everything, mi, Peili, Shuimin n Eunice went orchard lo... we went to KFC to eat... den funni thing is we all end up eating the same meal... haha... wonder y??? keke... while we were eating we tok abt sec sch, rp life n guys... keke! Found out tt Eunice n Shuimin dun really tok abt guys la... so tt topic was passed on lo... den later we say abt music... haha... my ears pricked up (omg, like a dog!!! lolZz)... it’s like mi n Eunice r the onli one toking... aiya... veri unfair to others... ok den we when to walk walk n Eunice has to go cos she has to buy sum stuff n had piano lesson later... so we bide goodbye at lido... den the rest of us went FarEast... we went in n straight into A BOOKSHOP... pple go there shop for clothes we go there READ!!! Haha... the rest of us likes to read lo... we were looking around den suddenly settled in the Chinese n comic section... jus settled down as in sit down on the floor like the place is the library like tt... lolZz... but luckily nobody chase us out or anything like tt... Shuimin den found out tt there is this really great bk she wanna recommend it to us but she alone couldn’t find the book so we three were hunting around for this one bk... den mi n Peili got tired so decided to look at comics... den we were discussing abt the comic character like we look at the books picture to decide how interesting the book is... haha... oh ya, I luv jap character in the ‘manga’, oh ya, I used to copy them out in my secondary sch days... I like young Kindachi, Doraemon n so on la... when we got out of the bookshop, we decide to go walk walk again... when we end up in another book shop, Peili’s fren, Sharon, joined us... Wa! A veri mature ger, not like the three of us, siao siao one... hehe... veri friendly too! But can c our taste diff la... but nvm all of us still got along well... well, by the end of the day I got to noe Shuimin better... den found out tt she n I luv crafts... her cross-stitches n mi beads... oh ya, btw, I hereby announce I noe how to make earrings wif beads... hee! Cos this Peili dunno n she was quite shocked... back to today, in the end mi n Shuimin went off first, as I was failing geographically in directions, Shuimin had to sent mi to the MRT station... mi feel so guilty, cos her bag was so heavy wif a veri thick VB book... SO I wanna comment tt Shuimin is a veri nice n really great friend having her as my friend is so lucky, man!!! Thks ger! Erm... ya not the end...after tt tot I could go hm n slp... received a call n had to go ChinaTown, my family were down at the night market... wa when I reached there I couldn’t find them... search for almost 45mins den found them... so irritating! But the place was so crowded, we walked for several streets n we reached the night market... the things were veri common like pasa malam like tt... but when we reached the food section it was WOW, the pastries n tutu kueh making my mouth water... so nice! U should image the dinner-less mi! den we brought the food home n eat... now I eating the egg-tart... wa ! Yummie!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmm... today the DOG's lessons again... wad to do... jus late again... but this time the DOG is more late... lolZz... hmmm... nth much la... the lesson is abt bouncing the ball... so lame... we spent our time outside doing the bouncing experiment... so 'FUN'... pple look at us like we siaoZ like tt... den after the lessons got RpWS... the prac is quite okay la... Mr Gloss is not as strict as i thought he was... lolZz... the music he really nice... i like the piece "StarShip" the most... so claming piece... other pieces are ok la... still can follow but cant play tt well la... but i'll JiaYou... all the best for myself... 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Forgot to write yesterday’s blog... too tired to remember... btw, yesterday nth much lo... jus went to guitar practice and play the song... it is a veri nice combination of instruments... but I guess I really need a conductor to cue mi in... cos after a lot of rests I got lost... got some notes oso in wrong key... aiyo... 13TH of july performing... how to survive... veri near liaoz lo... not much time to practice... hmm... now onli and wait n c lo... wad to do.. practice more lo.. haiZz... yesterday got watch the JIAN GUI, quite okay la... not veri scary cos I watch b4 le... lolZz... the lift part is so exciting... den this stupid show make mi forgot to watch the last epsiode of ALL IN... Damn it... did Ren He die? can anyone tell mi... wa laoz... sianz ji pua... today oso nth much to do la... return my books and gif Michelle my guitar... practiced my flute n guitar... so shuang! If onli m split into two den can play both at the same time... lolZz... impossible... but now can onli persuade my bro to learn guitar... so can play together... oh ya, den he can sing along... lolZz... haha... jus for huever’s concern he is a choir member, he went to the youth day ceremony yesterday... OH YA!! Which reminds mi, Y RP NO YOUTH DAY!!! I still a YOUTH leh... sianZz... my bro luffing at mi so PIA in my studies... -_-lll... sianZz... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Erm... today morning was really bad, due to sleeping late yesterday (some idiots disturbing me when I was rushing through my RJ!!!), I went to school quite late. To my surprise PeiLi is oso late... then on the way PeiLi complain to mi abt how she cum feel like going for VB lessons today... she is so stress... reach sch wif Mustaqim... so tired lo... didn’t feel like doing the programming for today, haiZz but the fac put mi as the leader so no choice la, havta do my job... In class I was racking my brains for the codes to the buttons and everything... den by the there and end of the day I was really mentally tired... den abt the floorball, it was having a meeting... so they had a friendly match, WA!, really long time nv touch floorball le... so FUN... but like a lot of malays in floorball.... but it was really long time since I played floorballl... so fun lo... finally a day of fun and happiness since the holidays has end... 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiZz... Jus finished my RJ... how to motivate myself... I jus write what came into my mind... no time le... okok... this morning rain lo... quite wet la, den go inside class den kept sneeezing... felt sick and hungry the whole morning... i tot i lost my jacket, saw it beside the window... oh ya, den got this new fac in our class... found him bascally ok la... the whole day keep thinking of one qns... go guitar of wind symphony, somemore i was a bit sick... so the whole day like nv do much things in the team... i was such a let down... sorri team... den i didnt hear much of the facilitor comment on the teams and the 6th presentation.. haiZz... i m worried abt the clashing of the ccas, guitar and RPWS, i like both veri much... and badly want to keep both Ccas... A lot of people encouraged me to drop one of the similar music ccas... but i jus dunwan... as i know how to play the flute in sec sch already... i begin to like it more and more, so i dunwan to stop practicing... and guitar???!!! could someone ADVICE me??? (BTW, the next instrument which i wanna learn is the drum set, it's jus amazes mi... how the player synconise so well!)is my dream instrument to play, and mow i finally got a chance... so how to choose i everyday got troubled face, today worrying about the clash of my ccas... i wondered wat tml will be... XP 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>