<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last morning i decided to go home and try to relax myself. It has been quite a while since i went home. 1 week or more na ata. When i arrived (around 6am) my 5 years old sister was about to wake up inorder to go to school. She was surprised to see me. It was obvious that she really misses me a lot. She immediately made plans and had asked me to stay for a while. She wanted to spend time with me. Upon returning from school, she immediately searched for me. We spent the day playing basketball, eating popcorn and watching DVDs to name a few. It was a sibling bonding. I needed that. For once, my mind was momentarily amused. Something which i really find hard to do. Imagine that. I found a momentary relief from an unlikely person.   I love my sister. I thank the lord for bringing her to my family.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It has never occured to me that being casual to a person who you have deep feelings for and whom you are involve with for the past 1-1/2 years could be so damn hard. The distant and cold treatments are some feelings which i hate to experience most specially from the person i love. Usually, when i txt her, i'd get a "Hi ney!" or "Honey!" message but now all i get is a simple "hello". To an ordinary friend, that would be ok but to a person you love, its a bitter pill to swallow. Can i blame her? Ofcourse not. She has a right to feel whatever she wants. She has her reasons. I should even be thankful that she is still talking to me. Its a consequence which i have to face. Its a consequence which i have to endure. Till when? I dunno.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its been a week now ever since that incident. I havent had a good sleep. I've been restless since. Lost of appetite has now occured. People tell me that i look different nowadays. Not as lively as before, not as upbeat as i usually am. Physically, i look old na daw. Something is wrong daw but i always brush there comments aside. Sabi ko i'm just stressed from work i guess.. yeah right!  God knows how much i cried this week. I tried to be strong.. but the tears just kept flowing down. I guess I'm just that much affected.  Crying for me i guess is a way of releasing the feelings that i have deep inside. Its either that or go "out of control" which i promised myself i would never do again or atleast try not to the best of my ability. The latter was the one which caused this predicament that i am into. There hasnt been a day which i had not regret the actions that i did.    Last Saturday, I was deeply affected by a small incident while playing Ragnarok. I saw Rina's assassin character at Alde Baran. I was hesitant to say hi because i was afraid that she would ignore me. Nevertheless, i still did say hi. I could'nt resist it. Anyways, what brought my feelings down once again was learning that she had partied (played) with another priest character. What made it a big deal for me was that she knows that i have a priest as a character and that she didnt asked me to party with her. She knows that one word from her and i'll be there at an instant. Add to that the fact that i basically created a priest character so that we could lvl up together and party up more often. I was extremely jealous and deeply hurt. From then on, i could no longer continue to play Ragnarok. I had lost my concentration and my will to play.   That night i found it very difficult to sleep. I closed my eyes and tried my best to clear my mind but to no avail. All of the sudden, tears started to drop from my eyes. I couldnt contain my depression once again.         
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Perfect song for me.. This songs says it all.. What I'm feeling inside..                         THE REASON                      by Hoobastank  i'm not a perfect person, there are many things i wish i didn't do  but i continue learning. i never meant to do those things to you  and so i have to say before i go, that i just want you to know   i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be  a reason to start over new, and the reason is you   i'm sorry that i hurt, its something i must live with everyday  and all the pain i put you through, i wish that i could take it all away  and be the one who catches your tears, thats why i need you to hear   i'm not a perfect person, i never meant to do those things to you  and so i hate to say before i go, that i just want you to know   i've found a reason for me, to change who i used to be  a reason to start over new, and the reason is you  i've found a reason to show a side of me you didn't know  a reason for all that i do, and that reason is you  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As far as i know, Rina and i have known each other for 2 -1/2 years now. We met through an online game in PinoyExchange. Our relationship has lasted for 1 yr and 6 months. Magseseven months na nga on the 10th of July kung walang incident na nangyari.   The way i see it, our relationship had lots of ups and downs. We are different in a lot of things. She was domineering and a workaholic, i was more of the shy and laid back type. She is a businesswoman while i came from a corporate lifestlye. She wanted a man who would dominate her, carry her, i on the other hand would always give in to her request because of the fear of making angry. I must admit that we had a rocky one but what made it last was that we where both trying to make the relationship work. We were both willing to give it a chance. For most part, i'd like to think that we had enjoyed each others company. Well.. i can only speak for myself. I was happiest the most when i was with her inspite of and despite of our differences and i am not ashamed to admit that.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The past week has been really painful for me. Me and Rina had a terrible fight that sunday evening. I'll be the first to admit that it was my fault to begin with. It all stems from my being too emotional. I let my feelings get the better of me once again. I ended up hurting her feelings and shaming myself along the way. I honestly tried to salvage whatever i can to what has happend but apparently i was too late. She called it quits. She wanted some time apart. Who am i to not give in to her demands. Love i believe is not selfish. It was hard for me to give in but i had no choice. I love her, but apparently, the feeling isnt reciprocated as much anymore. Anger and disappointment took over. Respect and trust is something that i value a lot. That is what i apparently lost that night according to her. The two and a half years of trust and respect that i worked hard for and earned .. gone at an instant..     And so we did part ways that night.   When i left my Lanshop that morning, i was in a relationship. It was far from perfect but hey, i cherished it. It was my first serious commitment to a person who i genuinely love and who i wanted to spend my life with. I valued it so much.          When i went home to my Lanshop, i was a different person. A person full of hurt and misery. I was empty inside, dying even. All my dreams and plans were shattered. Suddenly, i found myself lost once again.   Honestly, i didnt know how i even managed to drive myself to my shop that night. I can only thank the lord for keeping me safe.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Those who really know me might be suprised as to why i have started blogging. I don't like to write, nor do i enjoy jotting down my daily activities. So why the sudden change? Well, i believe that a person needs to somewhat find a way to release himself most specially in times of loneliness. To express how he feels, what he feels be it shallow or of great importance. Like it or not, at the end of the day, you only have yourself to depend and support.  This is my story. This is my life.         
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pop Quiz Hotshot!. Here's the deal.  Your GF asks you for some space. What do you do? What do you do?..    A. Give her the space she wants and wait for her to contact you. - Problem: What if she doesnt call u back? What if in the process she gets used to living a life without you? - Pros: You give her the time alone that she wants  - Cons: You dont get to see her nor hear from her. You begin to miss her like crazy  B. Try to constantly still keep in touch and still be there to prove how sincere and persevering you are. - Problem: What if she gets annoyed because she doesnt want you around and really wants time alone?  - Pros: There is a slim chance that she "might" take you back   -Cons: She gives you a cold and distant treatment which will surely hurt and leave a mark   AND THE CORRECT ANSWER IS:  ........................................
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For starters, i am not a jealous guy. I seldom allow myself to get affected by any interactions whatsoever by my partner. Its not because i am overconfident about myself, but more so because i have faith in my partner. I have faith in our relationship and the bond that we share. However this isnt the case anymore. For the past week, i have never been more jealous in my entire life. I know that at this point in time i have no right to be because of our current arrangement BUT I AM AND I CANT HELP IT. My GF's being distant and cold with me further aggreviates the feelings that i have. Maybe its because we are at a crucial point in our relationship. Maybe because the fear of losing her forever is getting to me. And yes, maybe i am getting impatient. Impatient because each day, each minute, each second that passes i feel I'm losing her and i dont want that to happen. I love her so much that its breaking me apart whenever i get the cold shoulder from her, whenever she treats me as if I'm not existing anymore. I so badly want her to love me once again. To treat me as an important person in her life once again..   When will my trial end. When will my suffering and agony stop..     They say a person has to face the consequences of his actions. This is what i am doing. Trying to handle as much as i can. However, after every hurt that i feel i begin to question if i do really deserve this treatment that i am getting. Regardless, i will be strong. I will try to endure each and every hurt that i experience as much as i can, to the best of my ability for i know that if ever she comes back to me, it will be worth it. I will be a complete person once again.    
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When i decide to put up my Internet Cafe business here in Las Pinas last January, i was very optimistic since this was a commercial area and the internet shops were not that many. From then on till now, a lot of new internet shops have spawned. This month alone, 3 more shops have emerged. For the past week, i have seen my sales decline at a certain extent. I find it alarming since we all target a specific market. No matter how many suki you have, you still cannot get as much profit like before since the abundance of competition makes it improbable.  I better think of a new gimik! I must keep my shop competative at all cost! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a heart to heart talk with someone which made me re-evaluate myself and my life. I've been having a hard time dealing with my situation lately and i think its about time that i took care of myself, fix myself. I have shed many tears and devoted a lot of time to this situation. I let my self get affected so much that i have forgotten everything around me, the other people who cares for me, and most of all i have forgotten to go on with my life.    Perhaps the most crucial mistake that I made in my relationship was that i gave it my all. I gave her my 100% love and devotion. I was prepared to face all the challenges that hit us as a couple. I was all set to spend my life with her. The only thing that i wasnt prepared for was she giving up on me and in the process losing her..  Times have changed now. I'm all alone, fazed and left in limbo. Sadly, i dont know if we'll ever be a couple again although I'm still open to possibilities. Only one thing is for sure. I am a better person now and i will be a much better person after this. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today i was suppose to go to the municipal of Las Pinas inorder to renew my business license but I didnt. Out of nowhere i had a change of heart. I wanted to visit Rina . I wanted to see her. Even just a glimpse. At the same time, i wanted to ask her out for a movie date. The last time i visited her which was a few days ago, she had promised that she would watch Spiderman 2 with me. Anyways, i was nervous but at the same time hopeful that she would accept my invitation, that she would remember. So before i drove to her house, i bought her a moist chocolate cake then got 2 advance tickets to the movie which was to be shown June 30. Upon arriving at her shop, i had asked one of her helpers to give the cake, the 2 tickets, and a note stating my invitation. I didnt bother giving it to her personally because she might get upset upon seeing me. I wanted to be careful with her. Afterwards, i drove home nervous yet anxiously waiting for a reply. After a few minutes while still on the rode, the message did arrive. She declined my invitation stating she already had plans...  Once again, my efforts were in vain. For the 3rd time this week, i drove from my shop all the way to hers with one thing in mind. To try to mend her feelings for me and spend quality time with her. And for the 3rd time this week, i went home a disheartened guy full of disappointment and hurt.   Honestly, i didnt expect that she take me back or that we be a couple at once. All i wanted was a sign. To see a glimmer of hope for me, for us. I didnt mind that i drove 2hrs to get to her place despite the stormy weather and traffic, nor the expenses that i had to shoulder. If it would somehow help in healing the wounds of our relationship then i'll gladly do it anytime.   Unfortunately, it didnt. I drove a long 2 hrs just to see her for 5 mins.. Then drove another 2-1/2 hrs.. going home disappointed, depressed and disheartened to the fullest. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nothing really special happened today. I went to the PLDT branch at Southmall and requested for my statement of account. Apparently my PLDT bills have pilled up. I havent receive any billing from them ever since my PLDT DSL was installed. I was shocked to see how much i was billed but it was legit so i paid it anyways. Wala nanaman ako money.. huhu..  Spiderman 2 opened today. Sayang, i would have loved to watch it. I usually watch highly anticipated movies on the 1st day of showing with...   Instead, i spent a quiet night alone. I guess its not so bad because i got to rest my worn out body.   Hmm.. Tama bang i-console ko sarili ko?..   Err... who am I kidding.. hehe     
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For the 1st time in over a year or more, i watched a movie by myself. Not really a big deal to some but for me it is. When i was still single, i usually watch movies alone and I'm really comfortable with that. I'm a loner type of a person and I'm not into gimik stuff. But ever since i got involved with her, that aspect of my life has changed. I always see to it that whenever a big movie comes, we watch it together. I watch the movie first with her.   Anyways, last night i decided to watch Spiderman 2. It was a nice movie. Nice effects, and i specially liked the story. Usually, when i watch a movie, i do it to relax myself. But this movie was different. It made me think a lot. The lessons it wanted to share reached me. For example. Love is not without problems and trials. Its the ability to work on the problem and trial that makes the love grow. In the case of Ms. Mary Jane Watson, she was blinded or troubled by what her mind wanted and what her heart really felt or desired. Good thing in the end she choose to go with her heart. It doesnt matter if adversities come as long as they face it together. And as a couple, they will conquer anything as long as they believe in each others love.  Hmm.. Makes me wonder when will my Mary Jane Watson come?..    Gosh.. will i analyze every movie that i watch from now on?.. scary.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ever have a negative gut feeling? Well.. I had one a few hours ago and I can't stop thinking about it. I hope that what I'm sensing is wrong.. (cross-fingers) .. =(
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am angry because i let myself down. Does that make sense? Hmmm.. perhaps i should elaborate further. I am angry at myself for failing to control the past situations that had recently occured in my life. I could have definitely handled it better. I am angry because i know and realize that I am the one that hinders my progress. Ako nagpapahirap sa sarili ko kasi i am still allowing myself to get affected by what is happening to her. I should change that. Dapat ilagay ko sa kokote ko na "I DONT HAVE THAT RIGHT ANYMORE!" I should stop thinking about her already and get on with my life. Whatever she does, whatever she wants, whomever she's involve with, its none of my business anymore.   Erick, get that into your thick skull then shove it to your heart! Its the brutal - cold truth.. Grrr...  Sometimes talaga it helps to just be out of reach even for a certain period (maybe out of the country?) and live out a totally new life kasi that way, i'd be forcing myself to move on. If i know nothing, i would not get hurt nor get jealous. I would be preoccupied. Ganun ginawa ko after graduating from college. Pero this is totally different most specially in terms of degree. I dont want to lose contact with her.   Come to think of it, that is what she wants and i understand her completely. She doesnt want to see me, play with me nor talk to me anymore because she wants to move on and forget. She wants to start a whole new life without me. And if i insist on communicating with her, i'd only hurt myself because for sure she would decline any of my invitations.  The next question that ponders in my head now is can i be good friends with someone that i had a relationship with. I hope so.. In time i guess.. When she is ready..     
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Has it ever occured to you that a simple PC game may affect your life more than you'd expect it would? I can attest to that because I am a living proof. Since it is an online game, expect lots of interactions from various real life individuals. The game teaches you the virtue of patience (in terms of boss hunts or item quests), comaraderie(when partying up), time and item management (when vending items), and of course strategy just like in real life. The one thing that i didnt anticipate was that it would affect my personal relationship as well.   Ragnarok was introduced to me by Rina. She was the first to play the game and then later on encouraged me to try it as well. From then on, i was hooked. I enjoyed playing the game but i loved it even more because we get to play together. This was something that we both could relate with and had enjoyed doing together. We used to belong to one "Guild" (group for those who are not familiar with the concept). Our guildmates used to admire us because seldom do you see real life couples play together. So they would always kid around and tease us, most specially me. They would give out flying kisses to her in hopes of trying to make me jealous or simply to make a joke. I must admit that sometimes it gets to me but more often than not i brush it aside because i know that this is just a game afterall. But times have changed. Since we are not together anymore, i find it very difficult to see her partying up or playing with another person(the same damn person all over again). For all i know, he might be even giving items and sharing stuff to her the way Rina and I used to. I can't help but feel furious at that person. Maybe because i feel that he is taking over my role. Maybe because i feel that i am getting replaced. I know that this is just a game and that i might be overreacting but still i cannot hide the way i feel inside. I know i have the right to feel this way but i also understand that i no longer have the right to impose my will over her. I often hesitate and think twice when going to Alde Baran, the place she often hangs out, the place i often see her. The chance of seeing and having a light conversation with her is truly a refreshing opportunity however the risk of seeing her particularly with that damn person all over again just makes my heart ache once again.   Sometimes i wonder if i should just leave the game for now to ease the hurtful feelings that i have. For as long as i play Ragnarok, i will always remember her. There will always be a part of me that would always wonder how she is doing. She was the one who brought the game into my life. She was the reason i started playing and is continuously playing. I enjoy playing Ragnarok but i dont think i'll ever play Ragnarok with as much hapiness, satisfaction, desire and love as i did before.     P.S : I think they should place a "hazardous to your heart" sign in the manual. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I feel better now compared to how i was the past few days. Is it because i dont care anymore? I don't think so. Its more of an acceptance of what has happened. The past weeks have been excruciating for me. I have lowered myself to a point wherein i gave up all my pride and as much as i hate to admit it, my self worth just to save something that i believed in. Yet in the end i still failed. It always takes two to make a relationship going. No matter how hard i try, it will not work so long as the other isnt willing anymore. It is always a two way thing. I was too stubborn to realize that or was it because i was too much in love that i didnt want to let go. Who's fault is it doesnt matter anymore as far as I'm concered because i believe that we both had our share of shortcomings. We both are responsible for our actions and the decisions we make. Bottomline, we had our chance and we didnt take advantage of it. We didnt take care of what we had. Only time can tell whether we will have another shot at this. Destiny will brings us back together if we are really meant to be. But only one thing is for sure. I must move on with my life. She apparently has and it would only be fitting that i do the same.   The next question i had asked myself is where should i begin. What should i do and where should i be? Should i try and find inspiration from someone else? Should i go on a self-exile so that i wont remember the feeling? I really don't know. To go back to how i was before the relationship isn't an easy task and honestly i dont think i'll ever be the same. It is always a burden to start all over again most specially if you are accustomed to doing something and being with someone. A sad reality but nonetheless i have to face. Perhaps i'll just have to face each day, make the most out of it and see where it leads me. For this is just a chapter in my life. A chapter that i will always keep close to my heart. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
            I'll always cherish the times we were together, the times when our hopes and dreams were one. May you find the happiness and peace that you deserve. I love you more than you'll ever know..  Always,   Erick          More Than You'll Ever Know   (Michael Ruff)  Take my hand We'll walk a while, We'll talk a while Feel my love, Always there beside you Be the one I know you'll tell me everything You are the one I cherish more than anything  I love you more than you'll ever know I love you more than you'll ever see More than my heart could ever show I love you more than you'll ever know  Think of me And know that I'll believe in you There'll always be This precious time together With every tear A love so strong No words could ever say A love to last forever  I love you more than you'll ever know I love you more than you'll ever see More than my heart could ever show I love you more than you'll ever know  Take my hand We'll walk a while, We'll talk a while Feel my love, Always there beside you Be the one I know you'll tell me everything You are the one I cherish more than anything  I love you more than you'll ever know I love you more than you'll ever see More than my heart could ever show I love you more than you'll ever know  Take my hand We'll walk a while, We'll talk a while Feel my love, Always there beside you Be the one I know you'll tell me everything You are the one I cherish more than anything  I love you more than you'll ever know I love you more than you'll ever see More than my heart could ever show I love you more than you'll ever know  Hooh...   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
            You said that all we needed was time apart and that you were not shutting your doors on me.. You said you'd txt me.. You said you'd call.. You said we needed to talk soon. How come none of those happened?.. How come i didnt get a chance?.. You made up your mind. You decided to leave me. I guess i have to accept that now. God knows how much I love you but I guess i have to set you free...      SET YOU FREE  --Side A--  And say that it's love Only cause when it's gone We end up being lonely So how are we to know That it just isn't so That we just have to let each other go There were many times When we shared precious moments But later realized they were only stolen moments So how are we to know That it just wasn't so That we just had to let each other go If loving you is all that means to me When being happy is all I hope you'd be Then loving you must mean I really have to set you free  Each day we meet my love for you Keeps growing stronger But everytime we meet Makes leaving you so much harder So how are we to know That this just wasn't so That we just have to let each other go If loving you is all that means to me When being happy is all I hope you'd be Then loving you must mean I really have to set you free  Letting go is not an easy task When smiling feels like I must wear this lonely mask It hurts deep inside And I just cannot hide That there's anguish at the thought That we should have to part If loving you is all that means to me When being happy is all I hope you'd be Then loving you must mean I really have to set you free  If loving you is all that means to me When being happy is all I hope you'd be Then loving you must mean I really have to set you free   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its been a while since i logged on to my friendster. I would have never imagined that i would end up changing my profile the next time i logged in. I browsed her friendster for a while. The first thing that i noticed was that she had changed her status. Masakit tignan and i-accept but it was the right thing to do. I had to change mine as well. Afterwards, i saved 2 pictures from her friendster. A solo picture of her and a picture of us together taken from Enchanted Kingdom which i think she would remove soon. It will serve as a reminder for me. My very first girl friend, the first girl i had introduced to my parents.. the girl i loved wholeheartedly without a shadow of a doubt and i am not ashamed to admit it to the whole world.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It has been a week or more that Rina and I have not communicated. It has been weeks since we last seen each and spoke to one another. I decided not to txt her anymore because i wanted to give her the space she wants and i guess i also wanted to accept the situation. To live a life without her. To go on and start living my own life. Last Saturday, around 7am i received a txt msg and call from her. It was an emergency and she needed my help. Unfortunately, my celphone got drain thus i wasnt able to hear my phone. When i woke up, i charged my phone and was completely surprised to see her txt. I called her unfortunately she got mad at me for failing to be there when she needed me and that she doesnt need me anymore. The more i insisted to provide help, the more she got agitated. I have waited for her to txt and call me for weeks and just when she did try.. i wasnt available. Tough luck for me. Anyways, to make the long story short i proceeded to her house to provide any help that i can do for her family despite the fact that she did not want me around.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a bit fatigued and kinda lonely. I could really use a nice warm hug and some soothing TLC from her...   hay... 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Nasaan Ka Na&nbsp; By Nyoy Volante with Mannos     Hatinggabi, di mapakali  Di makatulog, di makangiti  Bakit ganon? Hanggang ngayon nag-iisip, nagtatanong?   Sabi mo’y ako hanggang muling magkita  Bakit ngayon nasa piling ng iba?   Nasan ka na?  Nasan ka na?  Di ba’t pangako’y babalik ka  Hanggang ngayon nandito pa  Naghihintay, nag-iisa  Nasaan ka na?   Alaala mo nasa isip ko  Di mawaglit, di malayo  Mga yakap mong walang kasing diin  Di maniwalang di ka na akin   Sabi mo’y ako hanggang muling magkita  Bakit ngayon nasa piling ng iba?   Di ba pangako mo ika’y babalik  Naasan ka na?   Nasaan ka na?  Nasaan ka na?  Di ba’t pangako’y babalik ka  Hanggang ngayon nandito pa  Naghihintay, umaasa  Umaasang mahal, ako’y mahal mo pa  Nasaan ka na?  Nasaan ka na?  Ako’y iniwan na 
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its been a while since I've posted here. The reason is simple. I am trying to move on. Blogging has helped me a lot in realeasing the feelings that i have however, it has also become a reminder for me. It constantly reminds me of the recent relationship that i had. That is why the more i post, the more i think of her and its not helping me.  &nbsp;  People may call me idealistic or&nbsp;impractical but I simply do not care. I choose to follow my heart. Happiness does not rely on material things nor does it rely on other people. I believe that true happiness is where your heart is. I don't mind if I'm not well-off or as wealthy as some so long as i have my special someone to share my life with thru the good and bad times.  &nbsp;  This is how much i love her. I've taken so many verbal attack and abuse&nbsp;and yet I still love her with all my heart. She may not want me or love me anymore but that's her choice.&nbsp;Perhaps&nbsp;our degree of love is different. Perhaps my feelings for her is greater than what she's feeling for me.  &nbsp;  I am saddened by the fact that we both are unhappy. I am&nbsp; saddened because I thought i was the one who would bring happiness to her life. I am more saddened because i tried and yet i still failed 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have never loved a woman as much as I loved Rina. I was shattered when she decided to call it quits on me. As pathetic as it sounds for a guy, I tried everything that I possibly could for her to take me back. I stooped so low that I could not even imagine any guy with pride would do the things that I did just to get her back. I threw my entire ego and self respect just because I loved her so much and I wanted her back. Yet in the end, I still failed. And so, I had nothing else to do but to accept the situation. Something, which is easier, said than done.   The past two months have been excruciatingly painful for me. I tried to be strong the first few weeks. I really tried to handle the situation. Add to that the fact that someone is already courting her at this early stage of our breakup made my life so much miserable and difficult. It drove me crazy. Last week I could not contain all my grief. I literally attempted to take my own life. Yes, that was a foolish thing to do. I was bed ridden for 5 days as a result. For the past two months, my self worth and self-dignity was gone. I had given up on life. My depression had taken its toll on me. I loved her so much that the pain of losing her hurt me so deep it left me incapacitated. I wanted one thing, for my suffering to finally end.   Honestly, it was only a miracle that I am alive now. They said that my face was all dark and blue that they had prepared themselves for the worst-case scenario. My mom had a minor heart attack and my papy, being a strong person and all cried in front of me for the very first time. My family was deeply affected by the depression that I am currently facing. They have seen the change in me and on how I was slowly getting destroyed. They say that as parents, they could not bare see me like this and that if not for my little sister, they would have been goners. I didn’t want anybody else to suffer. I just wanted to move on and not get hurt anymore.  Up to now my love for Rina remains unblemished despite what has said and  happened. She means the world to me but I have also accepted the fact that we aren’t together anymore. I was trying to forget her because the pain of losing her stung like no other but I could not. Now I’ve realized that I cannot and will never forget her because I love her too much. Too much that I even offered my very life. Instead, I will just have to set aside my feelings for her. Unsure if I’ll ever get the chance to unleashes it again.    I’ve learned a lot from this experience. One is the value of life. We tend to disregard the importance of life when we feel down. We want a quick remedy to the hurt that we are feeling. Seldom do we realize that there are people around us who have a far deeper problem, people who would give anything to live a little longer. We neglect the blessings that we have. Second is up to how much Rina means to me. Up to what extent was I willing to give and do for her. They told me that I made a mistake. I left my guard down, I threw all my cards, I allowed her to see how much she means to me, that I left myself vulnerable. All I can say is that I don’t mind. Why? Because I love her so much and I’d rather want her to know that. I’m just being true to myself and I see no shame in doing that.       Today, I have a better outlook in life. I’m tired of the hurt that I am feeling and I want to channel the feeling in a positive way. Being gloomy and depressed every single day won’t get me anywhere. It will bring my downfall. I have to fight it. I have to fight for my family; I have to fight for my friends, and most of all I have to fight for myself. I must go on living. I have challenge death and I somehow won. I was given another chance so I must make the most out of it. I will make my life better and more stable so that someday.. someday when my special someone comes.. be it my dearest Rina or someone else.. i will be prepared. I'll make sure its forever.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I havent been in good terms with my parents the past days. We havent talked nor engage ourselves in a conversation. I prefer it this way. Masama loob ko because of something that i had found out, because of something that they did particularly my papy. I value my privacy a lot. I believe everyone needs his/her own privacy. Heck, even married people need there own privacy. They didnt respect mine. They read my personal site. Something which i currently hold dear to my heart. This is where i express myself. This is where i say what i feel. They didnt value it. Just because it is posted in the internet doesnt mean anybody can read it. No, you have to know the specific address inorder for you to access it. He apparently found mine. Maybe because i sometimes do my blog here at home. Regardless, that is beside the point for me. If he wasnt persistent on knowing my site, if he valued my privacy, if he respected my space and feelings he would not have regularly read my site. As parents, i do understand the concern and care that they want to provide. I appreciate all that really but there are boundaries on how far you must go. He has crossed the line.   He often asks me when we talk how come I'm not as close to him as before. I honestly didnt know why back then but now i do. Its because of his own doing. He has changed throughout the years. I've noticed that. He is still a good father and provider. Its just that there are things and attitudes that i slowly began to notice that made me feel uncomfortable, that made me distant from him.   I value my privacy a lot unfortunately, i lost some of it when he decided to invade it. I.. am angry at him for that although he is still my father and i still love him.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>