<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have now spent about 2 weeks in Portland, really enjoying the "vacation" my company sent me out here for. I have been feeling the wanderlust for the last few years and this last year has finally taken it's toll on me. In my quest for rediscovery, I have found myself longing for new stomping grounds, different attitudes and changes in latitude. Jimmy Buffett comes to mind. I have always hated the fucking desert, and I wonder why I still keep coming back to it. I grew up in a blasted shithole of a town. Left it to join the Navy, spending 4 years on a desert island. Now I spent the last 8 years watching my little city struggling to survive. It's kind of creepy how the environment changes the mentality of those living in it. My biggest observation here is how there is a sense of life in everything here, where Albuquerque is filled with despair and that scraping sound you hear is everybody trying to scratch out a life in this hell hole. Do I sound jaded? Maybe. All I know is that everything in New Mexico just seems really tired, tired of struggling, too tenacious to just give up and just let the sun bleach its bones. I suppose there is a certain beauty in the desolation and the pristine starkness of it all, but I just need a change of scenery.   I suppose there will be things I will really miss. My little neice is growing like a weed. My brother and his antics will be hard to replace. I have a little circle of friends, people who I enjoy spending time with when I can and the respect we share. I suppose the biggest miss would probably be B. Timing is everything, I guess. 
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I have decided that I have enough interesting crap happening in my life that I should start documenting it, sharing various photos of my indiscretions and generally making a nuisance of myself on the web.  No promises, no warranties expressed or implied, names have been changed to protect the innocent.  Do not suck a dissolution thing and not to be used as a food source.  If you like what is here, let me know.  If you don't, let me know. (like I would change it anyway, sheez!)
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      has arrived in Albuquerque.  All the doors in my house are stuck in their frames and Ginger has decided to play hide and seek with me by locking herself in the garage.  No small feat for a dog.  I paid her back by repeatedly shaving her.  She paid me back by waking me up while I was trying to sleep today.  I paid her back by putting on her electrical collar.  We will see how this ends.  K and I get to talk today, I guess she needs closure.  I hope that is all, I know I am pretty horny when I wake up (or go to sleep, or eat, or watch a movie...)  Anyway, I would hate to hurt her feelings, but I don't do make up sex, especially if I am not making up.  T decided to stay with her guy, and I say hooray for her!  One less pain in my ass to deal with.  Still regret wasting the time I did on her.  What a waste of $17.95 in raw materials.  I have started my special diet again.  Esentially, don't eat nothing till your face is ready to cave in, then eat just enough so it doesn't.  Repeat as necessary.  I enjoyed my trips to Oregon and Texas and I have a date with B Monday, and I want to fit in my slacks.  That and the hunger fed adrenaline rush is better than coffee.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from a trip to Austin for work, yeah work.&nbsp; I spent 5 days partying my ass off.&nbsp; Not bad considering the company paid for it.&nbsp; Met some crazy ladies, had a great time.&nbsp; A shame I am such a prude, no telling how many diseases I could have caught there.&nbsp; Texas wemmen are pretty crazy when they get a little alcohol in them.&nbsp; I missed Boo and Ginger terribly, but they were well taken care of.&nbsp; Came back after my breakup with K, looks like it will be alright eventually, just have to "talk" some more.&nbsp; (jeez)  J is still interested and a new twist has developed.&nbsp; B had a birthday!&nbsp; B is also single again.&nbsp; And we have a date, of sorts.&nbsp; I always saw something more in her, but just now she has started to become the beautiful woman I saw in her.&nbsp; It is nice to see a woman in between still having dreams and not yet at the point that some asshole has sufficiently fucked with her mind to the point of no return.&nbsp; Hope that never happens to B.  J has just about given me all of her game that I want.&nbsp; There is a warning about pretty girls, they usually have their heads fucked up at an early age.&nbsp; It is mostly not worth the trouble to waste your time trying to deal with it.&nbsp; I find her little games amusing, but not so amusing that I want to waste my time with them.&nbsp; We will see if we ever actually date, or how long it will take before I write her off.&nbsp; Shame though, bet she looks great naked... 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      barks the software, flash the message, somethings out there...  Comfortably back at home after my trip to Portland, what a wonderful time!!  I am definitely going through with my evil scheme, er plans to move there.  I have been watching the weather (I hate the cold) and the weather is never colder than Santa Fe, so why not?  There is lots of things I love to do there that aren't here, fishing, cruising, blah blah.  Besides the babes in Oregon are SOOO MUCH hotter than the ones here.  Chatted with my boss about moving, he is working secret plans also to move to Portland.  I guess we both appreciate it for what it is.  That and growing cows is easier there.  It is over with miss K.  After spending a little time with a person, you know their capabilities.  I have a huge trust issue and don't like to place trust in people outside their abilities.  After practically begging me to trust her to pick me up from my trip, and the ensuing conversations afterward, it is clear that we are on two vastly different paths in our lives.  There is no future there.  I must have rocks in my head.  I have finally decided to give the lovely and charming miss J a chance.  I have found in my experience that the more beautiful the woman is, the more jacked up her mind is.  Not to make a blanket statement or anything like that, but the "nice" guys are really intimidated by them and the only ones they get exposed to are the assholes.  Unfortunately, I guess, miss J is about the most physically stunning creature I have ever laid eyes on.  Paris Hilton has nothing on this woman.  That being said, she has passed the preliminaries and I have decided to make a date with her.  Only problem is my trip to Austin.  We couldn't get it together between work and stuff.  We'll see if she has the patience to wait till I get back, heh.  Another interesting twist, the lovely and somewhat misguided miss T has finally decided to regain her independence.  She will stay with me for a month, but only because of the history we had together as friends.  I feel a deep caring and concern for her that makes me want to see her in a better place, with or without me.  I wish her well with her apt. searching and we will see how it works out.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't know when I'll be back again.  I'm really gonna miss Oregon, the beauty of it all.  My "ride" failed to show as predicted, then commences to tell me how she is so intolerant of people who aren't dependable or reliable, or how they just want to use you.  Lot's of things to think about.  Got a notice from the city to greet me at the door, don't they know I have been out of town?  What the hell is wrong with them anyway.  At least Ginger was happy to see me.  Boo pretended I didn't exist, in true gato form.  My peev of the moment?  People that won't SHUT THE HELL UP on a plane.  I buy a magazine, (next time I'll buy porn, if I seem like a creep, maybe they won't talk to me.) have it on the tray, in every lull of her conversation, I pick it up, find an article and she starts up again.  I faked sleeping, didn't work.  I started to talk religion, just to get her to stop.  It worked for about 2 minutes.  I don't even know why I bother.  At least if she wasn't married, I might have been interested.
    
</post>


</Blog>