<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I went to the gym yesterday expecting them to have me taking all kinds of stress tests etc.  I was actually disappointed when that didn't happen because I was soooo psyched for it. They went over my application, weighed and measured me and set up an appointment for today for me to actually meet the trainer and go over the equipment and the routines. (Gulp). But omg...a few hours caffeine free had an affect on me I wasn't expecting.  I was shaking, literally.  My hands were quivering, I was antsy and nervous, and at one point burst into tears, all due to lack of caffeine.  I wonder if this is how an addict feels waiting for a fix.  Ironically thanks to the Nicoderm patch I didn't go through this when I quit smoking in January. Maybe later this year (2004 certainly has been a year of changes for me so far!) I will take a look at my caffeine consumption - I don't want to say eliminate it...omg no...but perhaps limit it a little - so I am not acting like some wild-eyed-crazy-crack-whore looking for her next fix if I have to go 5 hours without a tea or coffee.  I am going on my first date in 6 years this afternoon.  Just coffee....low key...nothing wild and crazy.  And I am nervous as a kitten.  Does one wear the tiara and evening gown at Tim Horton's at 2 in the afternoon?  Or is that overkill? All the "what ifs" are going through my brain as I search for another reason to cancel, back out and run to the relative safety of my keyboard.  But I cant, I have done that to this poor guy twice already.  It's time to shit or get off of the pot, as they say. Yikes.    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think I am on a health kick. Either that or my mid-life crisis has hit early.  In the last 2 weeks I have rejoined Weight Watchers (for the umpteenth time), bought - and riden - a bicycle, for the first time in over 20 years and joined a gym.  I must be nuts. (Who am I kidding? I am actually kinda excited about it all.)  I go this morning to the gym for my fitness test. I am gonna be weighed, measured, poked and prodded whilst they decide how many reps on what machine will best torture every muscle in my body until it screams for mercy.  I am not even there yet and already they have started their torture.  Part of the pre-test condition is no caffeine for 8 hours prior to the test. OMG you people are a bunch of sado-masochists!  I'd sell my soul right now for an extra large Tim Hortons. The boy - for whom this whole gym malarky was started - goes for his test later this afternoon.  He seems pretty keen himself...and isn't too upset about the idea of his mom joining too. Ahhhh, a bonding moment for mother and son.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't have daughters, but I am quite sure they haven't changed much since my own teenage years. I am curious to know who's face graces the wall's of Canada's teen bedrooms these days however. Pop poster icons that teenaged girls swoon over - have things really changed that much in 22 years?  My bedroom wall circa 1978 was adorned by John Travolta. Grease was  THE  teen movie we all grew up loving. And the double album movie soundtrack was  THE  teen album (yes vinyl, stop rolling your eyes) that we played until we knew every word by heart. John is all the rage again today thanks to Pulp Fiction resurrecting his movie career; but back then, pre-Kelly Preston, he was just this young dimple chinned,  blue-blue-blue  eyed hunk who looked amazing in a tight T-shirt. (H'mmm, the bicep and chest thing must have started earlier for me than I previously realized).   The next major heart-throb that I can recall gracing my Coverdale Walk walls was Greg Evigan. He was the star of an American tv show we had started getting from the US called "BJ and the Bear". This must have been circa 1979-80. He was drop dead gorgeous! He had a jaw line that was just like omg! My fascination with him went beyond posters and also included magazine articles etc. Then I heard he had gotten married....sigh....Next ?!  Now we slide into my "this is as close as I got to 'punk' era" circa 1980-1981. King of  my  wild frontier for sure - Adam Ant aka Stewart Goddard. Looking back now he was a skinny white kid who wore make-up, but at the time I was totally hooked and followed the band with an almost Beatlemania type adoration. Only thing physically I can say about Adam as my poster boy is he had beautiful cheekbones and eyes that pierced.  Finally...my last poster boy - the man who's face finally came off my walls when I got married at age 19. Martin Kemp from Spandau Ballet circa 1982-1986. It was definitely the eyes and the cleft chin that left me weak at the knees over Martin. He apparently in later years - unbeknownst to me - went on to become a tv soap star on Eastenders in the UK. See? Another reason I should have stayed in the UK!  Today at age 30-mumble, my walls, dresser and night-tables are host to another whole new selection of "poster boys". Notwithstanding my Fireman Calendar - it was for charity ....honest ! (ahem!) My poster boys (and girls) are those that are near and dear to my heart, the Boy is the most prominently displayed, as well he should be. From infant to Drum Major and Petty Officer Second Class, I have enough photos of this young man to wallpaper the Sistine Chapel if required. It's because of him, I am the person I am today. I like to think that that is a good thing. The other poster boy remains Maybe. It will get easier I know, and eventually I will be able to take those photos down and put them away. But for now I am still enjoying not only the eyes, and the biceps...but knowing the total package. The man himself, not just the eyecandy. My poster girl is mum. A woman I admire beyond words. I haven't talked about her much so far, either in real life or online. I think sometime this weekend I will take the time to sit and put some thoughts together on her. And finally dad. His first anniversary is fast approaching, so I will save my thoughts on him until that day.  And you thought poster boys were just pretty faces torn out of a teen magazine....sheesh ...what do you know!? LOL  This whole blog is turning more into a memoir than a diary, but hey I like it so :P with brass knobs on the end if you don't! 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    John Travolta - the first crush. For me it's always been about the eyes, the chin, the biceps and the chest.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Greg Evigan definitely a pretty boy. Yes, I am sure someone will make a chimp comment!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Adam Ant - not my typical poster boy, but he was hypnotic.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Martin Kemp - my last poster boy - and my favourite.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I keep in quasi-regular touch with my ex-boyfriend "Biff" (he of the frozen peas love letter) via email.  He is my 'go-to' computer god who has rebuilt and tweaked my old clunker Atari-wannabe computer so many times it practically rolls over for a belly rub every time it sees him.  Quasi-regular sometimes means dropping a bombshell, as he did 2 years ago in an email when he casually mentioned that he had gotten married the previous summer.  This from the commitment-phobe who lived with me for 7 years and avoided any mention of marriage after the first year.  Naturally I was struck by the "Harry Met Sally" replay of my life yet again.  "It wasn't that he didn't want to get married, it was that he didn't want to get married to me."  I must confess a certain amount of self-satisfied smugness when he mentioned earlier this year that they had divorced.  Even though in the 6 years since we split up and we never contemplated reconciling, I still have a soft spot for my hippy-dippy DJ.  So I was saddened when I received another one of his email bombshells this morning.  He has decided he has had enough of being homesick and he is moving home to Britain.  He and I are both guilty of looking at life back home through rose coloured glasses (as anyone who has read  urlLink "Ay Up Me Duck" can attest).  He however hasn't been back to his small Scottish village since he emigrated here as a pre-teen 30 years ago.  I am sure no amount of "Coronation Street" or "Keeping Up Appearances" will prepare him for the culture shock .  And I am as jealous as hell.  Green with envy.  The ability to just pack up and leave, no ties, no commitments, no responsibilities.  The world is his oyster.  On the flip side someone could look at his nomadic, reclusive lifestyle and feel the emptiness of a man in his forties who can basically pack his whole life up in a kerchief and has no one to account to (or for), except himself.  Naturally I wished him well...and asked what he was doing with his computer. :D 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This week seems to be flying by (not that I am complaining) but it was a very pleasant surprise when I woke up this morning to realize that it was Thursday already and the weekend is in sight - especially as seeing that Monday is a civic holiday here in Canada, so I get a LONG WEEKEND! Woo hoo!   I am feeling restless, I can feel a day trip to Niagara Falls or some other touristy spot coming on! I will run the idea past the boy on the weekend and see if he's up for a wee trip on the Maid Of the Mist - heck it's not like it's a "3 hour tour" - lol.   Weight Watchers went well last night, for anyone who gives a flying fart, another 1.6lbs which has brought me over the 10lb mark, so I was awarded my 10lb ribbon.&nbsp; I now stand at a total of 11.2lbs.&nbsp;&nbsp; I quietly&nbsp;scoff and roll my eyes&nbsp;at the childish awards of stickers and ribbons as signs of achievement, but you can bet your bottom dollar, I made sure I had my activity sticker (for working out at the gym) and my 10lb ribbon before I left there yesterday! Woo hoo - yay me! Another 9lbs and I will take another set of photos for the  urlLink web page  to see if there has been any visible improvement.   In an attempt to be responsible (huh?) and get things back on track after the expenses and upheaval of the last 12 months I decided to go sit and talk to my banker yesterday.&nbsp; ironically things aren't as bad as I thought.&nbsp; Having said that, I wont be making any large purchases in the next little while whilst I get some debt paid down.&nbsp; In addition we are going to open an RRSP account - planning for retirement.&nbsp; It's something that I have been meaning to do, and wanting to do for the last 10 years, so now I will be playing catch-up to get it all done.&nbsp; This may end up putting the kybosh on a few of my plans in the near future, but I am keeping an open mind.   OK - boring post today, just an odds and sods entry I know.&nbsp; Keeping my fingers crossed for something more exciting in the coming days.&nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Music has always been near and dear to me.&nbsp;&nbsp;For me music is connected with emotions and memories.&nbsp; I can hear a particular song and be instantly transported back to a time and place, recalling it&nbsp;with such clarity, that I can almost reach out and touch it.&nbsp; I wont attempt to cover them all in one blog, but will interspace them over the next few weeks.&nbsp; I  wont  apologize for my choice in song or artist,&nbsp; they were the songs of the time, and the memories they evoke.&nbsp; Memories don't tend to worry about what is cool and hip, just what matters and what is near and dear to your heart.        urlLink Tom Jones - What's new pussycat?     I was 4 years old, still living in Canada at this point, circa 1971-72.&nbsp; I was Jones-The-Voice's greatest mini-fan.&nbsp; Four year olds aren't self conscious about life, about singing, about dancing, they don't worry about who is watching, or who is pointing and laughing, they just do it, wholeheartedly with gusto and enthusiasm.&nbsp; I miss that redheaded imp, who freshly pajama-ed and pink faced from the bathtub would "bellock" *  at the top of her lungs into her skipping rope microphone, stood on top of mummy's leather ottoman, performing right there alongside Tom. Years later I found the CD version of the vinyl album I had owned as a child.&nbsp; "Tom Jones in Las Vegas".&nbsp; A picture of the man from Wales on the cover, resplendent in a blue&nbsp;cat suit and&nbsp;bare chested.&nbsp;&nbsp;Needless to say I bought it...and every now and then when my inner child needs to sing about the "Green, Green Grass of Home", "It's Not Unusual", "Help Yourself"&nbsp;or&nbsp; ask "What's new pussycat?" I throw on that CD&nbsp; and let the magic course through my veins again. Kinda like I did this morning, on the highway driving into work with "(It looks like) I'll never fall in love again"&nbsp; - a definite bellocking good&nbsp;chorus!       "bellock"*   - A word my Geordie grandmother used to use all the time for singers who screech from the pits of their stomachs.&nbsp; "That's bellocking, not singing!" Not a complimentary term, an example of a bellocking singer would be  urlLink Lena Zavaroni . &nbsp;Not found in the dictionary (not mine at any rate) but is surely a derivative of the word  "bellow" , meaning to emit a loud roar...or even  "bellows" , a device with airbag emitting a stream of air when squeezed.&nbsp; LOL - you old windbag! And not far off a  "bellyache"  which is what I am getting trying to explain " bellock" &nbsp; - I should have just said, "screeched at the top of her lungs".  
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Tom Jones  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I knew it had to all end somewhere but didn't really want it to be now.&nbsp; I received notice yesterday that my special shift accommodation has ended and will not be renewed.&nbsp; I am to resume working the compressed shift schedule (same as the officers on the road).&nbsp; So in a nutshell that means only 2 weekends off in 5, and I will have to work statutory holidays (unless they naturally&nbsp;fall on a regularly scheduled&nbsp;day off - "RDO").&nbsp; I will be back working the graveyard shift and afternoons, in addition to the day shift I have been working.&nbsp; The upside to this is (she said searching for the silver lining),&nbsp;that I will have stretches of multiple days off at a time, instead of 2.&nbsp; I will get shift bonus.&nbsp; I will accumulate lieu time once again, and I will be able to work overtime if I want to. Which would sure help with those bills I want to get paid off.&nbsp; They haven't given me a start/effective date as of yet, I just hope they don't say "As of tomorrow..." My only request in all of this is that I want to switch platoons.&nbsp; I have no desire to return to my old platoon. Numerous issues, most going back to last year.&nbsp; I haven't had the opportunity to make this request official, but hope to do so today.   The other option to consider is the main reason I have been hanging on to this job recently is because of the shift accommodation.&nbsp; Now that has been eliminated, there is nothing to prevent me looking for alternative opportunities, either within the service or out.&nbsp; For example, the fire department, or another police department, or just another section of this force.&nbsp; I certainly have a lot to consider.   OK enough silver lining searching, I need a few minutes to mope.     
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The two redheads.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Once we got everyone up and moving yesterday morning it was so nice to go for a leisurely brunch over at "The Sunset Grill", my local greasy-spoon cafe.&nbsp; Just a mom & pop type operation, but omg do they know how to make breakfast!&nbsp;   By noon we were back at the house to take a few goodbye photos (yes, yes, will post them here later or on the web site - hold your horses) and then it was time for us all to head out.&nbsp; Me, to go pick up the boy, who had already called to see if it was safe to come home yet, and my friends, to hit the McDonald-Cartier Highway, more commonly known as Highway 401, homeward bound.   The boy had an excellent day in Kingston from all accounts.&nbsp; I spoke to the girlfriend's mother on the phone yesterday whilst he was still sleeping.&nbsp; She describes her daughter running and launching herself into his arms yesterday as "right out of a movie".&nbsp; They spent 12 hours together on her pass from camp but had to be back at the barracks by 2300hrs.&nbsp;&nbsp;They packed alot of activities into that short time.&nbsp; Meals, the beach, swimming off the pier, going to the movies (he watched "I, Robot" with her even though he saw it just last week himself).&nbsp; They didn't make it back to Ajax until after 1 am, so his spending the night at their house last night worked out rather well, and to everyone's advantage.   The rest of the day was really nice.&nbsp; We did our weekly Sunday afternoon  urlLink matinee at the cinema &nbsp;and then swung by Blockbuster to pick up a movie and a video game.&nbsp; I was admittedly walking on egg-shells with the boy, I was expecting a frosty reception over my weekend guests.&nbsp; Thankfully his own happy weekend overshadowed any concerns he had over mine.&nbsp;   He certainly has a beaut of a sunburn on his back, however.&nbsp; He casually mentioned that swimming in the lake is much different to a pool because of the currents.&nbsp; Obviously he now has my  full  attention, as he goes on to tell me that he swam out a bit too far and almost didn't make it back.&nbsp; He was so exhausted at one point swimming back to shore,&nbsp;against the current,&nbsp;that he went under a couple of times.&nbsp; I'll leave you with that thought as I go and recover my heart, which is  still  hammering&nbsp;away double time in my throat.     
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Have you ever sat and chatted with a friend on the phone and the conversation just flows effortlessly? Completing each other's thoughts, impatient to share news, thoughts, opinions, and in general filling the hours without realizing how long you have been talking. You hang up reluctantly, but with a smile, knowing that despite everything else, someone out there thinks you are pretty special - or at least does a good job of making you feel that way. Whether you are talking about gardening, polishing or comparing favourite tipples. That's the way friendships are supposed to be - just like it was tonight - like a comfortable hug from a warm cozy sweater.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Shan and Ran arrived late yesterday afternoon on their way back from Montreal.&nbsp; They made it here in under 6 hours, which was a huge improvement on the 10 hours it took them to get *to* Montreal from Thorold last weekend.&nbsp; Needless to say I am just thrilled to see Shan again.&nbsp; She is one of those people that you feel like you have known all your life.&nbsp; She&nbsp;has a natural ability to make people feel comfortable, less self conscious&nbsp; and able to let their guard down.   We had a quiet evening, went through some photos that they took in Montreal and Quebec City,&nbsp; digital photography is so perfect for this NOW generation.&nbsp;"While you wait"&nbsp;used to be something special, now it is the expected norm.&nbsp; A perfect example&nbsp;is when I took the boy's watch in to be repaired a few weeks ago.&nbsp; I was shocked when they wrote up a work order and told me it would be 6-8 weeks as they would have to send it back to the&nbsp;manufacturer.&nbsp; What do you mean?&nbsp;&nbsp;You can't fix it right here and right now?!&nbsp; I would even have settled for them giving me new watch!&nbsp; It's just the level of service I have come to expect -&nbsp;nay demand - so when it suddenly isn't available it surprises me.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Anyways, back to the photos ....digital photography has totally transformed the way we think of photography.&nbsp; The results are right here, right now, and with a tweak here, zoom, lighten, brighten, smudge, blurr, crop and delete now even YOU can look like Cindy Crawford.....in fact...hey....isn't that Cindy's body you have pasted your face onto?!?   The rest of the evening&nbsp;we settled in with munchies to watch a movie on TV.&nbsp; Wild exciting lives we lead eh?&nbsp; I think the nearest I have been to anything more hip like "clubbing" was the desire to club a few of the people I deal with at work over the head.&nbsp;&nbsp;After a couple of glasses of wine, and two shots of penod and lemonade I was toast.&nbsp; I make a lousy hostess, I was falling asleep in front of the movie.&nbsp; I think this wild party animal was in bed before 1am. Probably not an exciting evening for my guests, but I would imagine after&nbsp;the&nbsp; 6 hour drive they had yesterday they weren't complaining any.   I gave up my room to my house guests.&nbsp; and&nbsp;initially considered bunking on the couch myself, the boy's room however&nbsp;looked relatively safe after I cleaned it, so I decided that was the more comfortable&nbsp;place to be.&nbsp; Despite the screams of protest his box spring makes every time you move, it&nbsp;is surprisingly comfortable and I slept like a log.&nbsp; (Hope I didn't snore like I was sawing said log too).&nbsp; The boy&nbsp;stayed overnight at his girlfriend's parents.&nbsp; He doesn't approve of my meeting online&nbsp;friends in real life.&nbsp;&nbsp;He is entitled to that opinion, and if I was meeting every&nbsp;Tom, Dick and Harry,&nbsp;he would have a valid point.&nbsp; However Shan and I have been friends for a long time, she has been my shoulder to cry on over many of life's calamities ...and I like to think I for her at times too.&nbsp; In fact Randy asleep in my bedroom is the first man who has even  laid there,  never mind  slept  there, in - omg&nbsp;- over 6 years! &nbsp;So I am&nbsp;hopeful that eventually the boy will&nbsp;warm a little to my friends. &nbsp;The very fact that I made it through the night without being disemboweled in my sleep should impress him incredibly.   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Up bright and early this morning to get the boy moving and human (not an easy task).&nbsp; His girlfriend of 2 years is spending the summer as a Staff Cadet at  urlLink RMC  in Kingston.&nbsp;&nbsp;She has this weekend off and her parents and brother are driving up for the day to visit.&nbsp; They have invited the boy along too.&nbsp; Needless to say he has been showered, dressed and ready to go for over an hour, and his ride isn't due for another 10 - 15 minutes!&nbsp; Keen? Nah, whatever gave you that idea??!   Despite other misgivings, I will admit I appear to have raised a romantic, caring young man. When I see some of the thoughtful things he does&nbsp;or makes especially for her, I smile and hope that my influences are at work there somewhere.&nbsp; This time he has purchased a book she has been wanting for some time, and he has no doubt has put an inscription inside.&nbsp;   They say "Te Amo" instead of "I love you" and&nbsp;had he this engraved&nbsp;on&nbsp;the silver bracelet&nbsp;he gave her at&nbsp;the prom, instead of a corsage. He sings to her on the phone, makes CD's for her to listen to and is teaching himself the guitar in hopes of conquering&nbsp; "Grow old with you", their song from "The Wedding Singer". Watching them brings back happy memories of my own courtships over the years, and makes me realise what is missing in my own life.&nbsp; It's all very well to build fortresses of protection against the hurt and pain of having your heart broken.&nbsp; But there is alot of truth in the adage, "It's better to have loved and lost, than never to have loved at all."&nbsp; In fact, is it truly called living if there is not love?&nbsp; Or are we simply going through the motions? A thought to ponder later.&nbsp;   My thoughtful, caring son has presented me with another dilemma.&nbsp; He received a phone call from a friend just a few minutes ago (7am).&nbsp; Seems the young man in question has managed to get himself kicked out of the house, and is looking for a place to crash for a while. (" While ": definition - a night, a day, a week, forever). My initial reaction was no.&nbsp; The young man in question is a relatively new friend, not someone I have had alot of dealings with, or to be honest I particularly warm to - I have a problem with people who wont look me in the eye when the speak to me or when I speak to them.&nbsp; From what I have heard (and I have no doubt only heard half of it) he is quite the typical sullen teen.&nbsp; The best way I can think to describe him is "goth",&nbsp; both in his look and in his mood.&nbsp; The boy is telling me that his friend snuck out of the house last night around 11pm and didn't arrive home until after 6am this morning, his parents were waiting.&nbsp; Hence the phone call.&nbsp; Now I am quite sure this is just another in a long line of indiscretions and blatant rule breaking.&nbsp; My initial reaction is to say no, slam the door, and check my wallet is still intact.&nbsp; But in the back of my mind I am thinking what kind of example am I setting my own child?&nbsp;   Where is the charity, kindness and consideration?&nbsp; The willingness to hold out a helping hand to others in need?&nbsp; If the shoe were on the other foot, and lord knows there have been times when I have been sorely tested, I would like to think there was a safe place that the boy could go whilst our mutual tempers cooled.&nbsp; I think of parents who have been driven to putting their teens out of the house, locking the door after missed curfews etc. in the hopes of "teaching them a lesson".&nbsp; And have no doubt the parents of  urlLink Leslie Mahaffey  relive that lesson every single day of their lives.&nbsp;   I told the boy to have his friend call back if&nbsp;can't he couldn't find anywhere else to go.&nbsp; We don't have an extra bedroom, but there is a quasi rec-room in the basement (think "That 70's show"), and he could always crash there for a while.&nbsp; My initial reaction was based on not wanting to bring a troubled teen into my home to lead my own teen astray.&nbsp; Although my own teen is quite capable of bringing his own brand of havoc upon himself with relative ease.&nbsp; But at the end of the day, he is still my baby, and I still have to protect him, no matter what.     Post Script: July 25th 2004. Just in case anyone was following this and wondering on the outcome. It appears the young man in question will not be needing to take me up on my offer of a roof over his head, but he sends his thanks and appreciation via my son.&nbsp; At this time he still remains under his parent's roof.&nbsp; I am sure that like most people, especially family members, &nbsp;who love each other dearly, things were said in the heat of the moment&nbsp; - and probably regretted instantly.&nbsp; Cooler heads have prevailed and I hope they&nbsp;can&nbsp;find a middle ground they can both live with.      
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've been relatively quiet this week, don't know if anyone noticed, but quiet for me at any rate. A couple of times I have started posts&nbsp;and then deleted them, or I sit and look at a blank screen - mind going a million miles a minute - but nothing coming out.&nbsp; It seems the moment I decided to censor my blog, I lost respect for it's validity and authenticity. Weird I know, I delete an abusive and derogatory post aimed at making me feel inferior and unloved - and I feel guilty for it! Go figure!&nbsp; Damn, I'd easily put a shrink's kids through college , and the fees would probably cover the post-grad studies too, trying to figure out why my mind works the way it does at times.&nbsp; Anyways this is just me rambling, hoping that "talking" about it will help resolve it in my mind.&nbsp;   Of course the fact that I censored myself by resolving not to talk about "maybe" anymore &nbsp;doesn't help either.&nbsp; Especially seeing as for me it's still so fresh.&nbsp; Tell me I cant have or do something and suddenly it's all I think about.&nbsp; Yes, it still bothers me&nbsp; beyond belief.&nbsp; It's going to take a while for this one to heal.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just my luck!&nbsp; For years I have been threatening to move to S. Africa where the larger woman is desired because of her size, not despite it.&nbsp; I would be worth at least an extra goat or chicken.&nbsp; It seems however that Western commercialism has even invaded the little grass huts in the village. (Must be since they all got cable).   According to the September issue of Oxygen the British Psychological Society is claiming that television images of skinny Western women have having a profound impact.&nbsp; For the first time ever, women told researchers they were dissatisfied with their bodies and wanted to be thinner.&nbsp; Weight was traditionally regarded as a symbol of prosperity and status in rural South Africa, but more and more women are giving in to the Western ideal of thinness equaling beauty because they think that is how men want them to look now.&nbsp;   Just for the record ...this sucks!&nbsp; Where to emigrate to now?&nbsp; Do they appreciate an extra inch or two of blubber up at the North Pole - or is Santa (that icon of Western Commercialism) a fatophobe too?   Just as a size observation seeing as this post was about weight.&nbsp; I was at shocked to notice on the weekend how much weight that amazon goddess Queen Latifah has lost.&nbsp; I saw&nbsp;a trailer for&nbsp;her new movie "Taxi" and I didn't recognise her at first.&nbsp; It was more her voice that finally made me realise.&nbsp; Whilst I am pleased for the individual that&nbsp;she has been working on her weight issues, I&nbsp;hope she is doing this safely, sensibly and for the right reasons, and NOT just because Hollywood&nbsp;says so.&nbsp; Since her early days of MTV/movies and television&nbsp;I have been a fan, I hope she isnt finally&nbsp;buckling to the system.&nbsp;&nbsp; Like she cares what us little fat people think, but it was nice to see a woman finally making it big based on her talent, drive and personality, not the&nbsp;size of her booty. &nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       W  is for  Wednesday  -  W  is also for  Weight Watchers .&nbsp; After my emotional weekend and a few edible indiscretions (blush), &nbsp;I really hadn't expected anything to have changed when I went for my  weigh-in  today (yes, another  W  word).&nbsp; Either crying burns calories and cancels out junk food or the gym is actually starting to work.&nbsp; Three Pounds!! Woo hooo! :D Grand total of 9.6lbs!&nbsp; Just .4lbs away from my 10lb ribbon.&nbsp; I am dead chuffed - I think I needed this boost in my morale right now.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Now I know I still have a long way to go, but I am feeling better already.&nbsp; The gym is making a huge difference; 2 hours a day 5 days a week has to start showing up at some point right?&nbsp; I think the biggest shock&nbsp;today however was when someone at the gym walked past and made it very obvious they were checking me out.&nbsp;At least I think that's what they were doing! Been so long, who can tell!   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Initially I had planned not to comment on the reply posted to my July 18th post entitled, "So I lied..."&nbsp; - but like a festering scab waiting to be picked, it was one of those itchy, irritating annoyances that just begged to be played with, even though you know it's going to hurt a little, probably leave a scar.&nbsp; I think it was the comment "do us all a favour and go kill yourself"&nbsp;and "you fat f**k"&nbsp;which finally helped me decide that the delete button was the best possible destination for this kind of comment.&nbsp; Now I am normally the first one to jump on the no censorship/free speech&nbsp;bandwagon but this is  MY  blog,  MY  diary,  MY  thoughts and I don't have to cater to anyone else's whims expect  MINE ! (heheheh selfish of me I know!)&nbsp; So this is definitely a case of if you all don't play the game nicely then I shall just take my ball and go home! :-P    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just call me painfully old fashioned, but there is something special about snail mail.&nbsp; It's amazing now that 90% or more of my correspondence is completed via email, I still have a hankering for snail mail.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  There is something exciting about receiving an envelope that isn't brown and is windowless.&nbsp; Handwritten addresses, hopefully in a recognizable scrawl.&nbsp; My own once beautiful penmanship has suffered over the years and&nbsp; is now just chicken scratchings on a page.&nbsp; Out of practice thanks to the keyboard I use at home and work daily.&nbsp; The callus on my finger from where the pen used to rest has long since worn away.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Impatiently getting back to that envelope, just the excitement of opening it. Opening precisely with the edge of a blade under the flap, or opening by tearing off the end like a chocolate bar wrapper,&nbsp;or perhaps - like me - one thumb or finger&nbsp;under the flap...slowly breaking open the envelope along the spine of the flap.&nbsp; Careful not to tear it too badly, so that&nbsp;I can refold the contents once they have been visibly&nbsp; consumed, and place them safely back inside.&nbsp; My son, definitely not of the snail mail era, rips into his envelopes like a rabid dog; sometimes to the detriment of the contents. &nbsp;Laid open like the butchered remains at the scene of a bloody battle, at times beyond recognition.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  The envelope is hopefully thick from multiple pages of hand written sheets.&nbsp; Maybe even a snapshot enclosed to bring a smile.&nbsp; And unfolding that letter, smoothing the pages with your hand, knowing that just a few short days ago, the author also sat and caressed the same page.&nbsp;&nbsp; The hint of tobacco, coffee or cologne still lingering between the pages. For a&nbsp; second you are both connected, whisked away via the senses on a different plain.&nbsp; Reunited, albeit briefly.&nbsp; The touch of the paper still baring the warmth of their touch.&nbsp; The perfume of a distant place reuniting just for the briefest of moments.&nbsp; Brother writing to sister, parent to child, friends and lovers.  &nbsp;  When I was 11, I started writing to penpals from all across the globe.&nbsp; At one point I maintained a collection of over a dozen active penpals.&nbsp; Believe it or not, I still keep in touch with one today from California.&nbsp; Admittedly all we exchange now is an annual Christmas card and a "Year in review" letter, her's always hand written, mine - &nbsp;in recent years - always typed.&nbsp; Empty promises to write more often, but we never do.&nbsp; Our lives are full and busy as professional adult women.&nbsp; We don't have time to sit and write letters by hand every week.&nbsp;&nbsp;School girl dreams, giggles and gossip.&nbsp; Envelopes covered in stickers and graffiti.&nbsp; Hand-drawn hearts with the name of this week's boyfriend or favourite pop star emblazoned across it, declaring "Tru Luv 4 Eva!" I smile now when I think back.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  When I was 15 I moved on to the more adult form of letter. The love letter.&nbsp; I seduced a young man by mail, (or maybe he seduced me).&nbsp; We exchanged letters for over 2 years, back and forth.&nbsp; I kept every last one of them.&nbsp;The fragile sheets of onion skin paper wore thin from the constant refolding, as I read each one again, and again.&nbsp;&nbsp;He wore Aramis and without prompting he&nbsp;would scent his letters for me so that it felt like he was right there beside me when I read them.&nbsp; He drew me cartoons, copied out song lyrics that were pertinent to us, and always sealed his letters with a kiss.&nbsp; The times I would come flying down the stairs at the sound of the letter box.&nbsp; An airmail envelope lying on the mat with it's distinctive red and blue border - and an "X" printed clearly at the point of the seal for all the world to see.&nbsp; It was one the most romantic times of my life - a time when I felt loved, appreciated and special enough to someone, that at night they would sit and put pen to paper to tell me such.  &nbsp;  Fast forward through the end of that relationship and definitely fast forward through my married years.&nbsp; I don't think my husband managed much more than a birthday and Christmas card in all the years we were married.&nbsp; Slow down and hit play at my last relationship.&nbsp; My ex boyfriend and I reinvented the love letter via faxes, love notes and messages on a BBS. (My initiation to the online world!)  &nbsp;  I remember he used to hide notes for me to find later.&nbsp; An "I love you" in my lunch box, "I am so glad you are in my life" under my pillow.&nbsp; He was a video producer and editor for a cable travel show at the time, and when away on assignment the hunt for the notes would go into over-drive.&nbsp; I once found a marriage proposal hidden in the freezer, taped to a bag of frozen peas.&nbsp; And even though he was overseas, &nbsp;for that instant he was there next to me, embracing me with his words and making me the happiest woman alive.&nbsp; I still have that letter, in an album I made - long before the word "scrapbooking" was in vogue - together with long&nbsp;faded faxes, ticket stubs, menus and match book covers.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Call me an old fashioned girl, but a real letter beats an email.&nbsp; It beats an instant message.&nbsp; It beats a voicemail.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  There is a song in the&nbsp;country charts right now by John Michael Montgomery "Letters from Home" about letters being sent to our serving men and women overseas.&nbsp; But for me the song that chokes me is an oldie by Nat King Cole.       Love letters straight from your heart,   Keeps us so near while apart,  I'm not alone in the night, 
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Monday morning for me has always signified a fresh start, a do over, a new&nbsp;beginning.&nbsp; For me this Monday morning is&nbsp;an opportunity to do just that....to re-group, re-strategize and hopefully re-emerge on the other side with relatively few scars and war wounds.&nbsp; Call it my rebirth. &nbsp;  I have to learn to put  "No"  back in my vocabulary.&nbsp; When relating to myself, as well as others!  &nbsp;  I have mentally sealed the romance book on Maybe, today is the start of our platonic&nbsp;friendship, if he wishes to accept that gift.  &nbsp;  Romantically I am taking a break.&nbsp; Having said that if  Mr. Wonderful  knocks on my door today, fabulous! (knowing my luck he will come however whilst I am out at work!).&nbsp; I am certainly  not  looking for any romance online.&nbsp; Those days are&nbsp;gone.&nbsp; If you see me even  hint  at&nbsp;an online romance,&nbsp;take me to task over it please, &nbsp;because lord knows the little voice inside my head is tired of being&nbsp;ignored whenever it offers such advice and warnings! &nbsp;  After a weekend of misbehaving (I am such an emotional eater) I am back on my diet as of today and back at the gym (I didn't go once this weekend).  &nbsp;  After a weekend of yet more guilt purchases I have resolved to stop trying to buy my son's affection.&nbsp; He's a teenager - it's his job to hate me - and no amount of money at this age will change that.&nbsp; He will&nbsp;still be just a moody teenager, except&nbsp;now with much cooler toys.  &nbsp;  In addition I need to start knuckling down financially and getting back on track, the bills are all paid, but I need to stop adding to them.&nbsp; Again with the guilt purchases!  &nbsp;  I feel a need to clear out my life, both mentally, physically and emotionally.&nbsp; I need to sort closets, toss out the junk, clear out all the deadwood and deadweight - people too&nbsp;&nbsp;not just items - and move on.&nbsp;&nbsp;Over the coming weeks I hope to accomplish just that.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Safe Keeping.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had a 3 hour online chat with  MAYBE  on Friday night.&nbsp; The boy confuses me so.&nbsp; The  backoff-c'mere-backoff  messages I am receiving have me so twisted up and confused beyond belief.&nbsp; Looking back on the archives,&nbsp; he doesn't seem to appear to want to let go, but at the same time doesn't want the headache of being involved either.&nbsp; He is offering friendship.&nbsp;&nbsp; He has told me where his heart is - and it isn't anywhere close to Ajax-On-the-Lake.&nbsp; I read some of my responses and cringe at how desperate and clingy I sound.&nbsp; Almost pleading, oh shit, who am I kidding, there was no  "almost"  about it. &nbsp;I was nauseating.&nbsp; I told the man I was his for the taking, if he ever changed his mind.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Is that where things have come to?&nbsp; Where I will beg to receive whatever crumb is left over, (sloppy seconds)?&nbsp; Am I that  starved  for affection? I  hate  submissiveness with a  passion , especially when the weak, whiney, simpering creature turns out to be   ME  .&nbsp;  &nbsp;  It always happens.&nbsp; At the start of any "involvement" I am the dominant one.&nbsp; In control, slightly aggressive, cool as a cucumber. You want me you are gonna have to&nbsp;prove it....and as soon as they do, I seem to metamorph into this&nbsp;clinging limpet/submissive wreck who is terrified they are going to leave. And&nbsp;they always do.&nbsp; Any betting man worth his salt would stake the farm on it.  &nbsp;  I need to brush up on my "Tough-as-nails-I eat-men-like-you-for-breakfast" (Alvaston Council Estate 101) .  &nbsp;  Talking things over yesterday with Deli helped.&nbsp; Her counsel and advice, as always, were good.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Mentally I am putting my heart on hold in a beautiful little ladybird box she gave me.  (See pic above) &nbsp; It'll be safe there.&nbsp; And if I find someone who wants it and deserves it, it will be there.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Like Deli said, I have already waited 6 years, another 6 isn't going to kill me if it means waiting for the  RIGHT  one.  &nbsp;  This bottom lip has quivered for the last time.&nbsp; And this  IS  my last public word on the subject.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      When two&nbsp;online friends meet for the first time in person it's interesting to note that initial greeting.&nbsp; Some people smile shyly&nbsp; and give an acknowledging nod.&nbsp; Some offer a handshake and a polite "Pleased to meet you". Some are more boisterous with a rousing "Hi there" and perhaps a shoulder squeeze or a high five.&nbsp; And there are some that hug, long, hard, and mean it.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  This may explain why at 8am in the morning, two bbw redheads were stood on the side of the road in a sleepy little Ontario town hugging, at least one of them (ok me) breaking down in sobs of emotion and neither wanting to be the first to let go.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Four hours later....and enough coffee to ensure the continued research of "The Best and Worst Public Washrooms in Ontario: Volume 1" ....I headed back to the city knowing that aquaintances are two-a-penny, but true sister-friends are a rare and precious comodity to be treasured.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I look forward to another visit on the return trip from Montreal back to the States next weekend!   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       There is relatively little traffic on the road at 6 am on a Saturday morning.&nbsp; Which is nice.&nbsp; I hate sitting in bumper to bumper, edging forward, trying to cut into another lane that looks like it's moving faster ...only to see the 10 cars who were behind me previously&nbsp;go sailing past - and I'm not moving.  &nbsp;  6am Saturday morning is  prayin'  and  zoomin' ..... prayin'  that the O-dots are patrolling another section of the highway whilst I am  zoomin'  along like Andretti.&nbsp; Nothing like the tunes cranked and the window down when you are driving. Only in summer, I hasten to add...not recommended in Ontario between October and April unless you want to die of hypothermia.  &nbsp;  I made it to Thorold in relatively good time, pulled up at the address I was given and was a little puzzled as to why there were no cars in the driveway...just a dumpster.&nbsp; A quick phone call to say."wakey wakey guys" went straight to voice mail...damn.&nbsp; I double checked the address...hmmm....nope I am in the right spot.&nbsp; I got out of the car and knocked on the door, no answer, peeked thru the window and the house is  completely  empty.&nbsp; Empty as in  unoccupied ...empty as in this can't be the right address because whoever lived here has  moved   out .&nbsp; I start to get a little peeved.&nbsp; I make another phone call....again to the answering machine..."hi guys very funny....now where the feck are you?"&nbsp; Call my friend's mobile...voice mail...damn doesn't anyone answer their phones anymore?  &nbsp;  Decide to drive up and down the street scanning for an American licence plate ...preferably Ohio.&nbsp; Mobile rings.&nbsp; "OK you are where? What street number? OK&nbsp;I will be there in a minute".&nbsp; Drive some more...what the feck?&nbsp; Mobile rings again.&nbsp; "Where are you?&nbsp; (getting testy now) I am&nbsp;on the street and the houses don't go that high...what?&nbsp;You gave me their&nbsp; old  address by accident? OK, I will sit here...you come&nbsp;get me!"&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Calgon take me away!  &nbsp;   &nbsp;   
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There are not many people for whom I would drag my ass out of bed for at this hour. (That is soooo a lie but it sounds good).&nbsp; But I am heading out into the wide blue yonder....to beautiful downtown Thorold, Ontario. ( where?)&nbsp; My online sis has come north of the border for her vacation, an over-night in Thorold and then on to Montreal.&nbsp; So I am heading over to meet her&nbsp;for breakfast.&nbsp; There WILL be photos.&nbsp; There WILL be tears.&nbsp; There WONT be enough time until she has to get back on the road and heading east.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;    Post Script: Forgot the camera on the couch, didn't realise it was missing from the pile of crap&nbsp;I brought with me&nbsp;until I was&nbsp;already on the highway.&nbsp; Spent the rest of the day hoping and praying I hadn't left it on the roof of the car as I drove away (Yes, I have done that with a coffee cup and my son has&nbsp;done it with his mobile phone...thankfully in the&nbsp;instance of the mobile someone pulled alongside us at the&nbsp;traffic lights and pointed it out&nbsp;so we were able to rescue it before it slid off and smashed to a million pieces.  &nbsp;       
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been doing a lot of introspective thinking and soul searching this week.&nbsp; I started to wonder what the hell was wrong with me, not in a pity party way, far from it, that type of behaviour just irritates me immensely.&nbsp; But more in a ..."OK enough of this,&nbsp; am I going about this all wrong or do&nbsp;I have a major character flaw that&nbsp;I can address?? For gosh sake tell me!"  &nbsp;  I took an online personality survey and was  brutally  honest, I mean "I would never even admit this to my priest on my death-bed" honest - and&nbsp;I am not even&nbsp;Catholic, but you get the idea. No holds barred, warts and all, just tell me how the land lies.&nbsp; How accurate it is I don't know, but here are the results.&nbsp; Nothing leaps out at me, other than I talk to much.  &nbsp;  The survey claims it is " not intended as an in-depth analysis of your complete being, but as a tool to aid in self-discovery." (In other words don't take our word for it, but you may actually be nuts... )  &nbsp;  The results :  (I have tossed in a&nbsp; few comments along the way...)    You have a strong sense of humor. You usually know when to lighten a difficult situation, amuse and entertain people.  (OK, I'll accept that).    You have a strong feeling of optimism, considered favorably by most people around you. Your perception is that the bottle is half-full rather than half-empty.  (This one surprised me, one of my girlfriends described me as "optimistic" the other night too.&nbsp; I have never thought of myself as that, but on reflection I am not a pessimist either. Is there not a middle ground?)    You have to be with people. This extends into the need to gain popularity, achieve social recognition and influence those people around you. The "bottom-line" is a strong people orientation.  (This one I didn't agree with, I actually prefer my own company to that of a lot of people I could name. I certainly don't "have to be" with people,&nbsp; and I don't seek out companionship and friendship "just for the sake" of not being lonely. If we are friends and spend time together it's for not for something as shallow as "better than nothing".&nbsp;&nbsp;This&nbsp;answer makes me sound social climbing.&nbsp; Oh my god, don't tell me I am a Hyacinth Bucket in the making!)     &nbsp;  The following statements offer a look at the natural behavior you bring to an interpersonal relationship.   You show sympathy to the feelings and needs of others. Your natural empathy style may draw others to you.  (OK, if you say so...is that a nice way of saying I am a loser magnet?)    You have a natural, outgoing style that some have labeled as the "natural salesperson." You are generally likeable, talkative and socially assertive. Your primary intent is convincing or persuading people.  (Sounds more like I am bossy and controlling)    You are a natural communicator. You love to talk, offer jokes and make sure that everyone is having a good time. This trait is especially evident at functions and outings.&nbsp;  (Life and soul of the party? Doubt it.)    You can generate enthusiasm in yourself and in other people. Your enthusiasm, often contagious, involves many people in a social activity who might not ordinarily become involved.&nbsp;  (Yay team!)    One of your great strengths is your ability to communicate and talk readily. Since all strengths may be overused at times, you may sometimes talk too much.  (*Indignant breath in* But...but.... *Rapid exhale* sigh)    What I need from others:   Plan sufficient time to talk and listen.   Talk about expectations.   Share specific ideas to carry out an action.   Offer immediate rewards for accomplishments.   Be sincere and use a tone of voice that shows sincerity.   Leave plenty of time for socializing and relating.   Offer opinions and ideas that are stimulating.   Ask for opinions and ideas.   Support ideas for change with facts, figures and logic.   Be stimulating, fun-loving, and fast-moving.   Take time to be certain that you reach an agreement.   (All sounds a little to huggy-liberal-hippy minded to me but if you say so ...)    Following are some of the specific strengths and/or personal characteristics that you bring. These may form the foundations of many of your friendships and dealings with other people. Some will seem obvious, but you may be surprised by others. Take a moment to reflect on each and consider what role it may have played in your past successes, and even failures.&nbsp;  (Ahh finally the part that will tell me where I screwed up....the failures section).    You like to gather facts and think things over before offering a strong opinion.  (Indecisive decision maker and procrastinator? I will agree with that)    You are socially poised and people-oriented.&nbsp;  (Do they mean Social climber?)    You are excellent at listening to your partner.  (They think you are listening provided you don't snore outloud or start to drool).    You have an excellent sense of humor and tend to see humor in events spontaneously.&nbsp; (Maybe my humour is too dark, warped, sarcastic it offends some).    You are optimistic and tend to make others feel good about themselves.  (Again with the optimism! I am just gonna have to rename myself Susie Sunshine).    You tend to enjoy life and share that enjoyment with others.  (uh huh)    You are very respectful of the needs and wants of other people.  (uh huh)    You are skilled at finding "win-win" solutions when conflicts arise.  (ummmm...)    You are usually enthusiastic about activities and planning.  (Sure if it's something I wanna do, cos I have tried and I can't get enthusiastic about laundry and housework.)    You are generally good at cooling down tense situations in a relationship.  (Yeah I will go with that...forever the peacemaker).    You tend to bring feelings of security and stability to a relationship.  (Read: Boring boring boring ...check me for a pulse).    You may want:   Detailed information about major decisions with complete instructions.  (most of the time, doesn't everyone?)    Time and opportunity to weigh pros and cons of decisions.  (Yep, I hate being rushed into making a decision, gimme time to mull it over.)    Sound relationships which form naturally, and are not contriving or scheming.  (Doesn't everyone?)    A predictable environment with few surprises that are not "planned."  (Oh my god I   am   boring).    An environment free from conflict or hostility.&nbsp;  (Doesn't everyone?)    Protection or insulation from aggression or confrontation.&nbsp;  (Doesn't everyone? Is there an echo in here?)    Peace and harmony.  ( I sound like a bloody Christmas card!)    Fewer changes, if many changes have occurred recently.  (wha?)    Time to adjust to change.&nbsp;  (hmmm)    Time to react to new ideas and sudden change.  (hmmm)    Security and safety procedures around the house: fire safety, smoke detectors, electronic security systems, etc.&nbsp;  (? - huh? where did that come from?)    Yanno I still don't feel any more self aware than I was at the beginning of this process. My journey of self discovery is that I am&nbsp;funny,&nbsp;(in a boring predictable safe kinda way)&nbsp;...and I talk too much.&nbsp;(and I am addicted to round brackets) Egads.  &nbsp;  It's shower time ...Thank God it's&nbsp;Friday.&nbsp; I wouldn't have wished this week on anyone.&nbsp; But in the same breath, I don't regret a single thing in the events that lead up to this week...  &nbsp;    Given the chance, I would do it all and say it all again in a heartbeat.&nbsp; Life is too short to hide your emotions; and living without loving isn't truly living at all. It's&nbsp;just going thru the motions.&nbsp;   &nbsp;    Life is not a dress rehearsal. &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am getting no-where fast on my Weight Watchers Diet.  I feel I am taking one step forward and two steps back every week.  I was bitterly disappointed yesterday when I stepped on the scale to discover I was in fact up over half a pound.  I haven't been as anal as I could be over recording everything and counting points, but I have certainly been good and would swear on a stack that I haven't been going over my points.  Lord knows this chocoholic hasn't had a sniff of the stuff in over 5 weeks.  So this week I am weighing, measuring and recording every bloody thing.  I have been exercising daily anywhere from 1-2 hours at the gym for the last 2 weeks - surely to God I am not looking at a weight increase from increased dense muscle tissue already?! The only other thing I can think of is ...ahem ...that  monthly  weight gain all women have.  Which may explain why I am so fricken emotional this week. Although the tears in my car yesterday were just bitter disappointment. (Feck, you must think I am a right cry baby, all I have done this week is cry).  I had planned on going to the gym, but instead I just came home. Running late....more later.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Woke up to the sound of a thunderstorm rolling in again.  Ten minutes before my alarm was due to go off.  Good timing!    Well I made it through Hell safe and sound, only the occasional person making my blood boil.  I have a knack of mentally flushing the call once it has been processed so that I don't have to carry around all that excess baggage that causes burn out. It's only the ones that touch your heart that tend to leave their mark ( urlLink Cecilia Zhang  and  urlLink Holly Jones ).  Those are the calls we rarely talk about, but keep locked safe and sound, away from harm, wishing that we could have done just that in real life.    Yesterday's "Oh my god! You are the reason I celebrate being single!" Award goes to:  The man who called 9-1-1, obviously very upset that he was still waiting after 240 minutes to see police to report a break in from the  previous night . A valid complaint! I explained to him about the delay (lack of manpower - a common complaint) and that we would be along to see him as soon as we had a unit available, but understandably we have to respond to the life and death emergencies first. (Customer Service smile plastered firmly in place).  That's when he got obnoxious.  He started ranting that if he had threatened to slash his wife's throat and kill her we would be on the way to see him.  I explained that a violent domestic was a different priority to a break in, (gritted smile).  He didn't see why.  (A red glaze started to shift in front of my eyes at this point).  I asked him was he telling me that he put the same emphasis on the health and well being of his wife to that of his home being broken into?  This is when he decided to tell me that the "break-in" was actually to his car, not his home.  (A crime that is generally reported over the phone for insurance purposes and as a rule does not even need an officer to attend).   "And that's an expensive luxury $20,000 car yanno..."  he ranted.  I told him (sweetly) he was basically talking out of his ass and he knew it. That there was no comparison. We would have an officer at his door as soon as we had one available.  If the situation changed be sure to call us back...but please don't call 9-1-1 unless it is a real emergency. (The standard response we use once complainants start to get unreasonable. - Well standard except for the talking out your ass part).    It wasn't 'til later that his comments actually sunk in....$20,000?  Hell that doesn't even buy a fully loaded Chevy Cavalier!  Feck!  I sure feel for his poor wife whoever she is. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had the shittiest nights sleep that I have had in a long time.  Seems I tossed and turned and looked at the clock every hour.  But strangely I have awoken feeling refreshed (she said yawning).  Probably around 7:30 am I will feel like crashing again...when I am stuck at work...straight phones.   Straight phones is purgatory - no correction - straight phones is hell. Call after call...complaint after complaint...screaming, ranting, raving (and that's just the calltakers).  Do you have any idea how hard it is to get vital information out of someone who: doesn't speak English, is having a heart attack and can barely breathe, is too drunk to know their own name never mind where they live, has been beaten/raped and dumped, has been shot, is going into shock, overwhelmed with grief, hysterical...all in under 30 seconds, to get help on the way. That is straight phones.  Call after call.  The mind boggles.  But we do it, and we are damned good at it too if I say so myself.  Purgatory is dispatching the parking desk.  Not quite hell, away from the public for a while, but still not heaven.  I had the parking desk 3 days in a row recently. I have learned not to complain. Actually by day 3 I was accustomed to their accents, they mine - and they also knew the meaning of the word "Stand by".   Then there is almost heaven, relieving.  Relieving is when a resident from hell (calltaking)is given a temporary pass to heaven (dispatching)to allow the resident of heaven to go take a break, lunch, whatever...  Relieving is kinda cool, because it gives you a chance to play in someone else's back yard and not have to clear up the mess. Stir the pot and move on as it were.   Then there is heaven.  Like love and hate ...there is a fine line between heaven and hell.  Heaven is dispatching.  Heaven is far from the public ...but heaven is also the busiest, most stressful and hectic spot to be in at times. Umpteen dozen unseen voices pulling you every which way to Sunday.  All expecting your full exclusive attention at all times.  Expecting you to be the all knowing voice of Oz.  The wizard behind the curtain pulling the levers. Get me this, call me that, where do I go, who do I see, can you check this, run that, what's the perimeter, where is the command post, can you call back the complainant, notify, monitor, shots fired, stand by, rush the ambulance, all in order.....breathe ...breathe ....dispatch can you mark me in for lunch?    The adrenalin can be addictive.  To watch a dispatcher is full swing is like a ballet. Smooth, flowing, flawless, energetic - especially when viewed on mute!   So it's time to hit the shower, I am in hell today - for a full day, so I think I will be more than ready for the gym by the time 3pm rolls around, with more than a few frustrations to work out.    Be safe out there. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I promise today wont be as long winded as yesterday (crosses fingers behind back just in case).   I spent most of the morning yesterday wrapped in the therapeutic comfort of my keyboard. Hence yesterday's version of "War and Peace".  The afternoon was primarily on the phone to one of my closest girlfriends. A woman who as soon as she heard what had happened Saturday night, sat on the phone with me for over an hour, whilst I ensured the stock price of Kleenex would sky rocket. I call her my American sister, my diet buddy, my chat buddy, and yesterday my shoulder to lean on.  This woman is amazing, and understands me (at times better than I understand myself). She even understands me when I am crying, full of snot (sorry but the visual image was needed), my full accent coming thru as thick as a Derbyshire Peak District pea-souper fog and with a full bottle of wine added to the mix for good measure!  She is definitely the kind of friend they talk about in chain emails.  The kind of friend that will be sitting next to you at the end of the night in the jail cell saying, "Oh my God I think we messed up!"  She would look "priceless" in seafoam-green, and would probably even wear it for me.  I am blessed. Shan, thank you.  In one of those strange "Unexplained Mysteries" moments, even my teenaged son, of whom I have seriously doubted the existence of his human side for some time....and with whom I have been battling World War III for the last two years, shocked me.  Not even aware of what had  gone before, he came to me, hugged me, and told me that he just wanted to tell me that he loved me, and he knew he didn't tell me often enough.  He turned and left to continue his battle with the online aliens in some StarCraft battle. Leaving me shell shocked, slack jawed, rooted to the spot - he didn't ask for money, and almost certainly doesn't read my blog.  Wow! Hey I've got a nice kid after all!  Yes, it still hurts. Yes, this is still raw. Leafing through a magazine at work today I found a 5 page article on Canadian Peace Keepers in Afghanistan.  I started to read, but had to wipe the tears and abandon it within minutes.  My friend is heading there later this year for a tour...I have to remind myself that the job of whispered prayers and silent tears falls now to another, I am equally jealous, supportive and commiserate upon what she is about to go through.   The drive home ...Shania Twain - "It only hurts when I'm breathing"....I was a mess. My apologies to anyone who passed me on the highway as I cry-sang the whole way home.  Damn, I forgot that this can hurt so much.  This will be my last public word on this subject.   RVM - 831 - Keep your head down. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       So many things I want to say. Questions I want to ask. (Answers I don't want to hear). Sharp intake of breath. Hesitate (eyes shift). Exhale (words left clinging to my lips). Feel the vice tighten another quarter turn in the pit of my stomach. Keep it stuffed down. Stifled. Doesn't hurt, (we make 'em tough back 'ome). Brave face. Stiff upper lip. Head up, shoulders back,  EYES FRONT ! Don't blink! (oh my god don't cry!) Don't breathe!! (hold it!!) The wave will eventually pass. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I met someone online about a year ago.  It was not long after dad died, so I am guesstimating late August early September.  Initially I put him off, he'd message me once every couple of weeks or so.  He seemed very quiet, almost shy in some respects.  We'd exchange a little idle chit-chat, nothing more, and he'd be gone again. He had two big things going for him though that piqued my interest.  He was from Derby(shire) and he was a soldier in the British Army. Just with that information anyone who knows me can already predict the next few months I am sure.  Well we chatted casually for a few weeks (my memory says it was longer but at this point it doesn't matter it's just a technicality - and dammit this is my story and I will take as much poetic license with it as I please).  Well it came time for him to rejoin his regiment, he'd either been on a training course or home on leave or some such thing, but the reason for mentioning this is that he wouldn't have access to a computer, certainly not a reliable one.  He said he wanted to keep in touch, so he is the first and only man online I have given my home phone number to.  And he called...  For this Alvaston lass there is something about a Derbyshire accent.  I soaked it in, bathed in it, luxuriated in it's cadence, wrapped myself in it's slow methodical rhythm and floated away on a sea of homesickness.  We'd talk about trivial things, our lives, his job, my job..etc. I was still very wrapped up in the Sea Cadet movement, and I remember one night we had a lovely long telephone conversation about how to properly polish a boot.  I smile to myself even now as I remember him saying that the pressure used should be the same as when caressing a woman.  Small, rhythmic circles...  Thank god he had a long distance plan, some nights we'd talk for hours.  And that's how it started...  His regiment moved back to their main barracks after a tour of duty, and we fell into a routine of phone calls and weekend online chat (home was close enough to commute to on the weekends).  I started to feel again...  His regiment went away for a 6 week exercise in Africa...and I felt I had lost my best friend.  But he called.  He left messages on my answering machine, just to say hi...just to say I made it here safe...just to say ...  And I saved every one of them while he was gone.  Played them back whenever I needed that comfort from home.  I started to fall...  Months of conversation and the intimacy that comes from slowly getting to know a person.  I had to go and spoil it all by falling in love.  I am sure the cynics out there will roll their eyes and say oh my god, how can you fall in love with a person you have never met.  Well I guess they don't base a relationship on the same kind of things that I do.  And perhaps they haven't been single for 6 yrs. This is the first real person I have connected with in all that time, since Iain and I broke up.  I told him, my soldier friend, how I felt.  He was once bitten, twice shy however and refused to wear his heart on his sleeve.  He was enjoying our liaison just as it was and didn't see any reason to change anything.  I think deep down I wanted to believe that he really did care.  I reasoned with myself, would he call from the middle of the jungle in Africa, or the middle of some field in Scotland, or ..... if he didn't feel "something"?    So I tried to back off a little, not use the "L" word as much, try and get back to our comfortable shoe polishing days, but then he phones, and my heart leaps. I am not the kind of girl who can just pretend things aren't happening, I am a redhead, and tend to get very passionate about things I feel strongly about.  I feel very strongly about him.   We were talking online a little over a week ago.  He had just celebrated a birthday, and he was saying thank you for the gift I had sent. And then he dangled the proverbial carrot.  We had fallen into discussion of "us" and he said "I don't see as this changes much, but MAYBE."  Well regular readers (me and God) of this blog will know how I reacted to that.    Final Act Scene 1...  He called Friday from base. The line was terrible, but I was just tickled pink to hear from him, we didn't talk for long, but it was enough to put a smile on my face after what has been a very long and ick kinda week.  He called again last night, thankfully the line was much clearer...although in my heart I wish that it hadn't been.  The axe falls...  He has met someone.  I felt like all the air had been sucked out of my lungs in a single instant.  The man that I had initially held at arms length, who found his way into my heart with descriptions of building water features in his mother's garden and taking the motorbike out on the country laneways of Derbyshire, was now telling me that he has met a girl back home.  And the pain hurts as bad as any REAL relationship, because for me this was a REAL relationship. This was the first man I have had any real feelings for in over 6 years.  Beyond flirtations of the keyboard, beyond the suggestive nature of the chatrooms - my friends there are just that, friends.  But this ...this was special.  He still wants to be friends.  Funnily enough I keep hearing Billy Crystal and Meg Ryan in my head from "When Harry Met Sally" (one of my favourite movies by the way) when they debate the question: Can men and women ever really be friends?  I am afraid my response is pretty much like Billy Crystal's .... "No you pretty much want to screw them too."
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well so much for that horoscope, it couldn't have been more wrong if it had tried.    My day yesterday was relatively normal for a weekend.  I hung out here (online)for a while until the boy surfaced from his steaming pit (his bedroom is kinda putrid), drank copious amounts of coffee (see post from June 29 and 30 regarding my caffeine addiction), found an amazing  urlLink website  with free graphics for my website (I was like a kid in a candy store!)and chatted online to various friends and acquaintances as they got up and started their day etc. It was nice, probably not the kind of weekend that makes too many people excited, but for me sitting on the front porch trying to finish the weekend crossword doesn't rock my boat either.  We all have different ways that we relax and unwind.  This is mine.  I was starting to fade mid afternoon (getting up at 4am will do that to ya), after having run a few errands around town etc.  The boy got home from swimming and was settling in for a few hours of online Star Craft gaming. So I figured I had better hit the gym or else if I sat down I would be out like a light.   I had the most amazing workout - OK stop the presses...take my temperature I must be getting sick. As strange as this may sound - and I may lose my position in the "We-walk-and-smoke-we-don't-run" School Cross Country Team for this - I have been really enjoying the whole gym thing so far.  I don't know if the quitting smoking has anything to do with it, but all I know is I dragged my ass in there yesterday afternoon at 4pm, two hours later I left there feeling absolutely amazing, and quite proud of myself on a personal accomplishment involving some kind of stepper/strider/glider type contraption. Yay for me!  Just as an aside... (like I have ever needed permission or much encouragement to go off topic).  There has been much talk about "spot" over the last year in my circle of online friends.  It's the part of the body - male or female - that just grabs you.  For some it's eyes, others butt, for two online friends in particular it was the area between the navel and pubic region, almost appendix - but I digress (now there's a first)up until now I had always thought it was eyes for me - and in fact it is to a degree.  But to conjure images of pure carnal lust I discovered yesterday at the gym that for me my "spot" on a man is more of a large splodge - biceps and pecs. Not over developed poser body builder, omg no - but a broad chest and a full arm... OMFG.  I fell in lust with a couldn't have been more than 25 yr old man at the gym there and then. Beautifully proportioned, stocky, almost heavy, obviously has a physically demanding job, those muscles weren't developed in any sweaty gym - just maintained. He had the look of either police or military about him which just sent me to a whole other level of my fetish too. It's nice the gym provides the occasional eye candy to help with my concentration with regard to my exertion level.  So you are thinking, well the day so far sounds wonderful (and it was). What could've happened to spoil such a pleasant suburban day?  The simple answer is, later that evening, I got my heart broken.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My weekly horoscope has me intrigued, so far this week it has been relatively spot on. For the remainder of this week it reads:  "Both Mercury and Mars are in Leo, and encouraging you to enjoy your sex life a lot more. If you are open about what you want in this area, then you will be able to be a lot more honest with others. Talk about your desires, and this may just help your partnership move to a new and more exciting level, as you have been hoping. Let sweetness and romance into your life on Saturday; you won't regret it."  Does this mean I am gonna finally meet someone or am I just going to masterbate more frequently?!?  In case you were wondering my sun sign is Capricorn, with Sagittarius rising, born in the year of the Horse. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's Saturday morning, I woke up naturally, my body clock is still on a Monday to Friday schedule I guess - plus I was in bed by 10:30 pm last night - so I decided I might as well get up.  I love this time of day, the house is asleep quiet, outside it's still, no traffic on the roads, no sounds from the neighbourhood.  Feels like it's just me out here. The sky is  just  starting to lighten in the east, and I am just going to sit, enjoy my tea, and watch the sunrise.  Of course this would be so much nicer if I was spending the weekend somewhere up north, in a cabin by the lake, but for now this is just fine.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I didn't get off work early, too busy at work.  Normally I don't mind, but getting the weekend off to an early start is always nice.  The traffic coming out of the city was nuts.  The  urlLink Lakeshore is completely closed  down due to the  urlLink Molson Indy   which is running all weekend and will no doubt make traffic a bitch.  Thank god I live in the burbs.  Before I left work we were already getting calls for people who were STOPPED on the Gardiner Expressway to get a better look at the race on the Lakeshore.  Yanno I think I have to stop worrying about people's stupidity and look at it more as Mother Nature's way of keeping the population levels in check....   On the way home I took my car in for an oil change and inspection.  Seems I need new tires too ...just not this paycheque.  *Sigh* It never ends! I have a pile of bills waiting to be sorted next Tuesday when I get paid as it is. In one hand and out the other as they say.  Dinner was a lovely bbq medley of bbq ribs and grilled veggies.  The boy has turned into quite the exceptional bbq chef.  And I am not just saying that to blow sunshine up his ass, he really is good.  Now if only I could get him to prep the items too ...then I could totally sit and let him get dinner for once ....hmmm will have to suggest that in a way to make him think it was his idea....oops ...letting out one of the sacred secrets of womanhood...they will revoke my membership from the sorority at this rate! LOL  My friend from Derby called. The line was terrible, but it was great just to hear his voice. He is working all weekend, but it was really nice that he took the time to phone; even if I spent the entire time shouting into the phone and saying "Pardon? Say that again?"  Funny how just something like that can lift your spirits, up until that point I was feeling a little melancholy.    Tonight is the first evening I haven't hit the gym in over a week, but I am sure one night off wont kill me. It sure feels weird, I feel guilty and sluggish as hell, think I will be in bed by 10pm at this rate. I will be back working hard tomorrow for sure!   OK ...need a cuppa ....talk at ya tomorrow.  Be kind to each other. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thank GOD it's Friday!  Yesterday was an emotional rollercoaster, I so hope today is a little easier to deal with.  Yesterday was my 6 monthly review down at Headquarters with the Medical Advisory Service.  For the past few years I have worked straight days - an accommodation for having a "special needs child" and more recently to help with a medical issue.  Every six months I have to reattend the bureau, armed with medical texts and letters to support this accommodation.  Every six months my life goes into limbo as I wait to hear if 'starting tomorrow' I am back on shift. So yesterday I went, armed with the recommendations of 3 experts.  For the first time ever they didn't give me a decision on the spot.  Normally they take the attitude, "Well this is our decision and it's final", yesterday they were more, "We'll talk to your unit commander and get back to you".  My unit commander, an evil career climbing non-people-person and a female (the worst), is on leave this week.  So they have left me dangling for the weekend.  I so need to find something else I am good at that pays enough to survive on.  I have put in for a couple of hours off early (2 hours plus a no lunch, which would get me off at noon) at the end of shift for today, but I wont know until I get into work if it was approved or not, it's all a matter of who called in sick and who didn't.  It's a numbers game.  I don't have any plans perse, lunch with a girlfriend if she is available, if not I will just hit the gym earlier than usual.    As far as this weekend is concerned, nothing lined up so far, other than the movies on Sunday.  Hot date weekends are a thing of the past it seems.  These days the highlight of my weekends is going to the movies with the boy, and how badly he thrashed me at air hockey prior to the show. We have gotten into the habit of hitting the arcade area inside the movie theatre once we have bought our tickets for a "best of 3" match of air hockey.  The only reason I have never mentioned it before is 'cos I have yet to actually win.  He smokes me every time, and to make matters worse he gets cocky with it. Playing with one hand behind his back, or kneeling ....one of these days...and boy will I trumpet it from the battlements for all to hear!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well yesterday proved I am well and truly back at work.  The contented, centred feeling of "Om" that I have been floating around on for the past few days, disintergrated by 9am and I was back to earth with a bang.   Today I was on the phones, we were busy, we were VERY busy infact, and it seemed that people haven't gotten any smarter since I left for vacation.  I could hear the exasperation level in my voice coming back and I hate that.  I am not normally a mean, hateful or bitchy person (at least in my eyes) but as the years go by this job is making me very, very cynical.  1. Calls 911 to report 3 small children unattended, all locked in a mini van in the parking lot of a plaza.  They appeared to range in age from 18 months to 4 yrs.  All 3 crying and in distress.  Temperatures outside humid and in the 70's - cars can heat up pretty darn fast, especially when the window has only been cracked slightly for ventilation.  My caller however elected not to stand by the vehicle to flag down my crews, but felt simply calling this in and providing a licence plate was sufficient.  She guesstimated the size of the lot to be approximatly 50 cars (it was quadruple that) and felt we should be able to find the van quite easily and did not see a reason to stand by. (ARGHHHHHHHHHHHH!)  2. Female clerk from a convenience store called 911 emergency to report a hobbo just stolen a bottle of pop from her store. A BOTTLE OF POP.  Come on people, "Emergency" means just that, lights, sirens, life or death ....not Coke or Pepsi. FFS! If you want to complain about the waste of your tax dollars just take a good hard look at the abuses of the systems. (ARGHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!)  3.  Female calling to have us go find her daughter, or more specifically, tell her where her daughter is.  I assumed she wanted to report her daughter missing.  "No, tell me where my daughter is" was the response.  Had her daughter been arrested or taken to hospital by ambulance, I enquired.  No, but my caller hadn't seen her in a few years and wanted to get in touch. The grandmother was dying, family reunion etc.  Ahhhh, so they are estranged, now I am starting to get the picture.  Sure ma'am, just give me her last know address and we can make a start there by having a unit go over, check the premises, talk to the landlord/neighbours....she was going to university where ma'am?  McMaster? That's in Hamilton-Wentworth ma'am, not Toronto.  You may want to call that police department?  I am not being helpful?  Well I am sorry ma'am, but I can certainly give you the telephone number to call for Hamilton Police.  No?  I can go do what?  I think that might be a physical impossibility, but thank you ma'am and same to you. (ARGHHHHHHHHHH!)     Maybe I am wrong, maybe there is nothing to get het up about.  But stuff like this makes my blood boil.  I have lost my sense of "Om" from vacation and I want it back!!!  If anyone wants to suggest an alternative form of employment for a cute devil with no formal education feel free 'cos I am getting to that point.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Made it to Wednesday - phew - and haven't lost my temper (too much) yet.  I always feel I can heave a sigh of relief once we have hit Wednesday.  It's all downhill to the weekend from here, it's "Hump Day".    There's a lot to be said for vacation time in releasing the pressure built up inside. Just wish I had more that 4 weeks of this blissful stress release a year.  Yeah I know the more years I put in the more time off I get.  Heck Spider is at the max - 7 weeks a year - but that's with 29 years on the job too.  Twenty-nine years, doing the same thing, day in, day out - I feel more than a little nauseous at the very idea.  What kind of person does the exact same thing for almost 3 decades? I think I would go stark staring mad. (Yes, I said "go" - I am not quite there yet).  I woke up to the sounds of a thunderstorm, thunder rumbling (possibly even lightening too, but my eyes were closed)....and the rain ....I love the sound of the rain.  I stood at the front door for a few minutes just watching the rain pouring down, running in torrents along the gutters.  There is something very romantic about pouring rain.  Which is why my mind probably skipped to Maybe, imagining him stood there in front of me, soaked to the skin, moisture glistening off his face in the pitch black of night and looking entirely kissable, touchable...oooook my mind has definitely gone off on a tangent now...scratch the earlier sentence re the rain being romantic and change it to: There is something very erotic about a summer thunder storm. Phewwwwwy!   Heading a little earlier than usual to the shower   - have a good day all.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was greeted on my arrival home with the news that the bloody serpent next door got loose during the night and the neighbours couldn't find it. (Did I tell you I hate... I did? OK, just checking, 'cos it hasn't changed!) Needless to say I scurried into my house, locked my door and did a mental inventory of all my doors and windows.  Any screens ripped, any doors left open, could the damn thing be slithering through the venting and ductwork waving it's little forked tongue at me? (Mommy!!!!!!!)  Thankfully by early evening the panic was over, Hissing Sid was found in their basement. He sure covered ground from a second floor bedroom.  Just the thought of keeping a snake in the bedroom has my skin crawling.  (I was about to ask who in their right mind keeps a snake in the bedroom, then remembered my ex-husband and decided to keep quiet).  Damn, now why did I have to call the bloody snake Hissing Sid?  I have that feckin' song in my head now.   The bravest animals in the land are Captain Beaky and his band  That's Timid Toad, Reckless Rat, Artful Owl and Batty Bat  They march through the woodlands singing songs  That tell how they have righted wrongs          Once Hissing Sid, an evil snake, kept the woodland folk awake  In fear and trembling every night  In case he gave someone a bite  Said Artful Owl, 'We'll lie in wait  And one of us will be the bait."  Said Captain Beaky, "Have no fear! For I alone will volunteer!"   It goes on for another umpteen verses so I wont bore you with it...but any English Gen X-ers will remember that what was a novelty song in the mid 80's exploded into a silly "Save Hissing Sid"  "Sid is Innocent" " The Trial of..."  etc etc ... all thanks to a BBC Radio 1 disc jockey at the time named  urlLink Noel Edmonds .  What scares me is I remember all this useless shite.  Anyway...I digress.... more later....heading for my 5am shower.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There should be a law about waking up at 4:15 every morning.  I am the first to admit to being a morning person.  I am at my punchiest, most amusing and sharpest first thing in the morning, it all rapidly runs downhill afterwards unfortunately.  But even for a perky, chirpy, early bird like me....4:15 is a little early.    I have my ususal routine, when I get up it's straight to the kettle to make a my morning cuppa tea.  Everything thereafter ...the mood for the day ....is set after a "narsecuppatea".  I generally plonk my ass here in front of the screen for 30 mins or so while I am drinking it, checking email (does my horoscope say just go back to bed and forget it?) and maybe a word or two with the late night people on the west coast and the early birds from the east (I miss chatting to my friend in Okinawa, Japan). Mentally I am considering what the day holds, write out a cheque for rent, pay a bill or two online.  5 am I hit the shower running, and I don't stop til I have my ass in the car heading for the highway.    Yes, I would save valuable time and probably make more nutritious choices if I packed my lunch for work the night before instead of at 5:15 every morning, but I never claimed to be bright. I try to be dressed and out the door for 5:45 at the latest (would be kinda funny in reverse...ahem, never mind), which at least puts me on the highway before the madness starts.  I have a 25-30 minute commute to work, which isn't terrible, but at the peak of rush hour it stretches to 2 hours. So I *have* to be on the road before 6:15 or I can just forget it!  This normally gets me into work early, very early....6:15 for a 7:00 start, but at least - and this is my reasoning - I arrive cool, calm and collected, time to check what's going on, grab a coffee etc before plugging in for the 8 hour shift.  The folks who roll out of bed at 6am and slide into work a minute before 7am are the ones, in my mind, who are walking the thin line that may one day lead to a "snap" and go completely postal.    Anyways, the reason for boring you with all this useless information is that I have a new dilemma.  My gym opens at 5am.  I could, theoretically, revamp my whole morning home routine.  But if I do, there is a chance I am not going to hit the highway til after 6:15 (damn certainty if you ask me).  Which has me arriving to work red faced (post workout glow - the bane of a red head - lasts for hours) and probably a little harried/flustered.  I would "definitely" have to get into packing my lunch and my gym kit the night before....ach...that sounds like being organised.  The reason I am even considering working out at 5am is that by the time I get in from work I will plonk my ass on the couch, or here...and I wont want to move. H'mmm ...I will have to think about it in the shower I guess ...5am ...I am outta here !  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I received an email from my coffee-shop date.  Seems I was right, he wasn't interested, "For me there was not quite the connection that would indicate something more" is the direct quote, but he certainly said it in a very nice way.   I ran into an old sparring partner a couple of days ago online.  I guess we first became acquainted almost a year ago.  He infuriates me beyond belief, and to be honest his mental health at times is in question - quite serious here all joking aside.  We tend to run into each other once every couple of months, and after a brief failed truce we square off for the next round in the bout. We had such an exchange the other night.  Guess I am safe now til Labour Day.  The simple solution would be the "iggy" button, but sometimes some emotion is better than no emotion at all.  At least for those brief few moments as the barbs are flying, someone out there has some feelings towards me...all be it blind rage, but beggars cant be choosers!  It's something raw, real, passionate in it's anger, pure in it's energy, a real adrenal high.   I think we ended in a draw, so I am keeping my eyes peeled for sneak attacks.  The boy found a snake in the back yard yesterday.  I HATE SNAKES! It was about 1 - 2 ft long, and we quickly established it wasn't a Grass snake.  He scooped the damn thing - did I mention I HATE SNAKES? - and took it over to the local pet store (in my goddamned Tupperware container?!?!) to see if they could identify it.  Seems it's a Milk or Corn snake, non poisonous (I don't care, I still HATE SNAKES!), probably someone's escaped pet (pet? You people are SICK!), still a baby around a year old (OMG I feel ill), very tame so obviously used to being handled (I don't think there is a typed short form for shrieking hysterically is there?)....and get this ..."Mom, can I keep him?" (oh why oh why couldn't he have had a puppy follow him home like all the other kids do?).  My only explanation for my response is that my throat was paralyzed with fear and the only thing getting in and out was air....and as I breathed out it squeaked something that sounded like "Yes".  Naturally I automatically start thinking, OMG what is he going to keep it in, where is he going to keep it? His room? I don't think so, what if the damn thing escapes?  Slithers over the landing to my room...and hell to be honest who wouldn't, it's a hell of a lot tidier and smells a lot sweeter than teenaged boy room. And OMG what do these things eat...mice? OMFG! Yes we have an empty aquarium in the basement, but it needs a REPTILE LID!!! I really really HATE snakes.  He decided he was going to hang out in the garage with it for a while and get used to handling it.  Needless to say I stayed indoors, it's non-poisonous, so knock yourself out, just keep the hell away from me, and no you CANT punch air holes in my damn Tupperware container! Finally after an hour I heard the screen door slam and the boy cheerfully announced the snake was gone.  Thankfully, I have raised a good honest to goodness wimp who when push came to shove was too timid to handle said reptile (urgh, even the word reptile makes my skin crawl).  But like the honest to goodness entrepreneur that he is, he sold it to a neighbour for $30.  MY NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOUR?  OMG I hope they have a proper tank for it with a secure REPTILE LID!  Did I mention I HATE SNAKES? Ok just checking....  I think I need to go lie down for a minute....   Vacation over ....time to head on back to reality...arghhhhhh!  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Invariably someone will ask, "So what are you looking for?"   Nothing sordid, nothing seedy, nothing secretive, or alternative.   In fact, just love, actually; and strangely enough, they are always surprised.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Just Sue&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday was a total write-off.  My fault - but I basically sat in front of the computer all day with small interruptions for important things - like food. I had full intentions of either hitting the gym or taking the bike down to the lake....I even got dressed to do these aforementioned activities....and sat in my work-out clothes all day. I swear I need someone to light a flame under my butt at times.   On the positive side, I got a chance to catch up with some old friends online. So my week's vacation from work is almost over...next week I get to use this Blog as my venting post for all the stuff that sends me around the twist at work.  Consider this, dear reader, as your one and only official warning. :-P  So I am gonna take a leaf out of the "Why Don't You...?" Team's book and switch off this computer and go do something more interesting instead(only old english farts like me will get that). I will hopefully have something more interesting to post later...keep your fingers crossed or I will be writing more of that romantic clap-trap I wrote 2 days ago. Can't even call it poetry...more like the ramblings of a seriously disturbed mind!   P.S. Is it only me that finds the fact that the spell checker doesn't recognise the word "Blog" as wildly amusing? - Later ;-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think my body has finally realised that something has been going on for the past few days - and it is starting to complain.  Not too loudly yet, but deffinite grumblings.  I worked out really hard yesterday, and I think my body is deffinitely not impressed! LOL  If anyone was wondering the "date" 2 days ago was nice.  We sat and talked over coffee for almost two hours.  The conversation was pleasant enough, our shared experiences of being single parents of teenaged boys was enough to carry us through the awkward moments. At the end we shook hands, made no plans to see each other again, and walked away.  No emails or phone calls since. So I guess the "not my type" was mutual. I am sure his list of "She's ok but..." is just as long as mine is. Back to the drawing board.  My week's vacation is almost over.  Other than the gym, I really haven't gotten much accomplished.  But considering the whole point of a vacation is to recharge your batteries, I guess I can declare this a mission accomplished! The closets I intended on sorting and the housework I had planned didn't get done, but I wont beat myself up over that.  Somedays curling up with a good book out on the patio beats dusting and polishing hands down!   Today I had planned a daytrip to the zoo, but my teenaged compadre has gone and made plans with his friends. So I was thinking a bike ride down to the lake, snap a few pictures, enjoy the sunshine....
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      MAYBE you are the one I have looked for all my life.   MAYBE in your arms I will finally find peace.   MAYBE, my hand in yours, our fingers intertwined,  will feel like the puzzle finally fits.   MAYBE with my head on your shoulder,  I will finally feel I am home.   MAYBE my eyes over a morning cup,  will make you wish you never had to leave.   MAYBE as I spoon against you in the night,  trailing kisses as you sleep, you will sigh,  content within my embrace.   MAYBE if I am here for you - no matter what.   MAYBE if I listen when you speak.   MAYBE if I listen even harder when you are silent.   MAYBE if I am your soft place to fall,  when the world rages.   MAYBE if I am your tower of strength,  when your own is failing.   MAYBE if I take your breath away,  and return it daily with a kiss.   MAYBE if I wait whilst you learn to walk again,  here to catch you if you fall.   MAYBE, one morn you will awaken,  and realise youve loved me too all this time...   ...til then I'll keep hanging on,  dreaming on a MAYBE.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Just Sue&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I have finally hit my first stone. Weight Watchers and the gym are slowly helping the pounds melt away. I have gotten into the habit of hitting the gym directly from work every afternoon, Monday to Friday (although admittedly Friday's are sometimes hit and miss) - but on average I am working out 5 times a week. Monday, Wednesday and Friday I work on my weights routine and Tuesday and Thursday I work cardio. I go Friday for my first evaluation at the gym since I started.  It's been eight weeks already, which totally blows my mind that: A) That I am still enthusiastic about it after 8 weeks. B) That I am still going period - this is exercise for crying out loud - the very thing that I have avoided all my life - ever since I learned how to fake my mother's signature to write excuse notes for Phys. Ed. at school.  It will be interesting to see how I manage to work the gym into life once I am back on shift next week. On afternoon shift I can either go directly before or after work. Same with midnight shift, although just the nature of midnight shift tells me I had better hit the gym before work if I want to be conscious when I do my routine. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      OK in keeping with the "I stole this idea from..." theme I am swiping this from  urlLink Rae's blog  (and she probably nicked it from someone too). I might tweak some of the questions a little..but the end result will still be interesting. I'd say be gentle, but yanno what? Just be honest. And for the lurkers who read this blog and never post even an anonymous comment - go on, get your feet wet, it doesn't hurt, and anonymous means just that.  Basics------ Where do you know me from? How long have you known me? If you're gonna lie, are you gonna to do your best to be creative?  What Would You Do If------ I cried? I said I liked you? I kissed you? I moved to another country? I started doing drugs? I stole something? I was hospitalized? I ran away from home? I got into a fight with you?  What Do You Think About My------ Personality? Eyes? Looks? Hair? Figure? Clothes? Voice? Humour? Mannerisms?  Would You------ Be my friend? Keep it real with me, no matter what? Lie to make me feel better? Spread rumors about me? Keep a secret if I told you one? Loan me some cash? Hold my hand? Take a bullet for me? Get into a fight for me on my behalf? Lie for me? Call me once in a while? Be there for me when my world is falling apart? Be there to celebrate the good times? Wear seafoam for me?  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Almost a month to the day he died I had a dream about my dad. I am not prone to dreams, or at least remembering them when I wake up, so the fact that I could recall this dream with such clarity made it stand out above and beyond all others. I wrote down the details and talked to a colleague who has a "gift" in such departments about them. Whether you believe in such things is incidental, I took comfort from his words at the time, and that is all that matters.  He felt it was a message basically telling me that my dad had reached the other side safely and that I should not to read into the specifics of the dream or the subject matter.  The Dream:  I am in what appears to be a large building, the size of an airplane hangar. It has been set up to resemble a prison visiting room. The room is divided in half by a wall of plexiglass that runs from floor to ceiling. Either side of this wall of glass is a long table, and there are partitions set up along the table making visiting cubicles.  Each cubicle is equipped with a telephone on the divider wall - on both sides of the glass (See, I told you - just like they show prison visiting areas in movies).  Sitting opposite me- on the other side of a glass - is a person I cant identify. They appear shadowed and blurred - I am unable to see their features.  My dad approaches us from the far side of the room.  As he comes level with the glass I can see that he looks more like himself.  Neat, tidy, pressed blue shirt, not the frail old man with untidy hair I saw in hosptial.  He exchanges glances and a few words of small talk with the person in front of me and turns suddenly to me.  "Well you've got my half of the house".  Despite the glass, I hear him clearly.  He makes a move to sit down and reach for the phone - wanting to talk to me further.  I raised my hand and place my palm flat against the glass, he mirrors this movement with his own hand briefly.   "But dad, you didn't leave a will, she got it all." He is on his feet, shocked, indignant and confused - as though this is as big a shock to him as it was to us. . The dream ends. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well my last week of straight days is beginning. As of next Monday, I am back to working all three shifts with "A" platoon. It totally sucks because I wont be around at my usual times as much to talk to the few people that I do chat with on a regular basis. But I guess we will play it all by ear and see how it goes. There is after-all email, offlines etc to keep in touch - hint, hint!  Back to the gym today after a weekend off, and back to the diet with avengance - weekends seem to be my weakpoint. But the weight is coming off slowly and surely - it afterall didn't go on overnight, I should expect it to come off overnight neither. I would just like to see a bit more than 1 lb a week for all my efforts.  The boy is is looking forward to the end of the week, his girlfriend will be arriving back from camp after 2 months away working as staff. They have kept in touch, letters (well she wrote to him - why do men never write back?), phone calls, and a visit. I am sure I wont be seeing much of him for the remainder of the summer holls.  It was a good weekend over-all. I was prepared for an emotional roller-coaster and it didn't happen. Writing things down helps beyond belief.  Ran into an old sparring partner again last night. A few friends will recognise the name apmcc I am sure. Other than changing his nick he is still as ...words fail me...infuriating as ever. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I got into a girlie girl conversation with a friend this morning online. And I realized I am soooooo not a girlie girl. I am the anti-girlie - the demon spawn - the one thing that makes a girlie girl wake up in the middle of the night, bathed in perspiration ('cos girlie girls never "sweat") screaming in fear - a Tomboy!  It started out innocently enough as a conversation about bunny slippers. I am just not a bunny slipper kinda gal. Bear claw slippers, Homer Simpson slippers, heck even beer can slippers...but cutesy bunny ears protruding from my feet? No, thank you.  Even growing up, I was the kid with more scabs on her knees and rips in clothing than half the boys in my class put together. Did ya never wonder for one second what the hell I was doing on the roof of that shed in # 34 of the 100 things list?  Whilst all the girlie girls were home playing house and dolls, my best friend Hayley and I were out building club houses and inventing secret societies. We were apple scrumping over the neighbourhood fences. We were riding our bikes down the steepest hills - legs stretched out - just to feel the wind in our hair. Fighting mock battles with the grass clippings left by the council mowers on "the Green", turf wars in the truest meaning of the word! Back before everyone suddenly got "hayfever allergies" to loose grass cuttings being shoved down the back of their shirt. Her dad took us scrambling with the dirt bikes up at "Newt Pond" - my love of motorbikes embedded deeper than the dirt we rode on. We were the girls who would hang upside down from the monkey bars and argue who was cooler -  urlLink Fonzie or Chachi . We would head out early in the morning, dragging some neighbourhood dog with us for companionship and explore all the overgrown greenbelt areas ...following the rabbit trails, collecting caterpillars and ladybirds in jam jars. Heading home when hunger struck or the street lights came on (whichever came first).  Eventually though puberty sets in, the comb is forced through the tangled mess of childhood and our mother's tried to create little ladies out of us. Stop laughing! Today it would be considered child cruelty! She even gave me ....a Barbie doll! (wild psycho shrieking).  Now Barbie wasn't overly popular in the UK in the late 70's,  urlLink the British version was Sindy . I eventually had both - oh gee, thank you Santa, sigh - (I had wanted a puppy). I figured Barbie and Sindy living together was too boring (I hadn't heard of lesbianism, even at that age - oh my god we were sheltered - now the kids in school learn about homosexuality in grade school for crying out loud). So I shaved Barbie's head (my online friend screamed at this news) and coloured her brush cut with felt tip pens to make her a punk rocker. Then I used felt tips to draw a beard and mustache on her face, tattoos on her arms...and the final  coup de gras ...I bashed her tits in, (my friend is now in the fetal position on the floor sobbing and telling me I am un-American). I thank her for the compliment.  Around age 12 I started to notice boys as more than playmates but as  "playmates"  and developed my first crush ...Paul McParland. He was the soccer playing genius of the school - and didn't know I existed. That's when I finally left the tree climbing and skinned knees behind. Paul liked girlie girls.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Doh!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Just not a girlie girl.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Every now and then you wake up rested. Happy for no particular reason. Content beyond belief. Everything is well with the world (or at least your little corner of it). The sun is shining, the birds are singing and damn you feel great. That's me this morning. Bright, perky (sickeningly so) and ready to see what the day has to offer. What new adventure awaits, what new path to explore, the world is my oyster. It almost sounds like I actually got laid last night - wishful thinking - but hot-damn the cyber was good. (wink) 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My dad died a year ago today, August 14th 2003. In the middle of one of the worst power outages seen in North America. The two incidents are not connected, although knowing my dad...you never know.  I don't know an awful lot about the man who's family name I carried for the first 19 years of my life. The only way I can think to describe him physically is a cross between Michael Caine and Danny Kaye. He was forever the showman. A dancer, an amateur dramatics thespian, at times a true " Rico Suave " and ladies man. He was also the most undemonstrative, cold, unloving and selfish man I have ever known.  My parents split when I was very young - around age two. After mum (and I) moved back to England I think I saw him a grand total of twice, when I was 11 and again when I was 16. On both occasions we were in Canada for a holiday and we arranged a few hours to meet. Aside from that, my only contact with him for eleven years was an annual birthday card with a $50 money order (when he remembered). I was not allowed to spend the money, it was put into a savings account. That was the nearest he ever came to paying child support.  Dad was back in the picture a little more after mum died. He and I corresponded a little more often, he even learned that phone lines could make international calls.  When I got married in 1986 he came to England for the first time in over 30 years to give me away. He stayed a week - and that is probably the longest I have spent with my dad in living memory. And during that week (my honeymoon) we toured all the war museums in England. Well probably not  all , but it sure felt that way. My new husband was pretty good natured and understanding about it all - thank god.  We never achieved that "father-daughter bond" I hear of so often from friends. Even later in life, after my husband and I moved to Canada with our infant son - my dad kept his distance. He didn't even want to be called "grandpa" because it made him feel old.  I remember once, after a visit, as I was seeing him to the door, I stepped forward to embrace him and he recoiled, "Oh you want a hug?". You could hear the shock and panic in his voice. There followed a quick, awkward and half-hearted squeeze (can't even call it a hug). Anyone who knows me, knows I am a hugger, a toucher, a caresser. My own father obviously didn't know me too well, eh?  We settled into a routine. He only lived a 2 hour drive from my home, but we only saw each other once or twice a year. Generally around Christmas, and ...um ...er ...ok forget that ...we saw each other once a year period. We never celebrated the holidays together, just a parcel drop off a few days prior.  He was in good health for 75 years old. Still working, partly because he was self employed  (book keeper and tax accountant),  but mainly because he always lived for today and never tomorrow, hence no pension plan. I received a call from his live-in girlfriend (whom I call the Martha Stewart clone) to tell me he had been in hospital for a few weeks. She was calling me now to let me know, because it didn't seem he was getting any better...and the bills were starting to pile up. I was pissed that she hadn't called sooner, equally pissed at the financial state he was in, and even more pissed that she thought I would cover his household bills ...like the phone bill. Heck they lived together! She was his common-law! She was a "younger woman" (late 50's early 60's) and still working, pay your own goddamned phone bill lady.   (Ok I didn't say that to her, but I thought it real hard!)    Well, to cut a very long (and bitter) story short, a few weeks later he passed away. He died intestate - no will, no life insurance and sod all in the bank. Despite verbal bequests made over the years, he never put anything in writing and due to wording on the deed of his house and the laws surrounding "common-law spousal rights" the "Martha Stewart Clone" kept the lot. Lock, stock and barrel. I have asked for a personal memento, and she has offered nothing.  The funeral was beyond awful. She kept it closed and private. Just me, the boy and her family (about 6 of them altogether - I was out numbered). We sat on separate sides of the room at the funeral parlor. No service, just a few words from some guy from the funeral home who had never met or known him. She claimed he didn't have any friends. I find all of this very hard to swallow, even a year later. After the funeral there was no wake, no invitation back to the house for a cup of tea, so the boy and I hit the highway back to Toronto...  ...I have not heard a word from her since that day.  I feel bad that I can sit and relate this tale with dry eyes, yet just mention my mum ...and I mist up. I should feel something, he was the only living member of my immediate family (save my son). But he was a stranger, we had no history, I am officially of orphan status.  He used to love to relate a story from when I was small, of how he had me believing he kept the cartoon character, the Pink Panther, in his shirt pocket. He claimed I would dissolve into fits of giggles as soon as he would start to sing the theme song, "Durum, durum". I have no memory  what-so-ever  of this. I would have been less than 4 yrs old if in fact it ever did happen. And let's face it, he was quite the ladies man, he could well be confusing me with some other woman's kid. But regardless, every year he would do the "remember when" routine. I eventually learned to nod and go along with it. Desperate for something, anything, so show that at one time he cared, that we had a past, a history, a time when we were like father and daughter.  I don't remember any of it though, I really don't think it was me - but that is how I will always remember him now. The man with the Pink Panther in his shirt pocket.  OK...now I found my tears.      
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        100 things you didn't know about me...    (and probably didn't want or need to know!)     Stealing this idea from my friend   urlLink  Jen    - it just appealed to the obsessive compulsive side of my nature. Damn that makes 101 things.   01. My favourite colour is blue. 02. I prefer the taste of Coke over Pepsi (even did the official Pepsi Challenge test at the mall!) 03. I have owned (and worn) a Jimmy Osmond T-shirt. 04. I may be a Canadian by birth - but I am a die hard Brit at heart. 05. I am left handed. 06. I am extremely short sighted. 07. I got turned down as a police officer with the Derbyshire Constabulary because of my eyes. 08. Twice! (I went back a second time hoping to slip through the cracks). 09. I am so ticklish I start tensing and giggling before anyone has even touched me. 10. I hate my feet - my toes in particular. 11. My favourite subjects at school were english, art, history and culinary arts (home ec.) 12. I used to swim competitively in my teens. 13. I am fascinated by medieval fantasy, folk-lore and legends (Robin Hood, King Arthur). 14. I love sparkles, sequins and glitter - I figure in a previous life I was either a magpie or a drag queen. 15. My favourite season is autumn (sweaters, conkers, open fires, dark nights, leaf piles). 16. I have hated my hair colour all my life, and hate it more when people tell me it's beautiful. 17. I dyed my hair once at the request of a boyfriend and looked like an axe attack victim when my roots grew in. 18. I can sit and look at the night sky for hours totally awstruck at the enormity of it all - it's the one time I actually feel  small.  19. I still recite the rhyme "Star light shining bright, first star I see tonight..." and make a wish. 20. Despite my best efforts, I am somewhat superstitious. 21. I have 14 wristwatches, none of which work for various reasons. I can't throw them away. 22. I didn't get my driver's license until I was 24. 23. In '87 I produced a manuscript, and scrapped it after the first publisher rejected it. 24. I have met my birthmother - we have a cordial relationship. 25. I have 2 half sisters - we can be described as casual acquaintances at best. 26. My birthmother refuses to tell me anything about my biological father. 27. I have 2 cats, Savannah (the bbw cat) and Xena (the warrior princess). 28. I have been to 3 concerts in my life, The Human League, The Nolans and Neil Diamond. 29. Only one of those concerts were attended voluntarily. 30. I have 2 birthmarks. 31. I started smoking August 1983. 32. I finally quit smoking January 5th 2004. 33. I am a Capricorn, born in the Chinese year of the Horse. 34. I dislocated my shoulder and broke my arm falling off a shed roof, my only fracture ever. 35. Walkers Crisps - Cheese and Onion flavour - (Homer Simpson drool noises) Nuff said! 36. I have 3 formal ball gowns. 37. I don't know how to dance. 38. I have a fetish for military men. 39. I have a love of horses that I never outgrew from my teen years. Maybe one day... 40. I am a procrastinator. 41. I am indecisive. 42. My left boob is larger than the right one. 43. I am self conscious about my teeth, but still smile regardless! British dentistry at it's best! 44. I still have a slight Brit accent, which gets stronger depending on my mood and blood-alcohol level. 45. I am a sole support single parent of a 16 year old walking blob of testosterone. 46. I can name every member of the British Royal Family and their line of succession. 47. My favourite fragrance is Beautiful by Estee Lauder. 48. I have never been given an engagement ring. 49. My love of theatre came via my grandad - the stage door man at the  urlLink Derby Playhouse  in his retirement years. 50. Deep down I am a blue jeans, beer and pizza girl - I just like to  think  I have caviar tastes! 51. I prefer instant coffee to percolated at home, but I do admit to a  urlLink Tim Horton's  addiction. 52. I am definitely a morning person. 53. I am stubborn. 54. I wear my heart on my sleeve. 55. I haven't had sex in over 6 yrs. 56. I miss hugs and kisses more than sex. 57. I want to run my own pub one day. 58. Christmas is my favourite holiday. 59. I have 4 piercings - 2 holes in each ear lobe (how very 80's). 60. I have been a gas station attendant. (BP - Raynesway & London Rd) 61. And a cocktail waitress. (Rhode Island Diner) We had to wear dickie bows and braces (suspenders)! 62. I have been a theatrical costumier in a fancy dress shop. 63. I hate an untidy house... 64. ... however I hate housework. 65. I once had a  urlLink Molly Maid , but used to clean before she arrived, so she wouldn't see the mess. 66. Dish washers are the greatest invention since sliced bread - wish I had one. 67. Once in a while I would love someone to make me a home cooked meal. 68. I love summer thunderstorms. The louder the thunder and heavier the rain the better. 69. I love oral - but this position just doesn't work for me. 70. I can't sleep in the nude, even if it's just a T-shirt, I have to wear something. 71. I sleep on the left and I snore like a freight train. 72. I dream so rarely, I can count them on one hand from the last year. 73. I know all the words to pretty much every  urlLink Showaddywaddy  hit from the 70's and 80's. And so my love of oldies rock and roll was born. 74. I plan to some day drive the  urlLink Trans Canada Highway  from coast to coast. Stopping wherever and whenever I want. 75. In an attempt to stay connected thru the teen years my son and I are becoming  urlLink cinephiles . 76. My favourite red wine is from Australia,  urlLink Rosemount Shiraz . 77. I have never been pulled over by the police, so I don't know if my "get out of jail free" id-card will work or not. 78. I have smoked dope once - but I didn't inhale (ahem) - and I got so freaked out by it, I have never done it since. 79. Yes, I really  am  that vanilla. 80. My favourite dog is the yellow lab. 81. I love airports and air travel - yes even the food. I could spend all day just people watching in the terminal...and sometimes we had to! Best airline ever was Wardair. 82. Favourite food is a little surf and turf ...crab legs and/or bacon wrapped filet mignon. 83. Favourite ethnic food is either Indian or Greek or Chinese or Italian...hmm...ok I like all food. 84. I am a  British chocolate  chocoholic - yes there is a difference. 85. My birth name was Shelly Lynn. I don't feel like a Shelly. 86. If I had had a daughter I would like to have named her Sarah (princess). But sometimes you look at a baby and a name just hits you. Sadly they wouldn't let me use ET for the boy (hey, he was bald and had long fingers!) 87. My dad played with the initials and tried to rhyme the names before giving his grandfatherly approval to my son's name. He himself had gone through alot of school boy taunting with the initials E.G.G. 88. My father was once a professional photographer. 89. He was also a pigeon (RAF - national service) - but I didn't hold that against him. 90. I consider my eyes my best feature. 91. I still don't know what I want to be when I grow up. 92. It's pronounced "Darbee" but spelt " urlLink Derby " - and my heart remains there. 93. I cry when I am happy, when I am sad, at movies, even reading books, and watching tv commercials. I keep Kleenex stocks in the black. 94. I want to one day own my own home. 95. I don't tolerate fools gladly. And I have no time for people who refuse to help themselves. 96. I am a survivor. 97. I avidly collect recipes from magazines, put them in my recipe box - and never make them. 98. I am typically British with my Christmas decorations. Tacky, tasteless, and leaving the Griswald's open mouthed and taking notes. 99. Did I mention I have a military fetish? 100. I still believe in white knights and "happy ever after".    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Six years ago, when Biff and I broke up, I moved from the city out here to the suburbs.  Three reasons:  In my heartbreak it made sense to put a little distance between Biff and I - he has a certain celebrity status, and although not quite gracing the social pages of the daily paper, I certainly didn't want his life without me rammed down my throat.  The boy was 2 years away from starting high school and I didn't want him going through his teen years in the city. Growing up is hard enough without all the added temptations that we know simply as  Toronto .  Without Biff's income or support, I really couldn't afford to stay in the city. So from that aspect it was a no brainer.  One of the first things I did, before I even moved a box into the 'burbs, was to check out what recreational or organized group activities there were for preteens. The boy needed to be able to integrate, feel like he belonged and get a sense of his new community (in my eyes) - and a little discipline/positive male role models wouldn't hurt either. He expressed an interest in the military,  so I did a little research on the web, and found the Navy League of Canada/Royal Canadian Sea Cadets. I placed a call, and the rest, as they say, is history.  Navy League & Sea Cadets ended up being not only a 6 year passion for the boy, but my salvation. I arrived from the city, emotionally battered and bruised, and found a new love. Within weeks I was finding myself getting roped into various aspects of the organization. Oh we need a volunteer for this, someone to do that. It was amazing to feel wanted and needed again. Ultimately I was elected to hold a branch position and went on to hold that position for 5 years until I resigned in September of last year.  I made new friends. I didn't feel alone anymore, or a stranger in a new town. Friendships that grew over the following years, to the point where a day wouldn't go by where I didn't talk to one of the other "moms". We socialized outside of cadets together as a group. Dinners, drinks, shopping, road trips, parades, family celebrations - you name it - the mom's were always together.  Last year, a year ago tonight to be exact to the day, a good portion of Ontario and parts of the northern USA were affected by a power outage. The mom's started arriving at my house shortly after 5pm. We sat, we drank, we lit candles and we waited by the phone. Finally the call I had been waiting for came; and my cadet moms were there with me to offer hugs of condolence, and share a few tears. At 75 years of age my father had passed away.  In my dark humoured kind of way, I observed that it was typical of my father, waiting until the entire province was having a candle-light vigil, for him to finally go. Forever the showman.  So it seemed fitting that the mom's all came together again this evening. A lot has happened in the past year. I will go into more detail in a later blog perhaps. Suffice to say, we don't see each other 3 or 4 times a week anymore. We don't talk on the phone two, three and sometimes four times a day anymore. However the fact that they all took the time out of their schedules tonight means a lot to me. More than they will ever know.  We sat in out on the deck, in the hot tub, polished off a couple of bottles of wine over the course of the evening, talked our faces off ...and most importantly we were surrounded by candlelight.  We talked about everything, from our kids, to the cadet corps, to our latest news. We didn't sit and dwell on the anniversary. We didn't get maudlin or depressive. But the fact, despite the different paths our lives have taken us this past year, that we all came together again for one evening makes me feel very loved indeed.  Judy M., Agnes, Judy B. and Wendy...thank you.  Due to it being a leap year, the actual anniversary by the  date  will be Saturday, so I hope to cover a few thoughts over the weekend.   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      (the story so far...):  Music has always been near and dear to me. For me music is connected with emotions and memories. I can hear a particular song and be instantly transported back to a time and place, recalling it with such clarity, that I can almost reach out and touch it. I don't apologize for my choice in song or artist, they were the songs of the time, and the memories they evoke. Memories don't tend to worry about what is cool and hip, just what matters and what is near and dear to your heart.       Dexy's Midnight Runners - Come on Eileen   1982 - and my girlfriends Maz, Marie, Tracey and I are regulars in the Saddler Gate wine bars on a Saturday night. 15 years old, drinking underage - as was everyone else - trying our best to look cool with our 80's hair, makeup, lace shirts, twice round belts,  urlLink ra-ra skirts and leg-warmers . Sipping on half pints of larger - long since gone warm - the fact we hated the taste meant it lasted longer on our limited resources. Hoping to meet the lad of our dreams before 11 o'clock came and we had to run to catch the last bus home.  The last bus was always packed, bodies crammed, standing room only - both upstairs and down - no doubt highly illegal, but when it's literally the last bus out of the city for the night, you don't really have a choice. You just sit there hoping and praying the drunk lurching in front of you, hanging on for dear life, doesn't suddenly decide to share his 10 pints of best bitter and greasy kebab with you.  Come on Eileen was our signature song of the week/month. Four tipsy teenagers - high on life rather than the 2 whole drinks we had consumed all night - huddled in a huge embrace, singing our hearts out on all the  urlLink "Toora loora toora loo rye aye"  parts.  What our mothers were thinking, letting us out like that on our weekend  urlLink pub crawls  (never on a school night), I will never know. Things sure are different today - and I make sure my son is none the wiser of his mother's wild past! ;-)  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    "Toora loora toora loo rye aye"  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The Bell Pub on Saddler Gate...one of many.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Gets kinda bad when even my daily horoscope tells me to lighten up!  August 11, 2004: It is important for you to not over-analyze every little detail of your situation at this time, especially when it comes to issues regarding love and romance. It could be that you are jumping to ridiculous conclusions based on purely circumstantial evidence. Don't lose sleep over things that you don't even know to be true. Release your stranglehold on certain issues, and concentrate on simply rebuilding your own self-confidence.   And on top of that, this is the 3rd time someone (or something!) has commented on my lack of confidence.  Dunno really how to be more confident without coming off like a braggart.  Then I will be getting comments like "Who-TF does she think  she  is?" lol  It's a no-win situation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have decided to attempt the  urlLink on-line personals  again. I ain't getting any younger and I am definitely too old to be doing the pub-pull for sure. I think the most difficult thing in the world, after filling out their little online questionnaire and checking off all the appropriate little boxes - is the section where you get to write a little something about yourself. Your blurb to the world. Your 30 second commercial in the Super Bowl of life. I sit and stare at the screen....mind blank....start to type...omg no that sounds too desperate...backspace....no that sounds too needy....backspace....too sarcastic....backspace....hell, even  I  wouldn't be interested in that person!....backspace ....sigh. Too bad I can't just throw in a blog link or a website link and then they would get to know the  real me . Not some glammed up glitzy pick up line, but the real McCoy. But then I remember the idea is to actually "attract" someone and not have them running to the hills or calling the nearest psych ward to have me admitted....sigh...back to the drawing board.   Post Script: August 16, 2004 Well so much for dating in the new millenium.  I gave the ad a week, and not so much as a nibble. I sent out 5 "icebreakers" to various local men who had ads posted.  And whom I consider "attainable" men, not adonis's, but normal everyday blokes.  Nadda! Not so much as a "thanks but no thanks". So I have deleted the ad.  The longer I leave it running and visible the likelihood of some joker at work coming across it and having a giggle is huge.  (I should know, we have giggled over others before). Back to the drawing board!  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I meant to mention this incident on Friday, but in the excitement of the new computer it slipped my mind. Not that this incident is overly exciting (obviously or I wouldn't have forgotten) or that is it worth an entire post of it's own - but it's 04:28 hrs and I grab inspiration wherever and whenever I can.  Rewind to Friday: We arrived at Biff's to pick up the two computers, downtown parking in Toronto is a premium, so I naturally parked at the grocery store. Do a little shopping ($15) and I can park here for free for 2 hours! We call Biff on my mobile, say "Hey we're here!", the boy heads over to the lobby to meet Biff, I throw the mobile back in my purse and head into the grocery store.  Forced grocery shopping is not fun, especially in a store that you don't particularly like (Sobey's) and even moreso even when you aren't familiar with the layout of the store. Initially I thought I would have trouble spending $15 (silly girl) but as it turns out junk food adds up  really   really  quickly ($26). I am about to walk away back to the parking lot with my bags and go to grab my phone to find out where the boys are...still up in the apartment or down waiting at the car - and it's gone.  I had that sickening  thud  in my stomach as I rifled through my purse. I always keep the phone in one of those Velcro outer-pockets on my purse, but I check every conceivable pocket and compartment anyways, as we all do at times like this, search anywhere and everywhere - found the TV remote in the fridge once using the " anywhere and everywhere "search approach (patent pending), but I digress (surprise, surprise). It's gone. I leave the groceries at the end of the checkout (it wasn't busy in there at least) and quickly check the aisles of the grocery store - as if by some miracle I will find it lying on the ground - and the whole time I am thinking to myself various comments like: "I didn't lock the keypad! Someone is calling Bangladesh on it right now!"  (not that I assumed the person who had my phone was from Bangladesh you understand, but it was the first "long distance charges may apply" that sprang to mind).  "See what happens when you come into Toronto?" "This is the reason I hate this city!" etc, etc, etc. It wasn't pretty. I was basically silently screaming the whole time about what a den of inequity Toronto was - and how a sweet good clean living suburban gal like myself just got ripped off. I assumed that whilst I was in the store, picking tomatoes, or browsing the shelves, someone had gone by and swiped my phone out of the pocket of my purse - fuckers! I left my name and home phone number with the cashier, "it's a flip phone with a cute little ladybird keychain attached to it" and headed back to the car (thankfully noone had swiped my groceries whilst I was frantically searching the store for the phone).  No one is at the car. I stand and stew about the whole situation. All I want to do at this precise moment is leave and go home. I want to go and phone my cell phone carrier, cancel my phone, make my police report. Just get me the hell out of this place, damn I feel dirty, I need a shower. I spot the fella in the parking booth - I wonder if that's what he wanted to be when the career counselors at school listed his skills against possible career paths - and decide even that's too catty for me. I head over and ask if he has a phone I could use. My plan is to call my cell phone and see if I can negotiate it's return for a price. Unfortunately all he has is a phone that calls "upstairs". I have no idea if this is to the grocery store, or maybe some great security hub of uniformed guards, one-way glass and computers whirring away in the background. He then proceeds to direct me to the nearest bank of payphones. Gee thanks!  I start to head back up to the lobby, hoping to find the boy and Biff, and they are heading to the escalator, arms loaded with cpus, wiring, and a box of CD's. I start to blurt the whole situation, my voice definitely up a few octaves I would guess , eyes wild, breathing uneven, (ironically give me a real emergency for someone else and I am a cool calm professional - throw me into a minor blip of a calamity in my own life and I over react!). The boy interrupts me, big ol' shit eating grin on his face. "I have your phone!" Relief!! Then the penny drops. "How did you know...?" Turns out the little bugger followed me into the grocery store (unbeknownst to me obviously) and lifted my phone as a prank. In broad daylight, in full view of both store staff and other shoppers, like Faggin's Artful Dodger. Both he and Biff apparently had tittered at my expense knowing exactly how I would react.  Ha! Ha! Very funny - Not! Then it dawns on me. Not a single persons bothered to stop the boy. Or bothered to call out, alert or otherwise notify me even! I can appreciate in today's society why people didn't want to tackle the boy - heaven's knows they may suddenly be looking down the barrel of a gun or feeling the pointy end of a knife. But what was the reasoning behind not telling me? What a sad reflection on society and the world we live in today. We witness a crime and do nothing. We turn a blind eye and turn our backs preferring to avoid the inconvenience of saying anything. Heaven forbid giving a statement or leaving your name and number may take valuable minutes out of your day. Perfect example - shots are fired at a local dance venue, and we wonder why out of several hundred potential witnesses no-one comes forward to say they saw something, anything....heck half of them won't even admit to being there on the night in question!  Sometimes I really think I was born in the wrong decade - or at least I should go find myself a little bumfucknowhere town where people still act like a community and the "every-last-man-for-himself" family, the "what-have-you-done-for-me-lately's" and the "what's-in-it-for-me" clan haven't moved into town yet.  Yeah I know it was called Mayberry. (sigh) 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well it wouldn't be summer if I didn't drag the boy out on a day trip somewhere at least once. On the recommendation of a colleague we went to the  urlLink Ontario Renaissance Festival . What a cool place! The directions were handwritten on a scrap of paper from work and initially we got a little lost. We were missing an entire street off the map and couldn't figure out why we couldn't "see the castle from the road - you can't miss it". Eventually, doubling back, we hit a small sign staked in the ground and were off down some rural looking road. I recognized the tour bus in the parking lot as one that we had been sat behind at the light when we had initially gotten off the highway some 20 minutes earlier - sigh.  No offence intended at all, but I was surprised at the number of non-Festival employees that dress in period costume for these events. The whole medieval/renaissance theme sure seems to appeal to the youth of today also. I saw more than a few Marilyn Manson lookalikes with their associated pale, emaciated, raven haired entourage. Although I am quite sure they were more into the weaponry, charms, amulets and witchcraft items on sale, than the stage-shows and jousting - just call it a hunch.  It took a little getting used to being addressed as "m'lady" and at one point being told I had the look of a "salty wench". I figured I would be offended one way or another so I didn't pursue it.  Initially the boy had a look of "omg I can't believe my mother has forced this torture upon me" but after an hour he got right into it and thoroughly enjoyed himself, especially the stage shows. The realization that this was probably one of the last "day trips" the boy and I will be taking together was very sobering. He is growing up fast, will have his full driver's license by the end of the summer, and no doubt will be taking his girlfriend to the next 'Ren-Fest' or whatever other event catches his eye.  Post Script:  The food offered at these events is certainly not the typical fayre of McDonalds and Burger King ...steak on a stake (pun intended) and turkey legs are brandished by would be Henry the VIII's  - on a personal note pass on the turkey leg.  They look and smell devine...and that's where the good part ends.  They are tasteless and deepfriend.  Yuk! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Opening ceremony at the main gates.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    We were about to head out the gate on the way home and I realised we hadn't taken a pic of me! urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The boy with his souvenir, an ocarina.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Getting a henna tattoo...I was tempted too but chickened out.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The birds of prey demonstration was excellent.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Queen Elizabeth I on a royal "walkabout".  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ironic...didn't I just say "all I wanted was a white knight" just yesterday?!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    At least they aren't tilting at windmills!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am a stubborn woman at the best of times I know. But I come by that trait honestly via mum's example. She raised me alone, with no financial support from my father, preferring to be able to hold her head high as she saw it rather than go to the courts cap in hand. The court system and the way it dealt with single parents back in the late 60's and early 70's was indeed archaic at best. I do the same; the headache and heartache of pursuing my deadbeat ex through the courts, and having him in our lives again far outweighs any relief such funds would provide, so I don't bother.  If anything was needed done at home growing up, mum did it herself or we did without. I remember just one occasion when she accepted the help of another. Our next-door neighbour Pete installed shelves for us in a broom closet. I was dispatched as his first mate, helper, "go-for", to help pass things, hold things in place etc. After he refused financial remuneration mum bought him a bottle and he was guaranteed free coffee over the fence for life.  Looking back I guess that was a funny practice, but it came so natural to us. We would stand out in the back garden yammering away nineteen to the dozen over the garden fence. I'd go in and make a couple of cups of coffee, and bring them out. We'd continue talking away, they in their garden and I in mine, mugs would be passed back over the fence when empty. It never occurred to us to invite them over for coffee, to sit in the house would have made it seem more like a visit, this was very casual and friendly.  The point I was trying to make - god I go off topic so easily - is that equally as stubborn I refuse all help and offers of assistance all the time. I struggle to do it myself or do without. My quick and easy ceiling fan installation took almost 8 hours. My arms ached for days afterwards. Of course I found out after the fact that I could have attached the blades before mounting the fan housing and light assembly on the ceiling. However, I did it, too stubborn to ask the spouses of girlfriends for help. It's a sign of weakness and I am not a weak woman. Naturally they always berate me later. "You did what?" "It cost you how much?" "You should've called Joe!" But I smile, silently strengthened in the knowledge that I didn't have to call Joe - or Tom, or Dick, or Harry, to come to my rescue. I am no fragile damsel in distress. "Never be beholden to anyone!" I don't know who branded that on my brain, it sounds like a grandmotherism. Always repay you debts! Coffee? Dinner? My first born? We sure ate out like kings this week to repay Biff the computer god.  For six years I worked tirelessly as a parent volunteer with my son's cadet corps. Some weeks I was busy six nights out of seven with meetings, paperwork, cleaning, fundraising, chaperoning, you name it. For six years I poured my energies into the community and into this youth program. I produced a newspaper for 3 straight years, managed their web interests, etc. My thanks and recognition was engraved on a plaque for four straight years. I know how it feels to contribute to something worthwhile and deserving. Why is it then so hard for me to receive the same? Am I a born martyr?  Perhaps that's where I am going wrong. Perhaps being too independent, self reliant and self sufficient is a major turn off. Most men after all need to satisfy their own "hero complex" and feel like they are rescuing the maid atop the tower, their damsel in distress. They need to feel  needed . Perhaps the biggest problem in my love life is the lack of a tall tree outside my bedroom window. Maybe being too pushy and forceful emasculates them. Perhaps I need to admit to my own inadequacies, admit to needing help, admit to being too pigheaded and too proud to ask for it.  Admit to needing to be rescued.   "All I wanted was a white knight, With a good heart, Soft touch, Fast horse..."   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well as you may have noticed I am back! Bigger and badder than before. The speed of this new computer completely blows me away. I should learn the specs 'cos I know someone gonna ask before too much longer.  My thanks, love and appreciation to Biff for all his hard work over the last week rebuilding the old computer and programming the new one. For spending the day under my desk yesterday (oooerrrr) plugging it all in (ahem), for running cables and getting everything up and running on both computers. The old Atari wannabe now graces a new computer desk in the boy's room, so now we can both be online at the same time. Too cool or what?? Hell I am impressed!  My love to Deli and Moonie who commiserated with me on Sunday when the world went black (day the cpu cacked - a true Sunday bloody Sunday) and spent almost 3 hours on the phone in a 3-way conversation with me, just kickin' back and talking. My love to M. for the sweetest offline I have received in a long time that actually brought a tear to my eye. Too bad they broke the mould when they made that one.  Well, that's all I needed to say ...on with the show... 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        A woman should have... 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It was suggested to me via instant message the other day, that my blog goes too far. I am too raw, too exposed, and too open. I guess to some degree that is true. For me my blog is my someone to talk to when I get home at the end of the day. My someone to say "You're not gonna believe this" to. My confessor, my secret keeper, my storytelling audience, my friend. The fact that a few people stumble across this blog either via my  urlLink website  or via the blogger main page and decide to listen in is just an added bonus. On the whole my life isn't that interesting to maintain an ongoing interest in what I have to say, especially if you don't even know me.  With one exception, the comments left by readers have been fine. Be they positive or negative, I invite the feedback comments. I just tend to get click happy with my delete button if the messages are hateful or threatening.  Through my adolescence I kept a diary, in the drawer of my bedside table. I would spill my secrets every night, "Dear Diary..." School girl crushes, events of the day - from age 12 through 18. A boyfriend - the man who went on to be my husband - decided to read my diary, and as a result I stopped writing for almost 20 years. Over the years those diaries have been discarded and thrown away. That they were lost is the only thing I regret, moreso than him knowing what they contained. The boyfriend/husband has long since gone, those missing years held in those diaries I can never get back.  So far only two posts on this blog have reduced me to tears. They were written whilst tears flowed unchecked, and even now if I read them my eyes will fill. But putting them down on "paper" instead of bottling them up inside is the best therapy around. Then, comes the question, why broadcast it to the world? Perhaps, so I don't feel so alone, perhaps to invite a comment from a kindred spirit, to show there is more to me than meets the eye, and perhaps there is still a grain of that 4 year old hammy red-headed performer inside me that loves to be the centre of attention. Pass me the skipping rope...  This is my cheap therapy. I get to sit and talk about whatever I want, whatever is on my mind (or in my heart). Occasionally you may comment, but on the whole, like the expensive therapists in the phone book, you sit back, nod, and say "uh-huh" in the right places. The therapists charge in excess of $100 per hour - you guys are a lot cheaper!  So if I offend you, if you feel I am being far too intimate with my life then please click the little "X" in the top right hand corner of your screen and allow me to resolve that problem for you. (Helpful lil devil ant I?) 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I am still computerless. It seems my old Atari-wannabe is putting up a good fight with Biff. He can't get the system to stabilize when he installs the latest Microsoft service package. He will be able to get it up and working, it's just he doesn't know how stable it will be. (sigh)  Sooooo that's why at 4pm yesterday I was scouring the ads for a new computer. The gigs and bytes and ram specifications are all alien to me, so I pretty much spent an hour on the phone. "It has what? OK hang on let me call you back." "Hey Biff, is this good?...." Sure it would have been easier to have Biff do the work, but I never do things easy. (Plus he never offered!)  Tonight I go pick up the new computer, Biff will configure and program and hopefully by Friday night/Saturday I will be back up and working! Apparently I have a "smoking kick ass system" now. I guess that's good eh? (Should be for the price!)  So I'll sign off for the rest of the week, and resume blogging with yall on the weekend, all being well and God willing.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My computer is poorly. Now there's an English word I haven't used in a while. I remember not long after arriving in this country I was talking to my new boss, going over procedures, routines and expectations, when I posed the question, "What happens if I am poorly?" He just looked at me blankly like I was not only from another country but perhaps another planet. "Poorly" for the odd non-Brit reading this is "unwell, sick, or ill". Finally a light came on in his eyes, as I tried to explain what I meant. "Oh you mean home, sick!" To which I nodded in amazement, I could take time off for missing home? Too cool! What a great country this Canada!!  My computer is poorly. By the time the boy and I arrived home from the movie theatre the gremlins has clambered into my hard drive and were having a gay old time. I naturally assumed it was a virus, but have since been advised a corrupt file. Either way it is not good.  I have a very addictive personality at the best of times, be it in love and in life generally. I am either totally addicted, besotted and involved - or not. I do attempt a casual middle ground but it just never seems to work too well for me. So it should come as no surprise to anyone who knows me that, yes (gasp) I am addicted to my computer. Once the realization sunk in that I was looking at a computer problem beyond the realm and scope of my capabilities (ie: turning on/off the cpu, hitting the return/escape key, clicking the mouse), I started to feel nauseous. Sunday afternoon on an August Bank Holiday Weekend? Good luck in finding someone to help!  I called my computer god, Biff. Doesn't anyone answer their phones anymore? For once incredibly he decided to get back to me within the hour. Someone actually not away at a cottage up north this weekend? Shock! Horror! Thank you GOD! OK panic over, Biff is here, breathe, breathe. We quickly determine that it wasn't going to be a speedy over the phone solution. Plus trying to dumb down the instructions so I could follow and my trying to describe what I was looking at was only succeeding in raising our respective voices and blood pressures. Unplug, unplug, unplug....oh my god look at the dust under there, I sure hope I remember where all these plugs go in...off to Toronto!  The highway is empty bang slap in the middle of a Bank Holiday Weekend. The crowds have already fled the city and it's still a full day before they are scheduled to return.  Initially the plan is to drop the computer at Biff's, all go for an early dinner, and then head back to suburbia leaving Biff to work his magic. The three of us have a highly enjoyable meal at a local watering hole (where they actually did know his name). Lots of laughs and "remember when" stories. Biff and I were always very talented at living in the past. He invites us back to his place to watch a movie whilst he tinkers. I guess he is enjoying the company and the reminiscing as much as I am. So that's how we came to be sitting on Biff's leather couch in his downtown apartment for almost six hours on Saturday night.  It was strange. Being surrounded by both the familiar and the unfamiliar. How many times had I dusted that framed photograph of his dad? His style and mine, such polar opposites. His apartment is white walls, lots of glass and windows, spartan, chrome, leather, black wood and minimalist in the extreme. Mine is colourful, I like to think cozy, some might say grandmotherly, cushioned, textured, an eclectic mish-mash that offers no theme or style, walls and shelves full of memories and personal expressions. A recent visitor on seeing my home for the first time said, "It's very you." I was smart enough not to enquire further, but perhaps I should have!  I was looking for signs of his exwife I guess, but didn't look too hard, just in case I found them. It wasn't easy being in a place with a man I knew so completely, knowing that this was the home he had set up with his bride. But the photographs, few though they were didn't hold any new faces, and I was pleased to see he still has photos displayed of the boy.  He has a 15th floor view facing south into the downtown core. In daylight the city lay spread before me, the wide blue strip on the horizon indicating how close to the lake we were. The same view at night looked like something out of a "coffee table art book". I so wish I had had my camera with me, the view was truly breathtaking. The Toronto skyline, financial towers lit like silent sentries flanking the world's tallest free standing Christmas tree - ok it was the CN Tower, but you get the idea. I was struck dumb by the beauty of it all and could only stand and gaze slack-jawed like some hick country cousin.  One movie turned into two, he was having to totally reformat the computer and progress was slow. Finally we joined him in the office, more talk, more reminiscing. Catching up on the lives of his friends, who until 6 years ago had been acquaintances of mine too, sharing my dinner table and I theirs.  We talked about our respective jobs, and for the first time I answered honestly when asked if I still liked my job. I said no - and didn't feel the need to immediately justify my response. This man knew how I had loved it for so many years, knew the agonies of the job, the stresses and the heartache. After 10 years he didn't need an explanation; as I in turn totally understand his desire to move on himself. He has irons in the fire for both New York and London, he is going through his "anywhere but here" phase.  He speaks briefly of his exwife, calling her "madam" and certainly giving the impression that she was high maintenance.  I tell him of my relatively non-existant love life since we split.  I mention Maybe, and he seems genuinely interested, and disapointed that things didn't work out for us.   I am well aware my relationship with my ex is not common.  Perhaps because when the break-up finally came our life together had been reduced to that of best friends or even siblings.  The love was there but the passion long gone.  It made the final breakup anger-free.  Emotional yes, heartbreaking yes, but without the pain of anger, accusations and betrayal.  We had simply drifted apart.  By 1am it is becoming apparent that this is going to take a little longer than anticipate.  We reluctantly leave the Atari-wannabe for her overnight belly-rub at Biff's and are homeward bound.  Even the parkinglot attendant has closed up for the night, barrier up, so I save $18 (welcome to downtown Toronto) and slide home free.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, I haven't a clue which direction this entry is going to take so be forewarned, and maybe if you aren't into a long drawn out tale skip this post (and some might say this blog) completely.  We are going to cover a little history. To some it will be ancient history, probably even before some were born (which is a very sobering thought). For me it feels like yesterday.  December 28th 1983 was a Wednesday and the first day back to work after the Christmas Break for most. A short week however with New Year's celebrations slated for the weekend. They say your entire life can change direction in the space of a few split seconds. That evening, as my mum came through the back door from work, my world crumbled.  Looking back I am very critical of what happened. It's so easy to play armchair quarterback and point out all the errors. But what's done is done, and having carried this with me for the last 20-odd years, I can vouch for the fact that beating yourself up over "shoulda, coulda, woulda" will never change the outcome.  Mum came through the door and immediately we knew something was wrong. My grandparents were still at the house on their over-Christmas visit. Together we managed to catch her as she collapsed in the doorway. Her speech was slurred, she said she had a headache and felt very tired. It never occurred to us to call 999 - ironic considering who I work for now - instead we called the family doctor, who's surgery was just up the road. He advised he was on his way, and he walked out on a surgery full of patients waiting to be seen and came to the house. He immediately called an ambulance. He could tell from her condition that she had suffered a massive stroke. He stood and watched as she convulsed again and I remember the  anger  I carried for years against him thinking he could have  done   something ,  anything , instead of standing there like a bump on a log. In the confusion, as my elderly grandparents tried to comfort their daughter on the floor; the doctor took me to one side and warned me that it didn't look good and to prepare myself for the worst.  I WAS 16 FUCKING YEARS OLD  - what kind of "professional" delivers that kind of news to a teenager like that?  The following 3 days are a blur of hospital waiting rooms, tests and tears. She suffered a second stroke after we arrived at the hospital and they moved her into intensive care where she never regained consciousness. By the third day they were suspecting brain death, and so after carrying out the required tests to confirm this they turned off the machines. At 49 years old, with no previous warning signs or symptoms, my mother died just before 6pm on New Year's Eve 1983.  I went out and 'celebrated' the New Year at a Derby nightclub with my friends. I wanted so badly to get drunk beyond belief - but nothing affected me. I thank God for my friends at that time, Marie, Tracey, my boyfriend Wayne, and the other associated hangers-on. I have since felt incredible  guilt  for going out that night, but at the time I guess it is what I needed. To be with my peers, to cry, to be away from my grandparents and their grief. I needed the mental distraction.  Three days later my grandfather collapsed and died instantly of a massive heart attack. He was heading for the bus in the Marketplace after going to get his hair cut for his daughter's funeral. Grandma and I were numb beyond belief. I never did properly grieve for the man who was the only male role model in my life from age 5 onward. In retrospect, I lost my mother and my father in less than a week.  The rest is a blur. I vaguely remember the funeral home, picking out what we wanted, ordering flowers etc. The Doctor, despite his lack of tact with dealing with teens, was a dab hand at prescribing sleeping pills and tranquilisers.  I cant remember if the funerals (held on separate days) were before or after my birthday on the 5th. But I do remember my grandmother had found the birthday card my mother had bought for me, and although not signed, she gave it to me regardless. Any memory of a gift I am afraid has faded.  In a perfect world grandma and I would have been perfect support for one another. Unfortunately that was not the case. I was never truly accepted into the "family" in her eyes because I was adopted, I wasn't  blood,  I wasn't a Pritchard. In accordance with my mother's wishes, Grandma was appointed my guardian until I was 18. After the funeral was taken care of, the Will read, and the financial settlement made, she returned to her home and life and left me to get on with mine. There ended her role as guardian. My adoptive father, estranged from us since I was 5, remained out of the picture. And so it was just me and a black and white cat named "Lucky", and thankfully some very supportive next-door neighbours who fed me for the first few weeks.  Grandma returned to the house once in the following months, to remove my mother's jewelry. Items that she and Grandi had given mum over the years. Thankfully I was able to salvage her engagement ring and wedding band, but everything else of value she took.  My mother was a local government officer for the local City Council. Thanks to some red tape cutting I was allowed to remain in our Council house, and that's how I came to work for the Council - my first job. I had to drop out of college, put my dreams on a back burner and earn a living. That dream has sat and simmered unattended on the back burner for so long now it has boiled dry and the pan burnt out.  Grief is a funny old thing, you think you are doing great and suddenly realise you have made two coffee's not thinking. Or something will happen during your day and you start to think, "Oh mum will laugh when I tell her," only to be stopped short by the realization that she isn't there.  A few years later, before I finally left England, I ran into my grandmother's next-door neighbours out on a shopping trip in town. They were uncomfortable, a little embarrassed, no doubt from having listened to all the "evil grand-daughter" stories. They informed me that my grandmother had passed, some time before. I was shocked. The woman obviously excluded me from her family and life to the extent, that even when she died no-one came to inform me - and all I ever did to displease her was have the wrong blood.  I have grieved for mum for over 21 years; ironically that's longer than I actually knew her, I was 16 when she died. My son is 16. I look at him, with his typical teen lifestyle of X-box games, music and junkfood and just want to hold him close, keep him safe, let him know he is loved, and silently wonder was I ever really that young. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink    December 25th 1983 having a Christmas drink with the next-door neighbours.
</post>


</Blog>