<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What in the world am i suppose to talk about first?? lol well the most current news for me is that i'm trying to avoid/get rid of my stalker. I mean the girl is loonier than the one who flew over the cuckoo's nest. i mean really...there is no need to call me 3 times and e-mail me a short biography in the span of 24 hours. I don't answer my phone when you call and i certainly don't reply to your e-mails...never have and i never will...The girl needs to invest some time in playing that boardgame called CLUE cuz she sure is lacking one. This youngin has been tracking me down for at least 4 years. She has successfully found me as i went thru 4 moves, at least 4 roommates and 5 phone numbers (even my cell)....The girl needs to sign up for the FBI pronto...i bet she would have found Osama within 24 hours of any attack. lol  Anyways, this girlie has found me once again and i am not quite sure how to deal with the situation as i don't want to go avoiding this person for the rest of my life. But if she calls me one more time i think i will send her a nice e-mail telling her to leave me be cuz this is getting out of control! She even stalked my mother in order to stalk me!! i'm sill mad at that one.   i have one question though: WHY do i attract all these stalker-like peeps? i just don't get it! if anyone has any tips or ideas on how to get out of this situation please let a sistah know ASAP.
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay so I am a member of BlackPlanet right? and I received a message from someone on&nbsp;the site&nbsp;today. On this person's profile they talked about how they are married and have been for 15 years. He goes on to say that he is looking for another woman, but that he&nbsp;WILL NOT&nbsp;leave his wife. Why is he looking for another woman then you may ask?  &nbsp;  Come to find out that&nbsp;his wife was in an accident 3 years ago and is now confined to a wheelchair. So his solution to that is finding another woman on the internet. Now is it just me or is that just completely selfish??  &nbsp;  I mean I understand it is probably hard for the man with his wife being in a wheelchair. But I mean c'mon on! It's 10 times&nbsp;worse for the wife!! She already has to suffer by being paralyzed and then to have her husband be with another woman on top of it all??  &nbsp;  My cousin(by marriage) was married to my cousin, Gail.&nbsp;Gail was a beautiful woman. Everyone always complimented her beauty and her sweet personality, and then she was diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis. She wasn't expected to live long, but she did. She lost most of her hair, gained a bit of weight, her speech and thinking were effected, and she was confined to a wheelchair. I always wondered if her husband would stay with her and believe it or not...he did. My cousin died not too long ago this year. Now I don't know if her husband was faithful to her, but I like to think that he was.  &nbsp;  Personally, I couldn't imagine finding a man on the side while my husband sat in a wheelchair because of a misfortune.&nbsp;How could anyone live with the guilt?? And with your vows it says "thru sickness and health" right?? And I would think the love for your spouse would stop you from going that route anyway.&nbsp;I just don't think that most people really know what love is all about. &nbsp;So, what would you do? Would you stay faithful to your spouse if they all of a sudden became confined to a wheelchair? or would you cheat or even get a divorce?&nbsp; Be honest now!   
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok so my girl Darnee and I went to this Male Review (that's a male strip club for you people not in the know) and we enjoyed ourselves immensely. Some of the men there were very fine but some were also very gay. lol....But as any woman, we can appreciate a nicely toned body no matter what the sexual preference of the male. :) So, anyways there were some males darnee and i favored over the rest of course. I won't lie...some of those white dancers had all the black women drooling and racing to the stage in admiration. I don't know what kind of breed of white men they were, but DAMMMM...lol  anyways, there was one particular dancer i liked and had my way with, and we shall call him Mister Gray Boxers because he was wearing, of course, gray boxerbriefs. :) So about a couple of weeks later after the club, I was working out at the gym like i normally do and i looked over to my right and my jaw DROPS. Who do i see??? Noone other than Mr. Gray Boxers himself working out at MY gym!!   I went through a series of emotions: shock, disbelief, unsurity, shock and disbelief again, embarrassment, and then finally admiration because ya boy still looked good even fully clothed. lol  Well, i had never seen him at my gym before, but now i have seen him twice since the initial time. I mean what does one do after seeing a stripper one night and now you seem them on the regular at your gym?? i mean should i go up to him and say "hey, remember me? Your crotch was in my face one weekend!" or what?? lol  I mean you're not suppose to actually SEE your strippers in normal everyday life because they are SUPPOSE to be just a fantasy.   i am so tempted to say something to him, but i don't think i should because it may embarrass him and make him uncomfortable because technically i was one of his clients...oh well, i guess i'll just keep it to myself.  One thing i also want to mention is that at a male review it's ANYTHING goes. The women are so rowdy and raunchy there, and they can do whatever they want with the males. But at a female strip club men can't even touch...  oh well..glad i was born a woman! lol... :o)  
      
</post>


</Blog>