<Blog>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well so far i've - Played tennis against the wall @ hartnell for a good hour and a half, then immediately afterwords, I - Played golf w/ Adam Franscioni, and i guess we tied (i gave him 30 strokes).  Now i have no clue as to what ima do for tha third one... Well, i'm going to a bonfire tonight, and i think ima bring my frisbee, so yeah... We'll see where that takes me, lol... i'm not gonna drink, i've already promised myself that... but we'll see how it goes anyways, lol... well i'll tty afterwords... 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Day three awaits, but i dunno if i have 3 sports available...  -ima play sum tennis in the morning, maybe w/ meryl (lol... i feel so bad, i woke her up when i asked her... i deserve to play w/ myself... lol)  -ima play sum golf w/ adam franscioni, i need sum confidence back after my bro beat me... lol... but i don't think i'll do as badly as i did yesterday...  -I'm stumped!... maybe we'll pick up a game of ultimate frisbee @ ty's bonfire... oh well, i hope soo, i won't have anything to do there anyways, i don't wanna drink, so i'll be a DD... 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   first sport - i played nine holes of golf @ salinas fairways w/ my bro, and he beat me!... i feel so shitty, lol... i don't think he's ever beat me, but i'm happy for him...  second sport - I, weakened by tha trifecta, sought only to practice tennis w/ myself and all i did was serve and hit against tha wall... tha whole time there were 'bout like 10 kids sitting behind 2 of their friends playing; they were cool, but this one girl kept on looking @ me, i dunno..  third sport - It's a sport!... lol, it says so on the wall of the billiard place... I played against Garrett (3-0) and then adam (1-0)... sandeys didn't wanna play against me, wonder why?... lol 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   first sport - I hit balls @ laguna seca golf club cuzz my dad was playin' tennis @ chamisal tennis club and wanted to hit w/ me...  Second sport - I played tennis w/ myself for a while, against tha wall @ hartnell... loner, lol... and then w/ my pops...  third sport - I went fishing w/ ty, from like 5:15 till past sunset, and we didn't catch a thing... ahhh!... so frustrating, lol...- 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   sups!  Today's day 2 of the 3 by 3! If you don't kno what i'm talkin' 'bout, tha 3 by three is 3 days in a row of completing tha trifecta, which is 3 sports, of @ least an hour and a half of, in one day... crze!... well once that 3 by 3 is over, ima see how much longer i can keep that streak goin'  stay tuned! 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This morning i told my brother what i really think of him, that he is prolly the most selfish person i kno...I kno i hurt him this morning, and i apologized to him... lol, i can't help but always feel like shit, cuzz i always hurt people or mess things up.  ahh, i cried extra hard in the shower today...  For those of you who don't kno, which is basically everyone except one other, i cry in the shower everyday.  I kno it's nothing to be proud of, but that is how i vent my anger, frustration, and most of all, my self-pity.  Not one day has gone bye where i don't ask God for forgiveness for the wrongs i have committed.  I've been staying extra long in the shower these past weeks, and i have begged and begged for what i do not deserve.  The truth of the matter is, taking a shower is the best part of my days, it's the only place where i can cry, and no one can hear me.  If you read this, don't think differently of me, i'm still an asshole, i don't need ur sympathy. 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, i hope ultimate frisbee counts as a sport, or how 'bout pushing Frank Smythe's beast of a truck up a hill, or maybe chasing Adam F. down the beach (tha asshole... lol)... well, i completed sumthing... 

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm pretty bored right now... so yeah...  july 3: I went to that bonfire the other night, it was pretty good... I met sum cool gurls over there, who aren't sluts (i think... lol), but thank god, i was 'bout to kill myself if i had to be 'round a bunch of those... but yeah, those gurls were cool, i think her name was Natalia and Camilla (her cousin), they were pretty friendly... Yeah, adam and i played frisbee for a little bit, hope that counted, haha... but i had sum mallows, so i'm good... lol  july 4: Last night i just went w/ my family and sasha to dennis tha menice park to watch the firewerks... lol, we had to get there @ 3 in the afternoon!, now that sux... haha... it's alright though, i had a chick magnet w/ me... lol, if u've never seen sasha, she's the cutest thing in the world, second to one other, haha... But yeah, all i had to do was walk down the beach, and "AWWWWW, can i pet ur doggy?, what's it's name?, she's so cute, awwwww, what's ur name?....." lol...  Today i just played sum tennis in the morning (7 am!... ima dumbass) and then practiced golf for a few hours... right now i'm pretty bored and bummed out, especially cuzz my bro wants me to play golf w/ him @ 4:30 (AAAAHHHHHHH!!!!... lol), and i'll prolly watch a movie w/ sum of u tonight... we'll see how that goes, lol... 

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Oh yeah!  I order this awesome tv lcd screen... u can come over anytime u want and watch sum movies and hang out... this goes to anyone, all u have to do is call me, so CALL ME!... lol... i'll be sure to have plenty of supplies for average movie-goer... call! 

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey there!  Well right now, i'm just chilling, doing nothing... lol... I saw Spiderman 2 last night... it was pretty cool.  I haven't kept a blog lately cuzz i've been pretty busy, but all i've been doing is playing tennis and golf...  I played in this cheezy little tournament @ twin creeks.  I gave my best half-assed attempt!... lol, and took and awesome 2nd place! yay!!! After that i played sum tennis @ hartnell (against the wall!!!... lol...).  I seriously need a partner, lol... but i sorta fucked my chances w/ meryl when i called @ 11 pm and woke her up!... lol... i kno, dumbass... yeah, i haven't talked to her since... i wanna call her up just to apologize, but we'll see... u'll be the first to kno!... lol...  Ok.. now onto today... well today i woke up @ 10:45, lol (cuzz i slept naked, i always wake up late when i sleep naked... hehe)... i had sum waffles and took a shower... then i found out i had to play sum golf, so me, my dad, and bro played sum golf down in pacific grove... 'course i whooped on 'em and make like 50 bucks off of my dad, i would be making more but my bro can't gamble... anyways i had sum dinner, watched jeopardy, then did sum laundry and cleaned my messy-ass room!... lol... i got sum new izod shirts and ima exchange my lacoste jacket...  Well tomorrow ima go to santa clara for a golf lesson from my coach, terry myers (http://www.terrymyers.com), then get a tennis racket, and got to the la coste store and but sum shirts and exhange my jacket for a white one, and i'm also gonna get sum warm up tennis pants there, they look soo awesome!...  This sunday i'm leaving for a golf trip to Brawley sumwhere in california... lol... it's  a PAL tourny, and we might actually win it this year!... i really hope soo, that'd be soo tight... i'm also signed up for the international junior golf tour (http://ijgt.com)... and all the tournaments are in santa barbara, san diego, sacramento, and all over America!... yay!... lol, and they during school!... if i practice really hard and dedicate myself, i might get really really good, so cross ur fingers!!!... 

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Whew!!!... long day... lol  Lemme see, I woke up early and putted, and then i went w/ my dad, my gramps, and my mom to santa clara so i could get a golf lesson from my coach... It went pretty well, but changing ur swing is soo freaking hard.  Anyways, after that we went home and i dropped my dad off @ Chamisal, and played sum tennis w/ nick (anable)... lol, i ended up being late to pick my dad up, but he was cool, so then i dropped him off @ home, and i went to twin creeks to practice sum more putting!... lol... now i'm home, just chilling, 'bout to take a shower, then ima eat sum salmon, and be online... 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Need sum motivation?  I read of a man who stood to speak at the funeral of a friend. He referred to the dates on her tombstone from the beginning... to the end. He noted that the first came the date of her birth and spoke of the second with tears, but he said that what mattered most of all was dash between those years. For that dash represents all the time that she spent alive on earth, and now only those who loved her know what that little line is worth.  Do think about this long and hard, are there things you'd like to change? For you never know how much time is left, you could be at "dash mid-range." If we could just slow down enough to consider what's true and what's real, and always try to understand the way other people feel. And... be less quick to anger, and show appreciation more and love the people in our lives like we've never lover before.  If we treat each other with respect and more often wear a smile, Remembering that this special dash might only last a while. So, when your eulogy is being read with your life's actions to rehash... Would you be pleased with the things they said about how you spent your dash? For it matters not, how much we own; the car, the house, the cash. What matters is how we live and love and how we spend our dash. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ahhh... yesterday morning my computer finally gave up and auto turned off cuzz i left it on for like 7 days straight... lol, and i was too lazy to turn it back on through bios, cuzz that's what i have to do if my computer cold-boots itself, so yeah... if u understand what i just wrote there, u have problems... lol  Well yesterday i played golf w/ Nick Anable and Uchikado, Uchi whooped me, and i whooped nick... lol... nick kept on going on 'bout how we're gonna get uchi piss drunk @ tha PAL (POLICE activities league... lol) trip... so yeah, that sounds cool, i just wanna see sumthing funny... lol... well contrary to what nick says, he did NOT kill me in tennis, he did however beat the shit outa me, but i put a fight... and i've only been playing for 2 weeks!!!... anyways, he said i was pretty good for having been playing for only 2 weeks, so that's chill...  Last night i went to a party in a san jose, it was ok... a lot of young'ens and overachievers (kids who drink twice the amount they can hold down... lol)... well i didn't drink, lol... that's a record!  1 party and a bonfire and sober!... lol... i didn't really wanna get drunk around anyone i didn't kno, so yeah... well i went to my granma's house @ like 1:30 am and went to sleep @ 2:00...  I had a tee time w/ my cuzz @ this new golf course in san jose called "The Ranch."  The tee time was @ 6:45 AM, and he was gonna pick me up @ 5:30!!!!  I woke up @ 4:30 w/ only 2 solid hours of sleep so i could get ripped a new one by the hardest course west of the mississippi... If you thought i was tired b4 that, imagine afterwords!!! i had to go to my cuzzin's kid's b-day party (SUCH A BRAT!!!), and i just messed 'round over there and did nothing much... i slept all the way home... begged my mom to drive... lol... i love her!...  Alright... this has been another adventure of Topher RAnd... It's 6:45, but ima hit the sack... haha... i still might be up later... bye.. 

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today i woke up and ran for 'bout 30 min, and then i watched the british open, hamilton wond... After that i went and played golf, i didn't do so well, i shot a 77.... After that i went w/ my bro to get sum starbucks, and then we went to another golf course and hit sum balls and we played in a putting contest and i won all 3 contests.... yay... lol...    I'm really bored right now, and my bro wants me to go to his narcotics anonymous meeting (he used to be addicted to like everyone, marijuana, gambling, etc.), so if u ever wanna talk 'bout sumthing, i'm here... but yeah, after that he wants to watch "I, Robot," and since i'm pretty bored today, i think i'll go...   

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Sorry i haven't been on lately!....    Well i was @ a golf tournament in Brawley, CA. It's way down south, like 15 min for Mexico.  I watched Anchor Man there, it was funny as hell, but really stupid, lol... well i ended up taking 2nd in the tourny and i watched a lotta dvd's on the way home, so if i ended up quoting one, don't mind it...    I saw Spiderman 2 twice, cuzz 2 seperate groups of friends wanted to see it... lol... It's pretty good, i ended up getting the game for x-box, even though i hardly ever play video games anymore... lol....    All i've been up to is playing golf, tennis, ditching football, playing pool, and trying to fish... lol... and i have also been very busy werking and helping (community service hours, can i hit 500?)....    Yeah, there was this party last night right across the street... I really felt like going, but i was a little depressed and tired, so i just stayed home...    I ran for 'bout 30 min this morning, so i'm a little tired, and i'm watching the British Open.... After that my bro is making me play golf w/ him, but after that i'm free, but i don't kno if i'm in the social mood, so yeah....   

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey!....    Wow... lol... sorry i haven't left a blog in a while.... i'm really really sorry, i've just been really busy... w/ u kno, golf, tennis, football, fishing, werk, interning, community service, reading, the phone.... maybe i should squeeze in a little space for a girlfriend... haha, no chance!    seriously, even though it's sorta old news (like 2 weeks), i'm not gonna ask anyone out on a date 'till after college (but that doesn't mean they can't ask em... lol...) i just don't wanna stress myself out anymore than i have to...    Well let's see... today:  I went to tha doctor to get a blood test (ewww!... needles!).... i went home and took a quick shower, but i had to go for a golf lesson in santa clara w/ terry myers... he's soo awesome!... and then after that, i chilled @ my granma's house... I then played tennis w/ my little cuzzin cuzz i had no one to play w/ (awww... lol), but then i found out my older cuzzin was there so i played w/ him, and i got my ass beat... lol... he's pretty damn good... so after that i helped my other cuzzin (none are bros or sisses, there cuzzins to eachother... lol).... so then i drove my mom and one of my aunts around san jose... and then i went to dinner w/ a bunch a people and everyone was a blur from there... lol... now i'm home... so yeah... yay! home!   

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   That's what i've been feeling like everytime i call my friend (i thought to be my bestfriend), and she is way too busy to have a conversation with me. She says she's not busy and can talk, but the conversation she always seems to be interested in is the one that doesn't involve me. It's ok, i guess, i'm not that important to anyone really... lol... But it still depresses the hell outa me when it seems like my bestfriend doesn't wanna talk to me anymore. What can i do though? If i tell her, all we'll do is fight, and i hate fighting... I guess i'm fucked on this one, all i can do is lose her...    Last night i told my parents that i was going over to anthony's house to watch a movie, but then we just played poker. While we were playing, my bro's friend called and i talked to him and told him what's up. When i get home, i find out that the guy i was talking to called my bro and told him we were playing poker, and my bro told my parents, and i got in trouble.    Today i played in a golf tournament and placed second.... i did really horrible on one of the holes, and if i did decent on it, i would have tied, but oh well... i also had the biggest headache today, and i told my friend off on the course, basically cursed him out, and i feel bad for doing that, cuzz he didn't do anything wrong...    Gosh!... can anything else in my life go wrong?!... Let's see... oh yeah! one of my dad's employees is taking my spots for werking, saying that i took her spots and she's getting me in trouble... So now, i don't even have enough money for the trip to hawaii that i wanted to relax and get away from all this shit for, so now ima get even more bummed out in hawaii...     i love my life!  

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   How fucking wrong i was!    I've been trying to call the same friend who didn't have time to talk anymore, and now she won't even pick up when i call.... yes!... i'm loving it!... I didn't kno i could feel any worse than i already did... well now i don't think i can feel any worse, but wait, there will prolly be sum new update to how bad things are doing... don't worry...   

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm in hawaii until the 6th, so i'll be talking to most of u then, but i'll still keep in touch with a select few... lol... u better have sum fun while i'm gone, cuzz i don't think i'll be having much fun... lol... my friends said they'd loan me a little... yay!... lol... i'll talk to y'all later... love u!... bye  

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well i guess i'm feeling a little bit better, but i don't wanna be sad anymore... I also don't wanna have other people worry 'bout me... I don't live on the streets, i'm not dying of anything, why shouldn't i be happy!?... why shouldn't you be happy?... so what ima do is I will smile towards every person i meet, and see their reaction. I've noticed they smile and soon, everyone around me will be smiling...and hopefully their smiles will make others smile too... i love it, making people happy... It makes me happy...  I dunno what's really going on,  but i kno i'm happy.... so be happy too!...  

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well i just got back from a hawaii a coupla days ago, and i haven't unpacked yet!... Well i can't really talk 'bout all that happened, so i'll just tell everyone in the next blog... I am really glad to be back, i love sleeping in my bed... so soft... hehe... Well i've been werking for tha last 2 nights, so if you've been having trouble contacting me, i sawwy....  i don't really know what's going on anymore, but i truly don't care... lol... everyone is just soo confusing to me, but hey, but it's prolly just me, i'm usually responsible anyways, haha... Well i dunno, @ first i was like, ok, i'm not gonna ask a girl till after college, but lately, i dunno if i ever wanna ask one of 'em out again, haha... if ur reading this, i don't mean any harm by it, i mean all u gurlz are cool, it's just that ur estrogenical side is killing me!... lol...  i dunno, i just been really tired lately... my mom is gonna take me to the doc tomorrow to see what's up... i hope nothing's wrong w/ me... talk to y'all later... buhbye  

						
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The first day i spent there, i stayed on the beach the whole day... i had the fattest sunburn ever!!!  In the first 3 days we ate @ this place called the cheesecake factory atleast 5 times... lol... on the second night, me and my dad were gonna play sum tennis, so we walked to these tennis courts that turned out to be a few miles away, and right when we got there, it started to rain!...  On the third day, we played golf...... and right when we were 'bout to tee off, it rained... lol... we played anyways......  On the fourth day we shopped and did stuff like that.... i would go w/ my bro into high-end shops like gucci, prada, and luois vuitton, and we would do stupid things in there.... we basically did that everyday... my bro went into this porn shop and was gonna buy the paris hilton video, but didn't cuzz it was $50, and my mom didn't believe him, so she went in and asked too... haha  On the fifth day, we were gonna play golf, but everyone didn't want to, so we didn't!... we, instead went shopping, and i got a lotta stuff, like this $100 nike shirt, and a bunch'a hats, and sum shit from hooters.... We also went on this dinner cruise that turned out to be better than i thought.... me and my dad finally got to play tennis, but we had to scuigee the stupid wet courts, and we only got to play for like 30 min, cuzz it rained again...  On the sixth day, we went parasailing, and i got castrated, i still haven't found those exposing pictures........... That night we went on this luau and i met this really cool chick, and the luau was pretty good too... haha... and i bought this scented candle there that looks pretty sick and i'm decorating my room in a hawaiian motiff because of it....  On the seventh day we played golf, and went to movies.... i met the actor who played Merry in the Lord of the Rings!!!!.... i'll tell u 'bout the little adventure surrounding that if u ask... we also went to Dave and Busters and ate @ this nice italian place...  On the eight day, everyone went there own ways, i just walked 'round everywhere by myself and met a coupla peeps (not as cool as sydney though... haha...) and then i just chilled that night, laying down in lounge chair for a few hours, staring @ stars, releasing as much estrogen as possible, but i liked it.... my parents went to check out sum condo/hotel thingies, and i think we're gonna have 2 vacation type condos there, so yay!... haha  On the nineth day, we played sum more golf (ahhh!!!!) and packed our stuff (awwww... i didn't wanna leave, especially after that last beautiful night....)  

						
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   7:oo am- woke up 9:00 am- got outa bed 9:07 am- ate sum cheerios and watched a movie 11:03 pm- took a shower 11:57 pm- went to practice golf @ twin creeks 1:29 pm- went to starbucks (strawberries 'n cream) and read 2:14 pm- went to practice sum more golf @ salinas fairways 3:01 pm- came home and read sum more 3:27 pm- played tennis w/ Anthony 4:58 pm- came home and took a shower 5:46 pm- road w/ my bro in his new car 5:51 pm- ate sum dinner 6:51 pm- did sum dishes 7:15 pm- bored so watched a little jeopardy (dork!)  

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't really wanna talk to anyone, well i do, but it's so frustrating and even more depressing when i try to call her... I love her so much (as a friend), but it seems like now, she could care less 'bout me... I don't really know what to do or feel, but i talked to her last night, and told her how frustrating it was for me to call so many times, and even when she does answer, she always seems too busy to talk to me... All she did was start answering back and trying to make herself right and me wrong, i guess she won those, cuzz i made me too sad to keep on arguing... I guess i had to tell her that i wasn't going to try anymore, i didn't wanna get cursed out by her bro every other time i called, and i didn't wanna get told goodbye 5 minutes into the conversation... She just got more mad and i dunno what really happened after that, cuzz i don't really remember, i sort of blacked out... lol... yeah... but i remember her friend saying telling me that she fell asleep, while i was crying!... I dunno what's wrong w/ me, cuzz if it were anyone else, i would've stopped talking to that person who treated me like this a long time ago....  I spent an extra hour in the shower today... twice... 

						
</post>


</Blog>