<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night I'm watching an older Michael Moore movie, The Big One. My favorite scene is where he brings the welfare mothers to the capitol somewhere (I forget) and one of them says "I'm a full time student and I have four kids." Uh....no. You do not get to be a FULL TIME STUDENT if you have four kids. You do not get to be on welfare and do nothing but go to school. First of all, a full time student attends class 12, maybe 15 hours a week. Second, kids didn't just happen to you, lady. Nobody catches a bad case of offspring. You lost your option to be a full time student. Get to work.
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so fucking SICK of this debate over gay marriage. There should be no debate. I fucking hate people that won't just see things my way. It really is the most annoying thing in the world. I will dispense of this debate in two quick steps.  First, the MORAL question. I refuse to simply dismiss this, since I do consider myself a fairly moral person, at least I try my best to adhere to a standard of morals that was set forth in the Bible. In this sense I do consider myself a Christian. You're probably saying, but Charlie, then how can you be FOR gay marriage. Well, I'll explain it to you. FIRSTLY, the Biblical objection isn't clear enough to make me really believe it's a sin. SECONDLY, assuming even that it was a sin, it certainly isn't any worse than any other sins. Let's take adultery for example. Now, that's one of the TOP TEN on God's Big List of No-Nos. But I don't see anybody bashing people that cheat on their wives. I don't see anybody suggesting that an adulterer not be allowed to remarry. Let's say a guy cheats on his wife and wishes to divorce his wife and marry the woman he cheated with. This is a sin. It's a HUGE sin. It's a TOP TEN SIN. Should we make a constitutional ammendment to keep him from doing so? If you think we should have one against gay marriage, you should also be for this. But actually you shouldn't be against either becuase you should mind your own fucking business and not worry about the sins of others. JUDGE NOT, MOTHERFUCKERS!  Second, the constitutionality of gay marriage. I cannot FATHOM that there are people that actually want to put this silly bullshit on our CONSTITUTION. Our beautiful sacred document that has sustained our country for over 200 years. Let me tell you something about the Constitution and the Bill of Rights. Thomas Jefferson didn't even want to have a Bill of Rights because our rights, like it says in the preamble of the Declaration of Independence, men are  endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable rights, that among these are life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness . In other words... WE DON'T NEED YOUR PERMISSION, OH BIG GOVERNMENT, TO DO ANYTHING. As long as we do not infringe on the (unalienable, endowed by creator) rights of others, we have all rights. They belong to us. The rights include, but are not limited to, everything in the first eight ammendments in the Bill of Rights. The 9th Amendment even reserves all rights not specifically and literally spelled out to the PEOPLE.  Along that same line, let's just talk about goverment in general for a moment. It is NOT the national government's JOB to legislate something like this. It is the reason we have a Supreme Court. A marriage, in the eyes of the law, is a legal binding document which entitles the parties to special tax laws.   And don't give me this shit about "marriage is between a man and a woman and is sacred." WRONG. Marriage isn't sacred. If you really do believe that, then get married and never get divorced. If you feel the need to force your beliefs on everybody else, then why not make a law that makes divorce illegal? Doesn't that destory the sacredness of marriage? Seems like getting divorced is worse than two people who both have the same anatomy loving each other.  Furthermore, the reason for marriage and relationship in general is NOT to pro-create. We are not animals, we are an advanced species. We have birth control. We do not fuck for the purpose of having children. We fuck for pleasure.  In conclusion, nobody's rights are getting infringed on when Adam and Steve get married, so you have no right to stop them. Not you, not the state goverment, not the national government. If they someday have to answer to their creator, then that's between them and their creator, just like we will ALL have to answer for our sins.  -Charlie
    
</post>


</Blog>