<Blog>

<date>02,agosto,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   here i am. I just wanna explain today my situation right now. I think that this summer may be the borest summer that i have ever had. I´d like to flyin' away from Spain to.........Los Angeles or Miami where i can speak "my english" and make it better (but i don´t really mind the place while it was away from Spain). Don´t be afraid! I love Spain but i am all the year here and i like change my way, u no... So, the problem is that i have no money and i can´t spend the holidays that i was thinkin' in. By the way, here in Spain i can spend a gr8 summer but at north(where i live) the sun doesn´t appear for Ages!!!!! (Almost it seems......) and i can´t go to the beach and do sun bathin' :( sniff sniff  As u see, this could be the borest summer holiday i have ever had.........But i must wait until September to check if it was. So, wot do u think about this?? Send me ur comments PD: Scuse my english........ ;D  

						
</post>

<date>02,agosto,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   howdy! how r u? Welcome to my blog, here i´ll write my problems and my thoughts everyday (almost i´ll try it.....)and ,definelty, all that i´ll be able to think and express..... I know that this is not as good as it should but i´ll try to make it better recently. So, i just wanna tell u that u can visit my blog if u r interested in me.Bye then! 

						
</post>

<date>02,agosto,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hola! Q tl? Bienvenido a mi blog, aki escribiré en los próximos días mis movidas, rollos, os presentaré a mis amigos, a mis amigas tb eeeeee jejeje y en definitiva todo akello q se me ocurra.....  Se q keda un poko soso esto asi de primeras xo weno non t preocupare q poko a poko lo ire mejorando (o al menos lo intentaré.......) 

						
</post>

<date>02,agosto,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hiya mates!!! this afternoom was so crazy, u´ll see.We went to the beach like all this days be4, at eight o´clock we took the train to went back to my village and wots went on?¿¿?? My mates and me decided don´t get out the train at the same train stop like allways and we decided get out the train at the capital train stop. But a train stop left, we had to get out coz the revisor (the man who check the tickets) was comin' !!!!!! So, we thougth that we must take a bus to get the capital but we didn´t know where!! lol  Finally we found one and took the bus right to the capital. There we met other classmates and we were havin' fun, talkin' and....why not sayin'?? lookin' for some gr8 girls.... :D Finally we took other bus to get our village and come home again (save and alive!!!! lolz)  Well, wot do u think about this afternoom??? Add ur comments. Thnx 

						
</post>

<date>02,agosto,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Howdy!!!!! Fortunatly, today the sun has appeared and Wot have i done???.....I have gone to the beach and i have spent there all the afternoom with my friends (We have really enjoy ourselves). I hope tomorrow will be the same; I mean, sun, beach, hot,sun bathin', enjoyment......... the sea was dangerous (red flag) but we can´t wait until other day for swim a bit,jump waves and all these kind of things that it used to do in the sea. Well, i hope u have  spent a gr8 afternoom too. Y don´t u tell me wot about u??? Add ur comments. Thnx 

						
</post>


</Blog>