<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So, I just got back from work, which went by verrrry verrrrrrry slowly today. Like UBER slow. I really despise the word uber, by the way. But anyway, I got mean guy today. Mean guy is the old man who is soooo picky. I went to give him his blizzard and he said he wanted me to "level it" and put it in a bag with a spoon and one napkin. Ok leveling ice cream, sure.  ONE  napkin, sure. Then I count back his change to him and he takes it from me, counts it again and says "you're welcome" and left. It was MEAN. Then I got this other old man who smelled and had like a lion mane coming out of his chest, it actually curled over his shirt. But the day was pretty good overall.     I spent about fifteen minutes hoping Lance would come and visit me, then I realized...I'm sweaty, wearing a DQ visor and I'm covered in ice cream and toppings, no I can't say I wanted anyone I know to see me like that.     So I got the schedule for next week and I'm bummed cause I'm not working during the Fourth of July parade, which would have been the only holiday activies I'd of seen. I'm working the night shift that day though. I have the night shift three times next week, which is cool because it goes by really fast.      Moving on...  I have this friend who over uses semi-colons. Here is an example. I like this kid; but he doesn't like me; he's already; got; a;;;;;;;...Drives me up a wall. But I think that I over use... which I know the name of but I can't quite recall. I'm gonna say it starts with an a. Maybe Ap... something. I don't know it's not clicking. All I can think about is Lance, which is bad because I know that our plans rarely work out, which makes me sad, and I know I like him and maybe(hopefully), He likes me too, and maybe like can become something bigger and maybe I can stop day dreaming... Speaking of Dreaming I had the oddest dream last night. And I'm going to tell you all about it. This person, I don't know whether they were a girl or boy, but this person, came up to me and he was wearing a cape. And he was talking, but I couldn't hear him...but I still understood. So what he somehow communicated to me was that we had to fly somewhere. I didn't question the flying, I could just suddenly could do it, and in this dream flying was swimming, but in the sky. So we flew to this huge building. It looked like a Grecian inspired temple, but it was circular and there were gold guilded rungs on a few of the colums. So We both flew into this huge building and there were sparkly things all interconnected by a huge sparkling ruby red string hanging from the very top of the building, which was probably twenty or thirty feet high. I noticed when I looked down while I was flying in one spot near the sparkling objects that there were five or six circles at the bottom of the temple. All of them had a symbol on it and for some reason I understood what they meant, like they were words. So I'm up at the top of this building still, and the man/girl/ person starts giving me directions. And I know whatever it is I was doing was important, I don't know what in specific it was going to, or will lead to, but I knew there was some kind of save-the-world purpose connected. So this person was telling me to grab with my teeth one of the shining objects. They looked as though they were covered in glitter, and they were all odd things like masks and keys and hands...each catergory of items was monotonously one color, I remeber the masks specifically were purple, but everything else is a little blurry. So continuing. I grabbed a mask in my teeth, then swung my foot up to grab something else, it was blue. And each of my hands were on the same object. Soon I was intertwined with all of the sparkling objects. And the person told me to say something, like an incantation maybe, and I said it and all of the objects started to glow. Suddenly I was down on one of the circles at the bottom of the temple. I knew it was the one that said either life or love. A fire lit in a great big pit in the very center of the temple, it was huge, at least twenty feet around and ten feet high. So I stood and I whispered something, from a book I was suddenly holding in my hand, and I was crying a little. Then directly across from me, a circle with either hate or death written on it lowered and this great big black figure rose out of it. I wasn't scared of it but I was angry, really angry with it. And I could see it through the fire and then the dream just ended.  Which bummed me out, it was a cool dream! I'm hoping it will pick up tonight. If anyone is good at dream interpretation out there, feel free to tell me what that means. Well I'm going to go hop in the pool, alone because no one loves me enough to join me.  Ta Ta For Now, The famous words of Tigger  Kayle
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              You're    the United Nations!      Most people think you're ineffective, but you are trying to    completely save the world from itself, so there's always going to be a long    way to go. &nbsp;You're always the one trying to get friends to talk to each    other, enemies to talk to each other, anyone who can to just talk instead of    beating each other about the head and torso. &nbsp;Sometimes it works and sometimes    it doesn't, and you get very schizophrenic as a result. &nbsp;But your heart    is in the right place, and sometimes also in New York.   face="Times New Roman">Take the  urlLink Country  Quiz  at the  urlLink Blue Pyramid     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd really like to get all this nostagia out, but last night didn't help very much. I called Lance after talking to him online, to make plans to see each other. Well, we dwelled on the past, seeing as I haven't seen him in a year, about us dating in the eigth grade, and about how our goodbye ended up unlocking feelings neither of us were ready for. It is really quite sad because we've liked each other a year, but haven't had the chance to act on it. I want to, I don't know why, but I really want to just have one more chance...things were cut off so short! But anyways... I talked to him until midnight last night and we reminessed and just talked for a very long time. I usually can't hold a conversation that long, but it was easy to talk to him and even though people say things to me, I know what he is really like and I don't take any heed to what I hear. I wish my friends knew him, understood how I feel. And oh good, I just wrote half a blog with the intelligence of an eight grade girl...moving on. I have to go to work today at Dairy Queen, land of soft serve and fat people who order massive icecreams. I don't mind it though, I enjoy working there. But since father dearest is off at an onsite I have to walk there today, not fun. I thought about doing some homework today, but no. Too much homework, no patience. I really ought to start my next essay, even though my first one isn't very good, and I'm very dissapointed in myself for the simple fact that I'm inept at creative writing. I have to question what I'm doing in AP classes, I don't feel as intelligent as everyone else, I feel a little underqualified but I suppose I'll just have to make myself blend.  Well, this whole post, again like the last, was pretty pointless but I really had to spit it all out, so I don't explode, like a spontaneous conbustion type of deal.  Auvoir mon amies! A demain,  Kayle
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I'm really not sure why, but I've been very nostalgic lately. Obsessively so. I want to reminess about the past and just not progress or change at all. Sit in my nice comfy now and only think on the past. I spent a whole day off thinking about things that really don't matter, like hmm I wonder where that ex boyfriend is and oh that time, it was fun. I have a stack of homework that sits over my laptop and is looking down on me, taunting me, shunning me for neglecting to touch it, and reminding me of the fact that I still have books to buy for AP classes.     Not  that I'm going to go out there and buy them, or even order a used copy on amazon... No, instead I'll continue putting it off, waking up at eleven, swimming and them changing into my work clothes until one o'clock comes around, then I'll just get home from work, and continue to lounge or maybe go to sleep or I could read Anna Karenina. And who on earth reads eighteent century literature by the man that wrote War and Peace...that'd be me, I have no life.  I'm not even going to fireworks on fourth of July, not that I'm complaining, because I really, truly hate fireworks. I don't see the fascination with them. People often look at me with that "what, what was that ohhh pretty colors what?" No, no I do not take joy in balls of colored fire flying down aided by beach wind. I'd rather do what I am best at and sit on my ass, order some chinese or something and watch the pretty New York ones on T.V.  T.V. isn't very interesting either, except for Will and Grace, ooohhh I love Will and Grace. Who wouldn't enjoy gay men who frolic about the set with rich bitches and wonderfully skinny fashion designers!? It is entertaining. Ohh and HSN, the Home Shopping Network. It's as if they took every piece of useless and overpriced junk and put it on T.V. with a bunch of women who look like giraffes with sparkly hands and long manicured fingers.  Well, you've just read possibly the most unproductive, horrid, boring and pointless Blog EVER. But, I promise I'll have one that has some meaning next time. Really, I promise.  Write soon...
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who don't know, I'm going to be a cat lady. I'm going to live up on a hill with all my cats and eat myself into a heart attack, and be alone forever. Sad isn't it? Not really, just inevitable. But that's ok. Until whatever controls my emotional state decides to calm down, open back up, and forget the past, I can't handle a relationship, I can't even like anyone because once I finally find myself attracted, they run off with some dumbass, bimbo, blonde memeber of one of those fucking rediculous groups of idiots, that depend on having four or more of them all at the same time together, no, James, I am not referring to you nor your girl pack, although I don't doubt that they've got plenty of space in their minds. Anyone who can't depend on themselves and has to travel with twenty airheads should throw themselves off a cliff. Honestly, I kind of hate girls. I can't think of very many that I get along with. My gay guy friends are great. They are like girls without the stupidity, and twice as much common sense. Yes, I'm a girl. No I don't travel in packs. I have friends who are girls, we all get together most of the time with boys as well, and have fun. We don't run around in a pack screeching like god damn monkeys. Thank you god for Chris and Rob and Jessie, these kids are just better then the dumbasses I see everyday.  ARRRGH.  But anyway. I attempted to date. But, thanks to my last few boyfriends, my emotional state and my lack of free time, I knew it wouldn't work. I hate it because I know it would help but I can't make it work. And I feel so bad too, because there is nothing I can do to make it better.  I hate my siblings.  You can have them. For the low low price of lack of privacy, sanity and vocal usage. You can just come and pick them up. Please.&nbsp;  I'm done. "Et Toi, Brute?" "You too, Brutus?" -Caesar.  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Odd, odd things happen sometimes when you are just whining to people about things. Oddly, I was whining to James and then suddenly, the things came. Ok. Hi, why are you here, how did you know, is God watching me and thinking, lets give her a little shock. It'll be fun. Ironic.  But moving on. I'm slacking on homework because I know that I will have the time in P.I. my favorite place in the world.  Well  that was a painstakingly short, unintersting blog.   Life keeps bringing me back to you. Oh. Life keeps bringing me home. It don't matter what I'm gonna do oh It's got a mind of it's own. Life keeps bringing me back to you.  Kayle  PS ten points if you know what show it's from.  
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so wiped out today. I'm just gonna sleep until forever. I don't really have anything interesting to say, or anything to rant about. So, whatever. I'll post real big tommorow.  Sianara,  Kayle
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so wiped out today. I'm just gonna sleep until forever. I don't really have anything interesting to say, or anything to rant about. So, whatever. I'll post real big tommorow.  Sianara,  Kayle
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so wiped out today. I'm just gonna sleep until forever. I don't really have anything interesting to say, or anything to rant about. So, whatever. I'll post real big tommorow.  Sianara,  Kayle
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so wiped out today. I'm just gonna sleep until forever. I don't really have anything interesting to say, or anything to rant about. So, whatever. I'll post real big tommorow.  Sianara,  Kayle
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bore is the word that describes my day and most likely my night. I'm home on the fourth of July. Yeah, I'm real cool. Well I haven't really got much to share with you all, I'm too tired.  We Shall Meet Again Kayle
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I get really annoyed with America, about once a month I'd say. This is one of those days. For AP (advanced placement) History, I have to read a book called A People's History of the United States, 1942-Present. It's very much like Lies My Teacher Told Me, which I read for Honors History last summer, but it seems to just spark in me list upon list of things that I despise about America. I, being of Indian Ancestry, The Mica Mac tribe from upper Maine, Canada-ish to be exact, take offense in the means we use to teach children today about Columbus. I've full intent on becoming a teacher, and if it were up to me I'd tell the little Kidnegarteners the real story.  It'd go like this (Me, looking teacher-ish, holding up a book speaking to a room of kidnegarteners in a circle) "Today we're going to learn about Christopher Columbus!" "Yay!" say the kids. "Can anyone tell me anything about Columbus?" "He's my hero!!!" A little boy cries out.  "No, no Johnny. You can decide that after I read you the book." I begin to read. "Once upon a time there was a man named Christopher Columbus, " "Yay" the kids call out again.  "and he went to the king and queen of spain for three ships. The Nina the Pinta and the Santa Maria. He promised the king and queen he would bring back gold and spices. He thought he was going to Asia." I turn the page to a picture of Indians coming to the shore. "But instead, he stumbled upon Haiti and the Arawak tribe. He noticed they had gold in their ears, so he left 39 men with them to turn the Arawaks into slave laborors and to find the gold." The children look up with confused faces. "Then his men killed them!" Gasps fill the room. "Columbus then goes to a place called Cuba. There he makes a rule that everyone over fourteen must collect a certain amount of gold by the end of the month. When they get that gold, they have to go and get a copper token put around their neck to show they got it." I turn the page to a picture with Natives looking up at the sky, their hands spurting blood." But, if they didn't have one, CHOP! The spainiards cut their hands off and let them bleed to death."  Some of the children look like they are going to cry. "That's not all," I turn the page to a picture of chained Indians. "they took many of the Indians as slaves..." I go to the next page showing an image of and Indian woman drowning her infant. "They ran to try to save their lives too. Because the Spainairds thought that killing the Indians was no big deal. Women killed their babies to save them from Columbus and his crew. And then we got America, by killing and inslaving all the Indians. The End." I turn to a page with "The End" spelt out in bloodied, mangled Indian bodies with a border of chained Indians. The children look up at me scared.   And that's how it would go. Ok maybe you shouldn't tell it to Kidnegarten, but I think Fourth grade would be a good time. I just hate that these kids think that America is some kind of Hero country when we just aren't. I mean look at Hiroshima, that wasn't so long ago. Look at the War on Iraq! We don't have anything justifying our right to be in that country at all. It is not our buisiness. Yes, it is sad, but that is what the UN is for. America is not some kind of world cop, but our minds are so polluted that children think we are good people. And I don't hate America, I dislike a lot of our policies and our morale is about as good as a baby-killing crack whore's, but we have things like Krispy Kreme doughnuts and huge malls to our name. But really, I just wish that we'd get a decent president for once. I liked Bill Clinton, he was a normal guy. I wish he would come back! Well now on to Kayle buisiness... I met this guy in yahoo grafiti. We talked for all of ten minutes. I know NOTHING about him. He wants me to come visit him in Vermont. Hmmm lets all take a minute and think of some posibilities of who this guy is. (1) Child Molester. (2) Very desperate ugly person. Or on an off chance (3) Guy who for some reason had an immediate attraction to me, is normal, and just wants to get to know me.  HA HA HA I don't like meeting people online, you can never know whether to trust the situation or not. It's frusterating. Well I'm off to do things like homework, because I have no life.  Visit me at Dairy Queen 5-9 unless you are an ex bf just coming to bug me... (James) Who will yell through my window go faster Kayle, faster faster faster. That sounded dirty. Oh well.   I love you, you love me, we're a happy family, with a great big hug and a kiss from me to you, wont you say you love me to.  Goodbye song from Barney.   Kayle
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woo. Finally took a deep breath. I was a little upset last night, especially after being yelled at, but I've mananged to calm down a lot. I had to work today, it was fine. I just had one jerky customer who threw a fit because his ice cream was "too soft". And we all know   I   have control of that...But moving on. Today was pretty normal, pretty boring. Nothing exciting. Oh That dream, much to my dismay, did not continue. I was trying to make up endings but it just didn't work. So, I suppose I'll just have to sleep until it pops up, gives me a bit of a suprise, you know?  My dog is snoring by my side right now, and I can't move her, that'd be cruel. What's a girl to do? Oh...I tried calling Lance today, wasn't home.  Dissapointing, but expected.  I ought to make a support group. You know, a "love yourself" type of thing. If you wish to join IM me at Kaymo06 or email me at that same screen name, at yahoo.  Or don't  Well of all my posts this has been the most pointless, and for that matter completely rediculous. But I feel to maintain sanity, I need to pour my day out somewhere, even if it is to a blog, which is rarely read, or for that matter, not taken heed to. Oh well.   And  Tommorow, Tommorow, Tommorow shall come.  Kayle  
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         About three months ago, I woke up late after being up until eleven studying for history, I, as a result, didn't have time to fold the laundry so I left it in the basket for the morning. Well I woke up late and didn't have time. I brought it upstairs to fold instead of eating breakfast and my father sees me and starts ripping things out of the basket telling me I was selfish and that the clothes were wrinkled. Rather then argue, I burst into tears. Not only did I cry but bawled, and was unable to stop until eight thirty. Well into my NWEA testing. So I had a rather embarrasing visit with my guidance counsellor after resolving that Sanford was not going to see me break down. She, as a result,  wrote down in her little book that I "bent" under pressure and that I was fragile. I am neither of these things, considering, and was a little offended. But I had explained to her the situation. That it broke my heart to hear my dad call me selfish after all I had done for him.     There  is  a point to all this.   So my dad spoke nothing of it that afternoon and acted as if nothing had happened. I hate that about my family. No apologizing. Just pretend. No, I do not think that is acceptable. But, the point. My Dad and Stepmom have just won the all time achievement award in being selfish, horrid people. It began as little, tedious things but has been balooning. They came back from Bermuda and started to have "alone" time. Alone time was in translation going out for an hour for "coffee" leaving me to babysit much to my dismay for I have better things to do then run up and down the stairs for a paranoid eight year old spoiled brat. That wasn't such a big deal, but it did bother me. Then they started buying things for themselves telling us when we asked for things that "they didn't have the money." These purchases were elaborate, things like a new Lexus and flying lessons and a hot tub...ok no money, right. Normal people can afford those things. I don't think so. So then we progress to a very, very selfish act. They started smoking again. They knew how proud we were of them, and how much we care about them being healthier. So, about a month ago, Nicholas, my youngest brother catches my stepmother smoking. He, to say the least, was not a happy camper. I was dissapointed. So then my dad starts up. "We'll just be weekend smokers" they say falsely. One night they were "stuck" with me and brought me with them for Thai food. They asked me to go get us a table inside, this was a THURSDAY, they were going to have a ciggarette. I said to them, I'm dissapointed in you both, really very dissapointed. They didn't care, I walked off not paying heed to them saying "don't be mad" Blah Blah Blah. I got us a table. We ate. We went home. Here is the icing on the cake. I get in the car tonight to go home after working when I wasn't scheduled to work, a six to eight thirty shift, which isn't bad at all. So my dad says, you have to go to your moms next weekend. Why, I ask, I have to work all weekend (well I know now I don't have to work sunday), Oh, we're going to Nova Scotia, taking a cruise, they say. Umm Mom is going to be pissed, I say. Oh well he says. I'm not calling her, I say, I don't want to listen to her scream about you dropping me on her, I do a skit of how the conversation would go. He says, well thats tough. I'm getting angry. Why can't I just stay home, I'll walk to work. You're only fifteen he says. I'm turning sixteen in a few weeks I say. That's too bad, he says. I feel myself starting to turn red with anger. Fine. I say. Selfish, horrible people. I say in my head. So I call mom. Mom screams, I cry. I can't do anything about this, I say. It's out of my hands, it isn't as if I booked them a cruise and said, Hey, you haven't been selfish at all! Your so giving and kind, go on a long weekend! No, no I did not do that. I have full intention upon staying in my house at least friday night. I'm not going to be the bad guy. I'm not the selfish one. I 'm not the one who gives her daughter the brunt of the screaming. I sit and I do homework, then I go to work, then I do homework. Yes I'm just so selfish, trying to get good enough grades for my parents just for them to say oh, thats good. I must be the selfish one, because you know, I babysit, and give my BROTHERS money instead of me getting even a thank you. I work, I try, I do all that I can and I get brushed aside. They actually tell me to my face that they can't wait for me to leave. Well good, because more and more I can't wait to leave a home where I am treated like a blister on a finger, a nussiance and nothing more. They are selfish people and I am NOT happy. Maybe I'm over reacting but, you know what, if your parents did that, would you think they're selfish. SELFISH SELFISH  SELFISH !!!
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jessie is my true love. She is the bestest friend a girl could ever have and I'm happy to have her. She is my rock, my ever-standing bridge, my earth. I love her forever and ever no matter what choices she makes, whether it be in accordance with my opinion or what her heart tells her to do. I love her for her, and I miss her always.  To my Jessie, my best friend forever.  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't lie. I'm completely inept when it comes to lying, and my dad is the best at disabling my lies.  I literally can't lie to him. I never have in recent years since I've matured. So when my dad says no he's a pot head I just turn red and try to argue my intellegence over it. My dad hates him. HATES him. I tell daddy it's not like he's the first, or worse I've ever dated. He doesn't care. My dad will never respect him until he pulls his act together and the worst thing is, I don't trust him to. I think mine is a lost cause and I'm wasting time on a dream that will never happen. I don't know what to do. I miss him and I want to see him but I know when I'm with him I'm loosing the respect of my father and of my stepmother. How long will it be untill dad tells my mom? Then what will I do, try to salvage and maintain through a phone? I don't think so. It's been four days yet I've already got so many obstacles. Help. I need help and I'm so afraid he is going to disregaurd everything I've tried to make him understand. He and I wont last if he does this. I want it to last, I do! I don't know how I can make the situation better for it is out of my control. I can't control another person, can't make them choose, can't do anything. I hate it.  Kayle  This is only the beginning, of the end that is. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm torn. Part of me is being selfish, feeling that though it's been two days I should already be top priority. Part of me is nervous, did I rush, is this real, am I just a last resort? Will this like all the others throw me back onto the floor? But what is selfish about wanting him to be him. Nothing influencing it, wanting my daddy to except him, my daddy the only man in my life who hasn't hurt me yet. Do I really have wounds so deep I will ruin this for myself. But. I do not question that I feel this is right. My heart says it is, I trust it is. When I'm with him it feels right. When I'm not with him it feels right. I miss him a minute after leaving. Am I too attached? I want to have him with me all the time. Am I already obsessed? I just want to be with him. He makes me happy and I hope I make him happy. I'm scared. I don't want to be hurt again, I don't think he'll hurt me but I don't know. I'm not psychic. I don't want to be ashamed of something that makes me feel whole. Why should I? I'm so busy being afraid that others will look down upon me for making a choice to be with someone that is very close to my opposite, that my dad will think me irresponsible for being with someone I've waited long to be with that I force my opinion on him. It's his life I can't control it. I just want him to be him. He's different and he doesn't see it. I see it. It's not the same person I fell for so long ago. It's a cocky, pretentious, rude, pompus, horrid, different person when he does it. Thats what I see. Not the gratuitous, wonderful, warm person he can be. But I can't make him. If I'm going to be with someone I want it to work. Is that so much to ask? Am I being pushy, over-emotional, just plain stupid? What am I doing wrong? I just want this to work so bad, I've waited so long and he is such a good person. For some reason only I see that he is such a wonderful person. My friends think I'm crazy but I'm not. It's my decsion and I think it was a good one. I sound like a tween. It's sad. But I needed to vent. I don't care if you like it, or read it. No one reads this. It's my diary. Just accsessable.  Love, Kayle Rae Morrissette  The only human flaw is looking for human flaws in others.  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't judge.   Mr. Billings was rumored to be awful. He is the best Drivers Ed instructor I've been in the car with. Honest criticism! None of the other ones would give me that. I appreciate it.  Lance called me right after he got out of drivers ed today, it made me happy. He makes me happy.  Kayle  Good tidings to you 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a punctual person. I like on time. I like keeping appointments. Hour by hour mapped to a T. My dad is not punctual. He goes with what may, he does not drive me places on time and is always late picking me up, unless I am with a boy. Then he is ten minutes early. I know this is out of love, but still, it angers me. Today I got ready to go to my dermatology appointment so my perscription could be tweaked or fixed or whatever but no. We were going to be late so I rescheduled. I hate late. I hate rescheduling. I hate it. I have homework I should be doing but I can't for the life of me concentrate on it. Oh And my sarcastic parents decided to make hot dogs and hamburgers to spite me and my decsion of veganism. When I came upstairs I had a banana and luke warm water for dinner. I'm literally starving because no one will bring me to shop for some vegan food I can eat. I've had a few potatoe chips today and thats it. It's one o'clock and I've eaten potatoe chips. And water. I have two apples to last me the week. It will be interesting for sure. I am going to stick with this too. I don't doubt it. But I'll probably die because my parents wont buy me a head of lettuce.  Kayle.  Goodbye. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got a story for you all today. Yesterday I woke up and I was in Heaven. Everything was coming up roses. I go to sleep pretty happy. But I then realize something is horribly wrong. I never have good days that continue. Suddenly I realize that I have been in Hell and Lucy put up a nice visage to trick me. Silly Lucy. I shoulda known you trickster. Ha ha, good day. That was a nice trick! You really got me. Lance, keep a promise. Thats a gosh darn laugh. It's now ten thirty and hour and some time past his so called phone call. I even tried to call with no avail... I'm sure I'll get a nice excuse. Naievity pisses me off.  A lot . I'm doubtful that most of you could fathom how much. People who are naive to things so easily solved just make me want to explode. Tea Kettle. My head pops right the hell off. I mean geez are you that stupid to think that life is a party? It's not. It's a full time job. A job to devote yourself to God and to please him. I'm serious. There are not enough religious people in the world today. Ethics, morals... where did they go? No one cares anymore about how materialistic and evil we've become. When did eating tourtured animals become acceptable? Bearing abnormal amounts of skin? Thinking of yourself before God? What happened to being good? I've got morals and I'm darn proud. I decided after a movie from PETA that affected me very, very deeply to become a vegan. Not a half vegan, not one who drinks milk and eats eggs, a true one. No eggs, unless they are the cage free kind, no milk, nothing with milk including ice cream regaurdless that I work at Dairy Queen, except on occasion. Rare occasion. I am not going to support brutal slaughtering of animals, mistreatment and utterly repulsive lack of respect and brotherhood towards something we share the earth with. I'm done. I am very upset right now on a few different levels, and I just hope that before you talk to me you respect what I have to say and do not abuse or poke fun at it. I do not ask for more.   Kayle    Amen.  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in heaven right now. Not half heaven, not pretend heaven, not heaven on earth. Heaven. 100%, bonified heaven. And it is because of a simple e-mail. For years I've had feelings, and having them returned is heaven. All I can ask now is that I finally get something I don't doubt.  In other news. This may be false hope. Who knows? Will I truly be a cat lady? I hope not. Today work was ok. I don't know. It was only ok. My mind isn't on work, or home, or all the homework I need to do. It's on him. Only him. And I don't fully know why. I just hope that I'm not just hoping for something I can't have Well I've absolutely nothing to say,  nothing I'll divuldge to my pretend readers.   And as she died she looked up at his face and said, thank you. Thank you for being you, and for being mine. Thick and thin, good times and... 
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes I wish God would put me in a fairy tale for a little while. Just a year of fairy tale happiness. With suspence and love and a moral that I'd never learn without it. I watched Spirited Away today and it made me so sad about not being able to live that way. Wouldn't it be nice, amazing adventures and romances and working towards an exciting goal that gives you some kind of wonderful thing. Just a fairy tale, a big fairy tale and just nothing but having this life experience. I want a fairy tale. I guess I could make my life into one couldn't I? Loose weight, overcome obstacles to learn what I really want to be, and have a sucsessfull life with love and I dunno everything. Ooch. That first part, the loosing weight. Ha Ha No. I like myself like this a little. I mean I don't, and it gives me problems, but I don't honestly care. Well, fairytale less and alone again. Kayle And they lived happily ever after. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So. I haven't written in a while, not that anyone cares but hey, this is my blog, so I care. Well, I had the best time ever last night. So much fun. I met Sam's Mike who is officially the best gay man I've ever met. I would sooo take him home if I could. We went to group, and played a game then we to Bickfords and had Coffee and desserts except for Kirsten who had chicken. Our deserts took forever so they took them off the bill, which was awesome because I'm cheap. Then we went to see the village at 10:30. Obviously, we have no minds. The movie would get out at about 12:30, when we have to drive home, in the dark, alone, after a scary movie. I liked it. Me and Mike were screaming like little girls grabbing each others hands while Kirsten tried to grab his shirt and he screamed "don't pull on my shirt" which lightened the moment a little, but still I was scared. So we left and I slept over Sam's and at eight thirty we had to bring me to Drivers Ed. Then I got home, and got my nails filled. They are pretty pink and I love them. Well that's all I have to say. We are having a bbq in a few minutes. Oh yeah and I think the manicurist, not the guy who does my nails but ya know the second hand man has a crush on me. He's cute enough. Love you all. My birthday is a month from today, don't forget it. Goodbye, my friends, for all is said and done, and I shall not return, for I've fully lived lifes fun. 
    
</post>


</Blog>