<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm...lets see. havent written in a while. but ill try to fill you in. jon came over a lot. hmm started hanging out with Megan again. cause she was in YellowStone for like two weeks. realized that she in moving. 5 minuetes away. (which isnt to far to ride a bike)..haha. answered all her "guy" questions and problems. haha. (shes not very "famillar" with that department)lol. its all good. hmm.. hung out with Sara, Matt and Hayden for a while. but today- woke up becuase my cousins were at the house cause i had to babysit them again. had to say no to going to the movies with chirstie and asa becuase of it. cousins left. and finnially....josh had come over..man i missed him. lol. hes cool. got caught up with him. lol. then we walked to haileys hung out there for like i dunno...20 minuets?...lol. then we walked home. and matt hayden and sara were outside so we hung wit them for a while and then joshs dad came to pick him up. so it was just me sara matt and hayden. lol....then the annoying girls from down the street came over and asked us to be in there movie...heres about the whole convo..lol  little girl #1- hey..um we were wondering if yall wanna be in our movie.. me matt sara &amp; hayden- (trying not to laugh).. me- and um..what mite this movie be about little girl #2- um..its about the hospital (we try not to laugh again) me- so um...what roles need to be filled in this hospital movie little girl #3- well..ya know..docters..paitentsand nurses. *awkard silence* ..................................................... *more awkard silence*..(lol)  sara- um...i dont.. (inturrupted by hayden) hayden- i wanna be the paient that dies *me thinking..WTF IS HE DOING?* me- i like ur barbie bike little girl #2- thank you. ***END OF STORY***  haha...they ended up being all pissed off and told there mom..(her mom was outside)..and she kept looking at us werid..haha..i almost gave her the bird...  that would've been cool. lol  fun times...  then..i FINNIALLY got my guatair fixed. it is so cool now..and in tune. yeah yeah. lol... then played poker over at saras till like 10:30...then my mom made me come home cause shes sick and wants to go to bed...AHH!..lol...  joey gaydos is hot!!!   urlLink www.joeygaydosjr.net   but when u click enter onto the site..dont pay attention to the red picture of him...go to his other pictures...and look at number 13.*sigh*  he is SO f-ing hot. but i think rite now he has a mullet.. BIG no no..lol   i have a PIANO LESSON tomarrow! ahh...OMG...it is suzuki style or whatever...and before i can get on the piano i have to BOW to HER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! and when i get off...i have to BOW AGAIN!!!!!!! this is so gay. lol. and he boobs go down to her waste and her skirt or pants come up past her bellybutton.  OMG i got a really cool shirt from wal-mart.. thats rite. lol..   quotes from my faveorite movie Napoline Dynamite- - c'mon tina u fat lard..come and get some ham!  - so uh..napolione..what did u do this summer? i already told you..i went to hunt wolverines at my unles farm..gosh....did u kill any? psh..yea like 50..god. what did u use? a 12-gage WHAT DO YOU THINK?  -(talking about pedros bike). wow..u got shocks...and pegs......LUCKY...(its funner than its sounds..u gotta see it)  -idiot  -yesssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss  -uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh  ^u probably dont understand any of this or prolly thinking that its not funny but thats cause u havent seen the movie...im serious this is the funniest move i have EVER seen in my WHOLE ENITRE 14 YEARS OF MY LIFE!..lol..when we walked in to the theater and gave our tickets to the lady..she was like.."yall are so gonna like this..yall are gonna have fun!"......haha..she even said it.......even though its not at mckinney movies but at plano legacy..and it costs six dollars..ITS SOOOOO F-ING WORTH EVERY PENNY!!!!!.  okay..im better now!  lol  call me- 9725293684  gots to go   later  K.  o yea--court--me u and josh are going to the movies!! okay!!..lol     
    
</post>


</Blog>