<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. - To be one (4:25) 2. (Choco) Hamasaki Ayumi - Vogue (2:46) 3. koda kumi - come back (5:37) 4. Amuro Namie - don't wanna cry (5:40) 5. Ayashi No Ceres - Scarlet.mp3 6. Ayumi Hamasaki & Gackt - Silent Night (3:25) 7. Ayumi Hamasaki & Keiko - A Song is Born (5:57) 8. ayumi hamasaki - a song for xx.mp3 9. ayumi hamasaki - boys & girls.mp3 10. Ayumi Hamasaki - Butterfly (DJ Mystik).mp3 11. Ayumi Hamasaki - Daybreak.mp3 12. Ayumi Hamasaki - End of the World.mp3 13. Ayumi Hamasaki - Evolution.mp3 14. Ayumi Hamasaki - Fly High.mp3 15. Ayumi Hamasaki - HANABI2.mp3 16. Ayumi Hamasaki - kanariya.mp3 17. ayumi hamasaki - love destiny.mp3 18. Ayumi Hamasaki - M.mp3 19. Ayumi Hamasaki - naturally.mp3 20. ayumi hamasaki - powder snow.mp3 21. Ayumi Hamasaki - Real Me (5:25) 22. Ayumi Hamasaki - Seasons.mp3 23. Ayumi Hamasaki - Voyage.mp3 24. Ayumi Hamasaki-Maria.mp3 25. Boa - Amazing Kiss (English Version).mp3 26. Boa - Dreams Come True.mp3 27. BoA - Every Heart (4:27) 28. BoA - Every Heart (English Version).mp3 29. BoA - Jewel Song.mp3 30. Boa - Kiseki.mp3 31. Boa - Listen To My Heart.mp3 32. Boa - Milky way.mp3 33. Boa and Koda Kumi - The Meaning of Peace (5:03) 34. Chinese Aaron Kwok- Please Don't Go Away.mp3 35. DDR 6th mix - So Deep.mp3 36. Do As Infinity - Raven.mp3 37. final fantasy 8 - Eyes On Me (Techno Almighty Mix).mp3 38. Final Fantasy X-2 - 1000 Words (Remix).mp3 39. Hamasaki Ayumi - Dearest (Strings) (2:10) 40. hamasaki ayumi - end roll.mp3 41. Hamasaki Ayumi - Trauma (4:16) 42. Hikari [Kingdom Hearts Orchestra Instrumental Version].mp3 43. Hikari.mp3 44. Hikaru Utada - Fly Me To The Moon (In Other Words).mp3 45. http://asianmusicnetwork.com - - ANGEL'S SONG (4:57) 46. Inu yasha - Dearest ED3 (Ayumi Hamasaki) - FULL.mp3 47. Inu Yasha - Fukai Mori.mp3 48. Inu-Yasha - Namie Amuro - Come.mp3 49. Inuyasha - Fukai Mori Instrumental.mp3 50. Jade - 1000 Words (orchestrated).mp3 51. JPOP Glay - Kimi Ga Iru.MP3 52. jpopzone-Hamasaki Ayumi-evolution.mpg 53. Koda Kumi - 02. Crazy 4 U (4:06) 54. Koda Kumi - Color of Soul (4:29) 55. Koda Kumi - m.a.z.e (4:01) 56. koda kumi - My Dream (4:37) 57. Koda Kumi - Pearl Moon (5:16) 58. Koda Kumi - Rain (5:08) 59. Koda Kumi - Trust Your Love .mp3 60. Koda Kumi 04 - 1000 Words (Instrumental).mp3 61. Kumi Koda - Gentle Words (3:46) 62. Kumi Koda - Love Across the Ocean.mp3 63. Matsueda, Eguchi - 1000 words (piano) (3:40) 64. MISIA - Don't stop music! (4:25) 65. Namie Amuro - You Are My Sunshine.mp3 66. Puffy Ami Yumi - Ai No Shirushi.mp3 67. Simple and CLean PLANITb Remix.mp3 68. Spice Girls - Who Do You Think You Are.mp3 69. TRUST.MP3 70. Utada Hikaru (&Foxy Brown)- Blow My Whistle.mp3 71. Utada Hikaru - Addicted to You.mp3 72. Utada Hikaru - Can You Keep A Secret.mp3 73. Utada Hikaru - COLORS (4:03) 74. Utada Hikaru - Eternally (8:11) 75. Utada Hikaru - First Love (Dance Remix) (4:06) 76. Utada Hikaru - Give Me A Reason.mp3 77. Utada Hikaru - Hikari (godson mix).mp3 78. utada hikaru - Hikari (Kingdom Hearts Theme Song).mp3 79. Utada Hikaru - Movin' On Without You.mp3 80. Utada Hikaru - Promise (5:24) 81. Utada Hikaru - Promise (5:24) 82. Utada Hikaru - Simple and Clean (PLANITb Remix) (2:30) 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      supah dupah mega mega ultimate raging blood decapitation pole flame beam slash hellfire kamehahamehamehamehaammeeaaa spam mega giant power zoom mech cannon blast flash annahilator cao fux hax couch hump.  i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord.  meh and teh tew chans pleh'd isketch earlier...it waf funneh....  GHEY FUX HAX POLE  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord.  i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord. i ish bord.  ^play Boys & Girls/  hehehe...sneaky amp pwns....  i hat c-chan....and SG...and ramee....and veg.  I HAT U ALL!!!!!  nut really....jus plehin...kay?  MKAY...ISH OUT  Mood-Bouncy happy joy joy fux hax pls kthx Music-Ayumi Hamasaki-Boys and Girls Quote- "Watashi gohan" (translation-"I rice")
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I stand on these rooftops shouting your name I can't find you I really need you  You were the one who saw me You helped me be me it felt so good to be around you  I really wish you would just talk to me I want to help if its that easy  I'm not too sure whats going on But I am always here for you So don't you dare cry don't let a tear shed from those eyes  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Crazy 4 U-Koda Kumi  sono kurayami de tsume wo migaite wa nerai sadamete kuchibiru ubatta shouganai desho kakugo kimete yo! konya wa nagai yoru ni naru wa  itsumade mo kawaranai nante arienai keredo demo hontou wa zutto kawaranai mama de itai no  Crazy for your love sono te de kowareru hodo no hageshii wana Only for you dakiai kuzureta mama no It's love game  kagiri naku tsuzuku yozora wa haruka kanata yagate kuru kakekaenai kono asa  sono kurayami de hikaru me wa nani wo kangaeteru no fuan ni naru wa konya kagiri no koi jya DAME na no sabishisa makesou ni naru wa  kokoro kara afuredashiteru amai mitsu no aji anata ni dake wa kanjite hoshii no watashi wo  Crazy for your love sono te de dakareru tabi ni hageshiku naru Only for you honki ni naru no ga kowai The trap of love  kasaneau sono kuchibiru ga furueteita hontou no kokoro wo ima miseru wa  Crazy for your love sono te de kowareru hodo no hageshii wana Only for you dakiai kuzureta mama no It's love game  kagiri naku tsuzuku yozora wa haruka kanata yagate kuru kakekaenai kono asa  Amazing Kiss-BoA  Tell me what you're dreaming bout tonight  I never want to let you go The lips that kissed my lashes and your sleepy smile Sinking into the darkest night A breezeless flow in the afterglow You and me together we could go that extra mile  Sweet nothings and time  Only you and the rhyme Dizzy vertigo  Round and round as we go  Amazing Kiss  Shining stars and I'll miss The flame that used to be ours, ours alone Cuz we made it happen...our miracle True and blue to our oracle Precious in my love...tu ru tu yeah I remember...  Amazing Kiss This is only shooting star The love that used to be ours,  I'm in love wow woh Joy, Affection... our universe Supernatural whirls Precious in my love... tu ru tu yeah  Looking for words our brainwaves  Found a way to communicate Secret sounds that you and I monopolize The moon reflected on the waves  Moving in time reverberates Drifting ashore to you deep into your eyes  As I lay awake Another night of heartbreak Longing for you  Hits me out of the blue  Amazing Kiss  Sprinkled pieces of bliss Promises that we'll be forevermore In the Milky Way I guess it's no more Don't you remember our vow, oh Precious in my love... tu ru tu yeah I remember...  Amazing Kiss  This is only shooting star The love that used to be ours,  I'm in love wow woh Joy, Affection... our universe Supernatural whirls Precious in my love... tu ru tu yeah  Tough enough to weather the hands of time Cuz our dream beams gonna shine on You and I will come this way again  True blue to our destiny Leaning up against this wall of ice  Never gonna let love fade away I don't want you to go So forevermore Just the way you are...  Precious in my love  Woh yeah yeah...yah~ Just the way you are... Precious in my love  Woh yeah yeah...yah~ Just the way you are...  Amazing Kiss  Shining stars and I'll miss The flame that used to be ours, ours alone Cuz we made it happen...our miracle True and blue to our oracle Precious in my love...tu ru tu yeah I remember...   Amazing Kiss  This is only shooting star The love that used to be ours,  I'm in love wow woh Joy, Affection... our universe Supernatural whirls Precious in my love... tu ru tu yeah  Amazing Kiss Sprinkled pieces of bliss Promises that we'll be forevermore In the Milky Way I guess it's no more Don't you remember our vow, oh Precious in my love... tu ru tu yeah I remember...  Every Heart(English)-BoA  Tell me babe, how many do I shed my tears?  Every HeartEvery Heart is not a gentle yet   Shall I do?I can never say my loneliness  Every Heart doesn't know so what to say oh what to do   was afraid of darkness cause I felt that I was left alone  So I prayed for help to the distant million stars   Round & round the planets revolve round the sun  And we always seek after love and peace forever more  Growing growing woe baby we can work it out  Look up at the sky every heart is shining all today   Show me now, What kind of smile do I come across  Every heart every heart can take a step towards the dreams   All of us what to take a lasting happiness  Whenever you feel sad, I wanna hold you  & give you a sound sleep   Someday every hearts gonna free and easy  We have peace of mind  Someday all the people find the way to love   Goes & goes the time goes on we are not alone  We live on together and we will find some precious things  Sometime we will smile sometime we will cry somehow  Don't forget believing yourself - Tomorrow's never die   There is the warm heart places on my mind  In my earlist day's there and it's so sweet  There are many stars they have talk with me so kind  They say yes always time's friend of mine so shine   Round & Round the planets revolve round the sun  And we always week after love and peace forever more  Growing growing woe baby we can work it out  Look at the sky every heart is shining all today   Goes & goes the time goes on we are not alone  We live on together and we will find some precious things  Sometime we well smile sometime we will cry somehow  Don't forget believing yourself - Tomorrow's never die  Mhmm...THX C-chan!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well...here ish mai plehlisht...It doesn't effen compar tew C-chan  1. - (5:02)     [I haff no clue wut this song ish....] 2. (Choco) Hamasaki Ayumi - Vogue (2:46) 3. Hamasaki Ayumi - Trauma (4:16) 4. MISIA - Don't stop music! (4:25) 5. koda kumi - My Dream (4:37) 6. Ayumi Hamasaki & Keiko - A Song is Born (5:57) 7. Matsueda, Eguchi - 1000 words (piano) (3:40) 8. koda kumi - come back (5:37) 9. Ayumi Hamasaki & Gackt - Silent Night (3:25) 10. Ayumi Hamasaki - Boys & Girls (3:56) 11. Ayumi Hamasaki - End of the world (4:41) 12. Ayumi Hamasaki - Fly high (4:06) 13. Ayumi Hamasaki - hanabi (4:56) 14. Ayumi Hamasaki - Real Me (5:25) 15. Ayumi Hamazaki - seasons (4:15) 16. Ayumi Hamasaki - Voyage (5:08) 17. Ayumi Hamasaki - Maria(4:30) 18. Boa and Koda Kumi - The Meaning of Peace (5:03) 19. Boa - Amazing Kiss (English Version) (4:36) 20. BoA - Every Heart (English Version) (4:33) 21. BoA - Jewel Song (5:26) 22. Boa - Kiseki.mp3 23. Boa - Listen To My Heart.mp3 24. Boa - Milky way.mp3 25. Chinese Aaron Kwok- Please Don't Go Away.mp3 26. DDR 6th mix - So Deep.mp3 27. Do As Infinity - Raven.mp3 28. final fantasy 8 - Eyes On Me (Techno Almighty Mix).mp3 29. HAMASAKI AYUMI - 06.Naturally (4:17) 30. Hamasaki Ayumi - M (4:26) 31. Hamazaki Ayumi - Love Destiny (4:57) 32. Hikaru Utada - Fly Me To The Moon (In Other W (3:23) 33. Do As Infinity - fukai mori (4:05) 34. Namie Amuro - Come (4:37) 35. Inuyasha - Every Heart.mp3 36. Inuyasha - Fukai Mori Instrumental.mp3 37. Jade - 1000 Words (orchestrated).mp3 38. jpopzone-Hamasaki Ayumi-evolution.mpg 39. Koda Kumi - Color of Soul.mp3 40. Koda Kumi - Crazy 4 U.mp3 41. Koda Kumi - M.A.Z.E..mp3 42. Koda Kumi 04 - 1000 Words (Instrumental).mp3 43. Namie Amuro - You Are My Sunshine.mp3 44. Utada Hikaru (&Foxy Brown)- Blow My Whistle.mp3 45. Utada Hikaru - Give Me A Reason.mp3 46. utada hikaru - Hikari (Kingdom Hearts Theme Song).mp3 47. Utada Hikaru - Movin' On Without You.mp3 48. Utada Hikaru - Promise (5:24) 49. Utada Hikaru - Promise (5:24) 50. Utada Hikaru - Simple and Clean (PLANITb Remix) (2:30) 51. Utada Hikaru COLORS.mp3 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok....2 'o clock this morning, my mom an dme are watching TV in the living room. I'm just laying there, listening to music with my eyes closed...and my mom gets up to go to the bathroom or something. I'm clueless to what she's about to do...and when she comes back, She slapped me in the forehead. Well...since this was unexpected,I like start convulsing...and then laugh my ass off as my mom like goes into a seisure from laughing. It was great. NEWayz...its like... 8:15 in the morning now...its raining like a bish...and my dog is spazing on my arm....go figure!  Mood-Happeh----ish Song-BoA-Every Heart(English Version) Quote- "Konnichiwa...Hajimemashite!"
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What the fux...I feel really good...but I feel really depressed and lonely....what the fuck!?!?!?!  Michelle and C-chan are my best friends(online)...I wish we could spend more time together...  So here's the deal...I'm listening to 1000 words...and all of a sudden...I feel the saddest I've ever felt in my life...  I dunno...I'm glad C-chan and Chelle are there though...they are fun to talk to and they made me feel a little better.  Mood-Depressed...kinda Music-1000 words...and other J-pop Quote- "Douka nakare riibu" (Translation-"Please don't leave")
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      THIS BLOG HAS MOVED TOO   http://www.livejournal.com/users/YellowFox777x
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The stars will cry The blackest tears tonight And this is the moment that I live for I can smell the ocean air And here I am Pouring my heart onto these rooftops Just a ghost to the world   Is that really me? I don't know anymore.....  Mood-Sad Song-Real Me 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
                 What Priston Tale Class Are You?     (Presented by   urlLink Aelice    )   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok...I'm gonna be gone for about 1 month...I have to go take Driver's Ed out of town...cause its cheaper...su...here is how you can talk to me.  1.)My Blog will be updated ALMOST daily...so comment here. 2.)My Aunt has AOL and AIM...so I might be able to talk on those 3.)Email me at YellowFox777x@hotmail.com 4.)If you know me...and my phone number...then call me on my cell on the weekends.  Other than that...sorry...I'll be back in a month 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I got bored and took a WHOLE bunch of FF tests today...here are my results (I took them all...so if you see girl ones...don't get all freaked out...I was bored and took ALL the tests)     urlLink       urlLink Which Final Fantasy Guy are you?         urlLink         urlLink       urlLink Which Final Fantasy Girl are you?         urlLink       urlLink Which Final Fantasy Summon are you?         urlLink       urlLink Which Final Fantasy Melody are you?         urlLink       urlLink Where in the Final Fantasy world?      
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      .................. My best friend......C-chan.....is gone.  GrayFox777x: Something very bad has happened... Rinos Atys: wut? GrayFox777x: dont expect to see c-chan on... Rinos Atys: Why??? GrayFox777x: her mom found Trillian Rinos Atys: OMFG Rinos Atys: Are you serious??? GrayFox777x: yes Rinos Atys: OOOOOOOOOMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGG GrayFox777x: I know .-. Rinos Atys: NNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO Rinos Atys: -cries- Rinos Atys: SHE WAS MY BEST FRIEND!!!!!!!!! GrayFox777x: ._. Rinos Atys: Hao u find out? GrayFox777x: Jin was talking to her last night GrayFox777x: then he found out it wasnt cchan GrayFox777x: but her mom Rinos Atys: WTF Rinos Atys: How can she sign in? Rinos Atys: C-chan hass password GrayFox777x: she must have left an away message up Rinos Atys: OMFG Rinos Atys: NO  .-. imma miss my ishhy........ -cries-
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. Koda Kumi - To be one (4:25) 2. (Choco) Hamasaki Ayumi - Vogue (2:46) 3. Hamasaki Ayumi - Trauma (4:16) 4. Koda Kumi - Rain (5:08) 5. MISIA - Don't stop music! (4:25) 6. koda kumi - My Dream (4:37) 7. Ayumi Hamasaki & Keiko - A Song is Born (5:57) 8. Matsueda, Eguchi - 1000 words (piano) (3:40) 9. koda kumi - come back (5:37) 10. Ayumi Hamasaki - Boys & Girls (Push Remix) (4:15) 11. Amuro Namie - don't wanna cry (5:40) 12. Ayashi No Ceres - Ayashi No Ceres - Scarlet (4:55) 13. Ayumi Hamasaki & Gackt - Silent Night (3:25) 14. Ayumi Hamasaki & Keiko - A Song is Born (5:57) 15. [Opening] ayumi hamasaki - to be.wma (5:19) 16. Ayumi Hamasaki - A Song For XX (4:44) 17. Ayumi Hamasaki - Boys & Girls (3:56) 18. Ayumi Hamasaki - Butterfly (DJ Mystik) (2:57) 19. Hamasaki Ayumi - Daybreak (4:48) 20. Ayumi Hamazaki - Depend On You (4:23) 21. Ayumi Hamasaki - Duty (5:16) 22. Ayumi Hamasaki - End of the world (4:41) 23. Ayumi Hamasaki - Evolution (4:39) 24. Hamasaki Ayumi - Fly high (Euro-Power Mix) (4:50) 25. Ayumi Hamasaki - Fly high (4:06) 26. Ayumi Hamasaki - hanabi (4:56) 27. Hamasaki Ayumi - I am... (5:31) 28. Hamasaki Ayumi - immature (4:44) 29. Hamasaki Ayumi - kanariya (Original Mix) (3:03) 30. Hamazaki Ayumi - Love Destiny (4:57) 31. Hamasaki Ayumi - M (4:26) 32. HAMASAKI AYUMI - 06.Naturally (4:17) 33. ayumi hamasaki - powder snow (5:02) 34. Ayumi Hamasaki - Real Me (5:25) 35. Ayumi Hamazaki - seasons (4:15) 36. [Opening] ayumi hamasaki - surreal.wma (4:42) 37. Hamasaki Ayumi - Trauma (Thunderpuss remix) (3:42) 38. ?? ??? - Trust(New Vocal&Mix/???????? ????CM???????) (4:48) 39. Ayumi Hamasaki - UNITE! (Yazaki Remix) (6:17) 40. Ayumi Hamasaki - Voyage (5:08) 41. Ayumi Hamasaki - Whatever (5:20) 42. Ayumi Hamasaki - You (4:40) 43. Inu Yasha - Inu Yasha Movie Theme (Ayumi Hamasaki) (5:48) 44. Ayumi Hamasaki - Maria (4:30) 45. Boa and Koda Kumi - The Meaning of Peace (5:03) 46. Boa - Amazing Kiss (English Version) (4:36) 47. Boa - Dreams Come True (4:56) 48. BoA - Every Heart (4:27) 49. BoA - Every Heart (English Version) (4:33) 50. BoA - Jewel Song (5:26) 51. Boa - Kiseki (3:59) 52. Boa - Listen to My Heart (3:54) 53. BoA - Milky Way (3:19) 54. Boa and Koda Kumi - The Meaning of Peace (5:03) 55. Faye Wong - Please don't go away (4:07) 56. DDR 6th mix - So Deep (1:34) 57. Do As Infinity - Raven (4:01) 58. Ayumi Hamasaki - Endless Sorrow -Original Mix- (5:29) 59. Faye Wong - Eyes On Me(Almighy Mix).mp3 (4:00) 60. Koda Kumi - 05 - 1000 Words (DJ 19 Remix) (8:34) 61. Hamasaki Ayumi - Daybreak (4:48) 62. Hamasaki Ayumi - Dearest (Strings) (2:10) 63. Hamasaki Ayumi - End Roll ~Original Version~ (4:48) 64. Hamasaki Ayumi - Trauma (4:16) 65. Hamasaki Ayumi - Trauma (Eurobeat Mix) (4:40) 66. Utada Hikaru - Kingdom Hearts [Orchest...] (3:42) 67. Utada Hikaru - Hikari (Japanese) (5:03) 68. Hikaru Utada - Fly Me To The Moon (In Other W (3:23) 69. http://asianmusicnetwork.com - - ANGEL'S SONG (4:57) 70. Ayumi Hamasaki - Dearest (5:27) 71. Do As Infinity - fukai mori (4:05) 72. Namie Amuro - Come (4:37) 73. Do As Infinity - Fukai Mori Instrumental (4:04) 74. Jade from Sweetbox - 1000 Words (Orchestrated Version) (6:23) 75. Glay - Kimi Ga Iru (2:43) 76. jpopzone - evolution (48:58) 77. Koda Kumi - 02. Crazy 4 U (4:06) 78. Koda Kumi - Color of Soul (4:29) 79. Kumi Koda - Gentle Words (3:46) 80. Koda Kumi - m.a.z.e (4:01) 81. koda kumi - My Dream (4:37) 82. Koda Kumi - Pearl Moon (5:16) 83. Koda Kumi - Rain (5:08) 84. Koda Kumi - To be one (4:25) 85. Koda Kumi - Trust Your Love (4:29) 86. Koda Kumi - 1000 no Kotoba (Instrumental Version) (5:58) 87. Kumi Koda - Gentle Words (3:46) 88. Kumi Koda - love across the ocean (3:36) 89. Ayumi Hamasaki - M (Above and Beyond remix) (4:15) 90. Matsueda, Eguchi - 1000 words (piano) (3:40) 91. MISIA - Don't stop music! (4:25) 92. Amuro Namie - don't wanna cry (5:40) 93. Amuro Namie - You Are My Sunshine (2:05) 94. Naruto - Ayumi Hamasaki (5:02) 95. Puffy AmiYumi - Ai no shirushi (2:49) 96. Utada Hikaru - Hikari (English PLANITb Remix) (2:28) 97. TRUST (4:49) 98. Utada Hikaru Feat. Foxy Brown - Blow My Whistle (4:06) 99. Utada Hikaru - Addicted to You (5:57) 100. Utada Hikaru - Can You Keep A Secret? (5:06) 101. Utada Hikaru - COLORS (4:03) 102. Utada Hikaru - Eternally (8:11) 103. Utada Hikaru - First Love (Dance Remix) (4:06) 104. Utada Hikaru - Give Me A Reason (6:27) 105. Utada Hikaru - Hikari (godson mix) (4:39) 106. Utada Hikaru - Hikari (Kingdom Hearts Theme Song) (5:03) 107. Utada Hikaru - Movin' On Without You (4:37) 108. Utada Hikaru - Promise (5:24) 109. Utada Hikaru - Simple and Clean (English Remix) (2:31) 110. Utada Hikaru - Simple and Clean (PLANITb Remix) (2:30)  Wow...I'm almost up there with C-chan  C-Chan: 113 songs Rinos: 110 songs  w00t  g2g to bed nao...bai  PS-TO BE ONE ISH PWN!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      OMFG...other than the fact that I had chinese food and listened to J-pop ALL day...today sucked  No one was online, the people that were online when I was talking were fuxed up ('cept c-chan and veg).......then I felt like playing FFT...su I'm getting off...cause when I feel like it...is right now.  I ISH BORD....pls help   Mkay....  Bai  Mood- Bored Song- Ayumi Hamasaki-Fly High Quote- None today...sorry  OMFG...if you want to hear a sad song...download Ayumi Hamasaki-Real Me I don't know why its sad...but I just found it as sad.     Real Me Lyrics  English  What I get? What you get? It may be an illusion And we may only want to believe That we have got  What I say? What you say? If we don't express Our thoughts and feelings in words They may not be understood nor reach  The present time Starts here  A woman never runs away A woman never hides away In order to survive You should not want to be healed Without fighting  A woman never shows her fears A woman never shows her tears In order to survive You should not easily Show your tears to someone  What I need? What you need? Maybe it's all right So long as I have desires And am not satisfied  What I lose? What you lose? Maybe I have heard enough people saying That they knew the value of something Only after losing it  Love It's here  A woman could be dangerous A woman could be generous In order to survive We cannot always be So good girls  A woman could be having fun A woman could be like a nun In order to survive We cannot be kind to others Before we know pain  A woman never runs away A woman never hides away In order to survive You should not want to be healed Without fighting  A woman never shows her fears A woman never shows her tears In order to survive You should not easily Show your tears to someone  A woman could be dangerous A woman could be generous In order to survive We cannot always be So good girls  A woman could be having fun A woman could be like a nun In order to survive As I know You see the real me      Romanji  What I get? What you get? Te ni shiteru mono wa Shinjitai dake de Gensou nano kamo na  What I say? What you say? Kotoba ni shinakucha Tsutawarenai kamo ne Todokanai kamo ne  Koko kara Ima ga hajimaru  a woman never runs away a woman never hides away in order to survive Tatakai mo sezuni Iyashi motomeru mon janai  a woman never shows her fears a woman never shows her tears in order to survive Namida wa tayasuku Dareka ni miseru mon janai  What I need? What you need? Yokubou ga atte Mitasarenai uchi wa Daijoubu kamo ne  What I lose? What you lose? Nakushite hajimete Kizuitada nante Kiki akita kamo ne  Ai nara Koko ni arukara  a woman could be dangerous a woman could be generous in order to survive Sonna ni itsudemo Ii KO bakari de irarenai  a woman could be having fun a woman could be like a nun in order to survive Itami wo shiranakya Yasashiku nante irarenai  a woman never runs away a woman never hides away in order to survive Tatakai mo sezuni Iyashi motomeru mon janai  a woman never shows her fears a woman never shows her tears in order to survive Namida wa tayasuku Dareka ni miseru mon janai  a woman could be dangerous a woman could be generousU in order to survive Sonna ni itsudemo Ii ko bakari de irarenai  a woman could be having fun a woman could be like a nun in order to survive honto no watashi wa Anata ga mite de kureru kara  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      AYU ISH PWN BOMB MAYN!!! U MUST DOENLOD ALL UF HER SONGS!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is the battle group for my final fantasy tactics game...please post your comments for who you would like to be in the main party and who you would like to be alternates. If you don't know what the job class is, click on it...and it will give you a description. Thanks.  Jin- Job 1:  urlLink Squire       Job 2:  urlLink Archer   Amara- Job 1: urlLink Monk         Job 2: urlLink Ninja   Ayamishi- Job 1: urlLink Summoner  Job 2:  urlLink White Mage   Arkonius- Job 1: urlLink Knight  Job 2:  urlLink Dragoon   Yasashii- Job 1: urlLink Chemist  Job 2: urlLink White Mage   Ramee- Job 1:  urlLink Oracle         Job 2:  urlLink Chemist   Kylie- Job 1: urlLink Ninja  Job 2:  urlLink Chemist   Rinos- Job 1:  urlLink Monk  Job 2:  urlLink Knight   Si- Job 1:  urlLink Ninja  Job 2:  urlLink Chemist   SG- Job 1:  urlLink Bard  Job 2:  urlLink Mediator   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Test 1: urlLink Monk  Test 2:  urlLink Knight   I'm a Monk...ne a knight!! w00t...I need teh all uf mai frends tew tak dis test pls kthx.   This is the quiz   urlLink http://www.insomniel.com/quizzes/ffclassesquiz.htm 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>