<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   How the hell can they lose 3 games in a row to one of the worst teams in baseball.  They better get a new middle reliever and/or closer, or they won't be able to hold on to this lead.  If the Cubs make the playoffs or even worse the world series that would be an unforgivable tragedy.   

						
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well I have been working on this damn thing for the last four months straight, no days off not even weekends, and the end is rapidly approaching.  Friday the 2nd I get to defend this damn thing.  Though my advisor keeps reassuring me I have nothing to worry about, I cant help but shake the feeling that something bad might happen.  Nothing would suck more than spending 3 years busting your ass in a lab, and then not get your masters (or more years and PhD, but thats not the case here). Maybe its just stress.  It may be the fact that I still haven't found a job yet.  Whatever it is, I can not wait to get this over with on Friday, spend the evening with friends, and then start planning for the rest of my life.   

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well now that Kerry selected a running mate, the election will start heating up.  My support goes towards are current and great President.  However, I am a little worried about his chances.  Everywhere I turn I hear how so many people hate him, he is constantly getting bashed everywhere you go, and for some reason other than talk shows the GOP isn't fighting back.  This was the same mistake his dad made, and I think this election is too important to lose to someone who has yet to take a stand on any of the major issues (Hey Kerry we know you wouldn't have sent troops, but we are there now so what would you do now if you were in office?) All I can tell people is to actually look at facts instead of read opinions, and at least make an informed decision. 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well the defense went surprisingly well.  Few questions, my committee was nice, and it turns out I never had anything really to worry about.  Now I just have to find a friggin job.  Oh, and the cards reasserted themselves over crappy teams, by handing the Mariners their lunch in a brown paper bag. 

						
</post>


</Blog>