<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm surfing the web right, and I come across a friends web journal. I'm curious so I start reading. It got me thinking about a few things.  See this friend is majorly in love with a girl. He's also pretty good friends with her. Now, he might have a good reason for this that's not know to me, but he won't and hasn't told her. He beleives it will hurt her. This friend has started into the self mutilation, razors; tacks and scissors. I never really knew and never woulda guessed. It's scaring me. I mean, I'm like any other teen. I have my periods of depression and I know a little of what it feels like. But never that far. What I'm getting at here is that I'm starting to think I need a way to tell her. I feel bad at betraying my friends trust in me over this since he told me who it was but I also can't stand seeing him hurt like this.  So if you're reading this man (Unlikely but possible), I'm sorry. It needs to be done. You're on a downward spiral. Been there, done that. It's not pretty. The only difference is that I know I hide my depression better. Either you tell her how you feel or I do. Ask her out. If she says no then fine. You love her enough to just be friends if that's all she wants right? And secondly, you fucking think she'd be impressed with this shit? I would bet a shitload of money that wether she loves you or not she doesn't want to see you like this.  And neither do I.  Don't feed me any bullshit about me having a girlfriend and therefor not knowing what it's like. I got news for you, I was in love with her for three fucking years before we started going out. Hear that? I'm sorry man but you have no freaking room to complain. And I almost forgot about that space where she dumped me for awhile. I'm willing to bet that's even worse. In fact I know it is. I was still completely in love with her and even more unsure over what she felt than before. But as I said, I loved her enough to just be friends because that's all she wanted.That being said, I feel your pain and I know what it's like. I hold complete sympathy for you but somehow I don't think that's what you want or need.  I also read about how you're not sure how any of your friends can respect you. Newsflash. It's because we're your  friends . That's all there is to it. I'm your friend man and always will be. So is everyone else. In fact, same goes for the Bluefish. None of us would simply desert you. Anyone who would can't be truly counted as a friend. When we did Julius Caesar in english class I remember hating Brutus. I couldn't give a fuck what his reasons were, he abandoned his best friend. Not only abandoned him but literally stabbed him in the back as well. Neither of you would get that from me and I hope from none of your other friends. My parents dislike most of you guys and I know it. It doesn't stop me from being your friend. I'm not your friend because I want to make a statement. I'm not your friend for the conveniance. I'm not your friend because I think it'll make me cool. I'm your friend because I like you and enjoy your company. You guys cheer me up, make me feel better and let me live life. I doubt any of you really realise how much you guys mean to me. How many of you would guess how depressed I've been for the last five months or so? None I'd hope. I don't like placing my problems on the shoulders of others. But you've all helped me never the less. Thank you.  Well, I'm worn out out for this evening. Can't think of anything else to write. It feels good to get this stuff down though. I can be almost positive none of you will ever read this but there's always a chance. So, to my (best) friend who hates the world, I'll leave you with this little thought: Has it occured to you that you're hurting the both of you far more by not telling her? Think about it.  Where Light Shines, Darkness Exsists,  -Dant 
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, lookit me go. Got myself a blog. I'm stylin now. So yah, guess I'll be writing in it from now on. Not regularly though. Not that it matters, I mean, what are the chances someone is actually gonna bother reading this?
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The world was just there. It exsisted and grew larger day by day. But, eventually the world became a little darker. Shadows surrounded me daily. Then came a flash of light into the day. Each day I would anxiously wait for that light and it never failed me. But as time passed I grew afraid of its brilliance and drew away from it. The light followed me though I kept a distance. It was still affecting me. A short time later I grew less afraid and bathed in the light. When the light disappeared it was sudden. I was left in blinding darkness, left in fear and pain. I was slow to recover from the loss of the light. But I did and in a measure the light returned. I was happy. However the light soon reappeared in full glory. Thinking that the light would never leave again I accepted it back and never questioned where it had gone. I was wrong.  Again the light left me, plunging my world once again into darkness. I felt crippled as every old wound reopened and new ones formed. My soul hardened and I sank quietly out of sight. In time I may once again heal. I will never be truly whole again though. A piece of me left with that light and will never return. For now, I am content to live in the darkness with my despair as a crutch. Farewell and goodbye.    Friends,   -Dant  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's times like this I feel alone. I mean, there's people all around me but it's like I'm seperate from them. Like there's a wall between us. I can't even really give a reason why. It just feels that way. And within my cocoon of solitude I sit and think. Think about me, think about my life. Think about what I've done wrong and every once and awhile I think about what I've done right. It's hard. People somtimes wonder why I isolate myself with games and books so often. It's because I'm afraid of ending up in that space again. When I'm reading a book or playing a game I'm somewheres else. I'm not in this world, with all it's problems and difficulties. And I get mad when interupted because it means I'm being dragged back into the real world. To tell the truth, that's a place I don't much like to be. While I'm here everything can come crashing in. The pain, the hurt.  And you wonder about me?    Life is wonderful,  Life is horrible,   -Dant  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Darkness needs a source, just as light does. The difference between the two is that light  is  the source of darkness. Without the light the darkness would not be there. Likewise, without darkness, light could not exsist. The two are polar opposites. Neither stronger than the other, neither weaker. What's that? You say that light always prevails in the end and pushes out the dark? Not true. The light may shine into the dark places and illuminate them yet the darkness simply flows around the edges, waiting and lurking. In its turn it will push back the light. and likewise will the light return to push back the darkness. It is a neverending struggle between two forces so evenly matched one can barely discern the differences between them. And so do good and evil fight.  And so do I choose evil. After all, if we are all pawns then what reason is there to be not? It all balances out you see. Without people such as me, that man there who gives away all he has to charities and is still cheerfull wouldn't seem half as good. Because if there were none such as me he wouldn't be. If everyone were like that it wouldn't be special. Instead he becomes a good man and is likely much loved by those around him.  Good for him I say. He has found what he wants, his nirvana if you will. And if he is happy then so be it. I myself will never be like that. And there is no middle ground in this war. There is no neutral. And so I turn to the darkness that is willing to embrace me. It alone accepts me as me. That is all I ask and all I recieve.    Hurting,   -Dant  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not to sure about my life. I really don't know wether to hate it and myself or love it. I have so many reasons to live and so many ways to enjoy life but at the same time there are so many ways to be hurt. You know what I'm talking about. Those times when the whole world seems to be out for your blood. When no matter how sunny it is there's always this dark cloud hanging over you. That's me right now. That's what I feel like. Everything I enjoy about my life is overshadowed by overwhelming shadow and pain. It's not like I can't remember the good things that have already happened. It's just that everything now, even good things, don't seem quite as good.    I guess it can sorta come from this whole past year. Since I started high school, things have been different. I got a whole different group of friends. People I really care about. Heck, we're probably the closest thing our school has to goths. Heh, thing is we're also the nerds. Not so bad really. I mean, I know my parents don't really approve of most of them. They're pretty much all at least a year older than me, with the exception of Mitch and Bussboy. And I think that's part of the problem. I know half of them I probably won't see to much of for the next long while. They'll be off to university and college while I'm stuck back here. I really don't know what I'll do without some of them. Gram, the Bluefish, Cam, Big Steve, Dev, Laim and even Cher and Tasha. They support me. They're there for me. Take Big Steve for instance. My parents really dislike him. They may even be justified. He drinks and sometimes has anger problems. But I mean, the thing is, I can pretty much be sure he'd be the first one there if someone was trying to kick my ass. I'm not the toughest guy around and I'm slightly a pacifist and, well, we don't call him Big Steve for nothing.  My point is, these guys (And girls) aren't exactly perfect people. But, you know, they're still my friends. And that means that all that shit doesn't matter. You are who you are. and that's all right by me.    But on to my next problem. Steph. I've had a major assed crush on her for at least two or three years now. We've been pretty good friends all the while. Now, we went out together for awhile and then broke up.  A few months later it was all fine again and we were still friends. Then she asks me for a second chance.  Now, you have to understand how this is working. I am still in love here. However, since she just wanted to be friends, well, that's all it would ever be. So of course I leap at a second chance. It seems to be going fine and as you might tell from a previous post or two it was indeed. Right up until she dumps me a second time. That was like almost two weeks now I think. I am still fucking shattered mentally. That's part of the reason I feel like I do.    And so it goes on. I also slacked off majorly this past year. This is not a good thing. My marks went from all high ninties to maybe mid eighties and a couple of seventies. For me, those are horrible marks. I just put no effort into things. I had no motivation. I think my only really high mark was in history. It was one of the few subjects I was interested in. This is probably one of the worst things to happen to me. I can only guess why. Both my brother and sister are like, friggin geniuses. They both got full scholarships and so on. My brothers already got a job programming that will probably get him more per hour than I ever will. My sisters simply got it pretty good. I'm not saying they don't have problems. We all do and I'm sure they have theirs. I'm saying I can't really ever hope to match up. I might be able to get good marks and so on but I'll never be  as  good. So I sorta accept that and slack off. It's not a good thing and it doesn't help me here. I mean I've always procrastinated but I've always seen that as a good thing. I work well under pressure. This is worse and scares me more than just about anything.    I guess what I'm trying to say is that this has both been the worst and best year of my life. MY lifes changed, for better or for worse I couldn't tell you. But I'm me. And I can live with that.    Forever and Always,   -Dant   
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is there pain?   Why do we, as a race, have the ability to suffer as we do? And when you   really get down to it does any of it actually matter? Life, love,   friendship. Pain.   But the pain matters doesn't it? Pain makes us who we are. Without it   we would be lost, adrift in a sea with no shore. Pain is life in a way.   But that doesn't make it better. Or make it hurt less. Because it   hurts. We all know that. It hurts in ways so deep they cannot even be   contemplated. It threatens your very essence. But you can never let it   stop you or even slow you down. Because if you do you will find it   impossible to start again. And the next step from there is that   inviting bottle of pills.....   But, you say, but what are you talking about? Pain is a purely physical   thing. The sting of a cut or throbbing of a bruise. I say you lie. The   pain I speak of is much more than that. This is the pain that is far   more potent than anything purely physical could ever be. I speak of   your mind. Of your feelings, hopes and dreams. I speak of what it feels   like when these things are shattered. All in one instant everything is   gone. Lost with only scars to leave their white hot trails across your   mind. And you say pain doesn't matter? Those who speak so are the lucky   few. For they are the ones who have never experienced this. The few who   have never felt true pain.   But I say again. We as a race need pain. We could not survive without   it. We seek it out and revel in it. Not consciously perhaps but we do   all the same. And often, even when we realise where it will all lead we   continue. Why? Because the pain is only what you make of it. And should   I choose to make love to that pain, am I truly wrong?  Here We Are,    -Dant  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those wondering why the last post looks a little odd. It's because   Blogger keeps freaking crashing my browser. And on top of that keeps  messing up the spacing and lines of the thing. Gah. So annoying.      
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sigh, I hate depression. Got up this morning around noon. I'm still tired. Plus I know I've got a bunch of things I have to do today, none of which I really want to do. To top it off most of my friends are going places. I'd feel bad that I wasn't asked but since both they and I know that I wouldn't be able to go anyways I don't really. It just means there's noone to talk to. Oh, and last I heard my girlfriend is working today. So bad day for me all around. Can't even write a decent Blog....  Tired of it all,  -Dant 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And why is that?  Well after waking up and realising how late it was I was thinking this would be a bad day. And was I so happily completely wrong.  First I have one of my buddies over and we watch some really bad Jet Li movie called The Enforcer. Standard Kung-Fu movie. So horribly bad it's good. Favorite scene is when the main character manages to defy the laws of physics and hang in midair for about 45 seconds(Horizontally mind you.) while firing a shotgun about five times(Without pumping it.). Second favorite is him tying his son to a rope and throwing him at the bad guys. The son spins around and kicks people. Great fun.  So that was fun by itself but by no means makes my day. Next off I get to finish mowing the freaking lawn with a newly fixed lawnmower. As a side rant,  I bloody hate lawnmowers!  The damn things always break on me for no real reason. Kinda like Windows. Of course I have a shower cause hey, I just mowed the lawn.  Then comes the part making me really happy. My girlfriend got off work and came over to watch some movies. Now, keep in mind that because of work(All minimum wage of course) we hadn't seen each other for about four or five days. And this is with us living like two minutes walking away from one another. So almost instantly the stress that's been building up on me for a while just melted away. As for what exactly happened to make me so happy.......  Fuck you and get your mind out of the gutter. Sheesh, perverts.  Drunk On Ambrosia,  -Dant 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm sitting here. Today is Canada day and hell, I'm proud to be Canadian. Now, one of my friends online happens to be American. His IM name is basically stating he doesn't give a fuck about Canada. Fine, that's his opinion. I want to know why. So I ask, like any other person might. What I comes down to is that he simply doesn't like Canada. He believes we're arrogant towards the US of A. Now I ask you, where the hell is he coming from on this? For the last hundred years or so Canada has pretty much been Americas bitch. So it seems that Americans think anytime Canada stands up for itsself or any other country we're being arrogant and egotistical. The Americans ban our produce for the most trivial of reasons and expect us not to give so much as a wimper while when we quietly point out that the war on Iraq is completely fucking pointless except to satisfy American pride and fill American coffers(And gas tanks). What, you're saying Saddam was a tyranical bastard who deserved to be removed? Why I do belive you're right. So, when is America going to move into all those other oppressed countries and "free" them. You know, the ones without any oil or money? Bah, the world makes me angry. This isn't directed at you man, nor the American people in general. I simply don't like your country or its policies. Or, for that matter, its president.  That being said the rest of my day wasn't to bad. Slept, messed with the comp, went to watch the fireworks. Only sucky part was that my girlfriend had to work until after midnight and so I couldn't watch them with her. Other than that though a good day alround.  Proud To Be Canadian,  -Dant 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again, on the off chance you read this.  I decided. I wasn't really thinking very straight when I wrote saying I'd tell her. I won't unless you want me to. For now at least. The rest still stands.    *edit again*    I actually considered removing this and the post it relates to completely. I'm not overly sure I want it posted here. Still thinking about it though.... 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can any live with this cloud. Hanging over me, ripe with despair and sorrow. The cloud of my tattered dreams and twisted memories. Shattered feeling and warped emotion. Is this all I am? Is this all I'll ever be? How can I go on, how do I go on? The world bleeds and so do those who live upon it. This spiral that cannot be broken, the path to death and the everlasting darkness. To redemtion? It hardly seems likely. Does the afterlife truly exsist or is it just one more lie in a sea of many. To many, far to many. Life, life is a lie. Pretending to be that which it is not. Not happy and warm yet neither cool and sad. Can any understand the meaning of it all? I doubt it. How can one understand that which has no meaning? But if it did would we realise it? Maybe it does. Or maybe not, it doesn't matter. It's pointless like everything else. Pointless as my exsistence. Making me feel small. Because when you get down to it I don't matter. My name will fade as will my memories. Fade and burn like so many before. Call it fate, call it destiny, call it what you will it is the same. Same as you and same as me. We are the same. We share life yet we are seperate. Broken as everything I know and everything I will ever know. Shards of what I think tinkling down like a broken window. That window is me, my exsistence. It's all I've got really. My most prized posession and my curse. Without it there would be no pain. But even the simple hurt of pain can feel good, just knowing you're still there, still alive. It helps to focuse you yet can suck at your soul like a drug. What soul? I don't have one. I never have and never will. You have to believe to have a soul. I don't, I can't. It's easier just to wallow in my self pity. I'm evil but is evil so bad? You have to have evil to have good. They balance, they lend meaning to their opposite. Without one the other doesn't exsist. And neither does. I confuse myself. I don't know why though. Maybe because I'm me. No man can understand himself in all forms. No man can understand another. I hurt when I try to think of that. It boggles me how this all works. Everything that is. It all fits. It's broken but it still works. It wouldn't work if it was fixed. Because then it would be broken even worse than it is now. We need it. So my big question is why? Why why why why? It doesn't have to be like this does it? And if it does then how come? And if so then why can't it be better? So what's better? Nothing and everything. Nothing is always better than everything though. Why nothing? Why not something else? Have you every experienced nothing? Yes. I feel nothing now. I am empty like a deflated balloon. That's what is better. Better than you and better than me. It feels good. Like I'm stoned but I'm not. I feel clean. Anything is better than what I was before. Before what? Before life, before exsistence. Merely being alive screws you up. It's unavoidable, bearing down on you full of troubles. Burning like a hound from hell. Only worse because hell only tortures you physically. And that's just pain, just like any other. This is deep down, far into the soul I don't have. Imagine the worst pain possible and multiply it by infinity. That's what it feels like. Can you imagine that? Yes you probably can. Because you can feel it to. Everyone can, living and dead. Everyone hurts in their own way. Everyone hurts in one way or another.  Reality Sucks,  -Dant 
    
</post>


</Blog>