<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      Hey everybody...It's time for my second post. First of all, let me tell you, I believe this post is mostly going to speak to those around my age or older.  I'm surprised that these thoughts turned out to be more serious than light-hearted but I guess the rain we had in Little Rock today had me thinking more on the serious note.    I titled this post "Can you tell me how to get...BACK to Sesame Street" because I often think back to the days when Big Bird, Bugs Bunny, and Mr. Rogers were the important things on my daily agenda.  Of course, I know there is no stopping Father Time from playing his role in my life...but oh...how I miss those days of my childhood and I am not   really   that old.  But time has passed quickly and now the important things on my agenda are going to work, paying the bills and the rent, buying groceries, cleaning the place and washing my clothes, while trying to maintain a healthy social and spiritual life.  Speaking of spiritual life, what happened to the days of Noah and the cute animals and Vacation Bible School??  My faith seemed so much easier  back then.  Things aren't so easy any more.  The world has changed even since I was a young child. Politics, media, ever evolving religions, and the internet, to name a few, have made their mark in our lives and the lives of the upcoming generation. I didn't have to deal with "grown up" things at a very early age.  Now, it seems, the world is so complex and I swirl about in its cyclone of demands, temptations, and pleasures.  Life seems so surreal at times.  I certainly am not expressing these observations as a person that is distant from the changes in the world today.  I express these thoughts as a person that is astonished that my life has changed so drastically in such a short amount of time.  Your parents always tell you that you'll be grown before you know it. Tis true, tis true.     I will not ask you to endure my reminiscing any longer.  Let me know what you think...do you ever think this way??? What do miss about being a child?    I think I'll go find Cookie Monster and ask him for a cookie...I think I need one. T.T.F.N.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      Greetings to all that find themselves reading this post on my blog. I am now entering the "rabbithole" of the blog world.  Sorta like Alice...I don't know exactly where this is going to lead...I'm not sure who will actually read these posts but I thought I'd follow the white rabbit. I do anticipate that my posts will be interesting, running the gamut from what's going on in my life to politics, religion, movies, music, and other tidbits of information.    During my high school years, I was told by my mother and grandmother that I was the writer of the family. (I'm afraid my sister has grabbed the poetic torch and ran with it...but I'm proud of her.) I've been out of practice for a few years so it is my hope that this blog experience will reignite those Shakespearean skills and that you'll be buying my number one bestselling masterpiece by the time this is all said and done.    For now, I'll get the next post brewing...so get ready....let's follow that rabbit together.  T.T.F.N~~~
    
</post>


</Blog>