<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So just go ahead and put the knife to my heart Either stab me now or rip it out again Do what you want The choice is yours... Cause I've given up on all senseless reason I've given up on acts of indiscretion Go ahead and kill me once more Just another way you show your perfection... I had a burden of giving you what you wanted I had a load of receiving your complaints But the measure of this world can’t compare to this Cause it can’t outweigh all my pain Go ahead, keep it all in, never give out before you go Go away, keep all those thoughts, never gave me the time of day What is really going on right now? You tell me that nothing is wrong, but I can tell that all is You try to change the subject, but one thing is only on my mind What is wrong? Was it something I said? Go ahead, keep secrets from me, I’ve never kept any of mine from you Go away, keep your wounds, I thought we would say it all upfront  What is really going on today? You claim you are busy, and can’t be disturbed It’s like you have another life, and I am unaware and unwelcome to it Well guess that’s the life we’ve made Guess that’s the games we play But it’s like I always lose and I can never win So I think today I will quit before I can begin Goodbye, goodbye Always hated leaving first, but now I fear the worst  So long, so long Always hate to admit it, but I can not forget it  I’m leaving now, better stop me before I go The doors getting closer and I just hate to leave Hello. 
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Your eyes-  How often I find myself lost in them, kind of like a fairy tale They take me away to a place that seems so very real Your goodbyes- How much the words hurt me, even when you’re gone only for a while Can’t you stay longer, make my dreams come true, just walk the extra mile Cause you know that I would do it all for you  I don’t need to tell you how much I care I hope by now you already know,  You know, that if you a had a burden I’d carry it for you And if you needed to meet me, I’d be there before you Just don’t keep me waiting much longer  Your mouth- Sweeter than the roses that resemble the color of your lips So perfect, so flawless, I would give it all away just for one more kiss Your soul- Gleaming of vibes that I could never comprehend, but I try to  Lights my way and gets me to the pathway’s end, and I need you Cause you know that I would do it all again for you  I don’t need to tell you how much I care I hope by now you already know,  You know, that if you a had a burden I’d carry it for you And if you needed to meet me, I’d be there before you Just don’t keep me waiting much longer (x2)  You, unlike me, see the world through better perspectives This viewpoint I have, can’t see much at all But you’re in my range, seems so strange to be here now  I don’t need to tell you how much I care I hope by now you already know,  You know, that if you a had a burden I’d carry it for you And if you needed to meet me, I’d be there before you Just don’t keep me waiting much longer 
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So go ahead and forget me I am not to be remembered But at least we had some good times Remember them before you say goodbye I can change with the flow I can, so I need to know just what to say What do I need to do? I know you’ve heard it before But the only thing I got going for me is you  I can pretend that I don’t notice you pretending I can act like I believe every word you say I’ve been holding my breath so I won’t take in your air It’s intoxicating, I just need to get away Just let me get away  So go ahead and overlook me I am not to be recognized But at least you gave me the second glance Recall us now, cause you never believed in second chances I can stay this way forever I can, but would this make it better if I did? What do I need to prove? I know you’ve read this note before But the only person I’d give my heart to is you  I can pretend that I don’t notice you pretending I can act like I believe every word you say I’ve been holding my breath so I won’t take in your air It’s intoxicating, I just need to get away Just let me get away (x3)  Let me give you a dozen roses Let me give you a dozen years I’d give you all the time you needed But that could never justify these tears  I can pretend that I don’t notice you pretending I can act like I believe every word you say I’ve been holding my breath so I won’t take in your air It’s intoxicating, I just need to get away Just let me get away (x3)
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You are captivating, capture me, lure me into you Eyes so blue, intricate yet they intertwines mine to you I know roads ahead look daring, but if dared, would you come with me? Never let me go, I need you now More than I have ever needed you You are magnetizing, maneuver your way into my arms Hair is so fair, flawless and soft, I want you in my arms I know challenges await us, just wait for me, I will be at your every step Never leave me behind, I need you now More than ever before, more than I’ve ever needed you You look like you need me too But this detour is blocking my way I don’t want to find another way, you might be gone Will you still be there when I come home? When I come home  When I come home  When I come home  You are me, and I am you, tonight we are one I melt into you, you explore all of me, leave no place undiscovered I know regrets may come someday, but someway, I will help you through them Never let me go, I need you now More than you could ever know I need you 
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Time- Time itself seems to be escalating And I can’t stop it from penetrating our wounds that seem to stay Bind- Tie these things together Maybe you’ll see things better when you are away (when you are away)  I have dreams, I have hopes I can breathe, and I can choke But nothing that you can say can reassure my beliefs that you are wrong You don’t have to leave now We can make it if we try  Don’t let this moment pass you by You don’t have to leave  Desire- I hope for so much more, but I will be pleased with what you give I’m not so selfish you see, all that I ask is for honesty Tired- I’m growing so very weary, carry me home, I can’t make it Wake me up when you return, I deserve all of this so don’t fake it  I have dreams, I have hopes I can breathe, and I can choke But nothing that you can say can reassure my beliefs that you are wrong You don’t have to leave now We can make it if we try  Don’t let this moment pass you by You don’t have to leave  Now that you are already gone Does it please you to know that I am not feeling so well? Now that you are gone for good Does it help you sleep better at night, knowing I’m not alright? You don’t have to leave  I have dreams, I have hopes I can breathe, and I can choke But nothing that you can say can reassure my beliefs that you are wrong You don’t have to leave now We can make it if we try  Don’t let this moment pass you by You don’t have to leave  Nothing that you say or do can replace your goodbye   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’d do anything for you to notice  When I am around But you could care less I see The vacant expression is showing And I know when to say quit But you and I both know that I won’t let you go  Writing letters, Showing I am alive Nervous again, “I think I’ll wait until tomorrow” I hold you eyes in my head I remember your voice  But do you remember mine? This is like out of the movies But I am the one who losses all  What if I could win? Would I be the head honcho? Or would I still be who I am  The one who can’t take “No.”  I’d do anything for you to notice  When I am around But you could care less I see The vacant expression is showing And I know when to say quit But you and I both know that I won’t let you go Well when all is said and all is done I will still be standing  When all is defeated and has been overcome I will still be standing  I will be waiting for you   
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s Friday night Time for us to put on our show This has become routine Are we growing into our roles? My act has become overused This worn-out mask I wear is growing thin I think I should go But that face you give It keeps me in my place And I give in with no trace of deception Seemed she never wanted me at all Seems the finer things she required All the gems that couldn’t buy her Were they put to good use? Or did she use them like she used me? Let’s forget tonight Leave this all behind Start over new, fresh and reborn But are growing into break ups? My act has become overcharged You never gave me the benefit of the doubt I never wanted out, but you seemed to have changed Let’s rearrange our settings But I’m betting you’re not thinking the same She never wanted me at all Seems the finer things she required All the gems that couldn’t buy her Were they put to good use? Or did she use them like she used me? Did she use them like she used me? (I’m on her string) Did she use them like she used me?  
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is my heart “For Sale” nailed for viewing Here is my apology “I won’t take back the words I said You know I was right.” You lied in saying we’d make it until the end Well I’m recyclable to you You use me over and over Thank you, come again  Here is my face “Caution when wet” tears cascading Here is my finale “I promise this will be it for me And you today.” Well you lied in saying we wouldn’t follow the trend I must seem reusable to you You use me over and over Thank you, come again  Why do I put myself through this? Time and time again I put myself through this pain I build up my downfall Thinking you’d change I change myself to seem better to you  And you lied when you said we’d still be friends Well I’m reconstructed from the pieces you’ve broken me into  You use me over and over Thank you, come again Thank you, come again Thank you, come again  
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kiss me once, just for good luck Then maybe you’ll see things more clearly Hold me tighter, until I feel suffocated Or at least pretend you’re holding me more dearly One day has gone by And still I fight these cries that the telephone is giving, so unforgiving One river that runs dry Washed away all my lies that I’ve been saying, that you find riveting So kiss me once, just for good luck Then maybe you’ll see things more clearly Hold me tighter, until I feel suffocated Or at least pretend you’re holding me more dearly Tell all your friends that we just reacquainted  And go ahead and fake it one more time Tell them lies, recline on the edge of this world And go ahead and rock this boat one more time Two days have passed by And I give in with no sigh, but let it overtake me, I’m over aching Two streams that intertwine Hold the same tears that gave a sign of how I am feeling, I’m over faking Kiss me once, just for good luck Then maybe you’ll see things more clearly Hold me tighter, until I feel suffocated Or at least pretend you’re holding me more dearly Don’t let the door hit you on your way out Cause by now I hope you know I won’t hold it for you Keep those secrets and bad deeds Live a lie and away from me, keep all those who adore you Don’t let the door hit you on your way out Cause by now I hope you know I won’t hold it for you Keep those secrets and bad deeds Live a lie, away from me, keep all those who adore you  
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tell all your friends that you just ended it for us Laugh about it, make up your stories I hope that you are happy now, cause I am down I want that note back, that Love Letter that has somehow found its way into your drawer I also would like back my heart, or unless you have secretly kept that too Just give it back, back to me when you are through It seems we are all we have, and I want you back so damn bad But this masquerade is a never-ending process And you think that you’re fooling everyone, but you aren’t fooling me  Keep your door closed, and keep all my clothes I don’t want them back- Your scent still lingers on them And that aroma you left still surrounds my bed Like a pheromone ghost, it still haunts my head I can’t stand it any longer It’s a never-ending road, that only seems to get farther And I have lost touch with love  Tell all your friends that you didn’t know what you saw in me Cause I don’t know either, but what would I care? I hope that you are lonesome too, cause I am  I want back that hat that I always wore And that jean jacket that seems to be torn  It’s almost as if you tore out my heart I throw out my notebook that I’ve had since 8th grade It’s filled with our notes, yeah it was great But this masquerade is a never-ending process And you think that you’re fooling everyone, but you aren’t fooling me  Keep your door closed, and keep all my clothes I don’t want them back- Your scent still lingers on them And that aroma you left still surrounds my bed Like a pheromone ghost, it still haunts my head I can’t stand it any longer It’s a never-ending road, that only seems to get farther And I have lost touch with love  You know, what they say has finally come true I never knew what I had until I lost you You were my jewel, gave me such pleasure One man’s trash is another man’s treasure And I treasured you that best I could Even if you never understood all my intentions that I held close To my heart, but I fear the most, it happened everyday And that aroma you left still surrounds my bed Like a pheromone ghost, it still haunts my head I can’t stand it any longer It’s a never-ending road, that only seems to get farther And I have lost touch with love Can you bring me back to love? 
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that we just had our secret rendezvous, but it’s a killer when you must leave These feelings that I’ve been holding back are needing to be released And if I say them it seems like another déjà vu,  It must be because there was another “It’s me, not you.” How much more, I wonder, can this relationship withstand?   We’ve survived some of our hardships, and this time our bleedings can’t be mended I used to be the cure you’d use, but now I am your tool to abuse And say you’re not alone, but I am alone (on my own) I get lost in your eyes, they capture me with their trances, a trend you intended to follow Hope you are happy, I am hollow and falling away  Another night wasted And I am wasting away, blowing in the wind like a futile flag I am just a one-time memento, a souvenir And it’s tearing my seams, and all seems black   I just need to be rolled up and put away until you need me again It’s cold out here, in this place, and I can’t survive this season It used to be the time of romance, yeah, our time to spread or buds and grow But we seem to be rotting to the core, trampled on and buried deep in the snow I received your letter, it was delivered on time this time It was only three words, not the three that I used to love to say “I Hate You.” written on the paper, should’ve been written in stone And now it’s you’re fault you’re alone, but I still am alone (on my own) I get lost in your eyes, they capture me with their trances, a trend you intended to follow Hope you are happy, I am hollow and falling away  Another night wasted And I am wasting away, blowing in the wind like a futile flag I am just a one-time memento, a souvenir And it’s tearing my seams, and all seems black  Another night wasted And I am wasting away, blowing in the wind like a futile flag I am just a one-time memento, a souvenir And it’s tearing my seams, and all seems black   I know that we just had our secret rendezvous, but it’s a killer when you must leave These feelings that I’ve been back are needing to be released, suppressed without much ease And if I say them it seems like another déjà vu,  It must be because there was another “It’s me, not you.”  
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Breaking up Breaking up all the good times that we had Taking up Taking up all the time I was thinking we could spend   Well at least you said we could stay as friends At least, you said, the phone calls won’t have to end But that phone call never came, and I haven’t been the same since you left me  Making up Making up stories just so you don’t have to come over Waking up Waking up alone but with that note you left me on your pillowcase  “I’ve had enough, I just can’t take this anymore.”  But you said we’d still talk every once-in-awhile Occasionally, I’d hoped you’d stay true to your word  So this is just a phase that can’t be mended now I’m just a hopeless romantic, I can’t break out And so this is the end of this relationship What a shame, what a shame  Break down Break down that overhanging light, that seemed to shine for you Bring me down Bring me down cause I just caught up in all of you  Well at least you said we could stay as friends At least, you claimed, we could try it all again But it seems that I have thrown it all away, while I’ve been waiting for you I’ve had enough, I just can’t take this anymore  But you said we’d still talk every once-in-awhile Occasionally, I’d hoped you’d stay true to your word So this is just a phase that can’t be mended now I guess I’m just a hopeless romantic, and I can’t break out And so this is the end of this relationship What a shame, what a shame  And so this is the end of this relationship What a shame, what a shame And so this is the end of another relationship What a shame, what a shame  
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alarm is ringing, time to start my day again What will happen? Or is it just another daily routine? No surprises, just a tedious expedition into my unknown Is there a way to push rewind? If there is I want to set my world back to then When you came, changed me the way  The way that it felt to be alive  Six forty-five The day isn’t getting older, just stays bleak I am so tired of this custom Maybe I will find you and it will all be okay Maybe  Phone is ringing, time to beckon some willingness to be What will occur? Or is this another call of someone just like me No amazement, just a dreading thread that pulls me into the web Am I just a little overdue? Cause sometimes I feel like I’ve been a little overused When will you come home? And can you change me?  Change me into the way that it felt to be alive  Six forty-five The day isn’t getting older, just stays bleak I am so tired of this custom Maybe I will find you and it will all be okay Maybe Maybe I will just be ‘okay’  Interesting how it all turned out Seems to real to think that this is my life But they say that it’s not the end of the world Well it’s the end of the universe to me,  And I still don’t feel like I am alive  Six forty-five The day isn’t getting older, just stays bleak I am so tired of this custom Maybe I will find you and it will all be okay Maybe Six forty-five The day isn’t getting older, just stays bleak I am so tired of this custom Maybe I will find you and it will all be okay Maybe Maybe Maybe I will just be ‘okay’ Maybe it might seem I am on the menu to start over yet again  
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know when I’m not wanted It’s when I am wanted I am not prompt It’s an inconsistency, such an inconvenience   But it’s like you say you’re here But to me your sound is muted Guess I should’ve of seen it all along Guess this shouldn’t be a song Cause what’s the point?  When no one sings I can write these words, but do you know what they mean? Well I mean the best, you mean the worst I can’t decipher your meanings or codes Well I was last, you were first I can make it to the finish line on my own I know when I’m not wanted It’s when I am wanted I am not prompt This is my last goodbye This is my last farewell 
    
</post>


</Blog>