<Blog>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "The British government has learned that Saddam Hussein recently sought significant quantities of uranium from Africa."  Again the following is a quote from www.realchange.org in which it states,  The "16 words" spin reveals just how shameless their lies are. Short lies don't matter? Well, Clinton got charged for just 8 words -- "I did not have sex with that woman." Even by that ridiculous standard, Bush is twice as big a liar as Bill Clinton.  The uranium allegation (the "16 words") is famous because the fraud is so obvious. That charge, which Bush stated directly in his State of the Union speech, was based on blatantly forged documents -- one purported to be from a Niger official, to himself. The Bush Administration knew they were forged. They had been told several times that the charges were false, including by our own CIA and State Department. Bush and his top aides fought to put the words back in his speech, using weaselly phrasing -- Defense Secretary Rumsfeld has actually argued that the statement wasn't a lie because Bush didn't SAY Iraq did try to buy uranium, he just said "British intelligence HAS LEARNED that they tried to buy uranium." Once again, Bush imitates Clinton, arguing about what the meaning of "is" is.  There were many other deceptive charges by the Bush administration -- about unmanned drones, orders to use chemical weapons, aluminum tubes, links between Iraq and Al Qaeda, etc. But don't forget the big picture. The Bush administration knew that there were no WMD in Iraq. They deliberately and consistently lied to the American people about this, to justify war in Iraq. And 300 US soldiers have died as a result.  This is just the start to the terror and lies that Bush has brought to use there is much much more so be smart and make sure to know the truth about the American President because a lot that affects the US effects us.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If only people realized how little they actually need to do to make the world a better place then people wouldnt have such a hard time doing it and really if people only understood that theres no shame in caring for the world then people wouldnt be afraid to do it and if people realized that what they do to the world will eventually come back to haunt them, well maybe not them but their children or their childrens children, they would actually WANT to care about the world so spread the word to help clean up the earth and over time you'll see a difference.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      George Bush likes to present himself as a straight-talking, regular guy. But it's an act -- regular guys don't go to Andover Prep, Yale and Harvard Business School, and straight-talking guys don't pretend to be regular guys after growing up in one of the most privileged homes in world history. Not only was Bush's dad president, his grandpa was a U.S. Senator and wealthy Wall Street banker, and his mom's blueblood family owned (among other things) the estate in Maine that Bush still hangs out at.   Now, as Bush's regular guy act is wearing thin, some of his other deceptions are becoming more obvious.  This quote was taken directly from http://www.realchange.org/bushjr.htm  Therefore more proof that bush is not what he seems  And this was taken from http://www.tarpley.net/bush1.htm  Who is George Bush? How did he become the 41st U.S. President?   He is said to be a man of the "old establishment," who "chose to seek his fortune as an independent oilman...." @s1   In fact, Bush was never "independent." Every career step in his upward climb relied on his family's powerful associations. The Bush family joined the Eastern Establishment comparatively recently, and only as servitors. Their wealth and influence resulted from their loyalty to another, more powerful family, and their willingness to do anything to get ahead.   Believe what you will but i say that George Dubya Bush is a phony and is not who he says he is.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Newly discovered... George Dubya Bush is like cancer. He grows were he isnt supposed to, he's not wanted by anyone, anywhere, he destroys everything ithat gets in the way of what he's after AND he cant be stopped until they attemp to remove him.  Bush should have a live porcupine shoved up his A$$ and then covered in fire ants and given the flesh eating disease and then while he is recovering someone should pour gasoline on his bedsheets and set him on fire AND THEN put him out and let him live a little longer only so he has time to say goodbye before someone shoots him in the funking head
    
</post>


</Blog>