<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It would be a couple of months until I heard from her again. Between June and December, I spent my time slogging away, trying to get a degree. And Gadafi kept me informed.  "She's one really smart girl. I can't believe she's like only 16. She's like my big sister. Actually better than my big sister. She rocks man."  Yeah, I could believe that. The hour I spent with her was enough to convince me that she wasn't your ordinary teenager.  So when I got home that Christmas break, I made sure to touch base with her.   [Hythiris] Hey there. Remember me?   [Sweething] Hmmm.. you sound familiar. *wink*   [Hythiris] Do I?   [Sweething] Hehehe, hey there Far!      She was still the same girl I met six months ago. That night, we chatted for hours. And when we logged off, I made her call me. And we talked some more.  Before I realised it, a week had passed. With us talking every single night.  Talking to her was like looking in the mirror. And I was amazed that I had found a bosom friend in a girl 8 years my junior.  Another week had passed. And we still hadn't run out of things to talk about. Gadafi would laugh when I told him about our phone marathons.  "Yeah, man. She's awesome. Be careful though. She's still a kid."  I laughed.  "You spoke to her recently? Or have you been busy with that new babe of yours?"  Gadafi choked. Coughing, he took a deep breath before answering.  "How did you know?  Ni mesti si Myra bagitau ni. Tak guna tul budak tu !"  " Eh. Tak guna tak guna pun, dia tolong intro, kau yang untung . I hear the babe's hot stuff.  Cerita ah sikit !"  " Cerita? Aisehman, ni yang susah ni. Nak cerita apa?  She's Myra's classmate. Came online once and Myra pointed her out to me. So that's it."  Man, this guy must think I'm dumb. Or hoping I'll just back off. Not gonna happen, mate!  " Cun tak? Intro sikit kat aku !"  "No way man! She's mine for now. When I'm done, I'll let you meet her. Gorgeous chick!  Langsung tak macam Myra . In every way. Don't know how they ended up being friends."  So Myra gave me her undivided attention. And I gave her mine. And, funny enough, this is where the story really begins. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      She had the most appealing laugh. Full bodied, throaty. Not like the twittering giggles some girls affected.  "Guys, I have to go. My parents don't know I'm out. If I'm caught, I'll be deadmeat."  I looked at my watch. It was only 9.45 pm, barely an hour from when we had gotten seats and started talking. Gadafi too looked at his watched.  "Aww, come on Myra. It's not even 10 yet. Just chill babe. Where you staying?"  I looked at Gadafi. Was he trying to make his move? Myra wasn't his type though. She was chubby, at the very least. And about 3 years too young. Then again, with Gadafi, you can never tell. I turned to Myra, who started whispering to a girl seated next to her. Rose-or-something.  "Not far. About 10 minutes from here. Taman Bunga Raya. But my parents are at my dad's office dinner and I don't know what time they'll be back. And I have to get back before they do."  Gadafi groaned. For the full effect, I groaned too.  "Aw man, that's like so close. We can drop you off later.  Kan , Far? Saves you a taxi and you'll get to hang out with us for a while still."  I could tell that Myra was wavering. She leaned over to her friend and whispered some more. Shaking her head, she got up.  "Sorry guys. Rita and I really need to go. I can't afford to stay any longer."  Gadafi's cigarette was poised above the ashtray.  "You want us to send you home?"  Myra shook her head.  "Sokay. We'll find our way home. It was nice to finally meet you G-man. Err, Gadafi. You're exactly like what I thought you would be."  And then she turned to me.  "And it was nice meeting you too, Fariz. Maybe one day we'll bump into each other online."  I nodded. Who knew?    
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Hi there. I'm Fariz. Go by the nick Hythiris. And you are?"  The girl blinked at me, then covertly&nbsp;looked left and right before looking down at my outstretched hand and shaking it.  "Hi. I'm Myra. Erm.. Sweething. New chatter actually. Well, quite new. But I've been here for a couple of months. Erm.. well sorta..."  She blushed as her voice trailed off.   "I should just shut up. Before I bury myself completely."  That caught my attention. She had spirit. Perhaps the evening wouldn't be a complete waste.  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "She did what????"  Instantly, I regretted asking. It was like rubbing salt to the wound. And he didn't need any more pain.  "Forget her, man. She ain't worth it."  I couldn't believe Gadafi was so depressed. He was the coolest guy I knew. G-man, they called to him as he breezed past the entrances of some of the most happening clubs in town. Girls flocked to him like bees to honey. And man, has he had some fine pieces over the years. But he was always the one to leave. Always the one who kept them coming back and crying for more.  And this was the guy who was quietly sobbing on the other end of the phone.  "Man, Far, you don't know this chick. She's different from the others. She ain't some two-bit cheap ass you can find on the dancefloor. She's got class and beauty. Oh God! And her smell would drive me insane everytime she passed by. Damn man! I don't know what to do! I got to have her back! I need her man! I need her!"  I could hear him hitting his head on the wall as he sobbed.  "Stop it man! Get a grip! It's just some bitch! Plenty more like her out there. What you on about? If she turned you down, she must be a dumb bitch too! And dumb bitches are the worst!"  And perhaps the tears became a bit too much for him, or maybe the words were too harsh. But I found myself listening to beeping of a dead line. Grimly, I replaced the phone.  "Stupid Bitch!"       
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Look, I can't deal with this anymore, okay?"  I looked at her, dazed. It was as though my brain had gone on a mini-break without telling me. I could see her lips moving and her hands gesturing wildly, but I couldn't get my head round the words.   She turned to me, her hair flying and her eyes wild. Her hands were fidgeting now and I could tell she wasn't sure whether she should look at me.&nbsp;Abruptly,&nbsp;she fell to her knees in front of me and grabbed my hand.   "You and I.. This... We're not meant to be together. Can't you see that?"  I looked down at her hands in mine. At that point, all I could think of was that our hands fitted well, with her fairness contrasting my dark tones. And I could feel my head screaming at the inanity of it all.   For a moment,&nbsp;it was quiet. All we could hear were the birds that occasionally flew by and the leaves that rustled gently with the passing breeze. And in that silence, I thought I could feel her softening. Relenting. Maybe it would all be okay.  "Tina..."  Wrenching her hand from me, she got up, screaming.  "Fuck you Fariz! I won't have you manipulating me anymore! You can't! I won't stand for it! I won't!"  The chill came out of nowhere, now creeping up my spine and enveloping my body. Just give her space. She'll cool down. She always does.  "I don't understand,  sayang . What's going on? Why are you so upset with me? Come on, let's be civilised about this.  Mari kita bawak berbincang ."  For a fleeting moment, I could have sworn that she looked confused. Almost dazed. Like she didn't know where she was or what she was doing. But I looked again and it was gone. Maybe I had imagined it. Wishful thinking. Hoping it was a nightmare. But this seething girl in front of me was real. Very real.  "Forget it, Fariz. We're through. And if you ever come near me again, I'll tell the police that you're stalking me. Accept it! Live with it! I never, ever want to see you again!"  And with that, my whole world came crashing down.  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sometimes you think that life will always wait for you. Well, not really wait. But that it will never leave you behind, floundering, drowning. That somehow, it will pick you up and put you back on that raft that's sailing slowly to nowhere. Or wherever it is you think you're going to get to sooner or later. Later rather than sooner.   Perhaps I would have never admitted it. After all, who would want to be perceived as being cocky, arrogant, over-confident. Even the word complacent has such a negative connotation. That smug knowledge that things will always work out in the end. And that life will be happy.   It never crossed my mind that some people died completely and utterly miserable.   Until the day my boat started rocking and I fell overboard.   
      
</post>


<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We've always been taught to obey instructions. Even from young, we are able to identify 'figures of authority'. Obedience being a virtue that is touted by most society. Law-abiding citizens and all that jazz.  But once upon a time, a teacher of ours gave us the chance to see things in a different light.   It was one of those general course classes where a student was given three weeks in a subject outside their area of study. One week it would be Home Economics, another week would be Religious studies. Sometimes the subject would be a complete bore. But sometimes, like this one class in particular, it would prove to have an effect on us years after we've flown the nest, so to speak.   During the first of the three classes, ridiculous assignments were set. Some laughed, others shook their heads. But we did it nonetheless. And then, right before the bell went, she asked us one important question - Why did we do it?   In the next class, she opened by talking to us about how we are socially conditioned to obey instructions without question. She brought up the  urlLink study  done by  Stanley Milgram.  They set out to prove that people would follow instructions from a 'figure of authority' even if it conflicted with their own moral values. The following is a brief description of the test (taken from the site linked above)        "There were two subjects in the experiment, an actual subject and an actor pretending to be another subject. The experimenter informed the subjects that they were going to be participants in a study to examine how effective punishment was for learning particular behaviors. The subject was assigned the role of "teacher." The actor was also assigned the role of "teacher" but claimed that his role was that of a "learner" so that the subject would believe that his role had been randomly assigned to him. Both the subject and the actor were given a sample 45-volt electric shock administered by an apparatus strapped to the actor's chair. The "teacher" was told to present simple memory tasks to the "leaner" and to administer an electric shock each time the learner made a mistake with the task.  
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      No, I am not a first time blogger. In fact, I've been around for a while now. Quite a while indeed.  No, this isn't me trying to change who I am by starting anew. Really.  No, this isn't an attempt at achieving fame with cheap drama and an air of mystery.   What is it then?  It's just a nice change.  So here's to hoping it will last. 
     
    
</post>



</Blog>