<Blog>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Welcome to another addition to The X Blog(DUN DUN DUN...). Cryptozoology is the study of undiscovered animals. There are many people out there who study these unknown species. Some call themselves "cryptozoologists", although one can not achieve a degree in the field. (Cryptozoology is not recognized as a true science.) People search for evidence of these creatures for one main reason: to find the truth. They commit time and resources in order to further the quest for answers, hunting for clues with a passion to discover the reclusive relics of nature known as CRYPTIDS.     Cryptids come in all shapes and sizes. From the 'Death Worm' to Nessie, there are hundreds if not thousands of "undiscovered" species. The more popular ones include Bigfoot, Yeti, the Loch Ness Monster(Nessie) and the Jersey Devil. I'll try to focus on a few of their little-known bretheren: the Mokele Mbeme, the Chupacabra,and the Beast of Gevaudan. The Mokele Mbeme supposedly is the size of an elephant with a long neck and a tail like a crocodile. It dwells in the Likouala swamps and Lake Tele in Congo, killing any human that dares come near. It does not eat its prey.     The Chupacabra, however, sucks all blood and life from livestock and other creatures unlucky enough to cross its path.( The direct translation of "Chupacabra" is "goat sucker". ) It is a bipedal animal 4 or 5 feet tall equipped with two short, clawed arms and almost reptilian hindlegs. It can reportedly jump quite efficiently and fly. It originated in Puerto Rico, but there have been sightings everywhere from the US to Chile. It resides underneath the soil in caves. Some believe it is from the future or another dimension, but this theory is recent. The killings attributed to Chupacabras are almost surgical(certain organs were removed in each,there were trace scalpel cuts), leading me to believe that the victims could have been the subjects of unauthorized livestock experimentation.(That's just my opinion...)     Another interesting cryptid is the Beast of Gevaudan. This cow-sized wolf-like monster terrorized the district of Gevaudan, France from June 1764 to June 19th 1767. It began attacking locals in June 1764 when it mauled a young woman, who miraculously escaped. From then on it gained a reputation as a werewolf, a demon, and many other things including a punishment sent by God. On September 21st, 1765, King Louis sent his best gunman, Antoine de Beauterne, on a massive hunt for the Beast. He was successful in killing a 6-foot long wolf believed responsible, yet the attacks continued. In desperation, hundreds of peasants from the district made a pilgrimage to Notre-Dame de Beaulieu Cathedral in the summer of 1767. One of the peasants was a man named Jean Chastel. He had his gun and three bullets blessed. On June 19th, he shot the Beast in a clearing with 300 onlookers. The killings stopped, and the Beast of Gevaudan was later concluded to be a striped hyena, native to Africa. It's an early example of mistaken identity and tradgedy in the cryptozoological world.     To conclude our look at cryptozoology, here are a few tips and pointers for the person looking to study these elusive creatures. Number one, don't pursue this as a serious career or academic venture. (Do not contact your local university for info about their cryptozoology department!) Number two, don't let your new endeavor control your life, become an obsession, or otherwise consume you completely. (This happens to some hermits and whackos. Beware...) Third, if you are pursuing a zoological career, do not let your interest in cryptozoology interfere with job oppurtunities. So basically, keep your interest low-key, but also actively pursue it. Keep the quest alive.          
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am open to all commentary and suggestions. In fact, I want you to e-mail me with topics you'd like to see and any other suggestions, themes, etc. So send your thoughts to: saralynfoster@hotmail.com SUBMIT!SUBMIT!SUBMIT!RESISTENCE IS FUTILE!MUWAHAHAHAHA!
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         To me, telekinesis(or psychokenesis) is a very interesting phenomenon. Behind it is the concept that one can convert the electromagnetic energy within their brain to kinetic energy used to manipulate outside matter. By these means one could move, bend, break and reshape anything.     There are many skeptics out there. With this in mind, some believers have conducted solid scientific research to prove the reality of telekinesis. James A. Conrad is one of them. He has worked for over twenty years in a specialized TK(telekinesis) laboratory, during which time he has come up with an equation that explains telekinetic ability: TK = CFe +VC +ZPE -SD - E+. It is known as the Conrad Telekinesis Formula. This equation states that telekinetic ability can be achieved through CFe - sufficient cerebral iron, +VC - visual contact, +ZPE - zero point emotions, -SD - no sleep deprivation,and -E+ - no excess vitamin E. His formula is based on testing he has done on himself including blood tests and other experiments. Conrad treats TK as an evolutionary trait that all humans are capable of, and believes that it is gene and brain-chemistry related.     Some spiritualists have different views, as the belief in TK as tapping into the universal Chi(life energy) and projecting it as kinetic energy. Either way, it is the same basic concept.    Whatever your personal belief, there are many tutorials and exercises you can utilize to develop your TK abilities. One such routine is to practice by bending a spoon or fork. In order for it to produce results, you should relax and hold the utensil in one hand. Next, stay focused and clear your mind of all chatter, clutter and noise. Rub your fingertips over the object's surface and try to get into the flow of its energy. Feel, don't think. Once you have gotten into the energy flow, simply bend the spoon, fork,etc. But don't actually apply force to the object. Just bend. Imagine your energy and the spoon's energy uniting, and then bend it. This is supposed to take a few tries, so remember to keep a positive attitude!   
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello and welcome. This is my first post here, so please forgive the lack of content. This blog will hopefully house a great deal of information in time. 
    
</post>


</Blog>