<Blog>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok well by the time i finish this entry it will be WAY past 3:27 but w.e. Im gonna post about me... Name:: Lauren Birthday:: March 18th Eye Color:: Blue Hair Color:: Dirty blone/brown...with blonde highlights Weight:: 113 Shoe Size:: 8 Name of your school:: Soon to be Forest Hill...(i think i might have to hire Vincent as a bodyguard) Do you Wear contacts?:: no Where were you born?:: Delaware How much did you weigh when you were born?:: no clue (what kind of ? is that??)  Do you have a retainer?:: nope!  Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend?:: no...: ( What color was your hair when you were born?:: u dont have hair when ur born...and if u do it was most likely light brown  *~*FaMiLy*~*  Are your parents Married or Divorced?:: divorced How many siblings do you have?:: 1 What are their name(s)?:: Connor Do you have any step brothers/sisters?:: nope Get along with your family?:: hahahahahahahahahahahahahaha *continues for 3 pages* Age difference between you and your siblings?:: 5 years Favorite cousin?:: ok well all of my cousins are tiny but the one closest in age would be missy (melissa).   Daddy or Momma's boy/girl?:: haha well my dads the one who buys me everything i value teehee Do your parents spoil you?:: once again....my dad yes...mom NOO How many people live in your house?:: 4 Do you have family get togethers?:: of course but it has to be a special occasion...my family is full of blondes who are loud and obnoxious and u can hear them a mile away Do you like your dad or mom's side of the family better?:: umm....my moms Does your older brother/sister boss you around?:: haha nope cuz i AM the oldest...i do it ALL hunn Do you like your family?:: hehe sometimes  *~*FrIeNdS*~*  4 best girl friends:: hmm Sam, Morgan, Kendall, Alysia, and Clara (sorri i couldnt onlii pick 4!!) 4 best guy friends:: Xavier, Esteban, Brandon, and Jesse Easiest to talk to?:: Umm Morgan or Sam Gives best advice?:: Clara Craizest?:: Alysia...HAHA Considers your family theirs?:: Sam You consider their family yours?:: Morgan Loudest?:: Me...lol but out of friends then hmm Morgan or Alysia Most athletic?:: Sam definately Hottest?:: out of guys or girls? cuz its kinda wrong to ask me about girls lol...but out of guyz...i dno Best Personalities?:: umm All of us Would do anything for you and vice versa?:: All of my BEST friends Knows you the best? You know the best?:: Morgan, Sam, and Kendall  *~*ReLaTiOnShIpS*~*  Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend?:: No... What's their name?:: N/A...lol How long have you known them?:: N?A Your anniversary?:: N/A Are you in love?:: N/A Have you ever been in love?:: yeaa Who have you been in love with?:: Brandon How many boyfriends/girlfriends have you had?:: haha...one...two...three...seven (maybe more)!!! Have you ever had sex?:: ok...age=14, age to have sex=at least not until im 14 1/2 JKJK no like 17 With who?: im not 17 yet i cant tell you Do you want to stay with your current boyfriend/girlfriend?:: no lol Do they love you?:: how the H should i know?  *~*HaVe YoU eVeR...*~*  Held your breath until you passed out?:: nope...almost did when singing though lol Wanted to die?:: yeaa....but shhhhh! Smoked weed?:: nope Commited a crime?:: nope Saved someones life?:: No... Stayed up all night?:: yeaa Been to another country?:: does the bahamas count?? (im with Kels lol) Loved someone so much it made you cry?:: of course Been cheated on?:: i thought so once but it turned out they didnt Let someone else take the blame for something you did?:: yeaa but i felt REALLY REALLY bad about it! Faked being sick?:: haha if someone hasnt they NEED to learn...its the best Driven Illeagly?:: yeaa Been to the Astrodome?:: the as-dra-what? Dyed your hair?:: no but i get highlights  *~*ThIs Or ThAt*~*  Hot/Cold:: cold Sun/Rain:: rain...i love the rain! Night/Day:: night Guys/Girls:: for relationships guys, friendships, either Lust/Love:: love Car/Truck?:: car Laptop/Computer:: labtop Kiss/Making out:: it depends...i mean if its just to show that ur still there and love them then just a simple kiss will do but if otherwise then make-out Dr.Pepper/Coke:: Dr.Pepper Summer/Winter:: Winter Lake/Ocean:: Ocean Prep/Goth:: prep Basketball/Football:: football  *~*Favorites*~*  Color:: pink Number:: 13 Animal:: cat Web Site:: ummm www.opendiary.com Food?:: WAY too hard to say!! lol but probly pasta Football team?:: Hurricanes for college and Patriots  Thing to do?:: to be able to hang out with friends and not HAVE to do anything...i think its the best for some reason Sport to watch?:: if im forced to? lol Sport to play?:: if im forced to? Holiday:: Christmas Friend:: dont have one...i have 5 lol Place to go:: the beach TV show:: dno...whatevers on lol Place to eat:: probly cheescake factory or Sailfish Marina  *~*RaNdOmS*~*  How many pillows are on your bed?:: i used to have like 7 but now i only have about 4 What color is your toothbrush?:: i dno what color it is...its a wierd color lol What brand of toothpaste do you use?:: whatever my mom buys How old will you be when you graduate High School?:: 18  What is on your desktop?:: thats mine? Kazaa, Musicmatch, AOL, AIM, and solitaire lol Have you ever been to a tailgate party?:: no but we tailgate at the football games Gotten kicked out of Wal-Mart?:: haha i could onlii imagine what ud have to go to get thrown out of there...lol!! Have you ever sat on Santa's lap?:: hmm...yess Gotten money from the tooth fairy?:: yeaa Do you have an online journal?:: umm no i dont think so *sarcasm* Do you love someone?:: not right now, no Who?:: n/a What channel is your TV on?:: probly like...nickelodeon or some stupid show my bro is watching Do you Like George Strait?:: ?????  *~*RiGhT nOw*~*  What time is it?:: 10:38 (damn i need to go to bad lol) What are you wearing?:: night clothes How is your hair done?:: its not lol What color are your socks?:: what sox Who are you talking to?:: kris and clara When was your last kiss?:: ............hmm......... Who hugged you last?:: umm i think Sam Last word you said:: Sam (lol) Color of your nails?:: clear (i onlii do clear when they look pritti) Do you have make-up on?:: nope What color are your shoestrings?:: when i wear sneakers? white... What's the date?:: July 1st What time is it?:: 3:40
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Something's messed up with the clock on my journal/blog and i tried to fix it but it wont work..if u wanna know the time just look at my heading mmk? I got home from work like...2 hrs ago and have slept eversince THATS how tired I am. That place makes u s0o exhausted by the end of the day...its insane. thank god i have tomoro off pretty much. DAMN i forgot to ask for my money today!! i didnt get paid AGGHH!! NOW im gonna freakin die..i HATE this. not to mention i dno if i can even go to kendalls right after the ortho cuz i might have to watch my bro since my dad just HAS to go back to work and screw up plans ive had for two weeks. Damn him. I gtg much love~~Laur
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok Well I have many, many journals just to test which one i like the best. I really didnt know there were so many sites that you can have a journal/diary/blog on...but believe me there are. Xanga, Blogger, OpenDiary, Livejournal, etc. etc. Well im @ work again (can u believe im 14 and i have to work over summer? s0o0o sadd huh? i barely even HAVE a summer...two weeks at camp thats it. Thats my summer. lol. thats so pathetic. Im pissed at Mike right now if hes the one who went on a sn like seth's. Thats so irritating and petty. I mean that just proves guys are worse than girls when it comes to not liking someone. Its amazing how many ppl waste time online (i cant talk i do it too...of course) but it realli is. imagine what the world would be like without the internet. I certainly couldnt. 10 days until camp woo-hoo!! i REALLY cant wait, its gonna be awesome. Morgan you BETTER save me one of the bottom bunks in the back! Well i gtg ill write later. Mwahz xoxo~~Laur
     

    
</post>


</Blog>