<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The weeks have gone by too quickly.  Bernadette is getting ready to take her annual trek to Pennsic War.  It's been several years since I've been to Pennsic.  I really miss it.  So, why am I not going?  Because someone has to stay to take care of the kids.  Why not Bernadette?  Because SHE has not missed a Pennsic and she likes it so much... Basically, because Bernadette comes first.  She's happy that I am still unemployed because it means that she does not have to find a temporary babysitter for the kids.  If I had the funds, I would take the kids to see my family in Colorado.  That's what we did last year when we couldn't find a sitter for the kids for Pennsic.  If my parents weren't going to be in Colorado for those two weeks, I would pack the kids up and go visit them in Iowa.  I've been thinking about looking for a job there since I can't find something here.  I'm starting to get frustrated about looking for a job.  Every interview I go on seems to go ok - I get great feedback about my resume and past experience.  Only once has anyone given me negative feedback, and that was with regards to the outfit I chose to wear that day. (Not Business enough for the company)   

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today was another of what is turning out to be a typical day for me.  I got up late, after staying up late with the 6 month old.  She's got her days and nights mixed up, so I haven't even been getting to bed until 4 or 5 in the morning.  This has messed up my natural bio-rythms just a bit.  I do much better if I'm up early (like before 7am) and work heavily until about noon or 1.  Husband made me breakfast (knock me over);  Blueberry pancakes from scratch and sausage.  Something is up because she's not that nice.  That's right, I said SHE.  My husband is a M2F transsexual (we will come back to this at a later time)  I thought maybe she had something to tell me, but if that was the case, she decided not to.  I should have thanked her, but I forgot.  That's my fault.  Since I'm still looking for a job, getting dressed was a necessity.  I applied to a local car dealership today.  Doubt if they want me, though.  Don't get me wrong, I can do the job - and I would be good at it.  But I don't exactly have the right "look".  I mean, I'm not exactly pretty, I'm overweight, and I don't drive a good looking car.  After that, I dropped by the hospital to inquire about a position for my husband, at her request.    After I did that, I bought a can of formula for my daughter, a soda for myself, and went home.  The "strays" were waiting for me when I got home.  The strays are the neighborhood cats that adopted us.  There have been just two, but recently, there has been one more.  The most wonderfull kitten has joined the ranks, but the others have not accepted her yet.  Shadow, my "slut" cat, rules the roost.  Her daughter, Feisty, runs a close second.  Neither cat is very loving (unless you have food) but they both like to be pet.  The new cat has been dubbed "Purry" by the kids, but I've taken to calling her Cammo (short for camoflage; she is a calico, but patterned like army clothing).  If there was a cat that we would take with us when we finally leave this place, Cammo would be the one.   Cats are important to me.  I used to have several house cats, but had to give them up when we moved into this place.  I'm empathic, and sometimes people's emotions mix with mine so much I need to sort them out.  And cat's help me to do this.  More specifically, the vibration of their purr relaxes me like nothing else, and helps me to sort out my emotions from everybody else's.  And being without this has contributed to the damage to my soul.  I'm going to go thank Bernadette for breakfast.  Better late than never, right?  --kyn   

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What is it they say,... today is the first day of the rest of your life.   And so it is.    I had reservations about doing this, but I needed a place where I could post and be me.  My life and lifestyle are such that I am constantly hiding at least a part of me from everybody.  These days, even from my husband - if you can call him that any more.  My husband thinks I'm a very negative person; that I don't have any happy thoughts ever.  He says that I dwell on the worst-case senario.  Making any plans at all is stressful for me.  I was trained to hope for the best and prepare for the worst.  For the last 5 years, it's what I did for a living.  It put a roof over our head, and food on the table.  And Husband makes fun of it all the time.  I take great paines to not say anything when plans are made these days because if I even open my mouth, Hubby says, "That's right, look for the worst."  He also thinks I'm an angry person.  He says that I start growling the minute I come in the door, and I don't stop until I leave for work the next morning... of course, now that I am unemployed, I growl all the time.  He says even the kids don't want to be around me.  Well, the kids don't want to be around me (or more appropriately, the kids don't want me around) because I expect them to finish their homework and chores before they watch TV.  That is not how I really am.  What he is seeing is the result of 6 years of going to work, coming home, and being expected to help with dinner, dishes, clean house, pay bills, do paperwork, check homework, and the myriad of other things I did when I stayed home full-time.  kyn 

						
</post>


</Blog>