<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        While  climbing  mountain      keep your mouth Shut and    avoid    breathing thru Mouth.It helps in retaining moisture within.    Walk like a baby, be prepared to roll on your every step.    keep a pace of walking such that , which you can    continue for whole day .      In rainy season while climbing slippery steep rocks, use rope for protection.    Stand straight while crossing river/stream.Do not sit or bend down while walking for Support.If in Group make a chain.      While  climbing down  any mountain/Hill    1) loosen your Shoes to some extent.It helps to be more flexible and avoids cramps.       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        We all came across in Weekend course on basic Astronomy conducted by mumbai University.Since then very much in touch with most of them.  urlLink  Astrocrazy yahoogroup    acted a vital player in keeping all of us in touch.Its been almost 2.5 years by now and we have spend lot of good time.We started with Lectures by all Astronmy Experts in Mumbai,went for Night SKy Observation at various places at OutSkirts of Mumbai.We also went for treking and usual Restauranting around the city.     &nbsp;   Most of the group memebers are students of Science.But we did had People from various background viz : we had one journalist,Diamond Merchant,Marketing Fellow,retired Scientist and many others.   &nbsp;   One of the guy out there is worth mentioning is Sachin Pilankar.He has come up with huge collection on Astronomy Stuff in Marathi languauge.Do visit his Web Site.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  urlLink  AvakashVedh      &nbsp;  &nbsp;     
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Talib  (working for Toyo (zapanese firm))      Hemant   (works for a US based Diamond merchant)      Sadik   (as of now runs a franchise of ICICI Prudential)      Ramesh   (might join Fire Brigade as of now doing coding on MS platform)      Amit   (did his studies in Geology)     Just yesterday got a news that  Amit  is Joining some Big Oil company, would be working at Jodhpur at the actual Site where they drill for Oil.He always wanted to work on projects where he travells to some weird place and collect samples of various rocks and other earthly stuff.       Hemant   has recently joined a Big/Rich merchant from USA and would be supporting his Diamond Business.He would be in Purchase of Diamonds in Mumbai and will travell to Europe and USa often....sounds good.     &nbsp;     Ramesh   is going to join some traning on .Net technology under  urlLink  Bipin joshi   . &nbsp;   &nbsp;     Sadik   is on lookout for opprtunity where he can make a big scam and make money for his lifetime.   &nbsp;     Talib   is getting married this October, iwould be Travelling with him to Indore for his marriage.     We are meeting for some outing this sunday..some good old mountain to hike together after long time.     
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Its been since years that with every rainy season i get in to treking business.  Peth , peb, Matheran,Bhima Shanker,Chinchoti are some of the all time favourite places.    What to bring   Pack sack  Raincoat or poncho (downpours are frequent)  Boots or comfortable walking shoes Sandals,  &nbsp;for river crossings or around campsite Warm clothing,&nbsp;(a fleece or sweater)  Hat for the sun Sleeping bag Flashlight Sunscreen  Water bottle  Plastic bags for documentation, camera    and a good dose of humor   Whenever you take a halt while climbing, always follow a golden rule.  Once you start leaving the place and get back to climbing, move little distance and then see back at the halt place to check if at all you are forgetting anything out there.  &nbsp;     
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi This is my first blog on bloggers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I came across this mail suggesting things to one person leaving for UK this weekend.      --->    This month is gonna pretty OK but from next months onwards its going to be hell of a cold , so tell her to carry all warm clothes .. jackets n all ,sweaters jo bhi garam kapda hai .. carry one umbrella also :)) u will get good one in India for less price.    * All masala for intial period of stay ..like Garam masala,chana  ( though u get it here later from any Pakistani shop)aur haan sabse badi baat .. Cooker bhoolna mat ..sab bhoolna magar cooker nahi ..(Dal banane ke liye)    * All food items in Check in Baggage NOT in cabin baggage.    * Take two xerox copies of all pages of Passport including Work -Permit (Ticket also , just in case )  keep one copy in hand baggage and one in check in luggage (This is for worst case in case passport gets stolen)    * Take few passport pictures also ( she might need her for her office ID card , nahi toh she has to run around for shops)    * Carry some coins if possible ( though it is tough to get in India  ) because phone booth mein sirf  coin chalega nahi toh she can buy anything from airport can get the change as well    * While cashing  Travellers cheques( if she has given) in Bank , make sure u have ur signatures on it and carry passport along with that to Bank    * DO NOT leave luggage alone whenever she is in International airport.    * Get all the stuff which is necessary for intial one month .. like Soap,Deo n all .. because it will take a while for her to find the nearest Supermarket.      *  yeah !! keep atleast two pair of clothes in Cabin/Hand Baggage .. its is because ..sometimes the baggage gets delayed ( which happens rarely) atleast she will  have somethin to wear for atleast two days to office :-))    *  DONT  keep any sharp object in hand luggage like nail -cutter or scissor etc    * Keep one pen with you because she has to fill some forms immigration in India as well in London Heathrow   
    
    
</post>



</Blog>