<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      by Renier Potgieter  The wet cobblestone path glinted in the first light of day, with water flowing in the crevices. Small black ants scurried to and fro on the stones in frenzy. Drops splashed down from the leaves of the rows of trees on both sides of the winding path.  Birds fluttered about overhead, catching moths and other insects that had come out after the rain. The smells of pure freshness were near overwhelming, especially where Ben stood at the entrance to the botanical garden. He had his compact video recorder in hand, making sure he missed nothing in his brief recording. He shifted the focus to the sky.   The sun was due to rise within the next couple of minutes, but the clouds on the horizon were ominous and dark, there would be nothing spectacular this time. He turned back to the fishpond just inside the entrance, knowing well this wouldn't help him once he has the film footage displayed on his projector.  He sighed, then lowered the camera and switched it off. He could just as well go home now, he was hungry and tired. "Buggerit," he murmured to himself, then made for the gates. He placed the video camera into its protective pouch that was hanging loosely from the strap at his shoulder, then secured the pouch with its custom-made Velcro straps to his chest.   He reached his hand to the wall next to the two spiked gates, probing absent-mindedly for the knotted rope that hung across a branch over the wall. He took hold of the thick rope, then glanced up at the top of the three meter high wall while placing his foot securely into a crack against it.  The wall was slick with damp moss, but didn't really pose a problem. Ben heaved himself upwards, then held his weight with his arms as he brought his feet together to the first knot on the rope. After a short while he sat on the wall, looking down at the ground, while hauling the rope up, rolled it and tied it with a simple loop, then threw it down on the other side. He had tied the end of the rope to the bumper of his car. The rope startled Graham as it landed with a thud on the hood.   His car stood right up against the wall, he had placed a fold-up chair on the roof to be able to get on the wall when he burgled his way into the botanical garden. Graham had removed the chair and put it in the boot, and he was now rubbing at his eyes and stretching inside the car before he would put the rope away as well.  "About bloody time," he grumbled as he opened the door. "Have I ever told you you're out of your mind?" He yawned and stretched his back as he got out. Ben smiled at him, maneuvering himself to the side on the wall, to get even grass under him and not the car, as he prepared himself to jump down.  "Yeah, I'm starting to think that's my name."   Graham smiled up at him. "Ha, Outofyourmind, get your arse down here, I need proper bloody sleep. And next time," he wagged his finger, "next time we do something decent, like a bank or at least bust open an ATM. This breaking into nature-stuff of yours has got to stop."   Ben chuckled before he leapt down, landing and rolling to the side in one movement. He got to his feet and started to undo the side strap that held his camera. "I told you, I want to catch the atmosphere of the scene, like nature, yet tamed, like an exotic garden or something, you know? By the time the place opens, people swarm the place and their presence spoils everything. Has to have atmosphere."  He pulled the camera over his head as it still laid in its pouch, then threw it onto the back seat. He watched as Graham dropped the rope into the boot, then struggled to secure the lock. It needed adjustment.  He looked again at his '58 Morris Minor. No, he decided, his life needed adjustment. He needed a vehicle with genuine air-conditioning, not ventilation that only worked when you opened a window.   At least it was still in a relatively unbroken state.  "So where to now," Graham enquired lazily as he sunk into the front passenger seat, more a sighing plea than a question. Ben's face turned bright and cheerful. "The harbor, I need shots of shells, seagulls and waves, water is a difficult medium, can't get enough shots of water."  Graham groaned and sank down into the passenger seat, suddenly making an effort to appear upset. Ben opened his door by leaning through the window to reach the handle inside. Ever since he sprayed the car, the locks acted up. And well, rust sprang up everywhere, only the roof held a shine to it while the left side had dried with sand and a couple of gnats stuck in the final layer. This was quite ironic, he trying to make a living from painting and all.  Ben got in behind the steering wheel, then fumbled around his pockets for the keys. He got the key in the ignition, then pulled out the makeshift choke while turning the key. The car sputtered to life, and he revved the engine just to confirm to himself that the little vehicle still had some spark left. Instead it backfired twice.  Ben grinned at Graham, then carefully reversed away from the wall and into the driveway and road leading up to it. The botanical garden was situated well out of town, with a small turnoff separating the parking lot from the highway.  "I'm leaning towards sleep myself," he said to Graham as he scratched the gears into first and turned into the highway.  Graham snorted in mock disgust, a heavy scowl on his face. "Bah, do what you want, don’t mind me, you artists are all the same." He glanced sideways at Ben, waving his hand dismissively. "You and your kind don’t care about us peasants anyway. Not intellectual enough, right?"   Ben suppressed a smile. "I paint, in actual practice, I don't see myself as one of those pissies that study art and pretend to analyze crap about different art forms – total waist of time. Have I told you about that one time Tretchicoff attended one of these huge art conventions, with some of his own art on display?   "He listened while three guys analyzed some of his work, saying how fine an artist he was and everything. You know the drill, speculating to what mood he was in when he started with the painting and that he had probably tried to express some sinister power through strong line definition and shading with his realistic approaches and what else. Tretchicoff said nothing, and none of these guys even recognized him. But he cleared his throat and you know, interrupted their little social conference."  Ben was using his left hand to create gestures of little importance when he didn't use it to change gears. Otherwise he would rest his hand either lightly on his lap or the gear lever itself.  "’Gentlemen,’ he said, ‘may I introduce myself?’ which he did. Then after they oohed and aahed and praised him on his magnificent work and all that, he raised the point they had made about his motivations for painting the way he did.  "’But I’m an artist, not a psychologist. There's no predetermined master plan to everything I do, no secret to every single color or chiaroscuro I use. I strive to be the best I can be, I'm just fortunate enough to laugh all the way to the bank while doing what I love."’ Ben looked sidelong at Graham as if he anticipated some wondrous praise for the little tale, and Graham just shrugged.  "Tretchicoff said that?" he asked. Ben nodded.  "He did, he said exactly that, and I could say its true for me as well, I do what I love and we share a common thing for perfection. Well, I may not have his ability, but I strive. Have you ever looked closely at his work? Better than realism, man. And I tell you, that is talent. But maybe even more dedication. If you tore a hole the size of your fingernail in a piece of paper and you moved it over one of his paintings, you'd not find a place on it that lacked his utmost attention."  Graham hawked and spat through his open window, then shook his head at Ben.   "You made that up, man, Tretchicoff never said that. How would you know what he said, anyway? You said yourself you weren't a pissy that talked about art stuff and that." Graham held back his bubbling mirth as he saw Ben turn a scowl at him.  "Would I lie to you?" Ben countered irritably.  Graham held up his hands in defense. "Nothing wrong with lying either. I make up stuff to tell you all the time just to sound important."  Ben snorted as his mouth turned back into a smile. "Ah? Like what?"  Graham scratched his chin in exaggerated sincerity. "Hmm, lets see, like the American president Teddy Roosevelt that wrote a whole lot of books, all describing in hidden text how he’d murdered two T.V. repairmen."  Ben burst out laughing. "What, like the Bible–Code?"  Graham nodded, grinning. "Exactly like that, only less complicated."  "Well, were there T.V. repairmen in the time that he was president?" Ben smirked as he glanced at his friend.  Graham shrugged. "I never said I was a good liar. Besides, lies aren't always supposed to make a whole lot of sense."   "Ahm, yes they're supposed to make a lot of sense, that's the entire idea about lying, to say things which aren't true in a way that makes them sound entirely believable."  Graham countered with an open handed slap to Ben’s chest . "Not the way I lie, you see -'  He was about to continue, when a long black shape ahead in the opposite lane got his attention. A six-door Rolls Royce, black and glinting at the break of dawn.  "You suppose they need help?" he asked as a man climbed out of the driver's side, then slammed the door shut. Ben was about to pull over, when he saw her.  She looked straight at him, her face contorted with terror, maybe even pain. One hand smacked soundlessly against the inside of the window, palm flattened against the glass. Her mouth seemed to form words in a plea, her golden hair spilling over the one side of her face. She was breathtakingly beautiful as he saw her in that heart stopping instant, her face turning back to follow him as his Morris passed the Rolls Royce. A pistol shone in the hand of the driver as he looked after them, and Ben simply kept going.  He was utterly stunned. Graham shook his shoulder. "Ben, man, are you alright? You look as if you seen my ex. Aren't we going to help 'em?" He hadn't seen anything other than a black limousine, still thinking they were merely having trouble with their car. Maybe it was better that way. Benjamin shook his head slowly, and spoke as if he was half in a trance.  "No, there's nothing we could do to help-" Nothing we could do at all. There was at least one man with a gun. There seemed to have been other dark shapes in the car as well, but Ben couldn't remember whether it might have been the headrests or something similar, or whether it might have been other men.   Ben swallowed hard, then forced a smile at Graham. "You honestly think people driving in a limo wouldn't have phoned for some emergency service already? Probably having their own personal limo mechanics fly out here. Besides, you know how people are these days." He kept going without daring to look back.            *     *     *  His eyes burned with the lack of sleep, but he just couldn't find peace. Her eyes. He kept seeing her eyes and it was an open conviction. Two days ago. He could have done something. Phoned the cops even. But he hadn't. He had held the damn thing in his hand, but he couldn't bring himself to dial a simple number.   If she was dead, it was his fault. Her death on his head. Why else would she bang against the window, unable to get out - pleading for help! - with that man with a gun in his hand? She was so beautiful, so flawless...  But he was trying to get his mind off her entirely. He had forced himself to watch thirteen hours worth of homemade movies of vegetation, rock formations and flowing water on his projector.   It always calmed him when he saw again the scenes of his travels even years ago, trapping nature on film so he could put it again on canvas.  He tried painting, he had several paintings he had yet to finish, and usually in times of depression he would find peace in completing his earlier works.  But he had even slashed one because he ruined what should have been simple color shading. The clarity with which he saw each detail of her terror stricken face, the way her hair shone in a half circle around her forehead, the way she crooked her fingers backwards when she slammed her palm against the window... her eyes most of all. He had taken in her entire being in an instant, in less time than it takes to blink, yet her shape was imprinted into the back of his mind.  The projector was connected to his video camera, simply throwing the image on the camera on a white wall. The running time of the video he was watching last had ended, so the image on the wall was a plain gray mess of static. Ben got up to switch off the projector and to turn on the countless lights dangling from his basement studio.   He lived in one corner, having erected pine frames with stapled white sheets as walls. His bedroom was separated from his kitchen, and that was all there was, all of which was also surrounded with these makeshift walls.   But he enjoyed it down here. He could hide from the world if he wished, lose himself in his work without ever being bothered. He had about two dozen completed works and twice that uncompleted, all pinned up somewhere. The completed ones were against the walls, the others against paint-messed trestles, standing all over the place, with dozens of lights hanging from the ceiling.   Ben sighed, rubbing at his burning eyes. Coffee could be quite welcome about now, he decided. He had a sink down here, he had devised his kitchen around it.   He switched the gas on to the little stove on which only one plate worked, and set a pot of water on it. Taking the largest cup he could find, he made the coffee extra strong. Without milk too, he decided, which was a good thing as well, because the only milk he had was long sour.  After the water boiled, he took his coffee back to his studio and set it down on a broken chair next to one of the trestles. He drew up a proper stool for himself to sit on, then tore off the current canvas. He took a sip of the coffee, then prepared a new canvas, keeping it in place with several drawing pins. He had a tub of diluted white PVA, which served as a base, so that the oil paint wouldn't be absorbed into the material.   He waited for the paint to dry, which took about ten minutes - dry enough for him to draw on it with charcoal - in which time he drained his coffee and made himself another cup. He had heard somewhere that the human body could safely digest seven cups of coffee a day. Whether that was true or not, he was determined to take that number considerably higher.   He placed the tip of the charcoal on the material and slowly began to draw it downwards, smoothly, barely registering the picture in mind. He took it line for line, sketching as he always did, roughly, yet with fine definition. He was drawing the scene that was bothering him so much, that stuck in his mind like a guilty conscience.   Nevertheless, he was shocked to see the scene again, as the face took shape. The features were almost perfect to the way he remembered her, horrified, her hand obscuring the bottom left part of her face. He left out the Rolls Royce, he simply made a frame around her face where the window should have been.   Then he got his palette and paintbrushes, mixed the colors he would need on the palette, and started to work. He had his colors, but he found himself only using black, working in shading and depth. He couldn't take his eyes off her, she was so beautiful. It was a strange feeling, painting the woman, most likely a dead woman, and so obviously obsessed with her.   He realized this too, and he didn't deny it. Emotion is what he liked in his work, his landscapes were always alive with a sense of freedom, open spaces, lowlands with sunshine and a lost tree amidst golden brown plains. It generated a positive emotion.   Or when he felt like it, he used dark contrasts and zooming effects in what should be a simple landscape – a branch in the foreground while ignoring the rule of thirds. It resulted in a claustrophobic atmosphere. Complexity was what he found intriguing, and obsession was certainly a driving force for exactly what he had never succeeded in.   A feel for utter depression.  And he could feel it clearly, even though the face was the only object on the canvas. Portraits were definitely not his specialty, in his twenty-seven years, he had always been drawn to nature and its elements. Even in art class, he never excelled in anything other than landscapes. Yet this actually looked close to photo-realism.  She looked desperate, her one eye slightly drawn to a squint, the haze of tears collecting on the lower lids. Her mouth was slightly open, full lips, her jaw protruding to some extent.   Perfect to the slightest detail.  He let her die.  Ben pushed the stool away from the trestle, the palette dropped from his hand, the paintbrush followed. He stumbled backwards past the stool, just barely keeping his balance. He had to get out. He turned and dashed for the staircase leading to the ground level, shoving a trestle with an uncompleted painting out of his way, not bothered as it landed with a loud crash.  He couldn't explain the feeling building in his chest, it was as if a hot numbing pain suffocated his very purpose for life. He reached the top of the staircase and threw open the door and just kept running. He barged into the front room of the hair salon, dazed and mightily confused. It was impossible to think straight, he just knew he had to get out and get back on the road.  He had to find her.   He couldn't ignore the surprised stares the customers and old Mr. Entino gave him, because he wasn't even aware they existed.   Ben headed straight for his car where it stood in the alley.  Mr. Entino had bought this building as a warehouse, then made it into four shops on the side of the road. A diner, a flower shop, the salon and a little fast-food restaurant. The rest of the warehouse was empty space, and he had no use for the basement, so Ben bought it from him for next to nothing.  Ben yanked open his door, got in and became highly frustrated when he couldn't get his car to start. It resulted in the screaming of words he never used, honking the horn and slamming the steering wheel. He shouted at a woman, asking what the hell she was looking at, as he forced the gears into first and pulled out of the alley.  He spent half the day driving around, looking for any trace of a black Rolls Royce after not finding it where he saw it last. In the back of his mind he knew it wouldn't still be there, but he didn't know where else to go. Regret was burning in him. If only he stopped. That man with the gun wouldn't have dared shoot, he wouldn't have been able to clear the evidence before another car came by. Threatened maybe, at worst. If only -  Ben sighed, then went back to his studio and started painting franticly.                   *     *     *  It was three days later, and he had just woken up. Ben combed his hair back with his fingers, then finally managed to heave his legs over the side of the bed. Graham had forced him to get some rest after he had gone about sixty hours without sleep. He seemed to have lost some weight as well, barely ate. He had made four completed collages and seven abstract paintings, two of which weren't quite finished. All of Jolene – the name he had given the mystery woman.  Graham came to visit uninvited as he usually did, simply popping up with a pizza or some take-aways he bought at Mr. Entino's. He had to go back for more, because when Ben finally remembered what food tasted like, he dropped his palette and devoured everything he could find.  Graham smiled at him where they sat opposite each other.  "You wanna see abstract art?" he said, then stuffed some fries in his mouth, a bite of bread, chewed a little, then closed his lips around the large ketchup bottle. He tried to smile at Ben as he chewed some more, then opened his mouth wide for Ben to see the red mess of food in his mouth. He tried to utter a "Ta-da!" but he couldn't quite manage it, especially not when Ben started laughing.   They ate, chatting, and Graham could see Ben's face lighting up with good humor. Ben still looked bad though, his eyes were sunken with dark pockets underneath. Something was wrong with his friend, and it wasn't a simple problem.  Nothing ever was with Ben.  He stood up from where he sat on the stool and turned his attention to what Ben had been doing all this time. He started to walk through the studio while Ben finished the rest of the food. “I'm worried, Ben,” Graham said.   “I hope you're feeling better than you look.” He was pacing through the studio, looking especially at the new edition.   “I see you've been inspired rather severely?” he made it into a question.   “Yeah, I guess so.” Ben cleared his throat as he walked to Graham, wiping his mouth and hands with a towel.  “Lets go for a drive or something. I need to get out of here.” For some reason Ben felt an urgency to have Graham leave his studio. He didn't want anyone to see these, they were his - he would never sell them.   His.  Graham however seemed to have something on his mind. “Talk to me Ben. What's going on?”   Ben said nothing for a while, hands in pockets. “What would you like me to say?”  “I'd like to know what’s been eating you.” Graham was persistent, and Ben knew he meant well.   “We'll speak about it later, Graham, please not now.”   Graham shook his head. “You can't keep this inside, and I'm right here. You trust me, don't you?”  “Its not about trust, Graham.” Ben dropped his eyes from Graham's, turning away. There was an uncomfortable silence in which Ben waited for the predicted words from Graham –  Sure its about trust  – but it didn't come. Instead Graham paced again, walking between his new editions of artwork, of Jolene.  He stopped in front of one of the uncompleted paintings. “Now see here,” he pointed at the rough edges where the shades of gray stopped abruptly into white canvas with bits of dried paint.  “This one is one of your first, right? One can see she isn't as defined as some of the others are, although she is strikingly beautiful. With the window or something only partially completed. She is heavily upset with something, crying even. You used only black and white, Ben, you were in one hell of a mood - I've never seen that in your work. You never use black without mixing it with browns or blues or whatever.”  Graham turned his head to the next painting, then walked slowly to it. Ben stood still, his heart beating in his ears and his breathing was erratic. Graham continued, without looking anywhere else than the painting of the woman, reading a book on a park bench.  “You placed the same woman in another scene, her face unmistakable. She isn't crying, but its definitely her. The background is edgy and rather sketchy to your standards, seeing that its what you've always insisted on which gave atmosphere to the painting. You've proved yourself wrong, you know, this piece is clogged with peace. The way the strokes blend and shove her as primary subject right in your face.  "Color too, soft greens and blues, almost the only colors you used - except bits of yellow as base that I can see there. Creates a nice positive feel, doesn't it? What you were going for, right? Not like the first one.”  Graham started towards the first collage, of Jolene, smiling, her head thrown back, dancing by herself. Her face was easily recognizable, even though her entire form was created from photos in magazines, face, hair, body, arms and legs. As Graham was about to start describing what he saw, Ben cleared his throat. “Get out.”  Graham turned back to him.  “Excuse me?” he said, dropping his head slightly to the side. Ben advanced a step, his hands trembled and his voice dropped to a low whisper.  “Get the hell out. Now.”  Graham met Ben’s eyes and inclined his head in an uncharacteristic fit of sarcasm. He turned on his heal and stalked to the door, then slammed it behind him. Ben kept watching the door for a while, not knowing what to think or how to feel. Some part of him had hoped his friend would stay, ask questions… but he sighed and tried to shrug the weariness from him.  In one corner of his living area he had an old dusty couch facing a black-and-white television set with improvised 6 by 9 speakers set in two shoe boxes. Something he appreciated about the set was that it had a F.M. radio simulcast feature, which meant he could listen to his favorite D.J. insult his sports presenter.  John the sports presenter was usually referred to as ‘Baldric’ – a calculated insult, a private joke. But the D.J. insulted his listeners in general anyway, so Baldric couldn’t claim it as indifference.   Ben lay on the couch listening at the radio for a while, but it didn’t help his mood. So he got up and walked to the little basin in his makeshift kitchen, sipping some water from his cupped hands. He was about to splash some water in his face when he glanced up at a tiny mirror he had pasted against the wall right above the basin.  He screamed and leapt backwards in fright, then felt the immense chill of the cold spot where he now stood. For a moment longer he could do nothing, the shock was too immense. He could swear he heard the whisper of the dead.   Free me!   Ben’s breathing was coming in hot gasps, yet his throat burned with ice. He never thought he could summon the strength, but he found himself inching forward again, bending over to look in the little mirror. He had to clench his teeth not to scream again.   She stood there, as beautiful as ever, dressed in a white blouse and short skirt. The bloodstain on her blouse did not spread, even though the amount of blood pulsing from her temple appeared not to stop.   He forced his grip to loosen on the basin, and he slowly turned his head to where she should be standing. There was nothing but empty space.   He covered his face with his hands and found himself mumbling that it was a dream, that he’d imagined it. But as soon as he peeked through his gnarled fingers, there she was, staring over his shoulder at him in the mirror.    Free me!    And she lifted her arm and pointed. Not at him, but at one of his artworks – of her. He couldn’t see which one she was pointing at, the angle was wrong.  But he knew. Their first.   He stepped back, his mind reeling. For a moment longer he couldn’t think. Then he found himself reacting despite his fear, driven by passion or stupidity – if there was a difference. He ignored what he was doing but he had to see her. He felt the chill of the spot where he found himself standing, staring up at her portrait.   Will you set me free?  the words ran like ice through him, inaudible, yet palpable. It made the hair in his neck stand on-end and his heartbeat thundered in his ears.   “Yes. I will set you free,” he said out loud, turning for his stack of scalpels, paintbrushes and palette knives. He selected what he wanted, then turned back to where he thought the ghost of his beloved Jolene stood.  “But not right now. Maybe tomorrow, though.” He looked down at the brushes in his hand and scooped up a white plastic palette at his feet, blotches of dried paint covering its surface.  Ben stood immobile for a while, wondering if Mr. Entino would mind horribly if he borrowed one of those large mirrors from the wall of the hair salon.   
    
</post>


<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tick.  I meant to say TICK.    I set my alarm clock last night for 6am instead of 8am, an honest mistake.  Why would I want to wake up at 6am anyway? So when someone's alarm goes off at 6am in the morning in a 16 bedded dorm, you're bound to piss a couple of people off.  I understand that.  I really do, I was quite upset myself until I realized the alarm was MINE.  But I can't remember that I have EVER found a reason to call someone - and excuse the profanity - a fucking moron.    So when I hear those words spoken at me I am not impressed.  In general I would ignore it, why bother?  It takes some doing to get me angry.  But at 06:01 in the morning I'm grumpy and no mistake.    Swearing in Afrikaans, my first language, has its advantages.  Firstly it sounds better, secondly a string of them only confuses, it doesn't have the same effect as telling someone they're a fornicating half-wit in crude terms.  That was my start to the day.  Why get up at all?  You just know its going to get worse.  And when I don't manage to get any new information of where to rent a flat in the newspapers or internet, I get frustrated.  And when I get frustrated I decide to hell with it and check up on my blog instead.    Unfortunately I don't seem to be getting anyone to COMMENT on anything, excepting for Ig and that lovely Svea.  Maybe I should do something really controversial like :     "Why The Toilet Seat Stays Up At My House"         or     "How To Listen - Shut Up I'm Talking - To Your Partner!"  I have a knack for controversial issues.  I also have a knack for putting my foot in my mouth and getting the humour bit completely wrong.  I don't always concentrate when I say something, and my love for humour and to amuse with the little bit of wit that I do have, has gotten me into trouble more times than I can count.  The most classic account of me getting it wrong, is in grade 8 in the English class.  We had the task to write a non-fiction essay about the marine life of various aquatic animals besides fish.  I chose  the octopus and did my best to research on it from the computers we had in the library.  I worked hard to find every last detail, from their latin names on various species, to anatomy.  And carelessly mistook its eight tenticles for testicles.    Not my finest moment.  That's one example of many of which I shall not indulge, I would like a shred of dignity left.  Its not that I have a short attention span or cannot devide my att-  okay okay I cannot devide my attention, like the rest of the male species.    I have put my attention to partly building up a 1958 Morris Minor though, and I think it deserves a mention simply to divert attention AWAY from the mental image of any living organism having eight testicles.     Slightly_Potty 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Where do I start?  I will try to be as honest as possible, maybe I even learn more about the Real Me.  I think I have to go back about a year, to right before I became a regular on the then free MsN Chatroom "Books"...    It feels such a long time ago, I can't believe I've changed so much in just one year.  It makes me wonder who I will be this time next year?  But that's not the issue here, lets go back to the creation of Mr_Mortez, or as he became known fairly quickly... Horny_Morty.    I created my new Hotmail Account and wanted the name Oblivious, or Oblivion, which it turned out, was already taken.  So was every other name I tried.  I did not want to add strings of digits, that I was very persistent on, so I struggled for almost an hour until I could take it no longer.    I was working on about the 10th draft of "The Life of Regor Mortez" a story I started writing in grade 9 as a shortstory and just kept at it.  I figured if the name - which is somewhat of a pun on rigor mortis was already taken, then I had no originality in the story itself anyway.    So Mr_mortez looked for a chatroom, and when he innocently walzed into the "Books" chatroom hoping to find similarly minded people or maybe even editors...    Technically we're the same person.  Mr_Morty and Renier "Potty" Potgieter.  But not quite in spirit.  Anyone who has ever been in a chatroom might know what I'm talking about.  Its very easy to say what you want because you're perfectly safe behind your keyboard.      Except for hackers and policemen searching for pedophiles.    But Mr_Mortez got to insulting any clueless brainy reader who happened to be interrested in Lord of the Rings or Harry Potter (cheers).  And they weren't the only ones.      Quickly on the Harry Potter (cheers) issue, here's a quote from Igkuk7 on a footnote I should add actually more concerning an old friend he lost contact with... no questions asked.  His quotes would have it that I'm the person writing it... which I'm not.            Iain says: say something likie "not five minutes would go by without someone birsting through the virtual door ranting and raving about harry potter, where upon several of the regulars would jump on then and literally knock the confidence out of them, Zennha, or heart_a_blaze being the best at this, although I never met her, I have a reliable source who tells me this is so. And no he wasn't drunk at the time of asking"      Exactly.  Now I didn't realize how an insult can go a long way until I met those more experienced at the trade than I was.  Like good ol' Jesusiscomingsoonsolookbusy.  An offensive name to fit to his character.  He was funny at times, but he and a couple of others could spoil the mood in the room in an instant.      So I turned my attentions rather from insults to making women feel good.  Complimenting them on their obvious good looks from the photo in their profile.  Even if they were as ugly as hell.    I had a lot of fun and nothing can replace old Books, and even if I did whip out the money to get membership, it won't be the same without the others.      Just to mention a couple, simply so I can lure them to look at my blog by saying "Hey you're in it!"  Here goes in no particular order: DinoDreams, ProudestMonkey, Oracle, Darwin,  urlLink Igkuk7 , the Kiwicheeser, Donks, Archangel, Breezio,  urlLink Adrienne , Ashley, Jon, Boo, Digi, Luna, Lovely Leda, Talhawkins, Gill, Civ, Misty, Mystical... sheesh, the memories is making me all emotional.     There is one lady I didn't mention who might be quite upset if I left her out, but she only really came into the picture after MsN closed their freechat and all the regulars moved over to Yahoo.  No offense and I certainly don't want to step on any legal issues, but Yahoo people are weird.  Very.       Back to Books though.    If you wanted to have a good old chat about books, you should go to the library.  Books was the wrong chatroom.  If you wanted to talk about sex, life and various twisted philosophies, then sure, Books was the place.  On Wednesdays there was what could be best described as Lesbian Nite, which would usually result in me grabbing a virtual chair, pulling it right up to a virtual stage and get the wummen to illustrate how they are poledancing.    Leda was a very good poledancer.    Still is, probably.    I made a couple of very good frieds there, and although it might seem sad to anybody else, I wouldn't exchange those days for anything.      And then, in October MsN closed their freechat and everybody migrated to Yahoo Entertainment and Arts/ On Broadway, simply because it was always empty.  Until we migrated, apparently, because all of a sudden it was flooded with the weird people I mentioned earlier.      But this is where I met another MsN Books regular, she remembers me in Books, but I hit on so many women, she probably just dissapeared into a sea of nameless faces, especially since we only talked once or twice in there.    By this time in Yahoo I changed my nic to Horny_Morty, which was honest enough, and then to enter the scene and my life...  Kinky_Carly.  An amazing woman, we had such a lot in common it wasn't long before we got to the internet dating thing.  Naughty emails, marathon messanger sessions till 5am in the morning...    She is from Chile, sexy and as intelligent as they come.  I couldn't believe a woman as good as that could like me, so I took it as it came.  Ironically enough, the women I dated previously back in South Africa - always briefly - never made me feel like she did, I started to realize what type of woman I am compatible with, that a pretty face alone was not good enough.      We were together for 5 and a half months, and other than that, I'm not going to go into further detail about the actual relationship or the break-up, because it still hurts a little when I think about it.  But she changed me more than any other factor, I think, she made me realize what  matters .  She will always have a place in my heart even though its over between us, the hot numbing feeling in my stomach when I think about her has faded.      She might have another boyfriend, I never even met her in person, but she'll always stay that Kinky_Carly, and I'll remember her with fondness.    While I knew her I had this big fight to get a Working Holiday Visa for the United Kingdom, which was denied the first time and accepted on my appeal.  Throuhgout that time there were ups and downs as I had a date in mind.    The month of July.    The delay caused by the refusal of the Visa was a big blow at the time, because I would have been able to visit Chile and meet my dream woman.  Now July is here and I know it would not have worked out that way, but I still wish I could get very drunk and sleep through the whole month - just to get past what could have been.      Arg, enough moaning.      But meeting Carly had been what has changed me to the person I am today, accepting that a loudmouth Horny_Morty was a waste of my time, first and foremost.  I'm better off with being myself, and its ironic how the old people are right time and time again?    My father always told me to be myself, and it took me all this time to discover it all over again.    I do have a further love interrest, and I'm going to put my money on the fact that I'll be a changed man this time next year... I hope its for the better.    I wrote this all in one session, so I'll update it as i go along and get a better perspective on what I wrote.    All for now  Slightly_Potty  To  urlLink My Writing Interrests     
    
</post>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I haven't posted lately and I'm pissed about it because I had so many ideas that I could gone on for hours.&nbsp; Well I have a little bit of spare time and I'll try to update near every weekday, and since I've made up my mind to invest in a wireless internet laptop (arg damnit, hard earned money) I'll be able to post at my leisure as soon as I find the right bargain.   Anyhow.  I have some very positive news - or thoughts - to share.&nbsp;   Prior to visiting my last Client as a Personal Carer, I've been exceptionally horny even for my standards.&nbsp; And I couldn't quite put my finger on why this was.&nbsp; The women aren't more beautiful than they are in good 'ol South Africa, back home we've got some mighty fine ones too, but the Hostel life - I think - gave me too much freedom, all rules are off, and for me that's bad.&nbsp; I like to have rules, feel secure in my own environment, although I don't have an issue with coping with independance.&nbsp; I don't particularly miss South Africa either, not in the real sense.&nbsp; I do still see it as my home though, England, awesome as it is, just isn't the same.  But being placed with Stu has fixed what was wrong in my perception, the way I view my surroundings.&nbsp; I stepped into a new world, England and its pubs and wine shelves in café's, horrible customer service (yes HSBC, that's you damnit), great mobility via the underground tube stations in London, forreign accents and countless other little things, that keeps reminding me I AM NOT HOME.&nbsp; Positives and negatives.&nbsp;   And then there are the mixed dormed Hostels.&nbsp; Its bloody marvelous, I'm not complaining, but that was probably the last thing&nbsp;I needed.&nbsp; Needed some solidity under my feet, get myself sorted.&nbsp;   With Stuart I stepped into a family environment, a nice big house albeit with two low chandeliers I kept knocking with my hea-&nbsp; with my mind.&nbsp; He has an older brother and slightly younger sister, and even though I'm no child any longer, his parents did lay some ground rules and had enough dominance in their household to make me long for Mum, Dad&nbsp;and my very own evil sister.&nbsp; If i close my eyes I was back home, a couple of years younger and happy.&nbsp; The atmsphere was&nbsp; there.   So what has this got to do with&nbsp;my physical or emotional wellbeing?&nbsp; I'm old enough to look after myself, even though sometimes I make toast with peanutbutter instead &nbsp;of a good wholesome dinner.&nbsp;   I now know what's been missing, I know I need a routine.&nbsp; Even when going back to the Hostel, I'll be sure to have my feet under me.&nbsp; A little switch in the mind, is all.&nbsp; Just like the little bulb switch that sparks ideas, I have found my little horny switch that shuts off main power to the brain.&nbsp;   Now that I have found myself, what am I to do?&nbsp; I dunno.&nbsp; Live and learn.&nbsp; Keep a date in mind for next year September,&nbsp;I think, when I'll be switching the Horny switch on again.&nbsp; Maybe.&nbsp; Hopefully.&nbsp;   For now, I'll smile at gorgeous women, make a little chit-chat and see what happens.&nbsp; But not too much effort though.&nbsp;  Keep it simple .&nbsp; That's been good advice in the past, I think I'll stick to it.  Now, next short-term goal for me is the laptop, then&nbsp;a better digital camera, I think, but that can wait.&nbsp; And with th laptop I'll finally have a workstation I can download my pics to.&nbsp; Remind me to get a pic of Stuart's gorgeous sister on the blog, she might have a boyfriend, but she sure is nice to look at :D  Well enough of my senseless babbeling, I think I'll try to think up something controversial for my next post, something sexist that is sure to get a comment or two.&nbsp; Or three.&nbsp; I've never had more than two comments... so I'll have to brainstorm to upset enough women.  Slightly_Potty  &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, I noted that Iain has added the link to a whole bunch of  urlLink London Pictures  but I feel that one or two deserve slightly more attention.   Note that for this to make any sense you need to have a separate browser open to look at the pics on that site, because for some reason links to my own pictures aren't working. Damnit. So I'll just give the picture number and then elaborate a little. And could you believe we ran into a couple of celebs??&nbsp;  Dscf0001 - This is me and Vera. She does not look impressed. I think it might be because my hand accidently brushed her butt in the attempt to give Iain the "Where's Potty's Hand" pic. And it WAS an accident. I do not grope without permission. And I'm serious. I have lots of respect for women, they're fabulous creatures and deserve every bit of it. She's a very nice lady.&nbsp;  Dscf0156 - This is probably my favorite pic yet. Kicking the ass of Johnny Wilkinson. And he deserves it. Ugly bastard.&nbsp;  Dscf0149 - Can you believe it?? A second round of "Where is Potty's Hand" and its right on Elle MacPhereson's glorious butt. She did NOT complain about the location of my hand.   Dcsf0151 - Iain and the gorgeous Salma Hayek. Wow. How did he get to be so lucky? Can you see the smile on her face? I bet she's asking "Is that a huge camera case in your pocket or are you just happy to see me?"&nbsp;  Dscf0164 - Iain and Humphry Bogart. Unbelievable, since it looks like ol' Humphry hasn't even aged.   Well the rest of the pics are mostly self explanitory, plus I'm tired and I'm kinda lazy, following Iain's example. Show enough interrest and I'll do the propper thing and add captions to all of 'em.   Slightly_Potty 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow.  What a woman.  If she reads this, which she just might because I DID give her the link and told her I'd be posting all about her gorgeousness, well, Alina, you're one helluva woman.    My vocabulary seems to have gone to shit.  Um.  Appologies, but you all know how my mind gets muddled with excitement.  The day - two days ago now because I've been lazy and hadn't posted religiously as I should have - started with breakfast for the two ladies Rosemary and Vera.  Although they slept through it due to having been out clubbing to 5 o' clock in the morning.    Iain (this is how you spell his name and not Ian as I've been doing, concider it a correction which I'll get to later) and I went to the Brittish museum and saw absolutely everything it had to offer.  it took us about 4 hours, and most of it we saw TWICE.  Which included some very interresting pictures.  Due to come soon, I hope *hint hint*  Having successfully traversed the museum, we went back to the Hostel and found there a Russian woman with a sweet american accent.    Alina.  I'll try to act natural and not be so obvious about liking her.  This being said after sending her a horny email and possibly scaring the crap out of her.  Anyway, another story.    She had a ticket to watch "When Harry met Sally" the theatre version at 20:30, and seeing as we had some time to kill, headed to the same Italian Restaurant as the previous evening.  The waiter mentioned was happy to see us, possibly because we were about the only customers.  But again, the food was excellent and the dessert even better.  And damnit I forgot to even out with Iain who insisted on paying.    We went from there to Trafalgar Square for her theatrical experience and Iain and I saw the sights.  Big Ben, Houses of Parliment, lots of other misterious buildings and the river Thames in which I chucked money in the attempt to gain luck with my so-called sex-life.    If only I was a bigger spender.  Damnit.  After seeing all there was to see - including a groom no less a raging lunatic who pulled faces to distract his bride who was posing at the magnificent fountain of Trafalgar Square - we searched in vain for a pub to kill the remaining hour before the theatre ended.  We searched for about an hour, which served to be killing time equally well than actually sitting AT the pub.    A cheerful Alina met us after the show and made up our minds to go clubbing.  Which we did.  And the topic of my defunct dancing ability was soon remedied.  She bought the drinks which was non-negotiable, and seeing as she's Russian, three shots of Vodka for the three of us.  Iain, remind me NEVER to mix clean shots of Vodka with beer ever again.  Although the Vodka could probably do it all by itself, beer mixed in with other stronger drink is just plain evil.   So I danced a little, but what I did not tell her before hand, was that alcoholic beverages does not increase my rhythem.  Just the lust factor.  She did promise to send me a picture or two, so as soon as she does, if its decent enough for a public audience *cough* I'll post it right here.  So then the world can understand why I drool at the memory of her.  Wow.  For safety sake, I'll just shaddap right about there, she's going to be studying as a Lawyer, and some people have good memories.    Next time I have a shot of Vodka, its to her.    Slightly_Potty
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A day to remember.  I enjoyed it quite a bit.  Shall I account for it in order or pull a Quentin Tarantino (Ig said its spelled right) and do it in weird Pulp Fictionish order starting with the good bits first?  Arg.  I'll just keep it simple.    Last night I went out and bought a small yellow alarm clock and a small padlock, then got to the posh 4 bed dorm and set the alarm for seven o' clock the next morning.  Mainly because I like to amuse myself and I thought it would be a good prank.  Then I locked the alarm in one of the small cabinets.    I left the dorm at 7:30 for breakfast, after adding my string of insults to the inconsiderate bugger who left earlier in the morning and neglected to take his alarm clock with him.  I felt somewhat cheerful.  I had the traditional English breakfast, bacon, eggs and orange juice pretty much overwhelming my senses until I finished my portion and looked longingly at the serving area.  They don't allow seconds.  So I get up sulking and head back to the room to pack and get out at ten.  I head to the Hostel I have booked for Ian and I for the weekend, and store my luggage before slowly making my way to the train station to meet him at Euston Station.  We met up and walked around, had some lunch and to my very wise instruction, checked into our 8-bedded room as early as possible.  Sure enough, there we encountered two very good looking women, Vera and Rosemary.  They might be opposites in character, but it was refreshing to find such lovely company completely unexpected *cough*  Rosemary is so beautiful and sweet, with what seems like a calculated intelligence in her eyes, gently taking in details. While Vera is also very good on the eye, but more spontaneous and a more obvious naughty streak.  The reason I'm defining their characters the way I see them are simply for the fact that I'll add pics of them soon.  We chatted a while and as time wore on dinner time arrived, so I invited them to have dinner with Ian and I.  He was probably thinking Joeli was going to throttle him at this point, but he didn't say anything.  Which was good, because keeping two women happy at the same time has not yet entered my repertoire of skills.  Such as it is.  We had dinner at an Italian restaurant and the food was excellent.  Ian insisted that I thank the waiter in Itlian as we left because its good manners, but since he is an Italian waiter in an English country, he should greet me in English.  Which he did.  And "muchos gracias" sounds funny.  It ended as a very nice evening, and Ian told me that he was sure we could not take out any women, singular or otherwise, the following day.  How wrong he was.  More on gorgeous women to follow...  or more particularly, one incredibly hot one by name of Alina.  Slighty_Potty   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Interresting times.    And I can end the blog right there, because for ME that's enough.  Those two words speak volumes.  That can be seen in context to many topics I have on my mind, one of which might be shampoo on my toothbrush.    But not today, I have something else in mind.  I seem to have the knack to meet the most fantastic women.  I can count them on my one hand, but one person shouldn't be  allowed  to be blessed with their presence even just for a day.  And then I lose them again.  Go figure.  At this rate even the Aussie women look more attractive, just for the sake of pinning my hopes a little lower.  That may be my problem.  Aiming too high.    I'm just a normal everyday guy with one or two slight differences.  Both positive and negative.  I have only one positive that I can think of RIGHT NOW, and unfortunately that goes together with finding the right woman.  Back to square one.    I have joked in the past that Fate is a lesbian manhater who has one nail sharpened just for me.  And I realized something yesterday.  ITS TRUE!  Damnit.  Now before I go on, please feel free to comment on whatever I write, but note also that I am NOT repeat NOT depressed or angry or remotely pissed.  Never take me too seriously, which is something I should tell ANY good looking gal right as I meet her.  Right.  Which does bring me to an interresting point.  Are there any good looking women out there who wants to take a complete stranger to their bed and make the hot luvvin' to him?  In the general area of the United Kingdom.  Preferably with a nice smile, dark hair (optional) nice breasts and a good butt.  They should also be eager to please and not be dissapointed in premature ejaculation.  Well then, DON'T CONTACT ME about it, because seeing as he is a complete stranger, how the hell am I supposed to have his contact details?  Sheesh.  You'd think that's logic.  Over the course of this coming weekend I might or might not post, seeing as my good internet buddy Ian aka Igkuk7 is coming to visit.  Good fun, I might take him to the ZooBar, a club/ pub in Leicester Square I know of where a blonde bomb with mighty cleavaged breasts is working as waitress, name of Mua.  Very nice.  And if she reads this, I think she has a really nice personality too.  Um.  Well, enough for the moment, I think, before I get myself into some real trouble.  Slightly_Potty    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its Cheekymonkeyislora's birthday, and a special mention to an old friend.  We used to have a lot of fun in Yahoo, Igkuk7 Cheeky and I.  Actually they were the ones quoting Monty Python, and although I love english comedy, I'm never sure if Monty Python is funny or just plain weird.  A combination of both, I think.   Well, a big HAPPY 19TH (??) BIRTHDAY Laura, and enjoy it, you're only 19 for 365 days and then its gone.  For good.  Although women have been known to stay the same age for several years.  That's my good deed for the day...  Slightly_Potty
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have no order in which I put these posts, its crazy.  I started the post on my writing because I thought I had something to say.  Well, apparently not.  Maybe I get inspired again, but for now I have something else on my mind.  South Africa is a place I'll always be drawn to, its still my home, and although I haven't really traveled yet, I can't compare it to anything.  I've been to a couple of small English towns and I love that atmosphere.  Its nothing like London and its Undergrounds and raging foreigners.  back in South Africa though, my uncle had a couple of sheep farms in the Orange Freestate, a 1000 km from the closest shoreline.  The air is dry, the sky is blue, the earth is hard.  The atmosphere is clogged with peace and silence.  The plants are adapted to get every last bit of moisture from the soil, and have you ever looked at a thorn bush and understood why it has those white three inch thorns?   Very obvious, but to contemplate it... To keep animals from eating its leaves.  Life there has evolved to that level where the greenery is sacred.  But even as dry as that, the country side is absolutely beautiful, and I will always love it.  And then suddenly there's a thunderstorm, a couple of times during summer the heavens fill up to breaking point.    After those hot summer rains, the thunder and lightning, the smell of earth is right in your nostrils, the sweet flavor of life.  After one day of decent rains the countryside is crisp and green, butterflies everywhere.  A total transformation so obvious its difficult to believe unless you've lived there all your life.  There it is all about small miracles, enjoying life for the little things because the rest of it is hot and dry.  If you don't like fishing, you need a decent hobby.  And then I can move to any other province and tell you about the climate and culture and how it makes that region special.  I love South Africa, it will always be the home where my heart lies.    But I live, and I'll see where life takes me, at this moment nothing is set in concrete.  I don't know how wise I am allowing this, but I've made my choices, I've made it this far and I'm going to stick with it.    And I have this blogspot right here.  Slightly_Potty     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm not going to pretend I'm the best Checkers player ever, but I do manage to win an awful lot.  Arrogance?  Maybe.  But its the only thing I can brag about right now.    Igkuk7, or Ian as he is now claiming to be, has recently tried his luck at beating me on a free online checkers site, and predictably, lost horribly.  He did say he was bad at it and he's an honest guy.      Joeli, if you ever read this, I've just proved without a doubt that Ian is a GOOD guy.  He never lies.  He might need a couple of lessons in checkers, but that can be remedied.    Anybody want to challenge me to a game?  Drop me a line, make a date, I'll post the results right here as honestly as I remember them.  I'm not putting the link to the site here, I don't know if its allowed, and I'm to lazy to ask.  But all you would need to do is create a free account so scores of your progress can be kept, and that's it.  Five minutes and you're set, I'll direct any to the site who means to offer a challenge.    Right, with the formalities out of the way, its time to get down to business.  I know the title is "   Checkers - c'mon, anybody brave enough?" but this is my blog, right?    So, um, nice weather we're having.      Acually no, its raining and its miserable and all I can think about is a nice warm woman next to me in bed.  But the funny thing about that is, right at this point in my life, I'm staying in a 16-bedded dorm in a Hostel, right?      Yes I know other people are doing the dirty and they don't care, you hear the grunts and the squeaking beds occasionally.  But I'm slightly more refined.  I think. I say this because I haven't made a single comment under my breath like "Bloody hell, nice jugs" when a particularly good looking woman changes clothes.    The wonder of mixed dorms.    And also its somewhat difficult to communicate with a woman who mainly understands spanish when pretty much all I can say is "te amo sexy chica".       So many nationalities here in this part of London, and I've actually started to like the Australian women... not so much that I want to jump them - AUSSIE AUSSIE AUSSIE OI OI OI - they're STILL the nation that beats and cheats South Africa at cricket.      But its not a bad place to be... just mighty expensive in the long run.  I'm supposed to be searching for a flat I can share with others.  I'll do it as soon as I get up from this very comfortable chair.    You know, I keep confusing myself...  What am I supposed to be talking about?  Checkers? Nope.  Done that.  Hot women.  That's more like it.    I met one particularly gorgeous woman not too long ago, none better.  Not to sure how that's going to work though, but time will tell.  And she's definately worth the wait, that much I've managed to establish.    I've been advised by more than one person to be smart and let women be for a while, but they're so soft, so beautiful, so... I'm looking for a whole lot of adjectives here.  But you women know what you have and generally that's what I like, so lets just leave it at that.  And I have to forget about it?  Sheesh.      That's whats been occupying my mind - and still is - and although I don't feel I've done justice to it, people I know will read this.  Possibly a very nosy sister.  So all scenes of naked women and /or sex will probably be edited out right before I save it, sorry.    Right, have to go for now, and I'd like to hear about any hopeful challenges.    Slightly_Potty     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I have always thought that once someone published an article, short story or novel, it made them a writer.  I know differently now.    You can have a bestseller in print and still not be a true author or writer, just someone who put something down in print.  I have never published anything, although I do have two completed Fiction Fantasy Manuscripts and a third currently under construction.  But I see myself as a writer.    Why?  Is it a double standard, you ask?    Nope, simply that I have come to realize writing isn't just something I do, it has become who I am.  I need to write or else I can't function.  I haven't had the chance to write much of anything of late, but I'm constantly revising and editing my own work so far.  Maybe I will include a review or two from people who have read the not-so-finished projects.     I have a short story I think I'll post here, just to see if there is any favorable replies.  To get the eyes to read this blog though...    I'll do some advertising on the net to get a steady stream of readers, so if you are one of the thousands (I'm sure) to have recieved the link and message "Free Red Hot Porn Right Here!!!" in a chatroom somewhere, then it must have been an accidental error, because I would never do that for hits.      Um.    What was I saying again?  Oh yes.      I have a short story I could post here and being the very impulsive person that I am, I shall name it  urlLink Joline     If you have any short stories of your own you want to get some reviews on, I'm always sure to check in once in a while, even if no one else does, I'll be more than glad to give an honest opinion... if you read mine first.    Mwahahaha.    If you want to find out  urlLink a little more about me ...       That's it for now    Slightly_Potty         urlLink  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right,  I said I'd post something controversial, and I'm going for gold.  What is the one topic constantly on my mind and which I can't seem to hold on to?  Women.  Right.  So no surprises whatsoever but I feel like I can add a twist to it.  I have recently read a blog of a woman that said she would cease posting about her relationship troubles and men, I presume because it made her depressed or made her SOUND depressed - or possibly because she got the impression I thought that was all she thought about.  I'm NOT following her example.  Women are gorgeous creatures and deserved to be thought of.  Terry Pratchett's Discworld characters believe once something is no longer believed or thought of, they dissapear.  I'd hate for women to dissapear, so I'm gonna keep on thinkin' about them.  Problem is that they seem to forget about me fairly quickly.  Anyway.  Live's a bitch and she's ugly and she smells.  And I don't care too much what other people think of me, so IF YOU HAVE COMMENTS AND WOULD LIKE TO PLACE THEM RIGHT THERE AT THE BOTTOM THANK YOU HAVE A NICE DAY you're free to post your thoughts.  Lets get started then.  Diving in at the deep end with concrete boots.     *  What goes through a woman's mind        a) at any given time?   From the counter question  "do men really care?"  I raise my hand and say "yes please", rather nervously.  The implications of actually finding out can be horrendous.  But here's what I think, in NO particular order.  Shoes; lip-gloss; waxing various painful parts; shoes; celery; fruit salad; evanescense; jewelry; Brad Pitt; g-strings and grinning secretly at men noticing no panty-line in tight jeans; tight jeans; Orlando Bloom (hell knows why);  a little deception from time to time; hair; white t-shirts in the rain (okay okay I should probably take that last one out because its my own personal preference but its my blog); nails; clubs; vodka; Bailey's; ABBA; men with long hair; men with short nails; romance novels; small cars; talking; moaning; flowers; shouting; chocolates and various other gifts especially shoes.  From that list it is quite clear I can go on for some time to come but I'm not going to because I'll be here all day.  Its also clear that I'm not on the list.  Orlando Bloom??  Sheesh.  I have a particular experience which could also fit in there somewhere, but its a perception, not so much a word or phrase.  I'm laying next to a beautiful woman and she's looking straight back at me, not saying anything.  She's looking in my eyes and she has beautiful eyes, so at first I don't mind.   I'm also fairly good at outstaring other people, but she doesn't look away.  After a while I look at her lips, her body, grinning, looking at the window and doing some thinking.  I'm thinking "What the hell does she find so fascinating?"  And right there, that very instant, I contradict myself.  I say women don't like me, but this particular woman, out of only a few I've knows fairly intimately, seems to like my immediate company.  Now I've heard of other cases such as this and I'm thinking this is rather common.  When this came up in a conversation with her, she said she was dissapointed that I looked away and thought I didn't like her.  But then why would I be laying next to her?  She's sweet, beautiful, intelligent... and well, she's female.  So I like her.   I'm not a complicated person, really.   But if what I have just described is common, a mind-game rather than an instant like or dislike, then its a perception I can generalise, and for the moment, until I've been told its not so, I'll take it as the truth.  I have a point, I'll get to that.   Point being, I got to name a whole lot of things women like, really easy, and then I have this problem telling if the female in questions likes me back.  She asks me if I like her and I'll tell her the truth.  They ask me for a promise and I give it.  And I keep it.  I have never had a single girl keep her promise.  The terms keeps changing.  I can go way back to kindergarden if need be.  So I end up saying I dunno what women want.  I end up saying I dunno if women know what women want.  I end up saying shit I'm in trouble.  And to close off this post, I have a good quote from one of my friends that goes...:  :If  its been bleeding for 5 days and it ain't dead, don't fookin' trust it."  Slightly_Potty   
    
</post>


</Blog>