<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A couple months ago, when gas prices started to break $2, there was a lot of talk on the internet about boycotting gas for a day.  According to these emails, everyone was going to not buy gas on May 19 and this would throw the oil companies into turmoil, forcing them to lower prices to avoid another boycott.  It is not entirely clear that any number of people actually participated in this boycott, but if you have been to the pumps recently it is quite clear that it did not work.  Gas prices are still pushing $2.30 around me, and while they seemed to level off to some extent, they hardly have started decreasing.  This is because boycotts like this are doomed to fail from the start.  There were a few major flaws with this boycott.  The first flaw is that it only asked people to avoid  buying  gas for a day.  While this might have caused a slight blip on the radar of various oil companies' accountants, it would not actually hurt them.  Even if people did not buy gas that Wednesday, they likely just went out and bought gas Thursday, or if their gas tank looked low and they were capable of planning ahead, the Tuesday before the boycott.  In the end, the oil companies get their money, just on a different day.  What do they care if it takes an extra day to get their money?  The second flaw is that this boycott was annoying for the boycotters.  You had to go out of your way to make sure that you had gas the day before so you wouldn't run out of gas while driving your Hummer on Wednesday.  Finally, not everyone could even participate in this boycott.  If you weren't going to buy gas on Wednesday anyway, you were out of luck when it came to sticking it to the oil companies.  So by this point you may be asking, "What's your point?   Why are you bothering me about a boycott that took place two months ago?"  Well the answer is simple.  I want to suggest a new boycott.  Instead of picking a day to avoid buying gas, I suggest that everyone go out every day and buy the cheapest gas around.  By me, either I can get gas for $2.30 or I can drive for 5 minutes and get gas for $2.09.  I'm sure the same is true in other areas as well.  If you find yourself in a situation where you absolutely must buy gas, and you can't find a cheap gas station, limit your purchase to $5 or however much you think it will take you to get to the next gas station.  This boycott should work.  If enough people start doing it, gas stations will start to have to lower their prices to compete with each other.  Even if it doesn't, you will have saved yourself a few bucks, so you will still be up on the deal.  So go out, find the cheap gas stations in your area, tell your friends, post this on your blogs, send out chain letters advising people that if they tell 3 of their friends about this boycott, Bill Gates will donate $1,000,000 to the war against terrorism, whatever, just get this boycott going. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One piece of Libertarian/Conservative dogma that never made sense to me was the idea that monopolies cannot exist without government intervention (usually excluding property rights).  This is patently false.    If you ever find yourself living in a Libertarian utopia and want to form a monopoly, just take the following steps: 1) Find a relatively scarce natural resource (easy because natural resources are always scarce) 2) Buy the worlds supply of that natural resource (this is a bit harder, but still doable) 3) Inform the market that you now have a monopoly on that resource and they will be paying whatever price you decide to charge.  Of course, I'm sure that there are other, more complicated, ways to create a monopoly in a libertarian society, but this should be enough to disprove any claims that government regulation is necessary for a monopoly to exist.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If anyone has missed the news for the past two days, Saddam had something that resembled an arraignment yesterday.  While I can't really see letting Saddam go free, although it unlikely that he could cause much harm at this point, I don't really like the idea of putting him on trial in a new Iraqi court.    The idea of impromptu war-crime trials has always bothered me.  I have little faith that they will serve any function in seeking justice, but instead are just ways of giving some legitimacy to whatever punishment the victors have decided to impose on the vanquished.  These courts and “laws” are often set up specifically to convict the defendant leaving little room for any form of due process or objectivity.  In the end, all they really do make a mockery of the judicial process.  Rather than set up a show trial for Saddam, I have two better solutions.  The first is to just throw him in jail or execute him with no trial.  Everyone knows that this will be the outcome anyway and at least you will avoid corrupting the legal process.  The second is to put him on trial at the ICC.  This court was already set up with preexisting laws.  Even though I have little doubt that this court will convict Saddam, it will be an objective trial where the prosecutions job will be to show that he committed war crimes and crimes against humanity rather than to design a process that will result in his conviction.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Slate contributor Steven Landsburg  does a good job of explaining exactly what I've been telling people about the minimum wage for years.  He points out that, even if it helps unskilled workers, there are much better ways of doing this.  Instead of increasing the minimum wage, an earned income tax credit (basically giving poor workers a tax refund greater than the total taxes they pay) is a much more efficient way to provide extra income to the poor.    An EITC has many benefits.  The most important is that it gives more flexibility when it comes to deciding who gets an income increase and exactly how much of an increase they get.  When you raise the minimum wage, anyone working for minimum wage gets the same increase.  This means that the high school student, who are working to get some spending money get the same increase as college students who are working to pay for tuition and books, who get the same increase as single mothers working to put food on their children’s table, who get the same increase as the elderly who are working to supplement their Social Security checks.  Now it is possible to think that all of these people deserve to make a little bit more, but there is no reason to believe that they all deserve the exact same amount more.  If we gave an EITC, we could ask questions that would allow us to figure out exactly who is getting the money and how much we want to give them.  The second benefit is that the EITC allows us to spread the burden out in a more meaningful manor.  When you increase the minimum wage, all of the money comes from the business owners and, if the market will let them pass it along, their customers.  While it is always convenient to think of business owners as miserly rich folk who are trying to exploit their workers, this is not always true, especially when it comes to small businesses.  Often business owners are just your average middle class person trying to make a living off a business that they hope will make a profit.  An EITC will come from the general fund, which in turn comes from taxes like the income tax.  These taxes can be set up in such a way that you are collecting money from people who can afford to pay them, rather than just from whoever happens to be employing the minimum wage worker.    Having the money come from the general fund also means that the pain of the EITC will be spread around.  It is easy to say that we should raise the minimum wage when you are not a business owner, because it does not cost most people anything, at least not directly.  Most people are not business owners and the cost of the minimum wage cannot always be passed onto the consumer.  Business owners may not be the least politically powerful group out there, but they still only represent a small number of votes.  With the EITC, everyone who pays taxes will be paying for it, so everyone will have to balance their philanthropy with their checkbook.  This will result in more thought going into determining to what extent our society can really afford to subsidize the poor.  Another benefit of the EITC is that it will decrease the problems of outsourcing.  One of the major reasons for all this outsourcing is that American workers cannot compete with foreign workers who are not required to be paid minimum wage.  If we replaced the minimum wage with an EITC, American workers could compete against these overseas workers.  The EITC would also prevent these workers from going hungry, because it could make up the difference between what workers have to be paid to compete and what it takes to actually afford to live.  In the end, an EITC would be much fairer and much more flexible.  You would be able to give money to only the people who need it and in amounts that represent their actual needs while taking money from people who can actually afford it, rather than people who just happen to be employers.     
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink The Salt Lake Tribune -- Hatch backs nominee who backs St. Paul   Bush is apparently scrapping the bottom of the barrel to find the most outlandish of the religious zealots.  One of his more recent appointees J. Leon Holmes (confirmed 51-46) apparently believes that a woman’s role is to place herself under the authority of her husband and that rapes do not result in conception.  The first of these beliefs is horribly outdated, the second is just plain wrong.  Although the article does no elaborate, it also implies that he has some unpopular views on slavery; a question that I had thought was resolved 150 years ago.    Senator Santorum also managed to once again make a fool of himself during the confirmation debates.  He tried to suggest that since liberals support tolerance, they should be “tolerant” of people who hold the types of views Holmes holds.  As South Park so correctly pointed out, there is a difference between tolerance is not the same thing as acceptance.  You can say that a person should be allowed to hold a certain set of views without saying that their views are correct or that their views should be allowed to make their way into the government.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Apparently, in an attempt to reconcile his Catholic religion with his pro-choice political stance, Kerry has said,  urlLink "I don't like abortion. I believe life does begin at conception. But I can't take my Catholic belief, my article of faith, and legislate it on a Protestant or a Jew or an atheist ... who doesn't share it. We have separation of church and state in the United States of America."   While I see this working in some situations, for example one could think that drinking is a sin, but still want to allow people to make their own decisions, I don't think that you can believe that life starts at conception, but abortion should still be legal.    While people often say, "you can't legislate morality," they rarely actually mean it or if they do, they have not though very hard about the question.  Almost all of our laws come down to questions of morality.  The reason why there is a law against rape, murder or theft is because morality.  We feel that it is evil (or bad if you think evil is too strong a word) to rape, murder or steal and want to protect people from this evil.  If the moral code of most Americans said that it was perfectly fine to murder someone or steal their property, it would not make any sense to have laws against either of these acts.  We do think that killing and taking (murder and theft require the act to be illegal) can be perfectly all right, or at least not bad, in certain situation such as self-defense and taxes, and in those situations, we have no law against the acts.  When people say, "you can't legislate morality" they really mean one of two things.  The first possible meaning is that you cannot make someone moral through legislation.  You can pass all the laws you would like criminalizing vice, but you will not succeed in convincing anyone that these vices are actually wrong.  You may succeed in discouraging people from committing these “immoral” acts, but these people will be refraining to avoid the consequences, not because they have all of the sudden become “good” people.  The second possible meaning, the one that seems more common, actually is that “you shouldn’t legislate morality.”  This view comes from the concept of separation of church and state.  The idea is that you should be allowed to decide what acts you believe cause your god to send you to hell, I get to decide what acts I believe will cause my god to cause me to be reincarnated in the form of a used car salesman and the government should stay away from this question.  However, most people would agree that as soon as your actions do more than potentially make your afterlife a drag, the government gets to step in.  Eating meat on Friday may cause you to go to hell, but it does not affect anyone else, so it is none of the governments business.  It is not entirely clear whether flying an airplane into the World Trade Center will send you to hell or get you 72 virgins, but it certainly affects other people and therefore it has become the governments business to weigh your pursuit of 72 virgins with the interest of the people that you might kill in the process.    This brings us back to Kerry’s statement.  He seems to be suggesting that just because his religion tells him something, that is no reason to legislate accordingly, and therefore is falling into the second meaning of “you can’t legislate morality.”  Unfortunately, what his religion tells him is that there is a second person being affected by the choice to have an abortion.  This is no longer a case of eating meat on Friday; this is a case where his religious beliefs tell him that having an abortion is killing another human being, a human whose value is equal to that of any human outside the womb.  If this is the case, then it seems like the only possible conclusion is that the fetus’ right to life, usually considered the most fundamental of all rights, outweighs the mother’s right to have an abortion.  Even the decision in Roe v. Wade was premised on the idea that a fetus, which has not reached viability, was not a person deserving of a right to life.    Now there are many ways to dislike abortion but still think that it should be legal.  For example, you could believe that a fetus is not a person and does not deserve a right to life, but God just disapproves of the act, the same way he might disapprove of masturbation or skipping church.  You could also believe that in the end, women who have abortions wind up regretting having had them and therefore you might disapprove of abortions the same way you might disapprove of getting a tattoo or eating too much cake.  The important part is that in neither of these situations have you introduced a second party whose rights you believe are being violated.  So what is my point?  I think that Kerry has to seriously consider what he believes.  If he believes, as his religion tells him, that a fetus is a person, then he really needs to get himself on the other side of the abortion debate, preferably before he accepts the democratic nomination.  It is also possible that he does not believe that fetuses are people and he was just reciting the Catholic dogma on the subject and what he should believe if he wanted to be a good Catholic.  This would put him in the same category as the millions of other Catholics who generally believe in the religion but disagree with the Pope on a point or two.  If this is the case, I think he should do his best to avoid trying to reconcile his religious views in public, as it does nothing more than make him seem disingenuous.  If he feels that he must appeal to the pro-life voters, I suggest he take one of the positions I suggested above that fall short of saying that a fetus is a person.    In the end, I am still going to vote for Kerry.  No matter how convoluted his views on abortion, he is still not Bush.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It looks like the new Iraqi government will soon be facing its first big test.  Moqtada Sadr, the Iraqi religious leader that caused all the trouble back in April, has decided that he isn't happy with the new government claiming it is "illegitimate and illegal" and has called for the end to the truce he set up with back in May with the US government.  This will likely put the Iraqi government in the position of fighting what seems like a very popular religious leader, almost certainly with the help of the US, not a good thing if they want to look like they are more than just a puppet government.    The Iraqi government has taken a few steps to avoid this problem.  They are apparently in negotiations with delegates from Sadr's Mahdi Army about dismantling the militia in exchange for amnesty.  If these talks succeed, the new government will have managed to avert their first major test.   If not, I expect some serious problems in Iraq in the near future.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In case anyone has not been paying attention to legal news lately, in between telling Bush that he cannot throw people into dark holes with no due process and telling Ashcroft that a painting of a naked child is protected speech, the Supreme Court declared parts of the Washington State sentencing guidelines unconstitutional.   The decision in  Blakey v. Washington  objected to the fact that certain facts were being used in sentencing that were not found by a jury. Although the Supreme Court said that they were only talking about the Washington State sentencing guidelines, the federal sentencing guidelines work in a very similar way, and  Blakey  has left federal judges around the country trying to figure out exactly how this affects the federal sentencing guidelines, and coming up with a variety of answers.   This whole mess has lead to one of the best quotes from a politician that I have seen in a while. In response to a Utah judge who declared the entire federal sentencing guidelines unconstitutional while saying that the criminal justice system was not, in fact, in crisis, Sen. Patrick Leahy said, “Judge Cassell, you say there's no crisis but you just held the entire criminal justice system unconstitutional?"     Correction:  I just noticed that the case was actually  Blakely v. Washington , not  Blakey v. Washington .&nbsp; I have gotten quite a few hits, including one from the DOJ,&nbsp;from people searching Google for the later though, so I think that I will leave it.     
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One of the disadvantages of going to school is that every so often you will find yourself with a big project and not enough time to do it.  I currently find myself in such a situation.  I have a 20-page paper on rape shield laws due on 7/27 and I have barely started to write it.  This means that for the next 2 weeks, most of my life will be taken up writing my paper and less time will be spent writing blog entries.  If you continue to check back though, I will start posting an entry a day as soon as I finish my paper.  I will probably get a few blog entries in during my spare time as well, but probably less than one a day. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       With the rise of libertarianism, there seems to be a lot of emphasis on economic efficiency.  The idea is that government interference cuts down on efficiency.  Income tax cuts down on incentive to work, government programs do not seek efficiency, welfare decreases incentive to work, trade barriers prevent the most efficient person from doing each job, etc.  Basically, whenever you have the government does something, it is less efficiently done than if you just let the free market take its course.  For the most part, this is true, there are certain cases where externalities make this not true, but these can be looked at as exceptions rather than a general rule.  The real problem though is defining “efficiency.”  If your goal is to maximize the country or the worlds GDP, then libertarians are probably right, you should let the free market take its course and either do away with government interference or at least limit to clear cases of externalities.  This of course is not the only acceptable goal.  Many people would probably agree that a world with a lower, but fairly evenly distributed GDP is better than a world with a higher GDP that is all in the hands of a single person or even a few people.    Some of this belief comes from morality, most moral systems support the idea of helping those less fortunate, but some of it actually comes from economics itself.  There is a concept of the marginal utility of the dollar, which basically says that the first dollar you make is worth a lot more to you than the millionth.  If you are broke and you drop a dime, you will bend down to pick it up.  If you are a millionaire and you drop a dime, or even a $100 bill, there is a decent chance that you will just keep on working.  When looking at the GDP, this means that a high, but unevenly distributed GDP will not necessarily bring the same amount of happiness to a country as a slightly lower, but more evenly distributed GDP.  The average happiness of a rich person and a poor person might not be equal to the average happiness of two middle class people.  Basically, my point is that economics is no more a way to determine morality than physics.  All either can do is tell you what your end result is.  Physics can tell you that if you drop an anvil on someone, it will hit them with a certain impact, but it can’t tell you whether or not you should hit them with that impact.  Economics can tell you that an income tax will result in a certain decrease in productivity, but it can’t tell you if that decrease in productivity is worth whatever you will get out of those taxes.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I really try to avoid conspiracy theories.  I would like to believe that, for all his faults, Bush still has some respect for the electoral process, but they keep coming out with things like this.  According to this article, counter-terrorist officials are looking into what steps would be necessary to postpone the November elections in the case of a terrorist attack.  I suppose its not that horrible of an idea, you wouldn't want everyone in New York City to miss their chance of voting because of another 9/11, but depending on what the plans they come up with, this really creates a risk of abuse.  Whatever plan they have better have some major checks in it, like the election can be delayed by one day with a 90% vote from both houses of Congress. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The  urlLink The New York Times  has a good article on how the Bush administration is pushing its conservitive values onto scientists doing research into topics related to sex.  Apparently, they have been cutting funding to a lot of studies and organizations that have more liberal views of how to deal with human sexuality.    The article also points out that the Bush administration has been playing fast and loose with the facts in this area, pointing to information on the CDC's pushing of the idea that condomns aren't that useful in preventing diseases, omitting information about contraception on its website and blocking funding to sex ed programs that don't focus on abstinence.  My favorite quote in the article was from the head of the "Traditional Values Coalition" who says "There's an arrogance in the scientific community that they know better than the average American."  I mean can you believe that someone who has years of education in a subject would think that they know better than someone who probably hasn't taken a science course since high school?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In 90% of all cases, when someone attempts to hide behind the justification of State's Rights and federalism, it is a sham.  Very few people actually support the idea of state's rights as a general principle.  In almost every case, it is just a refuge for people who don't think that they can get their position accepted in a national forum.  Conservatives are traditionally the party of federalism, well at least since FDR took office.  Conservatives have used federalism as a basis for their arguments against everything from Roe v. Wade to integration of schools to school prayer, always claiming that these issues should be left up the individual states.  Liberals on the other hand traditionally claimed that the federal government best controlled these issues; because states could not be trusted handle them appropriately.  Now, conservatives have pretty much seized control of the federal government.  Bush is a conservative, both houses are controlled by conservatives and the Supreme Court is, for the most part, controlled by conservatives (sure O'Connor votes with the liberals every so often, but for the most part, she is a conservative).  So what happens, do the conservatives in government use this as an opportunity to return the country to its federalist roots?  No, of course not.  They just start pushing there own centralized policies.  Ashcroft has taken on liberal state laws involving both medical marijuana and assisted suicide.  Congress has passed the partial birth abortion bill, removing the question of how to handle 3rd trimester abortions from the states and has recently attempted to pass the Federal Marriage Amendment making gay marriage a federal, rather than federalist issue.  Bush passed No Child Left Behind, which increases federal control over education standards. Even the Supreme Court switched its views on federalism when they overruled the Florida Supreme Courts ruling on Bush v. Gore.  Liberals have been no better.  On most, if not all of these issues, they have given up their stance that the Federal Government knows best.  Now the liberals are claiming that these issues should be left to the states.  My only conclusion is that, with the exception of a few principled libertarians, everyone really wants a strong federal government; just they want a strong federal government that supports their ideology.  When they cannot have that, they resort to claiming that the decision should be up to the states.  I would even suggest that libertarians don't really support state's rights, they want the government out of everything and they see moving power from the Federal Government to the states as the first step in the process.  Inspired by  urlLink The Late, Great States  at  urlLink slate.msn.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After the invasion of Iraq, when it started to become clear that the WMD and the links to al Qaeda were not going to show up, supporters of the war fell back on another justification for their war, mass graves.  If someone were to call up Sean Hannity and start mentioning that there were no WMD found he would respond "What about the rape rooms? What about the mass graves?"  Well the Abu Ghraib prison abuse scandal seriously put a damper in claims that we made Iraq better off by getting rid of the rape rooms.  After all, its hard to claim that as an accomplishment when it turns out that we just replaced them with our own.  But now, a report by  urlLink The Guardian  seems to be bringing the significance of the mass graves into question.  The original number thrown around by US and UK supporters of the war was as high as 400,000 people buried in mass graves.  So far there have only been about 5,000 found.  Now 5,000 dead is certainly nothing to sneeze at, and its likely that the number will turn out to be somewhat higher, as we probably haven't found every mass grave and probably not everyone killed by Saddam was buried in a mass grave, but unless this number grows significantly, Saddam’s “mass murderer” status will be put into serious question.  He will no longer rank up there with Hitler, Stalin and Pol Pot, but rather with people like Bush whose activities have only resulted in the deaths of 9,000 or so Iraqi civilians.  Well that comparison isn’t entirely fair, as Bush probably had a bit more justification his war than Saddam did for his purges, but it is still something to think about.  The point is that it is unlikely that the humanitarian crisis in Iraq was anywhere close to the magnitude that supporters of the war originally suggested. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For the past week, news agencies around the country have all but dedicated their coverage to the Democratic National Convention.  For some reason, I just can't get into this coverage.  I think there are two major reasons for my disinterest.  The first is that I have already made up my mind who to vote for.  I'm voting for Kerry, or more correctly, whoever happens to have a "D" next to their name in the presidential race come November.  I made up my mind pretty much in December of 2000, when Bush was officially declared president and this decision has been growing stronger with every passing day.  I have basically disagreed with every decision Bush has made, from his narrow, religious explanation for why the terrorists attacked us, to his faith based initiatives, to his tax cuts, to the lies he espoused going into Iraq.  Since I already know who I am voting for, campaign coverage has pretty much bored me.  The second reason is I see the DNC as a giant infomercial.  Its a bunch of people patting eachother on the back and saying how great their choice for president is.  There is no critical thought going into it, just marketing.  They are saying what they think will get Kerry elected and that is it.  When I see marketing, I am instantly turned off.  Its not so much that I think that they are lying, it is just that I don't think that the truth plays any part in the matter and so I am not interested.  This is not really an indictment of the DNC, I am sure I will feel the exact same way about the RNC.  I just do not find these types of events interesting.  Hopefully tomorrow, we will get a short reprieve from these infomercials before the RNC starts at the end of August. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Democrats in Congress are apparently getting  upset  about the Republican's abuse of procedural rules to get their agenda past. Because of the Republican's majority position, they have been able to do things such as block debate on Democratic issues and to hold voting open until they can manage to get enough votes to get it passed. The most recent example of this was a recent vote on a Democrat bill to modify the PATRIOT Act. At the end of the scheduled 15 minutes, the bill had enough votes to pass, so the Republicans kept the voting open for another 23 minutes until they could convince enough Republicans to come around and vote against it to keep it from passing. In the end, the bill was rejected by a 210 to 210 vote, one vote short of a majority.   Of course the Democrats have not been innocent of abusing procedural rules to get their way either. Republicans and conservative pendants have been whining that Democrats have been using filibuster to block Bushs Judicial appointments since 2001, when the Democrats first used this technique to block  urlLink Miguel Estrada . A week ago, the Democrats used this technique to block  urlLink three more judges  bringing the number of filibustered judges up to ten. Of course, they have confirmed 200 other judges appointed by Bush.   What both sides need to realize is that these are the rules of the game. If the Republicans can pass a bill by holding the vote open until they can manage to get the votes, they should. If the Democrats can block a few objectionable judges by blocking a cloture vote, they should. I am sure that in a few years, when the roles are reversed and the Democrats hold s majority in Congress (god willing) the Democrats will be the ones holding votes open and the Republicans will be the ones filibustering. If either side thinks what the other side is doing is unfair, they can always introduce a bill to change the rules.   I have no respect for the people who sit around complaining that the other side is using these longstanding rules to their advantage as if they were cheating. To me this is like a baseball player going to argue with the umpire because they just got out due to the infield fly rule. If the rule is out there, expect the other side to use it to their advantage. To do otherwise would be foolish.    Addendum: While debating a cloture vote for two of Clinton's Judicial nominees, Sen Orrin Hatch, a leading&nbsp;opponent&nbsp;of the current Democratic filibusters of judicial appointees said, "Naturally, in the last week or so of a session, there is going to be the threat of some filibusters. It is one of the few tools that the minority has to protect itself and those the minority represents."140 Cong Rec S 13969 (1994)&nbsp; Admittedly, he did also suggest that the President should get a vote on these nominees.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm all done with class for the summer semester.  I sent in my last paper in today.  Hopefully I will have time now to start posting on a regular basis again.  Now I just have to find something to post about. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>