<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      LOL. I passed my drive test today!!! YAY!!! Finally, it's about damn time. And it's like 1 in the morning and i'm tried as fuck, damn work. *sigh* So yah.. um... imma go now, kinda in&nbsp;a sore mood... I guess i'll ttyl! Bye! ~Vicki *now legal* haha 
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's sad cuz that's our "motto". No really, it sez that on my computer at work: "Scan until u die" and my log in thing: Scan4Life. Good times, today seemed rly rly long cuz I wuz so tired, I scanned only like 250 docs then I OCRed the entire time. I usually have a good lunch there but the girls I work w/ are like anorexic.... one has a salad sometimes and the other won't eat, and vice-versa.... or they both don't eat. It's kind of sick then makes me feel gross, u no how that is. But I guess I ignore it most of the time... But they're both rly nice girls. I'm taking my drive test this Saturday! I'm scurred.... lol. Then I have this dinner thing to go to that night to get acknowledged for being a "subject" and I dunno wut... lol. *sigh* I haven't seen like anybody this summer. Some ppl may be very suprised when they see me. Christina: I've cleaned up! lol. Work has done me over. (haha, it wuz all the nagging that&nbsp;got to me rly,&nbsp;I've just been stubborn)&nbsp;I got nice clothes, all high-neck shirts and stuff. Good 4 me? Yay perhaps? lol. Now I just need shoes.... lmao. But anywayz, I hope to get together soon w/ some ppl, as soon as that license rolls in yah? :-P And this thing, grrr... never posts for me on time, I don't understand. Hopefully this will this time. So I guess I'll talk 2 u guys later! Bye Bye! ~All Work &amp; No Play 
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, it finally showed the posts... they weren't working at first. So, just kidding about that... lol. Yesterday wuz soooo fun! I lit off about... 500+ bottle rockets, 30+ roman candles (some rly big ones that were pretty and exciting! lol), snakes, several fountains, artillary shells, flashers, flyers, a bunch of crazy shit. I only burnt my thumb several times but hey, it wuz so worth it. *sigh* It's the end of my weekend, I gotta go to work tomorrrow. 5 is so early! It's like skool! AAAHHHH! *chews on arm* Erm... yah... I definitely gotten hang w/ ppl on the weekend, maybe treat some ppl to a lil sumpin' sumpin' when I get paid. Hehe. The thingy wuz closed, AGAIN! *shoots it* Gggrrr... Well I gotta go, I need some sleep, no need to be cranky the first day of work + PMSing! How awesome! lmao. Have fun in the sun guys! TTYS! ~Vicki
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On my profile... y duzn't it show my recent posts? And y do i have to refresh when I click on my blog name?
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       LOL. I decided I'd make a blog thingy too, since other ppl r on here and TOD isn't so reliable sometimes. My summer's been pretty good so far. Went boating and innertubing and I have like 5 bruises, they're pretty tasty looking. I'm taking my written this Saturday and my drive next Saturday, it's about time I got around to it. Emily, Amanda, Carl, Marry, and Stina already got theirs! lol. Hey so I'm like 4-5 months slow.. i'm getting there! Haha. But OMG, I'm soooo happy! I was supposed to get this job for the entire sumemr, and then it turns out the opening wuz filled, then I heard this morning that I get a job for a month, which is cool, cuz if I don't have any money I can't drive my car anyways which would totally suk. How's work going for u Bailey? Hope everyone's having a blast this summer. The only downside is I have to wake up at like 5 everyday of the week! Aack! *pulls hair out* Hhhmm.... lol. Maybe one of these weekends I'll just throw a party for the hell of getting together yah? And where is the damn sun? Hehe, I wanna go to the beach! Hey well if anyone's bored and wants to pick my sad-ass up to go somewhere I am here! CALLLLLLL MEEEE! LMAO! Anyone seen Bailey lately? Well I gotta go do gay ass chores. LOVE YOU GUYS! ~Vicki 
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So yesterday I was all excited cuz I found out Rob gets to go camping w/ me for sure, and I went to bed all happy and wut not. But then this morning my mom decides to tell me that my dog wuz bleeding last night "oh, it didn't look too bad, not much blood." She's a fucking black dog, of course it's not gonna look like much when u can't see it? Couldn't she have checked more to see if it wuz  a deep wound?! Fuckin' A. Then she's like "and I wuz petting her and she felt very frail, her back bone was slim and she felt very thin." Uh yah, duh, she's old, and she needs to be fed more often. My dad knew that she had been wandering lately cuz unfortunately she's very old and can't remember anything so she just kind of goes whenever and can never find her way back, did he keep her inside? No, of course not, he'd rather let her wander off and die slowly on her own. If I would have known she was "sick" last night I would have taken care of her!!!! I am very mad and upset, I just want to see her before she's gone forever! She's my favorite, I got her for my birthday! So now I'm at work balling my eyes out for going on an hour now... I haven't done anything becuz I'm so angry at my parents. We're leaving for a week and I'll die if I don't find her before we leave. She means so much to me!!! If anybody (not like anyone rly live sby me) hears about her/finds her call me please! *Missing her Baby* 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yah well, almost. It's 12:28. Mite as well b one... I left from work at 5 today, didn't get home til 8!!! Traffic was HORRIBLE!!! and on... wednesday? I didn't get home til 8:15... crazy f*in traffic. I haven't been home on time once, ever, since I started work. *sigh* Work makes me sleepy, but i get monday off! Cuz I'm a pimp! lol. So imma go see The Village... I hope. Today Me, Emily, Tranace, and Rob cruised around for a while then I went back to Rob's. I'm so happy cuz vacay is in like, a week, it's gonna b the shit... minus the mom and dad part, then it'll b cool. lol. Wut else is new? Um... not a damn thing. lol. Things r boring that's about it...mmhmmm so now i have nothing to say... great. haha. Well I'm going to bed, it's now 12:32... haha. Leave me notes guys! *muah much*
</post>


</Blog>