<Blog>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Time Of Your Life - Green Day   Another turning point, a fork stuck in the road  Time grabs you by the wrist, directs you where to go  So make the best of this test, and don't ask why  It's not a question, but a lesson learned in time   It's something unpredictable, but in the end is right,  I hope you had the time of your life   So take the photographs, and still frames in your mind  Hang it on shelf in good health and good time  Tattoos of memories and dead skin on trial   For what it's worth, it was worth all the while   It's something unpredictable, but in the end is right,  I hope you had the time of your life   (music)   It's something unpredictable, but in the end is right,  I hope you had the time of your life    It's something unpredictable, but in the end is right,  I hope you had the time of your life   We had the time of our  in BMS!  Here's to the next years in BHS! Go class of 2008!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To People who think they know me.. You don't really know me.. You never really did.. You only jugded my by what u saw.. You Should look inside instead.. I'm not the girl I used to be not so long ago...I've finally Decided its about time to let the real me show.. I'm not a perfect person.. I never claimed to be... But I hate it when people think that I'm the girl I used to be.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      empty space inside my heart nothing will ever fill the hole  you've left inside of me when you left me  cold  and  still 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You're in my dreams every night...  Am I in yours too?... I wish on every star I see...  And wish to be with you.... I try my best to show you... That without you I'm real blue.... And hoping that you'll love me back As Much as I love you...   To ADC 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found a new obsession: one word....ELMO
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's like 1 in the morning, and I think this site is so awesome that I had to make another post explaing all about how I can't fall asleep or that I'm really hungry and really hyper....But I'm too lazy... I'm going back to bed....ZZZzzzz
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you have a weird obsession?  I used to but I don't anymore... At first it was feet... then it was cows... then it was Anthony...I don't have anything to obsess about anymore...Any Ideas let me know!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Anthony, There's so much I can write about about you! We've been through so much together in the past 2 years that I really don't know where to start... My life has changed so much since I met you.  You are always there for me when I need you no matter what, no matter when...  So thanks Anthony, I love you so much! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a friend named Josh (Hi Josh) he lives in the Welfare town too and goes to the same wefare high school I do... We have so much fun there (not really)  Anyway, Josh is cool and we have lots of fun on the way home from school on the Welfaremobile with our friend Carissa (Hey Carissa!) We like to make fools out of ourselves singing stupid gay songs and dancing like freaks (cuz to tell the truth we kinda are) Anyways... so ya... that's kinda it, besides that Josh is a happy person and is good to have around, cuz when I'm sad, he makes me smile instantally, so I just wanna thank him for all that he's done for me! I LOVE YOU JOSHY!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am!  April.. In my happy place... This is a place for people who need a happy place sometime...So read my pathetic thoughts and add some of your own... Maybe we all can be happy someday....
     

    
</post>


</Blog>