<Blog>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another attempt at creating an online journal. Let's see how long this one lasts for before I forget about it.  Sitting around. Waiting to go to K's. It's the day of our family Winter Olympics. Oh yes. It is. Events consist of: darts, carpet bowls, Mr-T card game, UNO, table tennis, bobs, nutella eating and beer drinking. Still have to choose a country to represent. I need to get some snags to take.   One week of my hols over already. Fuck it. I don't want to go back to school. It seems hard to believe that half the year is over already. I don't know what to do about next year. I don't want to stay there, but I want to get an ongoing position so I can go away and then come back if I need to. Fuckers. I hate it. Maybe it's because I've got shitty year levels. All the left-over ones that no one else wanted aka Year 9s. Give them to the teacher who doesn't know any better and has only been teaching for a year. You know it's bad when even the Principal makes jokes and acknowledges the fact that the Year 9's are the worst year level in the school. Yes. That's really good. I love teaching them. 75 of them. Hm. It's great. Yes.   If anything it's not making me want to continue teaching, it's driving me away from it.   So, one week left of doing nothing, but sleeping, drinking and being lazy.  I've got two hours to kill. I've already cleaned the house. I'm not doing school work. Maybe I'll just sit here. And sit. Actually, I might crimp my hair. How novel.   Let's keep count of how long it tkaes me to post again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      on toast. Together. Tasty. I feel a bit hungover. I'm still in bed. It's sunny and looks nice out but I just can't be fucked getting up. I'm thinking of curling up and going back to sleep for a few hours. Got home about 11 last night. Then the phone rings at 3am. I hate when that happens. It always scares the shit out of me. Anyway it was K, wanting to be picked up from the pub. Obviously she didn't remember that we'd left the car at her house because we were in no state to drive, hence not having a car to go pick her and B up. Fuckknuckles.   Yesterday was fun though. It's good when we're all together. We're so stupid, but in a stupid good way. I didn't win any events. Bastards. I lost darts by one fricken point. Call me loser. The beer was tasting good though.   M is working again today. I've just been trying to see if I can find a price on the net for a round the world ticket. The seed has been planted. It's time to start planning otherwise I'll just keep putting it off. Of course I don't want to leave my family, but it's just something I've wanted to do for sooooo long and haven't had the funds/opportunity to do it. By the end of this year there shouldn't be anything holding me back. I still have to talk to M about it, but I'm pretty sure we're thinking along the same lines. If not, then well... we'll figure something out.  Gomez concert is tomorrow. After all the hassle with my ticket, K says she might have one for me, but I don't know if I really even want to go. I like them, but I'm not that cut if I don't go to see them. It's GA and I won't be able to see sweet fuck all anyway. On the otherhand, it'd be good to go away to Melb. for a few days instead of just sitting around here.   Back to sleep.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>