<Blog>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a break during my math class and I have to write about the most amazing thing we spent 15 minutes talking about.  1. Cooking the Books 2. Fuzzy Numbers 3. History of Imaginary Numbers 4. Solutions  starting with #1   urlLink Cooking the books:  Knowingly providing incorrect information in a company's financial statements. Illegal.   #2  urlLink Fuzzy Numbers  oh...fuzzy wuzzy was a bear. fuzzy wuzzy had no hair. fuzzy wuzzy wasnt very good at fuzzy numbers wuzz he?  #3 History of Imaginary Numbers  Mihalek: You know...there was a time that nobody could do quadatric equations, but then somebody discovered imaginary numbers.  Some kid: Who discovered imaginary numbers?  Of course, not even my teacher knew this, so i took the liberty of find this out.  Acutally i couldn't find who discovered them...more of just  urlLink what  they were.   #4 Solutions  Sometimes...no solution is a solution in its self.  Isn't that so philosphical?
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently had a friend who was just crying in his LJ, "omg...I'm emo. worse than that, i'm a black emo! whats the world coming to?!?" but thats just a summarized version of what he said. Anyways. It made me giggle cause i'm like hehehh "emo..." So on his comments, some chick asked what emo was. How could someone not know what emo was? So I did me some research, and for those who are truly curious about what emo really is and its history, this is the site for you, but please... urlLink don't cry about it 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh dear god, for those of you who have ever written poety and write with alot of personal pronouns such as... "I" "me" "my"...well sorry, but you're gonna kill yourself. According to a computer designed by  Some Texan Proffesor 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have an  Online Journal  but i decided I needed somewhere to post my random sites. I didn't think it right to turn my journal into a blog. So here is my blog version of Pirate Flag.  Actually, I'm a bit confused. On the html i have www.livejournal.com/users/pirate_flag written, however when i published it on here, blogger changed it to http://pirate_flag.blogspot.com/www.livejournal.com/users/pirate_flag . Perhaps theres a secret war going on between LJ and Blogger. And this is their way of seeking damage. By not being able to link to LJ. Well, my thought to this is...didn't your mothers ever teach you to play nice?
    
</post>


</Blog>