<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    In case you didn't notice.. There is a LOT of sarcasm in that title.     &nbsp;   I am now pursuing the road of divorce.&nbsp; It is going to be complicated even though I don't have to worry about spousal conflict.&nbsp; I have moved within the last few months so I don't even know which state I will file under.&nbsp; It should be difficult to marry and easy to divorce.. Not the other way around.     &nbsp;   I am back to my old ways of having to many pets, hehe.&nbsp; I now have 4 rats and still 12 dwarf hamsters.&nbsp; They are all cuties though... The hours of cage cleaning makes them seem not so cute at times.&nbsp; At least the hamsters like me.&nbsp; The rats are newbies and are showing it.     &nbsp;   Well, that is all my main news for now.&nbsp; Didn't want my two blogger fans to feel I ignore them (I do have two fans...Right???)     &nbsp;  &nbsp;    

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday was my friend's 21st birthday.  I visted her at work with another friend.  We drank a little to much wine before hand though so I was like.."uh...duh...sleepy" hehe.  Not much else is happening really.  I am reading a StarCraft book.  StarCraft is a computer game by Blizzard and its a great game.  If I get lucky I will beable to buy a new computer within a few months and I can play online games again.  If you want to donate to my fund, let me know.. I only accept checks in dividens of 50 :)   

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, I have already fallen behind, haha.  My life really isn't exciting enough for a every day blog anyhow.  I went back to work after 6 days off, that is always a joy.  Got to fire pyrotechnics.. of course I was the one who did everything wrong.  I now have a missing piece of skin to prove it.  HAHA  And they want me to know how to operate fire arms..  If you want to watch a lot of awesome dancing.. see the movie, "You Got Served."  Defiantly some cool moves.  They story line really isn't new, but the dancing is impressive.  Another good movie, The Green Mile.  I just bought it, very awesome.  Just the little mouse makes it worth it, but of course it has a good story.  I am awaiting the Village to come out.  I loved Signs, so I have a feeling this will be a good one.  Looks like the producer is finding his genre.  He will probably be a favorite of mine.  This weekend is a friend's 21st birthday.. so if you see a puking redhead around the Soo... yea that is me.  If you don't know what the Soo is... Good ;)  That is all for now! 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here is the results of an interesting personality test.  Even though it doesn't sound real good... it is true.  Wackiness: 52/100 Rationality: 40/100 Constructiveness: 72/100 Leadership: 46/100    You are an SECF-- Sober Emotional Constructive Follower . This makes you a  hippie . You are passionate about your causes and steadfast in your commitments. Once you've made up your mind, no one can convince you otherwise. Your politics are left-leaning, and your lifestyle choices decidedly temperate and chaste.  You do tremendous work when focused, but usually you operate somewhat distracted. You blow hot and cold, and while you normally endeavor on the side of goodness and truth, you have a massive mean streak which is not to be taken lightly. You don't get mad, you get even.  Take it yourself  http://hokev.brinkster.net/quiz/default.asp?quiz=Better+Personality&page=1   

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is the kind of Heart that I have... what kind do you have?    Your Heart is Red    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Greetings Everyone,  I have decided to open a blog.  This way those of you who are really bored can read about my life.  Fortunately for you there is a spell check on this, hehe.  If you want to see photos of things you can go to  urlLink    As of now, I live in Michigan, am a Marine Science Technition in the Coast Guard, working on a divorce, and am the proud owner of 13 dwarf hamsters, two rats, and a Civic.  That sums things up nicely I think.  Tosha 

						
</post>


<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; mum brot home two more boys.&nbsp; we havnt seen dem yet becus mum sais jenkins might hav mites.&nbsp; i dont no what mites r, but i guess dey are bad. &nbsp; the boys are down below us in our old cage.&nbsp; we got a new one with a ramp so we wuld stop being so lazy.&nbsp; nuthin wrong with laziness. &nbsp; well, we are not letten the other two on the blog, so dont wurry bout seeing dem. &nbsp; The Rats.. &nbsp;  blog...what blog..i wan.....ACK!  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      our mom cleened da cage to day.  she says she buy a new n betta cage.  It betta be better.  neither one of uz screemed wen she pickd uz up.  robert also started to take treats frum her.  we haf to give her hope so she will buy stuff for us.  Robert and Jenkins
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      we saw mummi open a bog thing, so we wanted one too.  we are tu big gud lookin boy rats.  robert is a blu dumbo ear.. or that is what mummi says.  I dont tank robert look like dumbo at all.  jenkins is a blu hood rat.  ww hope u like our bog and visit ofen.  Jenkins n Robert
     

    
</post>


</Blog>