<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, ginanahan ako magsulat ng bagong entry ulit ngayon! Hahaha! Panalo Ateneo! Tanginaaaa! Ang exciting! Hanep Fonacier! Ang laki mo talagang inspirasyon sa team kahit di ka na makakalaro! Hanep Tenorio! Galing mo mag-tres! Hanep Intal! Galing mo sumaksak at dumakdak! Hanep Nkemakolam! Galing mo magcheer! You go dawg! Hanep Quimson! Ambano mo magfree-throw! Ikaw na papalit sa commercial ni Taulava sa Accel! Hahahaha! Siyet, wala ako sa sarili ngayon! Di ako tuloy makapag-"courtside reporter mode!" Ibabahagi ko na lamang sa inyong mga kababayan ko ang mga linalaman ng aking utak noong nagsagupaan ang koponan ng Adamson at ang koponan ng aking eskuwelahan, Ateneo.  Thoughts during the Game  Totoy ng Adamson. Ang yayabang. Ang fe-feeling. Talo naman! Taena tong si Hate. Mukhang pinulot sa terminal ng dyip. Tapos taga-tawag niya ng pasahero itong si Cabahug. Whoa! Kamukha nga ni Poloyapoy si Marvin the Martian! No bullshit! Mag-ama ata tong si Arao at Arrespacochaga eh! Baby-faced baby Tiu versus baby-faced damulag Bono. Hanep tong si Bono. Sana nag-Ateneo na lang itong dakilang anak ni Buddha. Galing galing! Idol! Punyeta. Sarap hambalusin ng baseball bat itong malanding baklang baboy na Adamson fan. Feel na feel niya pagka-sexy niya! Sexy nga naman siya.. para sa baboy! (during the release of Tenorio's last second three) Oye! Panalo na Ateneo! *sabay taas ng kamay* (after saying the sentence above) Swiiiissshh! *ball goes through net* (thought after the game) Ang galing ko talaga! Napakapsychic ko! Parang saranggola itong si Intal. Taena naman itong Quimson. Mukhang eksperto kung pumorma sa free-throw line sabay airball naman. Wawa naman si Tenorio. Siya na nga nagpapanalo, Larry pa rin ang sigaw ng tao! Taena, pagnandito pa si Fonacier, malamang panalo by 50 points Ateneo. Bilib din ako sa confidence nitong Hateng toh. 55-55. For the win time na. Nasa kanya ang bola. Nandyan naman si Cabahug, Abadia at Bono. Ayaw niya bitiwan yung bola. Feeling star-player naman tong ampao na toh. Buti nga sa yo. Mintis! Bobo! Parang Ateneo-La-Salle tong game na toh ah! (First Quarter) Hayup naman itong si Membrere! Energetic kahit 20 lamang ng Adamson! Talo pa niya si Mr. Pure Energy Gary V.! Hanep! Tama ung naisip ko nung Ateneo-Lasalle game. (See 7/12/04 entry, "Champion") Offense wins games. Defense wins championships. Tsambaleros never lose!  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa! I haven't updated this for quite a while. Because of public clamor, I feel that I owe my adoring fans an update. Here goes.  This week has been the most student friendly week so far. We only had 2 Math sessions and three Chem sessions. Two subjects were cancelled on Wednesday due to the long and seemingly pointless speeches by our pre-historic Jesuit administrators, we were dismissed at 12:20 last Thursday because of the University Awards and we had no classes on Friday because it was our patron saint's feast day. We also said our goodbyes to Mrs. Lacsamana, our perfect Geometry teacher, and Mr. Abadejos, our *clap, clap clap, clap clap clap clap, T-O-T-O-Y* Chemistry teacher, who won't be teaching us again. Mrs. Lacsamana we'll give birth to her first child and Mr. Abadejos will go to Maryland along with our first year English teacher Ms. Moredo. There'll be a "Mamoredo Despidida Part-ey" later this afternoon but I guess I won't be coming because I think that would be a waste of time. Many projects, reports and a Chem long test are due next week. Next week seems to be a very stressfull and hassle filled week. Oh goody. Just what I need. Oh well, must catch up. The clock's ticking and time's running out.  Thought  Why are there so many Larry Fonacier banners throughout the campus. I mean, he only suffered an injury. It's not like he died or something. But how come when Bugia, Membrere and Tenorio came down with injuries, there weren't any banners or streamers put up for them. Don't get me wrong. I'm not against the idea of putting up Fonacier posters. The only thing that puzzles me is why weren't there any Tenorio, Bugia nor Membrere posters? Oh and another thing. Why aren't there still no Carpio jerseys!? People are already demanding for those ya know! Right? ;) 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has been 3 days since our field trip so I'll just give a summarized version of our trip. Besides, the trip really sucked and I believe that I wasted 560 pesos. I mean, who the hell would pay 560 pesos for a day of fatigue and torture!? Oh well, here goes my account on our trip to the Banahaw Rockies.   I woke up at around 4 a.m. My SUPER GOURMET baon (Hotshots, chicken nuggets and a Big Mac. How healthy!) and my clothes were already ready. I only took a bath and a crap then left. I arrived at the High School at around 5:00 a.m., the supposed call time. But since Ateneo was so "precise" in their itenirary, we left the campus at around 6:00 a.m. What a way to start the day! Being delayed for an hour? Great. The bus ride wasn't that fun either. The tv and vcr were broken, the driver listened to stupid radio stations and my classmates were too lazy to fool around. To top it all off, I decided not to bring my trusty discman for the trip. I regretted that a lot. So basically it was 3 hours of boredom. That wasn't exactly how I pictured our bus ride to be. When we reached the rockies, nothing changed. The trek was still boring. We hiked for 5 fucking hours just to see a big old plain cross. Did I feel a sense of accomplishment when I reached the top? Hell no. All I felt were my aching foot and tortured lungs. I was to sarcastic and tired to notice the "wonderfull" view. Walking seemed to be an involuntary action that day. I just kept on going and going and going and going. To top it all off, some of us got lost since the tour guide had to wait for our sluggish teacher. As a result, we didn't get the chance to bathe in the river. Damn it. Wow. 560 pesos, DOWN THE DRAIN. Well at least my classmates were more game during the ride home. (It's about time fuckers.) We sang stupid fucked-up dance songs like Barbie Girl and Dr. Jones and some boy band crap for thirty minutes. I was even generous enough to share with my class my own version of the indian chant TONGGO. Whoppee. It was also fun watching my desperate classmates pee at Gatorade bottles and Coke 1.5 L bottles at the back of the bus. That's what I call B-boy Determination! Woohoo! Although the trip back seemed to be the highest point in our journey, bad luck naturally followed. It turned out that Katipunan was flooded. According to the news, there was ZERO movement. Our 3 hour trip turned into a 5 hour nightmare. Luckily though, I had the permission to sleep over at Miggy's house that night. I didn't have to go home to Talayan. I saved 30 minutes travel time. I thought that it would be smooth sailing from there on. Wrong.&nbsp;A 10 minute trip turned into a 2 hour trip. Great. Just greaaaaat. And that concludes my account on our field trip from hell. That's all folks. Thank you and have a bad day. xp   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally, the end of the week. This week has been catch-up week for me. Although I was able to catch up in some subjects, I topped the week off by failing our Geometry long test. Great, just greaaaat. Well, we only answered the long test a while ago but I'm totally sure that I'd get a fucked-up score. Niiiice. Anyway, we still have 10+ quizzes and one more long test for Geom. Must catch up. Although, this week was less than pleasant, I still have something to look forward to. Fiiieelldd Trriiipp! Field trips are always exciting since you'll never know whose cellphone will be broken next or who'd be the next B-boy to be injured! Hahahahaha! But seriously, I really look forward to this trip since we'd get the chance to bond as a class again in the hassle-free outdoors. Goody! I'd get to see a lot of trees and birds and flowers and butterflies! Hopefully, I'd get to see a rainbow! Whoopee! Whoops. I shouldn't have said those things. I better stop now. I'm starting to sound like a fag again.   Thoughts   Although I was busy STUDYING for the Geometry long test yesterday, I was able to watch some TV. I was channel surfing until a news program caught my attention. There was this bold star being interviewed. I really didn't pay attention to the conversation. All I remembered was that the bold star was bragging about her new-and-improved armpit. She was talking about how she spent big bucks to reduce the sweating of her armpit. Wow! What a way of spending her hard-earned money. Instead of investing it or buying a new car or buying new clothes or donating it for a good cause, she decided that lessening her armpit sweat was way more important than all of those things. She sure knows how to spend her cash wisely! God, ever heard of this roll-on stuff called deodorant? It's quite effective and it even leaves a pleasant fresh smell on your armpit. The best thing is that it doesn't even cost thousands! Come to think of it, what if everyone used their money to have treatment done on their sweaty armpits? What a fragrant world it would be! We'd rather starve to death than have sweaty armpits! Hooray!   We were tackling philosophy awhile ago in our A.P. class. We were talking about how people always want more. Our discussion awhile ago made me remember a thought that I always had in my mind. Here goes. If your're poor, chances are that you'd want to live a more humane life. If you're well off, you'd probably yearn for a life of more class and pleasure. If you're already rich, you'd want to be more filthy rich most probably. Money, money, money. Sure there's more to life than money like love, friendship and wisdom but let's be rational here. Everybody needs money. If you don't have sufficient dough, you'd most likely die a slow death. And the worst thing is, once you've tasted the sweetness of being rich, you'd probably want more. Once you've had a taste of how good having money is, you're doomed to a life of greed. Money is the root of all evil. But come to think of it, if it wasn't our yearning for more money, medical and scientifical breakthorughs wouldn' have happened. I mean scientists wouldn't waste half of their lives of finding ways to improve our way of living if there wasn't anything in it for them. Lawyers wouldn't defend the innocent if they weren't able to feed the mouths of their hungry family. Doctors wouldn't cure the sick if they wouldn't get money to supply themselves with their own necessities. Nobody would work harder, stirve harder, study harder, lie harder, cheat harder, steal harder, kill harder if it wasn't for money. It's sad to say but let's face the truth. Greed makes the world go round nowadays.   TV is the idiot box. No, I don't think that TV is the idiot box because it makes me dumber. The TV even gives me more wisdom! (Yeah right! ;)) Instead, I call the TV the idiot box because it showcases a lot of idiots. There are politicians making empty promises and superficial statements. They insult the intelligence of Filipinos nationwide on-air on a daily basis. Then there are those egocentric tv stars who never fail to make callous statements. There are also those who use the power of the media to extort money from prominent celebrities. There are ex-wives of celebrities who ask money from their ex-hubbies when they finally get a break. Plus there are those long-lost parents who suddenly resurface when their abandoned children finally gets wealth and fame. More stupid are those who give their abandoners a second-chance. They're to dumb and naive to see that those abandoners are there once again only for the money. Why do I think these people are idiots? They are idiots for being too helpless. Too helpless to even stand up by themselves. They are all pretenders who pretend to be someone else as a way of living. I am not generalizing all of the TV people. There are still decent people who are in the TV business in order to make an honest living. I'm just talking about some of the people who take advantage of the power of media. The TV is the idiot box. The TV shows us that there are many idiots out there in the convenience of our own living room.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Fuck, these&nbsp;are the lowest midterm marks I got ever! My QPI is failing. If this was my report card, I would've repeated third year. Goodbye Ateneo College. Must wake up....   &nbsp;  Geometry - C
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Funny how some people really act like bitches. I mean, you offer them help and they ignore you. But when they finally do need your help, they go back as if you're obligated to help them. And when they finally get the help they need, they don't even show gratitude. Fuck you and your bloated egos!  &nbsp;  I was surprised to see a gun on my mother's service. When you watch those typical Filipino action movies, you'd say that they exaggerate things a lot. But come to think of it, it's not that exaggerated anymore. When I asked the driver why they were issued guns, of course he said it was for protection. If I remember correctly, he said they were once ambushed in&nbsp;Pangasinan.&nbsp;A witness in a case was in a Tamaraw FX, the complainant's family only rode a tricycle and there was only one back-up owner jeep. They were not really protected since it was supposedly a small-time case. When they reached the highway that was notorious for ambushes, the Tamaraw FX sped away while the owner and the trike lagged behind. They only knew about the ambush on the owner and the trike the day after. Did anyone die? No. The tricycle wasn't even hit by a single bullet. The stainless owner jeep was hit but nobody inside was hurt. Come to think of it, the stupidity of the typical Filipino movie villain isn't that exaggerated. Filipino villains are really that stupid. That's reality for you.  &nbsp;  I'm just surprised that some things are labeled baduy by people. Some people say that Masculados, Sex Bomb Girls, and Jolina are baduy. They say that when a band goes pop, they become baduy. Honestly, I sometimes tend to think that way. But come to think of it, who are we to judge on what's baduy or not. Is there someone who's been given the authority to say that this thing is baduy? I guess not. Sure, everyone's entitled to their own opinion but when someone looks down on others just because they think he's/she's baduy, that's different. Oh well, that's life. Some people think that they're cooler than others. Shame on them! They should know by now that I'm the coolest person in the world! :p   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa..I haven't blogged for quite a while.. Oh well.. Strike one, strike two, strike three, you're out! And he goes down swinging! He's 0 for 3 tonight! Still tantalizing hey hey hey! Great, just greaaat! I'll just update this later..   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday, sunday, sunday!! Woohoo! That day was the best day of the school year ever! I mean, first, I miraculously got a fucking upper-a ticket thanks to ROMIR then I get treated to one of the most exciting Ateneo-Lasalle games ever wherein Ateneo would prevail at the end.(as usual..HAHAHAHAHAHA!) So how did my day start? Well, I woke up at around 7 am, ate breakfast then went online. I got to chat with mah sistahr, Cricket, for a while. I heard mass at around 9 then went back home. I just listened to music for the next hour to calm my excited nerves. I got ready at around 11 am. Ivan picked me up at around 12 picked up Chax and Mikko, then we went to the Big Dome. When we got there, we had to endure watching three hours of insignificant basketball. I thought, I should be playing instead of watching.. Besides, everybody wants to see DAH MAN at work! Hmm.. Hahaha! To kill time during those boring three hours, I met up with Cricket. Our meeting didn't last that long since I wasn't allowed to enter the "Starbuck's Area". No ID, no entry. Ayos, ginawa naman kaming sikyu. Anak ng.. Oh well, then after a few more minutes, the Ateneo-Lasalle game finally started. (Courtside Reporter Mode: ON) La Salle got a to a quick start and maintained their momentum for the first three quarters. At one point in the third quarter, La Salle even lead by as much as 15 points. At that time, Ivan and I lost hope and we decided to sit down. I was thinking, "Tangina naman, talo tayo sa La Salle. Tambak pa! Totoy naman nitong araw na toh." La Salle was already cheering their stupid "Go La Salle" chant. Although we had a counter "YEHEY! WEH TOTOY KAYO!!!ü" sign, it still didn't do anything. The Ateneo faithfull wasn't able to do anything but watch in envy. Besides, La Salle did have a very big lead. Honestly, I lost hope. Apparently, the team didn't. (So that's why coach didn't put me in...) At the final moments of the third quarter, Ateneo was able to gain some momentum and was able to cut down the lead to only 9 points. After that, Ateneo never lost their momentum. They were able to stiffle La Salle's offense. La Salle only scored 11 points in the last quarter. Ateneo iced the game when Larry Fonacier made the last two free throws of the game. (Courtside Reporter Mode: Off) Tangina, ang saya! Ang sarap isipin na 30 minutes ago, nagsasaya lahat ng La Salle fans thinking na pinanis na nila Ateneo! Ang sarap alalahanin yung mga supot na PEP SQUAD nilang feeling angas na pinagmamayabang ung lamang nila nung half-time! Ang sarap alalahanin na nagwawala si Yeo pagkataopos ng mga whatta whatta shot niya! Sabay talo din sa huli! Weh! Hahahaha! Etong sa inyo: YEHEY WEH TOTOY KAYO!!!!ü (Sa La Salle Fans: Hayaan niyo na ako magyabang ngayon, kami panalo eh! Kami may karapatan ngayon! Wahahaha! Peace!) Pero in fairness, ang galing talaga ng La Salle. Mas malakas lang talaga tsumamba Ateneo. Offense wins games. Defense wins championships. Tsambaleros never lose! Hahahaha! Pero tangina, hayup talaga si Yeo. Idol ko na yun. Mas magaling na yun kay Cardona. Si Cardona naman hanggang bato-bato lang yun eh.   THOUGHTS DURING THE GAME:  Saan kaya kinukuha ng La Salle ang mga pogi nilang forwards? Sta. Maria, Gaco, Sharma. Wow! Sa Bilibid ata eh! Astig ng buhok ni Yeo. Magamit nga shampoo niya sa susunod. Kelan kaya papasok si Nkemakolam? (After overhearing, ipasok na si Nkemakolam. Gayot naman lahat ng negro eh.) Tangina, ang lupit talaga ni Yeo. Bat nga ba ang mahal ng pizza dito? Meron na kayang referee na na-injure during a game?
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was the day I hung out with three wannabe niggers. It was cool hanging with these three "foo's" namely Ivan aka Steph, Bombee and Aric. Well before I share my experience I had with these three niggahs, lemme "report" to you guys what happened in school. No doubt, today was the greatest school day ever! No tasks, quizzes, seatworks or whatever. We only had a DEAR session for english, a lecture during A.P., an oral quiz on Filipino and a lab session during chem. We only had 4 subjects today because of our intrams opening. That meant muses, cheer rallies and those kinds of stuff. It was quite fun ruining the pictures of the guys who wanted a snapshot of our muse Roxanne from Star Circle Quest. Everytime a student took her picture, I would always sneek in. Hahaha! Anywaysss, today was the day I spent with the three wannabe niggers, Ivan aka Steph, Bombee and Aric. We went to Galle to watch Kill Bill 2 but because the movie would start at seven, we decided to watch Mean Girls instead. Wtf?!? Well personally, I thought that the movie sucked! :p I couldn't relate to the plot or anything. On the way out of the movie house, we saw a bunch of C boys. It turned out that not only me and the three wannabe niggers wanted to watch a chick flick after all! After that, we ate at Burger King then left. It was really funny hanging out with those three because of their stupid accent and comments! Hahaha! They would go.. Gadameet Aric.. Yow sow totoy! Oh well, call me totoy but I still think that they're quite funny! Haha! So there.. After that we went home then I slept. I was woke up by my father at around twelve thirty because my cousins from the U.S. had arrived. I really missed those guys. I'm really excited about them staying here for vacation! It has been six years since I last saw them so really missed them a lot! Oh well.. Gtg folks.. See yaaaaaaaaa!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A milestone is set today. Yeap. That's right! This is my fifth straight blog entry. This is such an accomplishment. Why, you ask? I mean, I never thought that I would even type 3 blog entries but now, here's my fifth. Kudos to me! Hahaha! Well anyway, what happened in this oh-so-terrific day? Nothing really. Nothing significant ever happens in school anyway. As usual, I slept during one of our subjects. It was religion this time. Besides sleeping during religion, the only "exciting" things that happened today was our P.E. class (P.E.'s always exciting. I mean, you'll never know who the next B-boy would break a bone or twist his ankle. Hahahahaha!) and the film viewing session during our A.P. class. Oh yeah, I finally got an upper-a ticket for this Sunday's game! Thank god! Hahaha! :p Whoa, after one week of hell, I get to enjoy one week of heaven. I mean, after numerous physical, mental and emotional stress last week, I finally get to relax this week. After a "surprise" fight, an unexpected personal failure and an expected academic failures I get A B for Geom, an emotional stress-free week and even an upper A ticket! Funny how life can seem so low at one point then it takes a total 180 in just a day. Funny how one FUCKED-UP SATURDAY afternoon could lead on to a "happy" week. Well maybe this just goes to show that no matter how deep in shit you are, nothing's ever hopeless. But I don't know. Could it be possible that I just overreacted last Saturday? Could it be possible that nobody's really in shit? I mean there are still some people that are supposedly deep in shit but don't look problematic. Could your emotions depend ENTIRELY on how you look at life? Oh well, I coudn't care less. Hahaha! Anyway, I gotta go folks. Good day mates!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No. I'm not going to start this blog be saying that I shitted in the first thing in the morning. This day was so tiring. We had two long tests and a Geom quiz which I totally flunked. Yes. After "acing" a Geom long test, I flunked a simple quiz. That's the irony of life. You fail when you expect to succeed and prevail when you expect to fail. Oh well, that's life. At the end of the day, we had our first Weightlifting Org session. Yep. It was tiring. Fooling around with 100 lbs of iron was not a good idea after all. My arms are so fucking numb right now. And after the org, we started our Science R.A. It was quite fun since we had to "travel" around the college. There were a lot of kewwwwllll sights there! The John Gokongwei Building looked so futiristic. I wonder... How come the Ateneo has funds to renovate the stuff in the grade school and college but not for the high school? Is there some conspiracy against our batch? I mean, everytime we leave a grade level, something in that level is renovated the year after we leave. Wow! How nice! At least I had fun "working" at the enchanted Eagle's POnd. Pooof! We even got the chance to watch the Blue Babble practice. God, how could a nerdy looking dork be the captain of the squad? Easy. He bangs on his drums like a devil. Trust me. Yeap, never judge a book by its cover I would say. Hahaha! Oh well, I'm too tired to type. Besides, I still have to watch Ginebra win its first championship in seven years. Bye! Oh and if you were wondering how I started this marvelous day, I started the day by taking a dump. Heaven if you ask me!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As usual, I started my day by taking a crap. Come to think of it, why can't be life be as simple as taking a crap. Think of it this way. You could remove all the crap that has been plaguing you all your life by just taking a dump and with one flush of the toilet, all that shit that has been bothering you would be gone. Hmm. Wouldn't that be great? Just thinking. Well, at least I won't be needing that. Besides, I'm quite satisfied with my life right now. I just don't get other people. Why do they make life seem so complicated by magnifying all their petty problems. Plain stupidity if you ask me. Anyway, as you can see, I am still sick. And yes, I am going to continue writing this entry in straight english. Mwahahahaha! So how did my day go... Well my day went quite smooth. Thank you Vicks. If not for that inhaler, my nose would still be dripping with mucus. So basically my day went smooth because of that little inhaler. See what a little inhaler could do to your life? We had a moderately difficult long test in Filipino and the Geometry and A.P. long tests were returned today. I was satisfied with the results. A D for A.P. and a B for Geometry. Yes, you read that right. I'm SATISFIED with a D and a B. Why? Although I'm quite dissapointed with the fucking D I got for World History, getting a B in Geometry unasissted by my tutor is as easy as cutting your toenails using your teeth. I knew that I could've gotten a C+ in my long test in A.P. if I just memorized that stupid map. Fuck. Oh well. Mr. Salalima's tests are quite easy anyway so I still have the chance to improve my so-so grades in A.P. Other than the Filipino long test and the returning of long tests, our workload for the rest of the day was quite light. Although we had two Geometry sessions, we only had exercises and lectures. As for religion, we reported on our collages. Thanks to ME, our group got an A. Bwahahahaha! (Huwag nang hihirit. Blog ko toh. Ako palagi bida dito! Hahahaha!) During English, I think we just had a game throughout the session. How should I know, I was asleep the whole session. And at the end of the session, we had a quiz. During Chem, we had to go to the Interactive Room to watch a documentary about "Pis Pands and Pis Keeleeng" After our Chem class I realized that our country is going to be run by a leader who coudn't even pronounce the word F-I-S-H correctly. All I can say is.... FLUSH THAT SHIT! And at the end of the day, we painted our "phat kick-ass chinese guy" logo for computer. Enter the Phatness Beiiittttccch! Hahahaha! Shit. Life's so boring. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow. Whatta whatta day. I'm sick. I knew it. I shouldn't have played basketball yesterday. Look at the effects. I'm still typing in english. I must be really sick. Well how did this oh-so-fabulous day start? I started my day by taking a crap. You guys should try it. Taking a crap in the first thing of the morning is oh-so-relaxing. Yep. Just think of it. Cleansing your intestines that are full of shit. Very healthy. I mean, shit in your body is never good right? Hahahaha! Well back to less gross things. Nothing really significant happened today. We had an "easy" quiz on English, a Briggs-Myers Test during homeroom, I was sleeping during Filipino, an activity during religion a seatwork during chem that required us to make a poem about water, a lecture during geom and an ms-dos activity and we made draft of our logo during computer. I know. School is so exciting. I love it. To top it all off, my nose has been a leaking faucet of mucus all throughout the day. Yehey!    Oh..here's an excerpt from the poem I made about water during chem:  Splish splash splish splash Water is a noisy gift from God.... H20 IS COOL!!!  I know. I'm very poetic.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bat kaya ganyan title? Doi. May blog na kasi ako! Woohoo! Finally may ASTIG nang blog. Ay. Bat nga pala ako nagtatagalog. Dapat pala english shpokening tayo dito. Oh well. I'll just make you sample sample of my terrific english dictionary. Today.. hmm.. What happened today? Well, I started the day off by playing basketball. After playing for 2 "gruelling" hours of basketball, the sport I revolutionized, I realized that....DAMN, I'm good. I should be in the nba. There should be Carpio jerseys in the market right now. Instant sell-out. Wow. I really do have great ideas. Think about it. You'd here children scream, "Mommy, mommy gusto ko ng Carpio Jersey!!!! Gusto ko yung XXXL para hip-hoppers ako mommy! Sige na! Tapos gusto ko ng bling bling para "playaah" na din ako like my idol Carps!" Although i enjoyed beating everyone else in the court.." I rottened them."(If you don't know what that means that means that pinanis ko sila oh see I do have a great english dictionary.) I think playing basketball today was a bad idea because now I think I'm sick. Oh yes, even cool people do get sick. Sad but true. What else happened today? Hmm.. It's my sistah's b-day party today! Haffeh Burdeh Sistar! Shit. Too bad she didn't have it in mcdo. Instead, she had it here. Damn. I miss fooling around with those mascots and clowns. :'( Oh well. Now there are about 15 young ladies in here forcing my sis to get them my autograph. Sorry guys, Carpio Fans Day is over. Maybe next year. Oh well. That's my day so far. Maybe I'll blog again tomorrow. WOOHOO! Nasasakal na ako sa aking pagiingles! Carps, welcome to the conyo society! Ahahahahahaha! Ok guys, I'll make babay babay to you na because I have to make alis alis na! :D
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Testing 1, 2, 3.. 1, 2, 3? 1, 2, 3! YEHEY!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow. I never knew that wake-up calls would hurt this much. It really hurts inside but fuck, it would be better to suddenly wake up and feel the pain rather than slowly bleed to death. Now a question stares at me right in my face. How would I answer this call? Should I sob over on what has been wasted or take this call as a challenge, a challenge to prove my worth as a person. Sure, I've had problems with being sincere to myself before but hell, I'm dead sincere on this one. God damn it, I'll prove my worth. You may say you don't care but I know you do. Ok, you may not give a fuck today but I know you'll do someday. And someday (be it tomorrow or next year or next decade), you'll realize that you were wrong. I just hope it won't be too late by then. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Person of the Year:
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Blah.  This week has been so tiring. Though we haven't been given a lot of schoolwork during the week, I feel so stressed. Catching up has been such a hassle. The worst part is, I don't know if I could still reach my desired goal. Why do I always promise myself things but never keep them? Oh well.. Basta, I promise to do my best next term. :-p  Thought: 
</post>


</Blog>