<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As many of you know I will be traveling to Europe this summer. I will be away from July 17th thru August 1st. I will be departing Miami International Airport at 7:00 PM aboard Swiss International Airlines, flight LX065. The aircraft is an Airbus A330-200, and when I arrive I will be aboard flight LX064 departing Zurich on August 1st.   If you wish to track my flight live please go to:     urlLink ">Link    Go to option #2 (Track a flight by Airline name and Flight number:) Then under airline, scroll down to Swiss Int'l Airlines, then under flight number enter 065.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Samantha! So much for our happy ending, you were everything that I wanted. Too bad you had to become some gruesome goth... Brian *sniff* Sorry.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, time passes so quicky! Now I only have 11 days left until I fly to Zurich. I will also be traveling in Europe during those 2 weeks. I will most likely be going to London and some other city, maybe Venice. I truly am excited, and cannot wait!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow Christina, I love your new look! You look amazing! Keep up the good work, can't wait for your two new albums this fall! ROCK ON!!!     
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Boom! Yeah baby, thats whay I am talking about!!!    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I made this map of all the flights I have done in my lifetime!     
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Samantha seems to have a crush with my online friend from England, Neil. LOL! Pathetic, not only does the bitch hate England, but she also insults the British students at my school. Now she is saying she wants to go to the UK! Samantha make up your twisted and sick mind for once...  For Samantha:  Samantha! See she's the reason for the word "bitch" I hope she's speeding on the way to the club Trying to hurry up to get to some Baller or singer or somebody like that And try to put on her makeup in the mirror And crash, crash, crash.. into a ditch!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            Whats your style?      Which on of these choices best fits your taste in style:         Punk rock, gothic... i like black & dog collers         Trendy whats in style at the moment         Trend setter i start the trends         Skateboarder...baggy pants messed up hair & skateboard         Dorky...high-water pants big old grandma shirt         sporty...sweat pants t-shirt         surf dude..swimming cloths blonde hair & the TAN         I have no style I just put on what I find           This  urlLink  Poll   by sweetnsasc1787        urlLink  Click here to view results       	
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ugh, I can't stand her. She definitely has mental issues. Not only does she cut her wrist, but she sticks needles into her fingers, then she denies it! I also remember at the beginning of the year when she though she was a vampire and cut her finger to suck her own blood. The girl also goes out with Maya! A lesbian, so that leaves me to suspect she also is a lesbian as she protects her so much...   Ha ha, check this out: (This is for all your bullshit Samantha!)   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, today is the beginning of a new journey to restore the scars left by 911! I am so excited to see this new building rise as I grow up to an adult, as I am sure many other American's feel this way! I am also looking forward to the fireworks celebration tonight! God Bless America, my home, sweet home!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>