<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aiya... Very tired... Nearly sleep everyday in class... Todaygot HMT RR... it was so hard... i dunno lots of questions... Aiya only RR so i dun reali care.... Saturday is preim oral.... a bit nervous.. sometimes stuck and dunno wad to say.... wateva just try my best...  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Overall, I think my NAPFA was horrid...I can have a chance to get gold or silver but everything was spoiled by the stupid inclined pull-up.... haiz....(sigh...)I did the others quite well except for the pull-up....Wednesday was Racial Harmony day... It was pretty boring.... wearing those enthic costumes was a bit extra....wateva, i don't really care.... today got 1.6km run... well its not bad, dun really feel tired.... but run halfway suddenly rain... all the water wet my specs... very hard to see.... but its SO fun running in the rain.... very cooling... then i took a public bus home, wet myself even more... no umbrella... I was drench frm head to toe by the time I reach home... Then i go IMM to shop.... aiya, still got home work must do.... gtg must give comments, bye!!! 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh No!!! tomorrow is NAPFA test.... wateva, i just want to get a&nbsp;silver badge because that is what i have been getting in the last 2 years... for sit-up i just do 25.... incline pull-up, i will do maybe 8.... shuttle run 11-12 secs.... sit and reach, i will just do 38cm... standing broad jump i will just do 147cm... ok gtg bye! 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!! Exams coming!!! I haven really study yet... Aiya, the results so-so can liao...aniwae,todae go 'n wash photos... the photos came out not bad, quite nice... todae go jing jia 's house again... we do homework... I got fed up in the end... thinking y must we DO homework....wateva,just do lor... won't die.... I'm going to play until siao after exams..... (",)
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I went Jing Jia's house... We did our Maths HW... Its a total of 50 questions... most of them were problem sums... I broke my record by finishing it in 2 hours... Well its very good for a slowpoke like me... After that we went to play and watch TV... In the end, we ended up playing hide & seek(hiding things).... It was fun... I'm happy to day because I both work and play... Can't wait for PSLE to be over... I will play until  siao .... aiya.. I got nothing to write any more so I'll end here... BYE!!!
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Now the teachers are giving more and more homework.... and I'm sleeping around midnight everyday... The onli thing i'm scared of is that i will fall asleep in lessons the nxt day... So i got an idea... so I drank a cup of coffee before going to sch everyday... and TRUE!  It works! I dun even need to take naps anymore... I dun even feel tired.... Today Mrs Chia gave us the prelimary dates.... haiz...  I'm tired of exams.... alot of ppl who failed their exams also become successful ppl in future.. 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haiz... Dun feel like doing my homework so I decided to play the computer lor....There are no nice shows on TV except Wheel of Fortune Singapore... I tired of all those VCDs... haiz... Why so boring? My making this blog is quite fun and I enjoyed doing it.... Haha... very  wu liao  right? I waiting for time to past so that I can grow up... Being a grown up is  SO  fun! Dun need to study can work play and relax everyday... How nice!
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a happy and bored day... there is tuition and I sat there for 4 hours listening to the teacher's talking.... but the teacher there very funny make me laugh alot... After tuition at abt 6.15, I went to my ah ma house for dinner... steamboat! Then i played with my pet rabbit, Charcoal... Oh No! still got alot of homework must do! But never mind tomorrow is youth day... no school... haha..we are not 'youths' why must celebrate youth day... ok la not much left to write... so I'll end here bye!   
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aiya, just got back maths and Hmt rr results... quite happy abt it.... friday celebrate national day in sch....then, got dragged by man xuan and cliantha to compass point.... ferlycia and melanie also got go..... we eat and shop.... I bought a pair of earrings.... but drop one of them while I was bathing...haiz, tml tuition buy one more... haha... think i'm getting hopeless because no mood to study in this exam period.... now watching a basketball show "Dear Boys".. hehe... on of the guys inside very handsome.... my mum says i'm mad because they r just figures being drawn out by other people...On friday sleep frm 2.30---6pm very tired... didn't sleep well that week, need to charge my energy... got 2 test paper 4 hw.. don't feel like doing but haf to..... ok la dun haf much to write....  
    
</post>


</Blog>