<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Time now is actually 1.15am, August 1... Man time files, 1 month gone in a flash, and what was those supposedly sad days seemed so near yet so far away... Start of a new month, maybe its a time for a fresh start in my life ?  Headed to Atrium at 12.30 today... didnt actually felt like going down, due to 5 tests coming on Monday, but had to hand the T630 over to the buyer at 1... so well, the trip there was inevitable... Saw TL and Alex not long after I reached the entrance of the arcade. Handed the hp over, got $350, and stayed till around 3.15 when I went up with Aaron and gang to PS to see them play ID and WMMT over at Star Factory. Felt hungry after that, went for lunch at the food court downstairs. Aaron accompanied me.  Backed down to Atrium again, to see some matches going on, and headed home at 6.30, to come back and do some stuff, at least before I head on to bed. Dont wanna hang out till 11 plus and then walk home again, lol, my legs ! Shacked out !  Just had a chat with Aaron on MSN, wah his words, kinda slapped me awake.... self induced depression.... ahh man... I have to just try harder, to get out of this mess, and live my life as was before, waiting for that special person to appear.  Night. 
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was Founder's Day at school, lessons were on only for the first 2 periods, and after that, its a assembly for the mass prayer in the hall. This time in our own school hall. Not the primary school's. And my, was it cramped.  Supposed to go Atrium after the dismissal at 10.30am, along with KL. But, decided that I'll go shift a 6 speed shifter than a tiptronic one.... so I PS-ed him and followed Joshua and gang to SuperBowl for a few games first. After all, it was still early. Had 3 games, and I headed home to bath and get ready for going out later. Dilly-Dallied my time, then went out at around 3.05pm. Down at CS, I played WMMT the whole way, and finished at around 4.45pm. Tried to plan out a time plan in a way that if I catch bus 72 then switch to 53, I'll get to Serangoon MRT on time. But.... still reached the darn place at 6, and had to wait 40 minutes for *Mr Hia Big Shot* to come.. =P 10 minutes late worr~~ =x  So we met Tong Lam, and headed to Atrium to meet the rest of the bunch. Walked to HMV, then to Ngee Ann City. My legs were really tired and heavy by the time we walked back to Atrium... lol, save on bus fees... (-.-") Yeah, and we stayed at Baker's Inn to drink a cuppa tea and to chit-chat (talk cock to be more precise). Thanks for the treat of Iced Tea Aaron ! *lol*  11 .30pm, we left and took one of the last trains home. Alighted at Serangoon Station, and walked with Aaron all the way home. After all, the last bus was long gone by then, and a midnight surcharge on a taxi didnt sound too good, since its quite a short distance, and its so non-economical. Talked a bit on the way, and after we parted, I kinda thought of some of my problems (yet again.. yes I know...) while dragging two "logs" that were heavy like hell and still managed to clock a time of 15 mins to home ! What a suprise. >. .  Ahhh anyways, I had to adjust the time back to put in this entry, time now is 2.15am, so yeah, I guess I'm in need of some sleep... Dont want panda eyes to come and look for me... Enough problems for me le.... ~.~" 
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Plain day. Didnt go to school as mentioned in the previous entry, went to see doc at 10 am. Got a MC, stayed at home the whole day. Somehow felt tired at around 1.30 pm, caught a wink till 4 when&nbsp;I woke up and bathed.   Looking back at this month, didnt have much time to rest other than today, I guess its a good thing. Feels so tired lately I couldnt do much of a thing. Didnt study much today, just slacked my day through. Boring.   Just wonder if tomorrow's after-school event would see me playing WMMT at Tampines, or ID at Atrium. I feel like shifting a H shifter so badly. And my time of 4'43 obviously doesnt show I'm that seasoned in this game.   Founder's day tomorrow, let off at around 10 am if everything goes well.. I'm lost&nbsp;in my mind&nbsp;again. Now my heads feels empty, cant churn out any more words to fill in. Guess that concludes my day.   Thot for the day&nbsp;-&nbsp;"You must be at peace with your mind, then you can form what you really wanna say." - Aaron.  Funny why this entry sounded so emotion-less. Nite. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Maybe its time I stop blogging about day events. Maybe its a time where I should let my inner soul take over me for just this period of time, as I'm writing this, to actually let whatever's out in this heart of mine, to maybe just ease this wretched fellow of his pains for a while. Thats what he always wanted, yes, Peace. It doesnt have to be eternity, nor it be a millennium. Just a while. Maybe at most a hour ? Really... just let him be oblivious to the surroundings, and happy, contented. Minds free from the&nbsp;troubles that revolve around his life.&nbsp;And maybe its time I sat down, thought hard, and made a decision on what to do next.  I feel so lost now, even lost for words,&nbsp;having argued with my mum about certain things that revolve around the one thing that make people berserk, MONEY. All started about one handphone bill being too costly for the month. And so the madness goes. Its like the third time this damn year. Thoughts and urges of suicide kept flashing through my mind and body, it just makes me wanna jump up from my seat, and just make a beeline for the window. But no, I didnt. And so I just kept on arguing, with no solutions whatsoever. Just going round and round in circles.   Somehow my parents mean good, but expressed it in the wrong way. I can get this when I'm alright and in a collected mood, but when its heated up, I just cant get sober to anything. Damn.. harsh realities in life... is there nothing it has in store... man.. I've got love, studies, and now, money to worry about. This is some big time shit I'm going through man... Just hope everything turns out well soon..  Cried myself out when my mum left the room, kinda felt good and relaxed after that. Couldnt even vaguely remember when was the last time I've cried. So numb to everything, couldnt remember anything. Actually this entry wasnt what its supposed to be, but since I've cooled down, my head became empty and lost. Forgot even what I wanna say just now.  Due to this event, I've decided to see the doc to get a MC tomorrow, to buy myself more time to study for the 3 tests that is bound tomorrow. Physics, Chemistry, and Maths. Killer subs if you dont remember them. Couldnt study now, mood's changed and all, and I couldnt pick up any info from the stacks of notes and worksheets. Hope a good night's sleep will help.  Thats all for today. Peace out. Yes, peace. 
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today it kinda felt good,&nbsp;at certain times of the day. Why is it always Tuesday that&nbsp;the most ups and downs occur ?&nbsp;Lol... I'm baffled.&nbsp;Became thoughtful in class at around 11am, just tried to re-organise the jigsaw puzzle I've had in my mind for coming to a month. Still, it didnt help matters. Only became messed up again, and didnt know why. Dont know how many times I have to go through this before I can get my thoughts straight again. ITs like... so many thoughts just flashing in your mind... all in a split second. Before you get what that signal is, another one comes. Its just so... disorganised.   Had a talk with the VP today. Complained about that stupid, egoistic idiot whos been giving me nonsense when I did not step on his tail at all. At least it kinda settled the chain of unhappy events thats been going on since school term started. So much so for being a nice guy and keeping quiet for so long. Didnt see any need to go fight it out with him... when hes just a&nbsp;empty nutshell and I dont see the help of knocking some sense into him when its only deaf ears I'm reaching onto... Ah, to hell with him. Get&nbsp;a life, take a hike.   Had a shocking surprise when the geography test papers were handed out.. All the guys who were the usual passers failed big time, getting scores of 3 to 5 out of a max of 15... And I, got&nbsp;a 9/15 for it... and that made me the only passer out of the whole class. Even William, coming in second, missed half a mark for passing.. with only 7....  Which leads me to think... maybe it was just a stroke of luck... maybe it wasnt the full understanding I had which lead me to get this kind of mark.. I dont even dare to think I can even get a good mark... But looking at the content which I wrote, somehow, it just seemed I've understood it well... Why are there so many things that make me confused...   Went with Kun Long to Kovan, ate at Yoshinoya, since we had the discount coupons... but somehow my bill amounted to $8.50... guess that didnt help much... Then we walked around Heartland Mall, seeing comics and CD's. By the time we went out of the building, it was drizzling again, and it was extremely humid. I stood there, then slowly but surely I began to feel sticky and stuffy... yucks. The weather at that time.... really sucked.   Got home, bathed, saw Aaron's blog. Well he really is in the dumps.. again. Not surprising but, somehow, I feel hes kinda taking it too rough. Some people just choose to ignore the situation, and escape it from reality. On the other hand, he, took it upon himself, the suffering, the pain. Hes just carrying it all by himself....&nbsp;As he said,&nbsp;in the rainy hour, he shall lift up his worn sword, with that little strength he has left, with a body thats bruised and battered, and&nbsp;face up to the dragon thats ready to attack him anytime. Well I really hope he can get back to be himself again, and if u do see this, please, cheer up man. It just sucks to see myself in this state already.. and I definitely do not want this to happen to any of my friends... I know how it feels, and your state is worse than mine.. I do hope you can&nbsp;pick yourself up, and be yourself again. Soon.   Haha, I still remember what Mr. Denis Koh said to me the last time we chatted, "Practise what you preach". Told him those words he tried to encourage me with, were the ones I used on my friends, cheering them up, goading them to go on. I give advice from my POV, making my friends look at it from a "bright" side.&nbsp;But when it comes to my case, its a worse case scenario...&nbsp;a whole new&nbsp;case to speak of again.&nbsp;I couldnt control it, goes into a total disaster, not knowing what to do.. and when I yearn for someone to be by my side at that time.. there is none. Me, myself,&nbsp;and my own thoughts. No POV's from other people. Bleah.   Ah well, still, things are as they were, nothing's changed, the same old me, in the seat, facing the PC, and blogging my stuff out. "People only remember bad things, good things dont last and slip by easily".   Nightz. Benedict signing out. Its been a thoughtful day.  
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a bad bad bad day. Some unpleasant things happened, along with the prediction that Lucien helped me to predict... today WAS a bad day for me, in this week. Well... felt tired again... in class... somehow Monday Blues really can get me all the time.. just cant seem to run away... Ah well, the habit of sleeping at 11 pm... lol.. and I slept late with some tossing and turning on the bed before I settled down and reach slumberland...  Had my heads on the table (again) after recess, couldnt pick up any more spirits to really take the pen and write some stuff.... just wanna sleep... time passed by real slowly then.. jeez.  Hmm... after school I just headed home, didnt have some interesting stuff to blog today, it just seemed very okay, but marred by unhappy events in the morning. Sigh. Just in a dilemma.  Really, whats there to say today.  Benedict out. 
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As usual, per Sunday its a tuition day.. not that worth mentioning... but hey, its a real significant event on my Sundays.... haha. After tuition,&nbsp;I kinda had lunch, then sat on the sofa watching TV... until 3.30pm,&nbsp;a wave of tiredness hit me... and I slept on the sofa till 5.45pm.   Had a bath when I successfully dragged my body into the shower, and felt kinda refreshed after that. Still, a tingling blurness hung on to my senses...&nbsp;Then began doing my stuffs when Aaron called me up, not so long after. Time was about 6.20pm.. and he asked if I wanted to go eat out at around our area (Kovan, Hougang..)   So I agreed, still somewhat surprised and kinda glad someone actually called me out. And not too far at that. Yeah, so headed to the bus stop opposite PLMGSS to meet him, and we walked to Kovan.. had a little chat on the way, too. Time somehow passes by quickly if you have someone by your side talking to you...   Decided to get a plastic cover for my newly bought T630.. after all the&nbsp;black cover cannot be taken out and washed, so i decided that a cover over it might be better... dont want&nbsp;the oil on my face to stain the hp... I do wash my 6230 sometimes.. thanks to the Express-On Covers... its just a breeze. Wash and dry. Thats it.  Although the guy took a long time to find the cover, I feel its great that its just $2, and I'm planning to buy another&nbsp;1 for my tuition teacher, and 1&nbsp;for myself as a extra cover (my neighbour didnt want it, he got the pouch liao)   Headed to Hougang Mall to test out the FD&nbsp;I bought from Aaron, met WanXiang along with his girlfriend I think. Argh, the FD wheel locks like no tomorrow ! Straightways also can wheel lock, and have u eating the wall... but its a good car overall... if I can counter the wheel lock, I suppose. Had a few battles with a Evo 4 with my half tuned FD... its gay how the Evo 4 dusted me on Irohazaka... >.  Played till 8.15pm when me and Aaron headed to KFC to have our dinner, and talked a bit on my problems again... Well, what was not so surprising was that what Aaron said, was what everyone said. Studies first.&nbsp;Love, later.&nbsp;How many times did these words enter my ears... Still, my mood gets the better of me... and something good will happen if I'm in a good mood... vice versa. Anyone&nbsp;can tell me&nbsp;how to overcome this ?   So... it was home after that, took 62 home.. along the way Aaron showed his picture collection on his hp to me... damn ! Walking multimedia centre !! Powder-ful 6600.... haha. Will try to have him send the pics to me sometime... hehe.   Yeah thats about it, a&nbsp;simple day, but rather fun. Will be sleeping later, since I caught a wink this afternoon, and I've left quite a bit of homework to do for tomorrow... yeah, I expect to be sleeping at around 1.30am ? Haha... gotta catch up on my work.. otherwise the new week will have me exhausted... and left behind..   Night peepz ! and.. Happy birthday to Karie ! (Lol... forgot to wish it to her today... so yeah, I'll just leave it here, although she cant see this...)   
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Guess I somehow woke up on the wrong side of the bed today. Had a spinning dizziness in the head when I opened my eyes at 9.30 am. Called up Whymobile at 10.10 am, they dont offer the door to door delivery&nbsp;from 9 am&nbsp;to 9 pm anymore, since they're short of manpower, and the only available times are after 6 in the weekdays.. gotta take note next time... In the end decided to go collect the phone from them at the outlet, since its just above Zone X @ Atrium. Besides, he offered a further $5 cut on the price if I did so... lol, why not ?   Dilly-Dallied my time from 10.20 to 12 noon... played CS, listened to music, whatnot. Then decided to bath and then head on down to Atrium, since I'm meeting my friend there. Further broke the record of Steve's 86 from 2'47'162 to 2'46'366... haha... this is just too great... 1 sec down... And somehow, with that,&nbsp;I feel that my touch of IDAS is coming back soon.. didnt feel afraid of the oncoming corner, or that hairpin. Just tackle it with all my might. Yeah.. so I suppose I should be able to be back on form by the middle of next month... Hope the mood can stay away (at least for a while)&nbsp;while I'm driving out my best...   Headed to CTP to meet Yap and gang, played ID from 3 to about 7... didnt really care too much, the mood started to kick in, but its kinda mild. Felt kinda sian around 6.. didnt get too active after that. Followed Steve and Kun Long to Toa Payoh, had our dinner and headed to Toa Payoh Entertainment Centre to play&nbsp;last few rounds of ID.. Irohazaka all the way... then it was a cab ride home.   Reached home at around 9.15, bathed, and felt kinda hungry after that. Had instant noodles cooking now.. gonna eat&nbsp;it once I finish this entry.   Hmm.... I guess thats about it for today, what else was there to be said ? I doubt it....   
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Had a very happening day today. Had some ups and downs at different times of the day. Felt good and bad. As usual, got mixed up again while trying to sort out some things in my mind.   Didnt expect anything special to happen while in school today, but during recess time, when I just walked out of the classroom, Mr Denis Koh, our DM, saw me and signalled me to go over. I was thinking, hell, I didnt pull off any stunts these days wad... why he wanna see me for ? My doubts were cleared when he just patted me on my back and said 'how are you?' Became kinda surprised and glad that someone did notice my existence... lol~.. I replied that i was okay, not too bad, but feeling down lately (as this blog mentions)... So he asked why and well, it kinda became a personal talk in a corner, then when people were walking by, they all had the same idea that I've stepped on his tail.. the kind of stare they gave me... just felt so funny.. well but it wasnt unusual la, expected de.. so.. just like that lor.. Told him some personal stuffs, and he, too shared his stuff with me too.. and I felt that my talk with him wasnt so important, so much so he shoved off all the students that had to meet him, and just dismissed them, without giving them a piece of his mind.. I'm the saviour i guess... lol~ Yeah, so I might look up the DM or VP (they are a couple FYI) these days... didnt really seem to have anyone who had a listening ear le... is there ? Did I miss out anyone ?   Went to Sherman's house after that, took Jarael's hp to go trade in.. guess what ? Out of stock still.. and the price for the T630 still cant be lowered, and out of fun, I queried a Nokia 6230 cover, the guy said $45, but i already located one shop that sold it at $38... peculiar, seems to me they aint doing proper business...undermining some stuff maybe ? Hate this...  So, kinda decided on the vendor i'm gonna get my T630 from,&nbsp;Whymobile is the one. Calling them up at 9.15 am tomorrow, and get a delivery to my door before&nbsp;I head out to meet my friends to go out... At least got some time to test it out.. haha.. hopefully got discount, since I'm a repeat customer...&nbsp;Went home after that...   Then, didnt really expect this, but, BUT,&nbsp;I still went out, this time to Atrium, to play some ID with Kun Long. I successfully broke Steve's record of 2'47'446 on the 86 Trueno... Got it down to 2'47'162, but felt very happy with it le... i dont really expect a top form, since I'm just beginning to stand up again.. mood is still sad and bottled up, although&nbsp;I did let out some today.. to the DM.. he behaved&nbsp;like a real friend to me.. not like his fierce usual self...  Went up to PS to eat dinner, and then headed down to Kovan to get some stuffs.. deodorant for Kun Long,&nbsp;facial wash for me... Neutrogena ? KL said it was kinda good, so I decided to give it a try... den headed to Comics Connection, bought a keychain (only at 50 cents, kinda cheap)&nbsp;&nbsp;and a&nbsp;Nissan GTR R34 1/61 model by Tomy.. will take a pic with the T630 tomorrow, hehe... my 6230 cant focus, or rather, capture it that clearly... its only good for far shots.... so .. yeah, thats about it... Time we went home was 9... so, took a bath, and here I am, blogging this for the day events... Kinda happy today lor, and&nbsp;that's pretty much about it lor...   T630, here I come !! :D   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Great day i had today, man. At least it was a lot of joy and fun throughout the&nbsp;3 hours we had at Seoul Garden Tampines Mall. Although the food wasnt so good, the people who turned up were.. =)  But first off, let me blog down the events that happened in school today..   Everything was usual, when during Physics lesson, Mr Ganesh didnt come and instead the VP, Mrs Maria Koh, came in to talk to us.. kinda a inspirational pep talk and a goal setting one at that for us... she told us to be 'what you want to be', must pass the exams and at O levels.. since its a milestone for us in our career life.. She says that we, the retainees, have character, and the spirit to face the syllabus again, and to come to school, only to see that the people in the class changed, but the level hasnt. Still 3. Focusing on my studies is also a point that she stressed, but hey, with my current status, what can assure me that I can pull it off well this semester ? Yeesh, as if things werent going smooth enough, the problem of love has to come knocking at my door this period of my life...   Yeah... and that left me thinking about what i should do right now, to be a lonely driver, or go find one... but its a uphill task, I can say. Became a lost soul again, I might go approach her if i need someone to pour out to, after all, she says her door is always open, and she'll be all ears if anyone has any problem. Hmm.. it aint peer to peer after all... Always an adult coming into the picture in my wretched life...   Headed home after school, and rushed to bath and get ready to go out to Tampines Mall, where we met the&nbsp;bunch of girls and 2 guys... their 'ah pa' and 'ah gong'.. lol... but i'm the oldest there... -.-" Went into Seoul Garden after that, didnt eat too much, i still had a loss of appetite.. but we talked a lot, and i enjoyed it very much. Like i said, i kinda hate boredom nowadays, since it ignites my thinking of my problems yet again.... Used to walk aimlessly on long stretches of road, but now, if I have the time to leisurely walk over a substantial amount of road, I would definitely think of something these days.   Played Final Password (in chinese la) after our meal, the one that gets the number that the judge sets, he/she gets punished.. in this case it was a real exotic cocktail of desserts, and a plate of meat that is marinated with BBQ sauce, Chili, Chili powder, and wasabi. The dessert had raw egg, ice, attap seeds, jelly, and some other stuff that those girls wouldnt reveal... and basket, I didnt even get punished de, until the last round, guess wrong number.... :/ haha.. nvm la, i got tactic, swallowed the food quickly, by the side of my jaws, and thus didnt get the full scale hotness of the chili and wasabi... whahah... see them&nbsp;choking and blowing, i kinda feel they kinda dumb... one of them took 2 mins to swallow down the piece of meat, but it already took him full scale le.. -.-"   Went to the hp shop to change the 3100, to a T630. Damn, the price of $280 was a white version.. Black one costed $330... felt like cheated lor,&nbsp;Whymobile selling at a nett price regardless of colour.. blah. Will think about getting from that shop. Cheaper somemore. $320 nia. See how tomorrow&nbsp;lor. Besides, Whymobile offers door to door deilvery service, that darn shop doesnt... haha.. chances are high neh...   Yeah that kinda concludes my day... Met Joei again today, felt a sense of attraction to her.. I just wonder if its my heart or my brain... trying to find someone only, or&nbsp;I really like her.. Man i dunno.. Wild shots in the dark ?   Can anyone give me a guide as to what I'm supposed to do... The aimless and clueless me is really in a spot...    
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This morning kicked off with a moderate downpour.. felt cool though.. and there was a traffic jam on the way to school..   In school, I laughed a lot today. Was like going to go nuts anytime man... lol. We were so 'patriotic', singing national day songs during geography test ! haha.. couldnt remember whats the other one, I laughed too much, it slipped off my mind... =x   Yeah, was a kinda good day for me too.. sunny.. hehe. That stupid idiot came to school, but didnt disturb me or what... and i stayed back after school to do library duty for the first time ever since school started... lol, kinda slack sia.. but i did do my part ! =D  Didnt have much appetite at dinner just now, just ate a few mouthfuls and i pushed the plate away.. don't know why too...  Tomorrow after school, I'll be off to Tampines Mall to celebrate the girls birthday.. Joei's falls on today, Jarael's tomorrow, and Karie's on Sunday.. wah... all like very close.. den i spent a big bill on my gifts... T_T lol..  So thats about it, I'll be buying a gift for Jarael tml, in the form of topping up the money needed for trade in for a new X430... she wanna change the colour.. so yeah, forgot to buy gift, guess this is the best for her le.. haha.  Looking forward to tomorrow, and waiting for that someone.... 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Still somewhat having a trace of that happiness i had from yesterday....&nbsp;side effect&nbsp;perhaps ? Lol~ The whole day&nbsp;I felt kinda good, and was very active, hehe. Had a rather brightened day..  &nbsp;  Somewhat that idiot who did something unpleasant&nbsp;yesterday was suspended today, when he didnt admit to another&nbsp;wrong he did... i'm so damn happy he is suspended, to hell with that loser. Smooth day today. Loved this day at school, haha. Somewhat the thoughts in my brain didnt surface, and my mood stayed clear the whole day... guess this should be a rarity in a thousand days ? Lol.  &nbsp;  Went to tampines to check out the price and the offer for EA classic.. basket, Challenger didnt have the offer around.... damn.. ended up with Kun Long buying his CD-Rs and DVD+RW... and got a CD for Joei's birthday... hope she likes it when she gets it... :)  &nbsp;  Relatively short entry...&nbsp;I suppose.. but hey, its a contrast to all the other posts way back... the mood's different, yeah ? hehe... Yeah, thats for today...  &nbsp;  Peace out. :)   
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Just when I was about to search for my geography notes and head to sleep, a call came from my neighbour. It was their mum at the phone, and she needed help from me to print something from a floppy disk.  Qi Xiang came to my house , and i got ready the stuff for printing. Printer, paper, and the com. I slotted the diskette in, but found it to be unformatted (faulty) and thus could not access the data inside. Qi Xiang went back and I followed shortly after. Went over to QX's house, and saw their mum's friend there, along with&nbsp;her&nbsp;husband and daughter popping her head over the door. I saw her for the first time, and had a better glimpse of her when her family walked out the door.  My.. she looked good ! She was the kind of girl I had in mind ! The looks.. so nice and innocent... ! Haha.. Bleah. =P  As she went out, i noticed she was kinda sad.. I think its due to her compo being lost.. I felt kinda sad too, lol, since i wasnt too big a help to her. =S  I just wonder if she'll come again.. with her new diskette and ready to print again.. hope i can get more chances to meet her.. perhaps fate is creating a chance ? Then again.. naw.. doubt she'll fancy me.. hmm... I wont push it ba.. like Aaron said, 'Unlimited amount of chasing will get you the opposite effect instead'. Moreover, I dont even know her at all..&nbsp;So, I'll leave it all to Fate...  This event really had brightened my day ! (or night :p) I'm happy enough to have seen someone so stunning ! Thanks God !  Hee.. a good night's sleep awaits me..... :D  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Didnt feel too good today. My day was ruined by some idiot who did something unpleasant which i would not say... and then i was like fidgeting the whole time in class after that. Well, it at least kept me from sleeping, haha. More or less got something into this empty brain of mine.  &nbsp;  Was supposed to pop by at CS today. But didnt go as a result of Sherman and me couldnt accomodate to each other, he wanted to go play, but i didnt want to, since i, as usual nowadays, couldnt pick up the mood to play. Lost the interest. I just&nbsp;wanted to have a relaxing walk around&nbsp;the two malls, CS and Tampines&nbsp;Mall.&nbsp;To top it off, i didnt bring my home clothes either. Ended up going to Superbowl with Benjamin, Joshua, James and William. Sherman went to AMK Zone X to play, alone. Man, hes strong on these stuff, no go and he meant it. Bugger. &nbsp;  Saw Ben and Josh bowl, along with William. Spent my time till 2.30pm when we went to Mac's to catch a bite. Saw Kenneth there, wasnt kinda pleased to see him.. Sheesh. Went home after that, and so tired till i nearly fell asleep on the bus.. although it was a very short trip. Dont know... this fatigue kinda striked on me nowadays.. causing me to doze off into half conscious state whenever i'm inactive.. what's happening...  &nbsp;  Another point to add is that i just found out and realised this.. after reading Aaron's blog..&nbsp;that I'm not good at expressing myself. At least if he's got something up his mind, he'll have a reaction to it. Cry, throw temper, whatever. But me, just quiet and moody. Seldom cry nowadays, dont know if i've lost the feeling to even cry.  &nbsp;  Yeah i guess thats it for today, watching my favourite Channel U show where u gotta search around for some prize cards.. Basket... one of the&nbsp;participants... kept all his 3 cards hidden at home, none was found, and after that at the mall, he got 7 out of 9 cards... total amount of prizes amounting to $10077.. man hes nuts, kinda greedy too...&nbsp;after that i'm doing my homework... felt quite energetic today. Wonder why. &nbsp;  Hope tomorrow will be&nbsp;a finer day. Benedict signing out. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Stayed at home the whole day. Had tuition, and nothing else was really that noticeable after that. Just a normal day, still couldnt pick up my mood to do some stuff, i guess its really time i stood up myself and really head on to a fresh start.. things cant go on like this forever... i've still got my life to live, and my commitments. i cant let this mood of mine dominate me on and on... its just not right.. &nbsp; Messaged Aaron today. Was supposed to meet him up today at wadever time hes free, and was looking forward to a soulful chat with him. at least to let out my cooped up emotions, that i had in me coming to 3 weeks now.. Alas, this was not to be, when he didnt reply any of my sms-es, man, its like... if he couldnt, then just tell me la... not as if i was gonna flame him off for not able to.. just let me know... jeez. with that i stayed home the whole time, listless and disappointed. Hope i could get him out sometime next&nbsp;week,&nbsp;the bottling up felt kinda stuffy. At least in my head. &nbsp; Gonna do some homework for now, and well, maybe head off to CS to buy another EA Classic, Renegade. I dont even speculate i might play at the arcade, i somehow spent too much on the outing yesterday. So, yeah, i guess thats it, dont know what to say too. Lost for words. &nbsp; And so i keep on waiting.. for my loved one to come to me... 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just thought i might do a little bit of blogging before i turn in to bed. Today was a rather memorable day, having met a lot of peepz in the local ID scene, and had a mass makan session with them.. it was very enjoyable.  &nbsp;  Met Aaron at the arcade at around 1.30 pm. he was playing some ID, so i thought i might go play some Wangan before i go with him to the second floor, where Seoul Garden is. met KC, Channon, Wayzik, Gwen, and a lot of other peepz... after that we went in and just whacked the food hard.... we took up a total of 5 tables, and were like so noisy throughtout the time we were there. Enjoyed the food, the self grilling, and got a little oil splats on my hand, and had great conversations with them.. even though they just knew me. Loved it. They were very friendly and a great bunch to hang out with.  &nbsp;  After that we proceeded down to the arcade again, to play Wangan. i successfully completed my second round of story mode, and is on my way to full tuning my R34, wads left is 1 more round of playing the CPU, and i'm ready to take on challengers. My card name changed to The Steel Wind, and it sounded very strong, haha.  &nbsp;  Headed to Atrium after that, and played some ID. As usual, i couldnt break any times. felt vexed at the way things are going... wasting money and couldnt see results. bleah. After that some of the peepz went up to see the movie King Arthur, but i stayed behind and watched all the way to around 10.15pm, and went home after that. Got to know Zheng Long, a member of X-T who lived very near me... just 2-3 blocks away.  &nbsp;  Told my mum how i felt these days, she just said the usual stuff, try hard, dun waste money. and get ur&nbsp;priorites correct. i knew it all long ago. just that, i didnt have the heart, the mood to do it. Well i guess i have and got to pick up from where i left off, otherwise this semester, i'll be darn screwed big time.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  After meeting Aaron for the first time today after talking to him so much on MSN, this is the first time i had a meal together with him. Or rather, same location, but 3 tables away. I kinda guessed that he was not wanting to sit with me due to the empty seats (i did feel a little sense of pung seh, when i hey-ed to him and he didnt look back, but i wont blame him) , and it would be occupied my Melissa and Zhi Sheng... the couple now, but the girl Aaron lov-ED. I felt he became kinda more depressed and disappointed when i told him how Zhi Sheng (Shiro), told mel that he was staring at her... He did tell me later at atrium, he just couldnt believe it. The words Shiro said.&nbsp;And yet, he cant do anything about it.  &nbsp;  This situation was kinda confirmed when about now, i've seen his entry for his blog today, and it was a entry full of emotions. His phrase, '   I know I'm not any handsome suave young guy girls would fall for, but certainly, I'm human too. I've my emotions. I know my limits, but please God, stop fooling with my life anymore. I'm on the brink of death and destruction.  ',&nbsp;really pulled out what i've got to say&nbsp;in this period of my life, and thanks to u, Aaron, i certainly didnt know what to type, but this, is really my point, that i have in my heart. Thanks a lot for putting it into words. I've been a bit too messed up these days&nbsp;that my previous entries was all kinda single-worded (i did notice it.. but my vocab couldnt pull anything else out) , darkness, lonliness, and all.. i know my english isnt as good as yours, and i, definitely couldnt express it out better than you. Thanks again.   Guess thats about it, had some time to think of stuff on the way home, on the bus, and felt very&nbsp;messed up&nbsp;about it. Still,&nbsp;nothing's been going right, and darkness is all around. What can i say, thats how my life is now.  &nbsp;  Night peeps. Benedict out.    
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of the moderately good days i had during this time of my life. i was occupied all day, and didnt have much time to think abt the matters i had... although i had time to sort out my feelings during assembly time and on the bus to AMK Jubilee..&nbsp;  In&nbsp;chemistry class, Sherman told me about what happened before he slept with Bernice .. i was like... omg. her parents were like so open... and Bernice&nbsp;herself too, popping a question of 'when are you going to have *** with me...' , really contrary to her shyness of meeting pple... lol..  &nbsp;  Still, i am envious of this perfect pair... i still wonder, how could i have made good friends with a guy who has been so fortunate to have his dearest, compared to me who lacks it... big time.. haha... fate really baffles me.  &nbsp;  Went to Jubilee Zone X to play some ID.. didnt run too good a timing, but i was still contented. i just wonder when my form will come back.. all that i've been striving for, working for.. slogging it all out for... just gone.. when i get this kind of bad mood swings, once in a while. i suppose its the third time this year, heck, does anyone give a damn...  &nbsp;  Perhaps few pple know the way i am, and i seldom disclose it, i mean, i dont wanna shun pple off when they hear that i got some sad thoughts, depression, and all the crap... i've always thought of other pple to be happier than me.. emotionally... i've a stable cash flow.. for going out and stuff, but.. for the things money cant buy, i've nothing by the name of love. Aaron told me today, certain things just cant push it, unlimited amount of chasing may get me the opposite effect instead. then again, we control our destinies.. so do i go push it, or do i sit on the fence, waiting for something to happen ? i dunno... i'm lost.  &nbsp;  To pick up from where i left off before this started would be a tall order... it just seems that i've been given a mission to jump into a black hole... and finding nothing inside.. coming back up seems impossible ATM... guess i hope i'll not linger for too long before a ray of light comes shining in, and i can walk into it.. with the help of a kind helping hand.  &nbsp;  Everyday i claim that i needed&nbsp;help from someone, hell, couldnt i just be independent ? things would still be the way they were, and the world keeps on spinning. the fact that i'm feeling down probably didnt matter to other peepz, since its my own private business, and it doesnt affect them, too.  &nbsp;  Living here WAS a nightmare, IS a nightmare, and ALWAYS it is. Just felt this way. Let me free..   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well today wasnt as bad a day as it seemed, at the very least i felt kinda normal today. my heart felt empty. no bad emotions whatsoever. on a scale of 0 to 10, i'll rate myself 5... its darn normal.. i dunno, but when its always on the way home, i'll have that period all to myself, oblivious to the surroundings to me, and just sorting out my feelings for the day in school.  School isnt as enjoyable as it really seems.. to me, its just a place where i have to slog my guts out for half the day before the cold rounded metal rounded piece of metal rings, and a crowd of happy guys rushing out, all set to head back home, or just hang out, have some fun, before heading to the comfort where they always spend surfing, watching TV... all the things that teenagers can do at home.  Maybe Aaron was right, one tends to be the person he is behind a face. And that face, is the thing i'm looking to right now. the PC. I'm my real self here, having all said the stuff i've been keeping inside my hearts. All this blogging seemed to have freed me a bit from my bottling up of emotions, words, and expressions. Saved me from making things into a bunch of mess, and then just worrying and thinking of someway out. Do i really have that much to say? I mean, i'm quiet and all in school, with friends, and parents. But, in this blog, says a thousand words i would like to have poured out to someone. A listening ear, which i couldnt find.  These days the rain had the coolness going, despite i still havent the mood to pick up from where i left off before the holidays. Managing to scrape 3 passes out of 6 subjects isnt the scene where i would like to be caught in.. and i very much fear what i can pull off this semester, with all this stuff hitting me hard.  So who said i was vulgar. Who said i was nutty, crazy, and cracking jokes, funny or lame. I didnt really mean what the heck i'm talking about, they just came out of this mouth of mine. I'm lost... maybe my life has once again shattered itself into pieces that i'll have to try glue it back.. and the moment it didnt hold it all together, the low tide will once again approach me, and be with me for a period of time it feels contented, and i can get on with life. Move on, no one's gonna wait for you.. Time doesnt. Tide dont. Friends neither. The special someone... i have none.  Having the house all to myself tonight was a really great idea, no parents nagging for 1 night. But it really pulled the innermost tinglings of my hearts out into words i tried to type, but still, they just stayed as if they were parasites. Sad, but true.  She didnt give much of a reply after all, well maybe she wasnt interested at all. Hey, with someone of my quality, i find it common that loneliness will be here to stay. At least it did, for 15 coming to 16 years of my life. Worthless me.  Will anyone tell me what to do.... I'm in darkness trying to find some kind hand to lead me out....
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was kinda cool too, with all the rain coming thru and all.. didnt run today, was sick and had a bad cough.. at least the MC convinced the PE teachers...  Everything was kinda normal in class, nothing went too bad, until Sherman told me Joei said i was "very cute", after that day when we went to see Spiderman 2. i was like har ? (-.o") got ger fancy me ? or my looks ? wow... wad a surprise.  Before that the medicine i took had its drowsy effects on me.. i kinda laid my head in class the whole day... but hearing that, i kinda had a sudden burst of energy and vitality, dunno why.. haha.  Anyway, had a conference for 1 and a half hrs in the afternoon around 4.30pm with Karie and Sherman... i was, haha, the listener most of the time... was kinda fun tho.. hee..  Messaged Joei at around 9.30pm, she didnt reply.... ahhh~~ i was expecting her to ! den just now sent another one... still no reply, so i tot i'll just leave it up to her ba, to reply or not.. but i sure hope she does ! lol.. feel kinda funny now.. excited, yet disappointed. well, i guess its up to Friday whether i'll see her or not... den can talk more to her i suppose.. if she doesnt dao me, that is..   I'll be looking forward to your reply.... :)
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      School was kind of okay today, with little crap in my class today.. they began the classroom locking when its recess or we need to go to other places like the science labs and after school too. this kinda sucks, since i always stay in class during recess.. now need to find some other place to go and while away the break time le..  CME lesson wise, what we did was just to complete the page where the CONDUCT is on, and have sentences formed from each letter of it.. and talked about racism.. blacks, whites, yellows, niggas. blah. our maths cum form teacher is going off for NS reservist soon, so we'll be having a relief teacher from now on.. duno until when, but i kinda look forward to his teaching...  Today was a real rainy day man, rained twice in the afternoon.. and i got a bit wet from the rain around 2.45pm... but yeah, managed to get a cab to go to CS, before the real stuff came... phew..  Actually wasnt planning to go to Century Square today, but since Kun Long and Kenneth were going, i tot it might be good to join in the fun too... kinda hate boredom these days... otherwise my mind will think of all sorts of things again.. sigh..  Played WMMT and ID v3 today, but again, its mostly WMMT... i got my timing on New Belt Line to 4'43... super happy, to top it off, my R32 in ID got its shomaru time reduced from 3'11 to 3'10'876 in the first run, but the second one was a real pleasant surprise.. a 3'05 !! a great leap !! Uber happy today !!  After that headed to Popular in Tampines central.. since the one at CS was too small and had nothing to see ard.. headed to the hp shop where Sherman asked for the price of T630.. wah.. drop again... need to pay $280 only if i traded my 3100... not the $318 before.. We bought 2 EA classics, and got 1 free. but we shared the price equally among the 3 of us.. since each taking 1 game... and i bought a box of CD-RW and DVD-RW too.. made full use of the 15% discount NKF voucher... haha...  Went back home to see doc, guess what ? they start at 7... i got there at 6.35.. decided to head home first, den go see.... come back, wah the crowd was like so many.. waited from 7.20 to 8... den see doc.. the doc was like pampering a small kid sia.. keep patting my arm.. and showered a lot of "motherly" care on me... whaha... but good la... better than one dao one.. hehe. Been sick for over a week le.. den see doc..  Btw, Bought a box of rojak home for my parents as a surprise, but they didnt really appreciate it.... or so i suppose..  When nearly reaching my house, suddenly 3 sms came at the same time, making my phone ring a big big beep. was wondering... got 3 pple send me sms at same time ? rarity leh... but all came from Karie.. she was like all urgent about getting a extra hp for her fren... but i think she got too urgent, and scolded me vulgarities in the last sms, say i didnt wanna reply.. i was like har ? O.O"?? Then i msged her on MSN... she, as per usual, was kinda the not interested to talk to me... with a tone that friends doesnt use.... i wonder, wads her purpose for doing this.. i see her blog, was like all happy and stuff, but to me, shes cold as ice. or maybe even colder. sheesh. i doubt Saturday i'll be off to the movies with her and her friends... since, i'm the only one, and i'm kinda short in that gang too, i suppose. bleh, one step at a time ba... -.-~  Well i hope shes cooled down, my medicine doing the work, and everything's gonna be OK tml... had a very happening Tuesday.. just like last week. oh, forgot to mention, yesterday was the first week old of my blog.. haha.. 1 wk, and this much crap le..lol.. blogger can tahan anot.. i wonder... Ok la, i'm off to do my things le, and to sleep early tml...   Man.. all this blogging... kinda takes up a long time.. this entry took like.. 40 mins ? i'm getting burned out here... saw the article.. on burned out of blogging.. disturbing the normal rhythm of pple's normal routine.. i guess i'm one of them too.. but i'll try my best to blog everyday, and whenever i have the time.... and not to be this lengthy, haha. >.<"
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just thought i might do 1 before i turn in to bed, and to get ready for a new day full of hope, joy, and fun! (Crap... does that ever happen..) Nvm..  Anyways, i didnt do my homework as said just now in the last entry, well i couldnt focus well and thus, i whiled my time away talking to Kun Long and packing up my bag.. I found that my focus time is around 5 to 7.. evening time rather, i found myself with lots of zest and energy at that period of time, and i suppose its time to do some re-planning of my time schedule.. to do my work in the evening, and mostly whack some games at night..  I feel that this might be the best arrangement for a person like me, trying to recover from some emotional breakdown. Karie's invited us to go see a movie this Saturday, everything's not been settled yet, but Sherman's already given me the red light.. saying hes got tuition and stuff, and most likely if i did go, it will be me only...  Ah anyway, enough of beating around the bush, i'll fill in more of the details tomorrow, now is my sleep time le... was kinda tired today, fell asleep once in class.. during history.. i hope that tml i wont do this kinda thing again, must stay awake and not miss out any details... Later ! :)
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Start of a new week. was supposed to go running at 2.40pm in school, but since it rained, heck it la. was drenched a little bit on the way home, but hey, its nothing at all.. compared to the affairs in my heart.  I suppose today was practically a normal day, with nothing much to say in particular. the rain that came in noon kinda made me feel refreshed from the morning heat, and it kind of felt good, since the heat these days were unbearable.  In class, Sherman was like talking about the days he spent in Bernice's house.. sleeping on the same bed... doing some stuffs which i, personally, suspect a lot. (Sherman did clarify things, but heh, i doubt hes kinda truthful about it...) he was like kinda scared smth would happen... u know, big stomach ? So much for encouraging pple to have birth in SG... well here's a great proposal... encourage teenage pregnancy, den 100% the birth rate would go up man.. skyrocket like no tml~  After school Sherman headed for Century Square to whack WMMT again (man hes RICH) and he kinda jio-ed me.. but like i said before, i need to resist the temptation of WMMT and ID for at least a week, i dont want this mood of mine to let me have a faulty run, and waste my money. Hope that things can settle down soon. as expected, i declined his offer, and made my way home straightaway.  Going to see a bit of TV den do my homework now.. well i guess thats the end of this entry... Ciao !
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So i missed out one day of blogging... didnt have much to say yesterday, since its a whole day at home.. sick and kinda out of mood to do stuff..  Yesterday night Wee Meng sms-ed me, and he was like saying how he felt sad about me like this... he wants me to 'wake up' and strive hard... all his pep talk kind of fell on deaf ears... as i went to slp yesterday night with lots of regrets of things i did in the past, and fatigue. Sorry Wee Meng.. I'll try my best to work myself up and get back my perspectives.. just as what Heron said, I need a break and time to come back strong... I know its hard but i'll just try...  Still somewhat feeling down.. (is there any day i wont ?) and it seems pple are involved in love one way or the other... Heron liked a girl but he couldnt tell, and the girl couldnt accept. He just tried all he could to protect her, any way he can, and i feel thats VERY noble... to not able have someone by your side but still caring for him/her always...  Went to Dhoby Ghaut to pass the DVD-RW back to the buyer, and on the way home i was like thinking.. the pros and cons of having a relationship... but i'll still rather have someone i can talk to than be alone and facing the 4 walls that surround me all day...  Sherman called me at 9 plus in the morning today, we talked a bit.. his favourite hamster died, and his dear Bernice and him talked all night till the morning.. he was like comforting her all night... wow.. the power of love, making him stay on the phone and not sleep.. I think i could do it too, but, whos gonna even give me the chance to ? Fate Fate Fate... blah.. be patient.. and all that stuff.. i dont really think i can wait any more...   All this mood change is causing me a lot of trouble in my daily life. Not able to finish homeworks on time, unable to run good timing in IDAS, and off form in wadever i try to accomplish. This sucks.  To top it off, what a addition to this entry, i was like trying to put the cover for the pillow in, and this time it wouldnt go smoothly. My mum came in, saw me throw the cloth on the floor, and she started to shout at me. Really, she didnt notice about this reaction of mine, yet she cared more was about the damn pillow cover. Nice. Doesnt anyone ever pay attention to me ? Not even my closest parents ?   .... Let me die in my sleep. Please. Life has totally lost its meaning, at least on me. Let me DIE.
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Starting to get a little tired of things... arcade games, studies, life. Maybe i shld take a break from ID and WMMT these few days.. or even a week - 2 weeks.   In school, i kept my head on the table most of the time, and i kinda fell asleep soon after, if not struggling hard to stay awake. CME lesson talked about what we shld do when we are out on a date... crap, everyone will be in their best right... to leave a good first impression.. SE would be better... :x   Went to Century Square with Sherman after that, off to whack WMMT and ID. In the end we ended up playing WMMT only... with a few sidekicks of ID V3.. i got my timing down to 4'44, using BB on New Belt Line CW.. and then, after that i started to get a little tired liao.. on the way home i nearly fell asleep on the cab..   At home i wonder why today i'm playing CS for a long while.. playing all the funny maps.. and stupid Willy told Shu Yun i NEED a girl... i was like (-.-)"  Playing Linkin Park - Numb on my com as i'm typing this entry...   YES I AM going NUMB... OBLIVIOUS.... 
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      SGRacer chatter box slanting into matters of the hearts again... sigh, talking about that special someone in our lives.. again.. Sigh... Still waiting for mine... really dunno wad to say le, out of words, out of breath, and out of love.  And.. So it wasnt true. not a 4'40. but a 4'50 on the blackbird. ah nvm, just gonna try harder and whack the bloody track harder....  looking forward to tml, can play WMMT, but cannot meet either Yap or Aaron.. sian... Nvm i still got Sherman !
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok... boring day i suppose, its just a normal day at school, but with the rain that started around 1.50pm, i felt that it might be a good time for me to let my soul take over me for a while... was thinking that on days i dont have anything to share, i might let out a bit of how i'm like in this life of mine...  Playing Michael Learns to Rock - Take Me To Your Heart right now... have liked this song since i first saw the ad on TV... haha. The rain's still on now, feels kinda cool.. i feel its like me.... making others happy (since its cool) and leaving my inner soul to the elements of nature (sad) - in this case its the exposure to pple in my life... sheesh, the rain is always alone where it goes, and not very liked by some since it kinda spoils their day.. like outing to beach or smth...  Karie's off to her camp, and i gave her the morning call half an hr later! omg.. gd thing Sherman called her on time... Hope everything's well and goes fine.. and yea, hope that nothing gets cancelled or disrupted due to this rain... my raft making was cancelled due to this rain on the first day at around the same time too... 4 pm... lol. Enjoy ur camp Karie ! (well not as if she can see this... but well..)  Sherman's been a little fidgety after recess, doesnt respond much when i call him... ah heck.. i can sense it.. dun tell me NO hor ! hehe.. everyone's got their ups and downs.. he even dao me and walked off with harry after school... lol nvm.. >.  Tomorrow going off to Century Square again... with Sherman, to play WMMT... just wonder if Shini (Aaron) and H.Z (Yap) joining me or not... best if they did... haha.  Ah i guess that concludes this entry... i might come up with another one at night (see other pple's blogs only 1 per day, mine's like... 2-3... wonder if those seeing my blog will think i very free ? O.O" haha.. and yes, my entries are all lengthy and stuff, other peepz are shorter... jeez.... ~.~"
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      6.15pm, Just bathed and got dressed.. after the trip down to Compass Point. Was expecting to see the usual 5 coming to meet us, but only Jarael and Karie turned up.  Sherman really the cock-eyed sia.. see some NVSS come out from NEL, den he hurriedly grabbed my hp to call Karie.. instead while he finding the number Karie appeared from behind.. LoL~ Went to KFC to get lunch.. Basket.. i sick still go.. haha.. whack la, who cares...  den we go shopping for Jarael's track pants, and off to mos burger's outdoor seats to sit and wait for Jarael's "crush" to call or sms her... then we go le.. I say wanna go toilet, after come out all gone lo.. wah.. super PS sia...lol~  hmm, today felt a bit better and more expressive in front of Karie, i talked quite a bit i suppose.. but still she didnt look at me directly or wadever lor.. haha.. still the same.. hopes she like my present :P (a necklace with her horoscope Leo on it..) Maybe its the fact that i committed myself to "me and her isnt possible" attitude, then today treated her like normal fren, so i could express myself better ? i dunno... just have this gut feeling.  Come back liao, Sherman on MSN suanned me seh... Love ROX! thing is... he know i lacking it... sigh.. but i know he do it in the name of fun... so nvm la, let it go hee.. his jokes have led me to lose the girls fee for the movie tix, basket, shout so loud, treat them all la.... BWG... BTH.. haha....
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoa.. what a day. some ups and downs i had in a single day man.  First off, today wasnt really the day i was expecting, since i'm feeling down lately, and the second lesson for the day, CME lesson, talked on reasons for dating and BGR relationships... after that, straight came Pastoral Care lesson, guess what ? Family ties... All these affairs of the heart really had me slanting towards the deep dark side of me again.. in class somemore.. then after that i kinda lost a bit of interest to do wadever there is.. maths.. as well as chinese homework.  Brought my home clothes today, (just a green shirt, lol) and went to Century Square Fun Factory to play Wangan Midnight. Just barely 4 games, me and Sherman were kicked out, due to the fact that we didnt change our trousers.. Actually had a hunch when i first looked into the arcade, there werent any school students, or related clothes.. As expected, the rule to us first timers was unknown.. thus, 30 minutes and we had to leave the premises. Whats so bad is that Sherman didnt even get to experiment with the game, and we were out of the place. Sorry Sherman.. i've been hogging the machine to last my extra $2 start to the max... but didnt know u cant play as a result... sigh.. sheesh.  Then at night, Sherman intro-ed me a girl (again -.-"), called Sharon, chinese name Shu Yun, (surname still unknown =X) studys at Serangoon Sec Sch... At first i tot the sch was in Serangoon, but OMG, its in Hougang... lol.. further than CHIJ Sengkang.. Goodness...  She dun wanna gimme her hp number.. then had to ask Sherman for the number. He say he not sure have or not sia... power.  Tomorrow meeting "her", Karie, again.. bought her a gift at Yellow at Century Square.. A necklace carrying her horoscope, hope she likes it... hee. Compass Point will be the place..  Still feeling kind of down, but somewhat felt better, when i commit myself to the fact that one cant be forced to love.. haha, still and STILL having my darn sore throat and fever, but it got much much better now... taking panadol later, and its off to bed.. for a whole new day tml.. dunno whether can slp first anot, cos i napped for quite a while at 6-8 pm... hehe..  Ok, thats about it... wow, kinda lenghty, dunno the page can support anot... haha, nitez pple... and even tho i'm not Christian or whatever, but, God Bless. :)
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One day's ended just like that.... Portugal lost to Greece 1-0 in Euro... my skyline NUR R34 got tuned to 520 HP in Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune, wasted my day doing nothing.. nv touch my hw too...  Down with sore throat and fever... now whole head red and hot... sian... why in the hell would i get sick sia... lack of water maybe? hope tml i'll be better ba...  Came to terms with the fact that i couldnt be with her as an item, well, let nature take its course.. but when will mine come ? i'm seriously looking very much forward to it... pls come into my life soon... my world is in darkness without u...
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Actually i've got someone on my mind, i've just met her, watched spiderman 2 with her, sherman, and a bunch of her friends. perhaps i may be too rushed into things, due to the fact that i've havent known her well enough, but after that day, conference on the phone, she stopped replying to my sms, and even msn.  which leaves me to say that i couldnt have any other ways to know her better, but i think she doesnt fancy me ba... shes been talking to sherman and looking at him in the eyes, but to me, if i didnt ask any question, she would not care at all.  at that night, things got even worse, i relayed sherman's messages to her thru typing on msn, den i typed smth that pissed her bad, and shes been not in contact ever since.  she's just been out of love, and i seriously hope i can be the one to heal her wounds... take care of it... well now i really dun think that chances are high...
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just created a new blog... seems to me like everyone's got one... well, at least it helps me to store whatever i've got to say... and not coop it up in my heart..  been feeling very down lately, it just seems that no one really cares, still looking for one i can pour out to, the understanding kind soul. but alas, i doubt i'll find one anytime soon...  seeing those couples on the streets, i'm so envious of them... or shld i say i'm lacking the love ?
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm.. Stayed at home for the whole day (usual stuff..) and preparing for my Maths CA paper tomorrow... Had a real big propotion of tuition.. a whopping 3 and a half hours totally sucking my energy dry..  Other than that I've really been lonely and moody at home, had to control my hunger for during the tuition... Missed my lunch, haha.  Sigh. Nothing much to say really, just staring at the books and the sky... while it pours heavily down my area...  Just hope I can pull off the paper well tomorrow..  Ja... 
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its kinda late now. Had a rather rushed start of the day, and now, a stupid running nose is bugging me... Damn. Read a few blogs and a post of "Love in friendships" on the canadian forums, before I decided that its time for me to do my post for the day.  Actually woke up at 7.10 am, but due to the tired me (only 6 hours of sleep beforehand), I decided to stay in bed for a while before I get prepped up and go for my chemistry remedial. But alas. I got into a semi-conscious state until 8.30, that was then I suddenly remembered that I had something on ! So I rushed up, did my stuff in a hurry, and left the house hurriedly, taking bus $2.40 to school. Reached there at 9.15, in quite a good time since they just started the lesson. Whew.  So I took a seat, and did what I'm supposed to do (duh) and the whole class was kinda quiet. I liked it, since, normal lessons would consist of those who werent interested to learn, so they made a din at the back. Worse, I'm now sitting at the back of the class. Today's atmosphere was a quiet and serious one, with a few jokes of mis-pronounciation of some terms by Louis. Besides that I could concentrate pretty well. Thats how a class should be.  Chemistry remedial ended, I decided that I make a move rather than stay for the Maths one.. since I cant really understand what Mr Koh's trying to say, as well as his sudden mood swings. He will just go nuts, scolding the whole class. Once I tried to clear a doubt I had with a problem, he was in a foul mood, so I got scolded for nothing, and the whole class looked at me.  Went with Sherman to Atrium, played a bit of ID, where he got cut into pieces by a Cappuccino because he mis-judged the level of the player. Sigh. And he played wet with a FR. Nice.... laming him. Got my Nokia 6230 warranty card stamped, and headed to PS for a round of WMMT. Took the train to Chinatown while Sherman would be alighting at Outram.. since hes having tuition at Holland Village. Met Heron while going up the escalator. What coincidence.  Went to Mac. Had McWings meal, and talked a bit with Heron. Didnt study as was supposed to. But well... Someone in the team is obviously getting out of hand, and its gonna explode like a time bomb sooner or later. Kicking him out is the best I say.  Stayed at CTP till around 7.15pm, had dinner with Yap, Ivan and Steve, and headed back home. Got a new pack of Neutrogena (Mines running empty soon).  Bathed, and decided to come online to look around. Found this interesting topic, Love in friendships. Saw that he was actually friends with a girl for some time.. but all along, the girl treated him like a cushion whenever she fell, and when shes lonely. How should I put this.... The guy was there for her all of the time, but heck, she didnt even take much notice of it, except saying that hes the best. AND yet finding other boyfriends, when a good choice is just beside her. Kinda unfair for the guy who worked hard for his special spot in that girl... Being close friends, and yet, the girl didnt want to progress further with him, even though hints were dropped time and again. Even confessions. The girl just looked out the window, when theres already someone in the house. Dumb, blind, whatever. And the guy hooked her up with one of his best friends, and whom the girl had a crush on. Became a love triangle, with a line missing.  Emotions well up me as I read through this, as well as some other peeps' love story.. Helping out others, doing good, at the expense of your own happiness. Or simply, sacrificing something important, just to do some good, and the bad outcomes, taking the blow yourself. While the other person enjoys the good result of it. The nice guy gets the lousy end of the stick of it all, despite the (noble) sacrifices he made.  Well I feel that I'm also like the "I'll do good deeds even if it brings me down" type, the emotional "doormat" for the people, letting them get comfy after letting their stuff out, and doing my best to try to console them. Then they treat you like normal friends, not giving much concern to you. When something bad happens again, its a vicious cycle repeating itself again. And they never see you in a romantic way, because it all boils down to looks, despite all the crap they all say. So much for having a good character and all. Brave fronts and happy outlook ? Hahaha. Tell me its really like that.  I do all this hoping that someone someday, will notice the hard work you try to put in to other people's lifes, brighten it up for them, and that someone will appreciate you doing all this. But somehow this somewhat never happens, and even if it does, its just a microscopic chance. Maybe one in a trillion ? Makes no sense, and probably never will. Ah, love.  I dont expect a good reward for everything nice I do, but hey, at least something nice should happen even if its once in a blue blue moon ? Just a little gift for all that arduous work you've done.. I think its more than reasonable for even that to take place.. Just once. I dont ask for much. I'll cherish it, I swear.  Nice guys finish LAST. I second that. Whats so nice about my character being good and all of that crap ? All that proper chivalry ? I just dont get it. Twisted sick ideology ? Maybe. From end of June till now, I've been stuck in a storm, when the rain just seems to let down for a while, it starts a new wave of tides, and the weather makes a turn for the worst, again. All I can do now is to wait it out, and hope that theres a rainbow at the other end of the horizon. All I wanna do is to make someone happy... Is that too hard for me to do ? Jeez.  Food for thought tonight, as I sleep with all these in my mind. Might be kept awake, even though I've been out all day, and I'm totally shacked out.  Good night peeps. Hope my running nose stops its nonsense, because I'm really not liking it. Not at all. 
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just got back from Atrium, realising tomorrow I've got chemistry and maths remedial. Decided not to stay too late but it was already 11pm when I saw it. So yeah... Took the train to Serangoon, and walked back from there (took 25 mins.. but... felt it was good excercise, and kinda freed my mind for a while... kinda relaxing to walk a bit ba...)  Went to Aaron's house at 6.15 pm. My, his corner terrace design is like a rectangle.. not the usual square... kinda big for the terrace porch, and as well as the rooms. Nice house hes got. Haha. TL was with Aaron when I saw him too.  Browsed stuff on Aaron's com till around 7.35, and we headed down to Atrium.. had dinner (fast food again!), i went up to play some Wangan, only to find that theres only 2 machines left... Man... it sucks.. But oh well, TKA.. Heard that its going to HongKong.. What a pity. Got a 12'49'300 for my Metropolitan Highway, on BlackBird. Since BB is a out-of-control car, this timing wasnt too bad I suppose. Gonna try out the Reina GTR 32 soon. Expecting something like 12'49'500.  Stayed around Atrium and played a few rounds of ID, challenged a Evo7 which I took to Akagi first, then he took me to Myogi (lol) and that was it. Talked to Uncle Phillip, as well as some of the other guys. Got an extra $5.50 free when I topped up the $15.  So thats about it, gonna sleep already, if not I'll be a walking zombie again tomorrow, Nitez ! 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm... Friday again (sweet.. 3 day school week) and its time for me to run out and have some fun le ! Haha. Just thought I might do a short entry right now..  So school today was ok, managed to stay awake the whole day (clap clap) and kinda enjoyed the day through...  Went to Tampines area with Sherman and Chan Lun, to get several items ticked off my shopping list. Adidas Climacool, Nokia 6100 Blue cover, and a Nokia 6230 Original Graphite Keypad. Also bought a pair dri fit Nike low cut socks.  Had lunch at Yoshinoya (thanks to the coupons) and then headed to Royal Sporting House. Biggest size was only 9.5, couldnt fit my leg too well. Then we went to Sportslink. Found that the biggest size was 11.5 (-.-") and I tried on the 10.5 and 10... Found 10 to be the perfect size.. So I took it, along with the pair of Nike socks. Total, $130.75.  Took a bus to Street 44, where MobileRange is. Bought a 6100 dark blue cover, as well as a graphite original 6230 cover. Total, $43.  So let me make a tally of the things I bought this August alone (>. -Hang Ten shirts and U2 pants : $100.40 -Adidas Climacool Shoes with Nike Dri Fit socks : $130.75 -Nokia 6100 (Second-hand) : $190 -Nokia 6100 dark blue Xpress-on Cover : $18 -Nokia 6230 Graphite cover with keypad : $90 -More to come (namely a Swatch watch and a Deuter backpack) So thats $529 and counting.... eek... this is the most I've spent in 1 month..  Gonna go tight on my budget after the next few items are acquired... Damn.. Financial status going to hit the red line soon...  Will blog again later, Seeya ! 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Already over 9pm. Actually this entry was supposed to be done at around, say 5.30 pm ? Just switched on the computer, but I leapt into bed for a short nap (well it aint that short, around 2 hours..) So after having dinner outside, I decided that I do this entry earlier. Since.. there might or might not be time later.  Needed this nap kinda badly. Felt so lethargic in class that I slept through the first 2 lessons of the day. Maths. I sure hope I didnt miss out any important details of it though... After which I sort of got back the energy to do work again, so I stayed awake for the whole day..  Sitting in a corner at the back of the class (due to register number order), I could say that the corner by the window sure was a cozy area, and it provided a gateway to letting me think of things.. a whole lot of them. And due to the teacher not always laying his attention on me, I could think of some things without disruption. I've always enjoyed my time while I was there, having a wall to lie sideways and backwards, and a handrest on the bars. Beats me but since young, I've always preferred corners rather than open areas. In a secluded world of my own ? I wonder.  So today was a good day, nice sun (crap), and a smooth day at school. And I got my chemistry and history test papers back. Guess what, I topped both of them, with 31.5/49 and 18/25 respectively. Very pleasant surprise, because like I said, I dont put high hopes on my work. At least not since Sec 1 ? Didnt expect to pull this semester of so well.... already topped 2, and came in second for 1 test. No, for readers who dont know me well, I'm not a bright child. Serious. And thanks to William for letting me "peep" into his physics test paper, since I didnt got enough time to study for it... Haha....  Went to Compass with KL and Sherman after school, couldnt find a running shoe I want, so went home feeling disappointed. Didnt even have lunch, both of them were broke.  Maybe it was due to insufficient sleep, I had a bad temper till I woke up... but gladly I didnt have the chance to throw it on anyone.... Haha.  Ok la... thats about it for today, dont really have anything much to blog, just that, seeing the couples on the streets, makes me envy them a lot. Lacking the love. Haha. Usual stuff. Whats new anyway.  Benedict signing out. 
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A hectic Wednesday, kinda expected for the day after such a long weekend break... BUT, much to my surprise, a dumb stomachache already threathened my agenda for the whole day since early morning, as early as before morning assembly ! Damn.. it has got to be one of the worst starts for a day....  So I had a struggle with it until I couldnt hold out and rushed to the toilet to relieve myself.... Ooh.. Relief at last. (What the hell am I blogging this thing for ? Beats me.) And the day kicked off, with a whole load of crap coming out of my Aussie teacher mouth.. and PE... the dumb teacher insisted that I do a jog, despite my wobbly self from the incident before. So I ran, and hell, did it took all energy that I had at that moment. Left me gasping for a while.  Along came the English Common Test paper straight after recess, and somehow, I found the paper to be within my handling... moderate questions... kinda ok for me.. After that was Chinese lesson. The teacher gave us back the test papers, and uh.... didnt perform up to my wish... haha... lost to Joshua by half a mark.... 47/50... while he stands at 47.5... argh.. I'm second... but that aint too bad..  After school I went to tease him a little bit, but he went "I can win you by that little margin just because I've got love, and you dont. Go find your love la !" Got me startled for a second (why did he suddenly say this ?), while his saliva splashed all over my face. Aww crap...  So somehow it gave me a mood swing after that, making me think of relationship stuffs again (ahh... hello lonliness !) , and I continued with it since the English test is already over, so theres nothing much to affect my performance on... Stared at the sky during TP, kinda lost in the air for that moment. To hell with what my form teacher's saying. Haha.  Thought of how she told Sherman I was lack of love, and lonely. Other than that she found me pretty ok... but somehow, I just couldnt click to her ba, didnt talk in around 2 weeks already. Hmm.. Also dont know what to say too... Seeing her nick somehow pushes the cursor away, preventing me from clicking it.... But yeah, so I really am outta love, its a fact that I couldnt deny. Well, live with it then. As if I can do something about it. Say, go around asking everyone's number ? Thats nuts. (Yes yes I know I live near a girls school, but that doesnt mean my circle of female friends must be very wide, and I'm always attached isnt it ? Duh.)  So I met KL after TP, was supposedly me waiting for him, now its the other way around since my teacher decided not to cancel TP... Went to Heartland Mall, decided not to let this mood swing get to me for too long, so I kinda acted to be the usual me, had lunch at KFC, and bought another Tomy Nissan FairLady Z Version S. Now I got 2... looks kinda nice when its a duo.. lol.  Headed home (alone) after that, and not long after I see KW calling me for a few times on my handphone, so i got back to him, he told me the graphite cover is here, and hopes I can collect it today. So I took a shower, and rushed down to Raffles Place where he was. Paid him the $62, took my stuff, and headed back home. But I stole some time off to play a bit of Wangan at PS... haha... Hand itchy...  Mum called, told me to get toothbrush and dinner. Bought the stuff, and headed home again.  Noticed that its already 9 when I stepped out of the shower, so I quickly did some things that were due tomorrow and now blogging here, kinda late.  Its really been a long and hectic day, but yeah, somehow I could enjoy it. Its also been kinda thoughtful, since... matters of the heart came knocking on my door again...  Oh yes.. my godfather is going to be cremated today, but I couldnt make it due to school... Sigh..  Thats about it, nightz people ! 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      End of the long holiday, school starting off tomorrow with a common test paper with a subject I somehow couldnt study.... English. And I figured out my physics retest would be postponed (YET AGAIN) to maybe thursday... since the time of the test takes up the whole physics lesson plus half of geography... haha..  Still stayed at home the whole day with my dad, didnt do much, just slacked around the com and did some stuff of packing up my table, gonna finish the job in these few days before I study for my common test next week. Figured I'll study better in a neat environment. Everywhere's dusty and all... I need to do a big clean up before I hit the books, else I'll be sneezing all day...  Saw a few peepz online, actually felt like msging them, but in the end I didnt, maybe its because I'm outta words to say, or maybe I need some time alone. Didnt know how to start the conversation going. Bleah...  Asked Aaron out for dinner in the afternoon, he somewhat made it sound like its a interrogation... says that I have no choice. I must go, and musnt put him on an aeroplane. I was like kinda puzzled as to why he would say that.... Ah well, its over, I couldnt make it, and he couldnt either, having some OT till 6.30pm.. otherwise he'll be the one putting me on an aircraft. Phew.  Parents gone to the funeral, and me, all left at home. But I guess its a good thing, some silence in the house. At least this time my mind didnt run wild, but I just felt like a empty nut, sitting there, staring at the screen... My mind in a blank.  Concluding my day, I would like to add, my mood still hasnt changed for the better, still feeling down and lonely, but oh well, as if there would be someone waiting for me after school.. Or me doing the waiting...  Its just me, walking home, alone. 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So today is our nation's 39th brithday, and the whole country seemed to be in high spirits... everywhere I go, I see people in red, haha...  Basically I stayed at home till about evening when I headed down to Sembawang to my godfather's funeral again, on the way I parted from my parents to fulfil my sudden craving for KFC spicy chicken, and stole some 25 minutes to play some cheap Wangan before I took bus 859 down to their block....  Tried 760/DG on my R34 (since its missing the last 2 upgrades, so no 800/DG), didnt found it to be up to expectation, since top speed was only 330kmh. Wanted something like 350+, but I dont think thats possible. Meh, my New Belt Line Clockwise timing is still stuck at 4'39'397... With the BlackBird... Hope can get it down to 4'37'500...  So this was pretty much my day, I seriously didnt find much worth the mentioning to blog about.  On a side note, my eyes still felt pretty tired, and on the way home, some drunkard vomited on the bus step... By just about 5 seconds more he could have touched earth and spilled his crap there ! He made the damn bus smell like a rubbish dump... and the driver was so pissed... a black face... lol.  Maybe I'll try to get myself to study some english, since its my CA paper on Wednesday, along with my physics retest. For now, its my beauty sleep again ! Ja ! 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another usual Sunday, with the oh so dreadful session of tuition with the sub that kicked my ass all the time, Maths. The teacher gave me a 3 hour dosage of it, making me all down and out with no energy to practically do anything.  Slacked around for a while when KL called me. Met him at Atrium, although didnt play any ID today. Took the train where he alighted off Yio Chu Kang and me, Sembawang. Headed to Sun Plaza to play some cheap Wangan (same price as CS) and when I was at my last round, Shiro came running to the cabinet and shocked me ! Along with Melissa who went to my ear and shouted she wanna challenge the Evo VIII guy sitting next to me.  So they started, and wow, she slapped on the start and dragged him by around.. say.. 700 metres ? Poor guy. Lol. Left at 7.30pm, met my dad to go the funeral of my godfather at his block's pavilion.  Saw my godfather in the coffin, he didnt look like he was... uh.. RIP ? But somewhat its kind of sad to see him go... he treated me kinda well and all... and now hes gone, just like that. Sigh..  Stayed till 9.45 pm when my mum egged us to go home, wonder whats the hurry but oh well... headed for home lor. So I'm awake till now, surviving the fatigue in my eyes to type out this entry. *glad*  Oh did I mention I woke up with a bad sinus in my nose ? Sneezing and whoozing the whole day until late afternoon when it got enough and stopped the manifestation of mucus. And my eyes, somewhat listless, couldnt get me to open it for long, had to close once in a while... the eyelids felt especially heavy today.. Ahh... I need to sleep in !!!! ~.~"  Ok.. so heres the last post before our nation's 39th birthday... Happy birthday Singapore !! *Woooo* Cheers ! May the upcoming year be smooth and steady ! *lol*  Good night everyone ! =) 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blogging late again today, due to the fact that I had to rush out of the house at 10am just to meet the seller for the 6100. Took a cab hurriedly to Parkway Parade, located the Nokia Care Centre, and then waited for him to come. Man.... hes.. kinda  sissy... ah gua you know ? Somehow got a little bit of cold jitters down my spine... seeing the way he behaves... but look at it on the bright side, if hes like that, he mostly would be delicate with his things... and with no exception to the 6100. Hahaha. Paid him the $190 when he handed the set to me.  Pushed our phones in for flashing of the latest software and checks for faults on the 6100, and we went to have our lunch at the food court and played a few lame fighting games at E-Zone. Possibly one of the worst arcades around. And the poorest one at that.  Collected out phone at 2 pm, took bus 31 to Kallang MRT where I changed trains at Outram to Chinatown. Met Steve, Yap, KL, Heron, Ivan and Kira there. The loser, supposedly to have "forgotten" today's event, didnt come down. No balls, and it shows.  Played till 5.45 pm when I left with KL and Heron, took the train to Dhoby and going up to Bishan to look for some clothes to buy. Called up my mum, she was just about to go home from Sembawang coincidentally, so I decided to meet her and have dinner there.  So she came, and we have our dinner at Yoshinoya. Man... the 6 dollar meal is so damn worthy ! 3 pieces of chicken wings, a beef/salmon/chicken bowl and a regular Coke for $6 ! Had that again. Felt full and good after that.  Shopped for my stuff after that at Hang Ten and U2, bought some stuff that amounted up to $100.40 . Woo.. havent spent so much on clothes in a long time. Headed for home on bus 53 after that, and came home all tired and out for about 12 hours.... half a day.  Took a bath, saw some TV, and here I am. Had a very fulfilling day, and happy even though I'm tired out.  But a sad event marred this day : My godfather finally lost the battle to the cancer in his liver.. gave way, and gave up breathing, at 3.09 pm in the afternoon. Felt sad... but I got the news at around 9, so it didnt affect my mood outside... Yeah, thats it...  Rest in peace my beloved godfather...You will live in my memories and heart forever.  And good night. Argh. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ahh.... Had a.. well, kinda a good day perhaps. Could be the mood of having a long holiday ahead and everything went somewhat smoothly today.. No hiccups in the midst of it...  Went to school empty handed today. With my 6230 in my pocket. Haha. Teachers dont check on special occasions, so I knew it was a safe bet to bring it along. Met Zheng Long at the bus stop (on several occasions liao) and had a little chat with him. Kinda surprised when I saw him in his basketball jersey, not the usual school uni.  School started off with a parade of the flag being brought in, and after that it was a lame session of sitting in the hall, watching some dumb marbles roll down the tracks. And some cardboards trying to float with weights on them... Such a waste of time. Back to class, had a National Day Brainiest Day Marist quiz, and we got in second. Damn Mario, answering all the questions so fast... haha. Couldnt get a chance to answer :(  Unexpectedly, I went bowling with Joshua, Champ, Hai Kiat, Benjamin, Mark and Evan. Daryl and Wei Kwong came later. 3 sets, and I headed home to bath, for my dosage of WMMT at Century Square.... Darn, waited 1 whole hour for the seat, and guess what, after a few games a headache developed.... Had to stop after losing to the R200 club (changed to 3 ghosts driving Namco Toyota Corollas, not BCNR-33's..) three damn times in a row... Too painful to drive with full concentration..... Met Stewart there playing ID too, didnt talk much, before I had my lunch at Yoshinoya.... at 5 pm ! Did not take breakfast... so this was considered my first meal of the day ? Haha.  Headed home by bus 72, nearly missed the stop to change to 53... headache made me somewhat dizzy and sleepy then... But now its gone since 7 pm, and I'm fine now.  Am kinda looking forward to tomorrow, where it will be another massive PN meeting at CTP Mac. Gonna discuss how that egoistic retard is gonna be dealt, and to see whether he will apologise or not. Man... what could be worse than friendly fire... And then trying to act nice to see if u're ok or not... Hypocrite. Get a life u moronic loser. Things dont always go as you plan all the time. And lastly, the world doesnt revolve around you, so scrap that idea of yours.  Thats about it for today, feeling kinda ok, but somewhat lonely... Since I didnt have any company to go to Tampines with... so, maybe the feeling kicked in ? I dont know... seeing so many couples during the time in Tampines... and me being a lonely soul...  Bleah... Cant help but feel this way... Life just doesnt treat me good enough.  Umm... Gotta go catch some sleep soon, meeting the seller for the 6100 tomorrow, gonna flash my firmware of the 6230 with him.... haha.. Nokia power ! *woot*  Benedict signing out ! =) 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just thought I'll blog a bit now... Since its so boring at home... Haha.  Well, I'm really lacking sleep now.... signs of me having no energy to work tells me its time I slept in for a while, and get back my vitality. Was a zombie in school... walking and dragging my foot as if they didnt leave the ground. Chem test today was a open book one, and my Physics test got dragged to next Wednesday (yet again).  After school, I headed to the library to do a bit of duty. Decided to play truant on the Science Week event in the hall at 2.40 pm, since its just sitting there and talking.... its darn useless like that.. waste of time.  Didnt even have the mood to take a bus or walk home, took a cab straight home. Sheesh, havent done this for a long time..  Asked Aaron whether if he wanna go out after work, havent reply yet, so now I'm left with 2 options : take a much needed nap, or go out, and shift the much needed 6 speed shifter on the Wangan cabinet.  Maybe blogging again later, I guess thats it for now, so yeah, cya ! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wah. Had a bad bad sleepy day. Think I lacked sleep due to the re-tests and all... Had a bad spinning headache, as well as a slight fever in school. Guess the heat subsided already as of now..  School was pretty fine, just that I skipped PE lesson, due to the headache of mine. Just sat in a corner. Felt kinda hot in the head... and sleepy, of course.  After school I took bus 100 to Serangoon MRT station.. was planning to take the MRT to Kovan, and change to 113. But somehow the "feeling" of walking home from there caught me.. as a result, I saw myself walking home under the scorching sun, but I still felt good, headache already took a turn for the better... Wonder why I'm walking home these days... There's just this urge... and well, enjoyment.  Walked past PLMGSS when Joshua and Benjamin spotted me. Crossed the road to talk for a while, they teased me for having a motive (uh.. see girls they claim ?) to walk home by there.... (-.-") Dont know what they will say tomorrow.... Sigh.. >.  Headed home, got a call from mum to see my godfather.. so i bathed and took a cab down to Toa Payoh where I caught a train to Novena to meet my mum. Went to Tan Tock Seng hosptial, saw my godfather in a poor state... all skinny, and unable to talk.... Sigh.  Went to meet Aaron at Novena, went to AMK Funland to play some ID. Met a guy whose name I shall not mention, ew. First time he ever lowered his ego and talked to me with a smile. At that moment, I just felt we had switched identities... Lol..  And Shiro was there too. Played a bit, headed to Macdonalds at 7 pm. Darn fast food... its getting really tiring and heaty eating this stuff.... my fever is gonna come back soon... eeks.  Came back home on a cab, with Aaron. Studied till now, blogging, and heading to bed ASAP for my beauty sleep. Damn... I dont want to flunk my Physics and Chemistry test tomorrow... lol...  Nightz ! 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      First off, I expect this entry to be a lenghty one, due to what had happened at night. Earlier this day I was thinking in class, it wouldnt be too long to blog today. Just a jiffy. But, I dont expect this to happen now...  School was per normal, and I got back my Maths test.... 6/20. Disappointing. Didnt expect this kind of results.... at least a 11. Ah well... Just had to accept it. Later at 12.10, we had our Chinese test, and I could handle most of the questions (even though I did answer every one), but just had this feeling that some answers were wrong, not confident enough to get it right.. But well.. I did my best.  Sherman still didnt pay up, he used my money to go see the doctor yesterday (-.-") . And a rare sight of him too, bringing a hp to school... was supposed to be a Panasonic X300, but it became a Siemens ST60. Lol, hes blur.... haha. On the way home, he was like receiving sms-es from his gf, all were so sweet and full of concern for him... man... I wonder whats the chemistry that makes us good friends... 1 having the nourishment of love, and 1 lacking it big time... haha.. dont know la... confusing...  So we spent around an hour and a half in my house, playing and listening to songs. After that we headed to Serangoon Stadium, for our dreaded 2.4km NAPFA test... the sun was scorching hot, pierced my skin like needles.... pain sia... Then after that I somehow decided to walk home, not take the bus like I normally do, but called Willy along too, to Upper Serangoon Shopping Centre to check out the games shop. But it was closed from yesterday till Wednesday... So yeah, we left with nothing to see... Gonna check it out soon...  Back home, I just bathed and started to get settled down and do my stuff when Aaron rang me up. Called me to have a meal with them at Kovan Heartland Mall, so I thought, why not, since its so near. Again, walked down to Kovan.. I wonder whats with me today... Walking all the time... haha... Maybe I felt good when I walked home last Friday night... But that time was so cool and windy, not like today, humid, and hot. Coupled with the disgusting smell of vehicles' exhausts. (>.  When I got back home, my mum told me, my godfather aint gonna make it through anymore.. Blood pressure going down, discharged blood, and whole body going weak and a unclear state... When I heard this, I was deeply saddened, and I wanted to go see him for the one last time.. But I could not as I have school tomorrow... I feel so.. useless... not being able to see him for one more time, if not the last. My mum's off to the hospital now, only me left in the house, blogging it out...  Life and death are part and parcel of life... But why does it strike so suddenly... His condition deteriorated so quickly within 2 days... Making my mum in a dilemma, as shes got a night part time job too.. so now she has to decide whether to go or not... And me, all shagged out today... with the run and all.. Wanted to go see but couldnt.. Got physics test tomorrow.... Sigh. Life....  I just wonder.. looking back at all the Tuesdays' archives... Things always crop up on Tuesdays, and the most events pass by me on this day. Maybe its destiny ? Fate ? I dunno... feels so strange... yet it has a tingling of coincidence.... 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah well, I missed out of one day of blogging yesterday, since, yeah, as per usual, its a stay home day for me... with the tuition in place. Had been studying and mugging hard for 5 tests due today... well actually it was only 2, but it snowballed when I bought some time on Thursday last week and skipped 3... so yeah... Final schedule is that, today had my Social Studies test and Maths test after school, Chinese test pushed till tomorrow, and Chemistry scrapped (other tests percantage higher), and Physics date of retest yet to be confirmed.... What a handful of info.. haha..  So, yesterday was kinda occupied, even wanna go to CTP to settle a incident that happened also no time... just stayed home and thats it.   Well, off to today...  Okay day, perhaps. Everything went smooth, and the coolness of the morning shower lasted until around 11 am.. loved the little water droplets hitting the leaf... makes such a nice scene, and a crisp sharp sound.. *piak* hehe...  Sherman didnt come today, everyone gets sick once in a while.... so hes not excluded. But the MIA IT rep sure made a statement : without him, its gonna be messed up trying to set up the Mac and the projector. Haha. Gonna pressure him to give me back my $50... dammit, he says end of July, now its August ! Pay up ! *lol*  So I went home after my maths retest, kinda found it quite ok to handle. Only didnt know how to handle 2 sub-questions.. the rest were ok.  Tomorrow's my NAPFA 2.4 km run, yeah, and that kinda concludes today...  Now I'm off to bed to get some much needed sleep, yesterday had insomnia and extra use of my eyes... studying the stacks and stacks of notes... *yawn* Nearly fell asleep while having my hair cut today.... (>.  Ja ! 
      
</post>


</Blog>