<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       CBA  (Can't Be Arsed): A top secret organisation that deals with extreme boredom and laziness   Patheticism  (Pa-the-ti-siz-em): The act of being pathetic   Groovon  (Groo-von): A change of attitude, e.g. "she's had a major groovon"   Undradesk  (Un-dra-desk): To hide from a teacher (to undradesk from a teacher) (Verb: Undradesking)   Soph  (Sof): (Starboard out, port home) A person of a very low class, opposite to posh.   Gravytree  (Gray-vee-tree): A word said to point out you have no idea what a person wants you to guess   SRE  (Super-Rapid-Echo): A repetition of a sound so fast that it gives the effect of a computer generated voice   Bijovial  (Bi-jove-ee-al): Something that is confusing and shocking   Uppervolta  (U-pa-vol-ta): A country that has never been heard of before  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some of the words in "The Lovegrove Dictionary" may already exist, these words have just been assigned alternate meanings. If you are a serious dictionary reader (as if!), you may want to check the real meaning at www.dictionary.com
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Lemonology  (Le-mon-o-lo-gee): The anatomical, aerodynamic and scientific study of lemons (Lemonologist)   Plumatics  (Plu-ma-tics): The geometric and mathematic study of plums (Plummatician)    Bucket  (Bu-ket): A word used in replacement of an offensive swear word (Plural: Buckets)   Germoin  (Jer-moin): A German Germ (Plural: Germoins). These germs were discovered by Andrew James Wiseman in 2004   Diddums  (Di-dums): A word used to convey not caring through sarcasm to someone in distress   Bannister  (Ba-nis-ter): A word of no relative meaning, the word is a product of an outburst of extreme ecstasy, or a product of randomocity (Plural: Bannisters)   Doughboy  (Dowe-boy): A verbal of physical punch bag. Often subjected to poking, prodding or verbal abuse (Plural: Doughboys)   Bough  (Bof): A person who’s IQ and sense of superiority is allegedly higher than fellow classmates, friends or colleagues   Cretin  (Cre-tin): A person referred to as annoying but is pleasant on separate occasions   Mank : A person, action or object that is assumed to be unhygienic or disusting (Manky, Mankage)   Stokie  (Stow-kee): A person deriving from the British industrial town of Stoke-on Trent. This can also be referred to as an abbreviation of Stoke-on Trent (Plural: Stokies)   Reminisce  (Re-min-iss): A word used by R&B artists in the 90s, copied by teenagers and used randomly in sentences. The word’s real meaning is unknown.   Plek : A quick, effortless expression that points out unnatural weirdness (Pleky, Plekage)   Goon : A word used to point out extreme stupidity in another person’s actions (Goony, Goonage)   Croat-crout  (Crow-at-crowt): A Croatian herb, also meant as a light offence to point out stupidity (Plural: Croat-crouts)   Dif : An abbreviation of the word different. Often used in a sentence where a person does not feel like spelling the whole word or cannot actually spell the whole word   Rararret  (Rar-ar-et): A word used to test the versatility of the tongue and to find out whether a person can pronounce the letter ‘r’ Imaginetics (I-maj-in-et-ics): The dynamics of sharing imaginative thoughts in a group conversation   Randomatics  (Ran-dom-at-ics): The dynamics of random subject occurrence in a group conversation   Imaginate  (I-maj-in-at): The stating of a word, phrase or subject that required a lot of imaginative thought   Randomate  (Ran-dom-at): The stating of a word, phrase or subject that required no deep thinking   Imaginocity  (I-maj-in-o-si-tee): The human subconscious force which powers thoughtful imagination and helps in stating imaginate words, phrases or subjects   Randomocity  (Ran-dom-o-si-tee): The human subconscious force that powers the stating of random, unrelated words, phrases or subjects   Lemin  (Le-min): A blonde person that wins by luck (Plural: Lemins)   Woot : A sound said to have been made by a dragon creature from Greek mythology, sad to sound like a mixture between an Owl and a child shouting ‘woo!’   Siggie-figgie : An abbreviation of significant figures often used in mathematics. Invented by Mrs Walker (Plural: Siggie-figgies)   Gyp : A word used to express short sharp of slow mild pain in a part of the body   Jip : To leave someone out of a group act or to get left in a location to defend one’s self (Jipped)   Obstreperous  (ob-strep-er-uss): Means disruptive, loud or unhelpful. A word used to confuse the uneducated   Befuzzle  (be-fuzz-el): To totally and utterly confuse someone (Befuzzled)   Sexcellent  (Sec-sell-ent): The fusion of the words ‘it’s’ and ‘excellent’. Often misinterpreted   Kat : A word that expresses total and utter blondeness and utter lack of intelligence   SWYT  (Swit): Say What You Think, used to describe a very outspoken person who cannot control the out bursting of his/her thoughts through speech. Out bursting of thoughts is often related to intense exhilaration, ecstasy or hate.    DWYT  (Dwit): Do What You Think, used to describe a person who cannot control his/her actions. Out bursting of actions is often related to intense exhilaration, ecstasy of hate.   HWYT  (Hwit): Hint What You Think, used to describe a person who shows what he is thinking through intensive body language or eye contact. The transference of body language signals is not classed as an outburst.   Mindburst  (Mind-berst): The bursting of thoughts through any means; speech, actions, hinting. Can be divided into 3 categories; SWYT, DWYT and HWYT (see above). The categorisation of mindbursts into SWYT, DWYT & HWYT was concieved by the late Andrew James Wiseman 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>