<Blog>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will be healthier and my immune system stronger after being sick than before. I will get enough sleep. I will drink enough water. I will excersize by using weights and aerobics 3x per week. I will cook and eat interesting food that is good for my body. I will weigh 125 by the end of the year, and be a comfortable size 8. I will be able to drive and not drink Pepsi.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have decided to change this blog to the rantings of an irate housewife in response to my mentally deranged husband who has for the umpteenth time accused me of going on websites, specifically online dating services, which accusation is of course ridiculously false.   However, in response to his ongoing accusations, I have decided that if I am going to be accused of something , then I might as well be doing it. I have decided to join as many online dating services as possible.  Note to Ivan if you are reading this:  if you think I'm kidding, then ask my mom what I did when she was accusing me of smoking pot!  oh yeah, that's right,she's dead!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yesterday I worked on organizing my house.  went through the drawers to make sure everyone had their own clothes.  looking for stuff to go to charity.  this year's goal of getting rid of anything not bought or used in this century.  old granny underwear.  costco clothes.  nursing bras.  maternity clothes.   figure everyone only needs 7 of anything.  one for each day.  anymore is a waste. got a cold.  best thing about getting sick is feeling great when you get over it.  worked out even when sick.  feel suprisingly good.  lifting 3 times per week for muscle and bone atrophy, and doing aerobics on off days for endurance.  weighing 143 or so, which is really heavy for me.  gave birth at this weight usually.  like to get down to 125 to get rid of the spare tire I have around my middle I never had before.  moved dining room table outside since it's summer, and hung the tarps.  financial goal of saving 10,000 sits at 5,000.  can i make it by the end of the year? socks in sock drawer,underwear in underwear drawer, winter clothes put away since it's july. like to get rid of old bedroom set and the furniture that doesnt work in the kids room anyway.   empty storage-file all paperwork.   declare bancruptcy and file taxes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Husband brings home bill from toll road for me.  Not my licence plate.  They won't talk to him, so I have to call.  Not only is there 3 violations I don't know about under my name, there are 24-recent ones.  The licence plate issue?  That's the responder number-my responder.  But wait-the picture is a dark color Ford and a man is driving!  Who is this masked man?  It's my husband's business partner!  When I start screaming jail time, my loving husband tells me to calm down and not cause a problem.  (I love how I come first in his life) Later he postulates, "Maybe the transponder is in his glove compartment and he doesn't know it's registering?"  "Don't worry, he will pay the bill".  Gee, my husband must now be psychic.  Calls me later-yep, transponder in his buddy's glove compartment.  What a coincidence!  How did it get there?  He's had it over a year in there when he retrieved it when the car got repossessed(by me), but he forgot he still had it. So the million dollar question is:  who called up and ordered a replacement transponder in June recently?  Wait-there's more.  When I try to contest the violations, they say they don't care, it's under my name, and by the way, what about the $2,500.00 bill for the violations for the Black Mercedes 430 SL?  (My husband's car). 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>