<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All alone, or in two's, The ones who really love you Walk up and down outside the wall. Some hand in hand And some gathered together in bands. The bleeding hearts and artists  Make their stand.  And when they've given you their all Some stagger and fall, after all it's not easy Banging your heart against some mad bugger's wall.  -pink floyd
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its so simple and complicated the way you can crush me No matter how much this hurts This is through I get as far as your door before I get caught I make up excuses just to touch you and I can't stop, I can't stop So are we playing for keeps These days begin and they don't end for weeks Leave me left out of anything to do with you Excuse me while I fall apart don't flatter yourself sweetheart Let me take the wheel and I'll crash this car Do you have to make this So hard Your so good At pretending everything is alright Your as welcome as cancer but my door is always unlocked
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ..And I, I don't want to speak these words cause I, I don't want to make things any worse Why does tonight have to end Why don't we hit restart and pause it at our favorite parts we'll skip the goodbyes If I had it my way I'll turn the car around and run away just you and I....  *Best thing so far about today...talking to devin and savannah....  emogirllovesu: U shuld get a job therre nOiSyLtLfKr: for a month emogirllovesu: Like a bannana leaf for child labor emogirllovesu: Cuz they pay in banana leafs out there right? nOiSyLtLfKr: lol emogirllovesu: And there's monkeys running around emogirllovesu: That's how I picture it emogirllovesu: Ur all in a hut nOiSyLtLfKr: lol nOiSyLtLfKr: and im online how? emogirllovesu: And with no pizza emogirllovesu: Uuuhhh emogirllovesu: Thru coconuts ..................................................  Sgt Hussein: warning the following comment is gay Sgt Hussein: joey has a nice ass for a girl Sgt Hussein: not in a gay way but in a i wish i had one of those way Sgt Hussein: comprende? nOiSyLtLfKr: haha nOiSyLtLfKr: ya Sgt Hussein: seans is bigger nOiSyLtLfKr: i havent had a good look Sgt Hussein: just grab it he wont mid Sgt Hussein: mind Sgt Hussein: anthony has a hairy ass nOiSyLtLfKr: haha nOiSyLtLfKr: did u just sit there n stare Sgt Hussein: he told me and i was like u cant beat me Sgt Hussein: ask vanessa nOiSyLtLfKr: lol nOiSyLtLfKr: urs is hairy too? Sgt Hussein: i gotta fuckin carpet ................................................................................. *senior year... soo woop... i found my senior quote its cute im not gonna post it tho... so its a fact that its not a good idea to peel the skin off of a cut..its only makes it worse... peanut butter and jelly sandwiches arent the same anymore... i dont like smelly dogs... i want a black cat with green eyes... and now that i think about it i wanna go home...i dl bunch of matchbook romance songs...janelle! august 24th isnt for a while...i dont wanna wash my hair...  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so ive come to a conclusion... friends arent people your suppose to compare yourself to and try n compete with... your friends are suppose to be the total opposite of that. like u can have a friend who hates your music... or the way you dress or doesnt beleive in the same things as u... but as long as you respect each others ways... your still friends... im not saying you cant have things in common... i mean hello... theres obviously something that brings you together... like theyre still always the friends who r into the same shit as u... but thats not whats always important... and the relationships between people change throughout the years... like one year ur inseperable and the next you see each other about once a week. but that doesnt mean that you dont care about those people.... and if they are your real friends... they should be there for you no matter what... whether your crisis is a broken nail or a broken heart!.... you should be able to trust that person.... that doesnt mean they have to know every fact about u... and you dont necessarily have to be on good terms 24/7... like some of your best friends can be the people u hate at times! and sometimes people need space... and sometimes friends do things towards their friends that they do regret... and if your going to say sorry for something you did.... you should actually be sorry!... and now i have to piss.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *INFO*  ~They call me: frances ~Also: bob ~Sex: Female ~My First Breath of Air: 10-30-87 ~Status: single?  ~Nationality: Chilean  *REWIND* ~Most memorable memory: ...being little and beleiving that peter pan was going to come for me ~Worst Memory: finding out i was going to die someday... ~First Words uttered: papa/mama... one of those ~First Friend Ever: rosa grandez- she lives in alhambra *FAST FORWARD* ~College: dont know yet ~Occupation: marine biologist ~Future Resident of: cali ~Wedding: on an island in the sun ~Children: one or two ~Looking Forward to: tomorow ~NOT Looking forward to: tomorow  *PLAY* ~Feeling: stuffy nose ~Listening: free fall without a parachute- senses fail ~Talking to: my aunt whos asking me where she should put my clothes ~Thinking of: how much i want a book to read ~Craving: water ~Missing: everyone ~Hating: my cold  *FAVORITES* ~Song: burried myself alive- the used(for today) ~Radio Station: kroq kiis k-earth ~Hang out Spot: um... ~Actor: adam brody, ashton kutcher,  ~Actress:kirsten dunst, brittney murphy  ~Food: veggie egg-rolls,   ~Character:   ~Book: the perks of being a wallflower  *LOVE* ~Love is: a feeling ~Love or Lust: either or ~Best Love Song: most mariah carrey songs... or ... everything i do i do it for u-new found glory(cover) ~Is it possible to be in love with more than 1 person @ the same time: i guess ~When love hurts you: i fall asleep ~True or False-All you need is love: sometimes ~Is there such a thing as love @ 1st sight: um.. in order to be in love with someone u have to understand them, and want them regardless of there flaws  *OPPOSITES ATTRACT* ~Turn ons...Physical: eyes, teeth,  Mental: smart n funny ~Turn offs...Physical: if you smell eww lol Mental: if you're super dumb and cant carry on a conversation ~Do your parent's opinion on your bf/gf matter to you?: not really ~What kinda hair style: um.... like adam brodys... or spikes ~The sweetest thing a member of the opposite sex can do for you: understand me and not care what others think... not be afraid to act stupid or be a dork ~Where do you go to meet new people: you just meet them along the way ~Are you the type of person to holla and ask for #'s?: um.. no  *PICKY PICKY* ~Dog or Cat: i want a black cat with green eyes... or a cute lil fuzzy dog ~Short or long hair: short or medium length ~Innie or outie: innie ~Moon or Sun: one right after the other ~Basketball or Football: football ~Righty or Lefty: right ~Hugs or Kisses: both ~1 Best friend or 10 aquaintances: id rather have 1 best friend ~TV or Radio: radio ~Starbucks or Jamba Juice: starbucks ~McDonalds or Burger King: carls jr. ~Summer or Winter: winter when its not raining ~Written letters or e-mail: for recieving- written letters... but for sending-     e-mails ~Disney or Nickelodeon: disney ~Car or Motorcycle: motorcycle.. except for when its raining or extremely cold ~House party or Club: house party with not too many people ~Sing or Dance: neither ~Freak or Slow: slooow ~Yahoo messenger or AIM: aim ~Google or Ask Jeeves: google  *MISCELLANOUS* ~Can you swim: ya ~Whats your most embarrassing moment: in 7th grade when erika told david rodriquez that i liked him ~Whats under your bed: shoes books ~What are you scared of: rats ~What is your greatest accomplisment: ...making it into the 12th grade ~What kinda roof is over your head: the kind that they put on top of houses ~Do you like tomatoes: sometimes ~Internet connection:um.. i know we have a cable modem ~How many TV's in the house: 2 in my aunts house ~How many phones: 2 ~How many residents: 5 including me ~How many DVDs do you have: dont know ~Last doctor visit: a while ago ~Last phone call: anthony
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just throw it back, for one more night On a starlit and moon-struck night. The ground did fold and eat us both But all my love, I did devote.  .....  I´m bored 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>