<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The main point of this article is whether or not computers should be incorporated into the curriculum at such a young age.&nbsp; This article is very controversial in the sense that I am battling with this very issue in my own home.&nbsp; My children are ages 3 and 6.&nbsp; My husband is a software engineer, and we have a computer in most every room of our home.&nbsp; My son is able to surf the net, only when supervised, to find Nickleodeon.com, or Barney.com for my 3-year old.&nbsp; I am always asking myself if he will be athletic or if he will be creative in school because he is often only interested in playing computer games.&nbsp; With this in mind, my husband and I began to limit his computer time significantly.&nbsp; After doing so, my son learned--almost immediately--to tie his shoes, to get himself dressed, and also how to build skyscrapers from Legos.&nbsp; He also began playing outside more with the neighbors, and has since acquired a new best friend.&nbsp; My son is on a soccer team where he was the team MVP during the Spring 2004 season.&nbsp; I am confident that this all stems from the fact that I turned off the computer, and introduced him to a world of so much more.&nbsp;   It is however, very important for students to have computer skills.&nbsp; I think that the important thing is for parents to monitor computer time as they would anything else.&nbsp; Many parents look at computers as babysitters.&nbsp; If a child is computer literate and younger than 14, they can spend countless hours on the computer.&nbsp; Parents can do chores and take naps, and the child never bothers anyone.&nbsp; Students should have the privilege of technological exposure, however, just as you must watch a child in a swimming pool, you must use the same judgment with children using computers.&nbsp;    
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This article is of special interest to me, as I am&nbsp;a Vocational Education Teacher.&nbsp; It often amazes me when I observe the rapid growth of technology, and how important it is for teachers to stay abreast of the constant changes.   The main point of this article addresses the need for a growing number of career academies, not just in Washington, DC, but all over the country.&nbsp; Philip O. Berry is an academy high school in the Charlotte-Mecklenburg school system that opened in August 2002.&nbsp;&nbsp;The vocational programs in high schools and academies are transforming to meet the needs of a technological society.&nbsp; "This country has shifted from an industrial nation to a technological one," says John Wittman, administrator of Chantilly Academy.&nbsp;   As cited in the article, it is very clear how important it is for high schools to share in the responsibility of preparing students for what the Department of Commerce predicts as an enormous growth in the information technology industry.&nbsp; The forecasted growth for for the information technology industry is expected to increase in the United States by 78.7% from 1998 - 2008.&nbsp; This growth is higher than the average expected growth of all occupations.   Again, as a technology educator, I agree with the need for more training and education at the high school level.&nbsp; I teach at a high school where most students come from low socio-economic backgrounds.&nbsp; Most students are not interested in college simply because they would have no way of paying for it.&nbsp; With a career in technology, many students who are more than capable would have a chance at a better life.&nbsp; Students could use certifications to land jobs that would assist family members, support themselves and their children, as well as seek opportunities for advanced educational opportunities.&nbsp; Technology based education would not only keep the society up to date, but would also enable those underprivileged students to be able to have opportunities that they might not otherwise be able to experience.&nbsp; This is a good way to start closing the achievement gap.   
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This article is of special interest to me, as I am&nbsp;a Vocational Education Teacher.&nbsp; It often amazes me when I observe the rapid growth of technology, and how important it is for teachers to stay abreast of the constant changes.   The main point of this article addresses the need for a growing number of career academies, not just in Washington, DC, but all over the country.&nbsp; Philip O. Berry is an academy high school in the Charlotte-Mecklenburg school system that opened in August 2002.&nbsp;&nbsp;The vocational programs in high schools and academies are transforming to meet the needs of a technological society.&nbsp; "This country has shifted from an industrial nation to a technological one," says John Wittman, administrator of Chantilly Academy.&nbsp;   As cited in the article, it is very clear how important it is for high schools to share in the responsibility of preparing students for what the Department of Commerce predicts as an enormous growth in the information technology industry.&nbsp; The forecasted growth for for the information technology industry is expected to increase in the United States by 78.7% from 1998 - 2008.&nbsp; This growth is higher than the average expected growth of all occupations.   Again, as a technology educator, I agree with the need for more training and education at the high school level.&nbsp; I teach at a high school where most students come from low socio-economic backgrounds.&nbsp; Most students are not interested in college simply because they would have no way of paying for it.&nbsp; With a career in technology, many students who are more than capable would have a chance at a better life.&nbsp; Students could use certifications to land jobs that would assist family members, support themselves and their children, as well as seek opportunities for advanced educational opportunities.&nbsp; Technology based education would not only keep the society up to date, but would also enable those underprivileged students to be able to have opportunities that they might not otherwise be able to experience.&nbsp; This is a good way to start closing the achievement gap.   
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    This is me and my husband and best friend, Tony.  He is a most supportive husband and father, and I am grateful to have him as my soulmate.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This article really ties into my technology autobiography.  I had to laugh to myself when I read it, as it brings to mind so many conversations that I have had with my parents.  I have two children, one is 3 and the other 5, and they both know how to turn on a computer and find  urlLink Barney.com .  My father has to use both of his hands when operating a mouse, while my 3 year old can control the mouse with one hand and drink juice from a cup in another.  The point that I am trying to make is that children respond to what is around them.  Computers are everywhere, and students are able to do so many things with them. They are able to focus for hours on end on endless possibilities that technology offers them.  One point that I would like to make concerning the article is that this article focuses on upper middle class teens.  I currently work with low socio-economic teens in high school.  So many of my students have not had the exposure that the students at Prospect Sierra Middle School have had. I taught Computer Applications this past school year, and all assignments that I gave students had to been completed in class because so many students did not have computers at home.  This is also a reason that many students use the internet inappropriately.  Students have not had guidance when exploring the internet and when they encounter sites that are inappropriate, curiosity gets the best of them and they often get into situations that they can not handle.  I am convinced that technology is becoming more popular among all people, especially students.  I often remember the card catalogue that I used to find books and articles in a media center. Currently, there is so much more information that can be found from the confines of your own home.  It is necessary for our teens to be well rounded individuals, and technology will enable them to possess knowledge beyond expectations.  Adults must continue to monitor our children, and talk to them so they will understand how important appropriate computer usage is to safety.
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Computers have always been a major part of my life.  When I was in high school in the late 1980's, computers were pretty new.  Although technology was not as advanced as it is currently, I took computer applications in high school, and I was a part of a pilot class where I learned computer programming.  Little did I know then, computers would play a major role in where I would go in my education as well as my career.  I entered college in 1988, and computers were emerging in businesses, schools, colleges, and universities.  There were several computer labs on campus, however, I utilized a word processor to type papers.  Soon typewriters and word processors became a thing of the past.  Anything and everything that you wanted to do was possible by the use of computers.    I escaped the technology surge of the century by graduating from college  before  computers became a requirement for admissions.  When I visit my college campus or friends that live in dormitories, I am amazed to find high speed internet access and desktops in every room.  This is indication that the needs of technology education are a must for everyone if they are to be productive and competitive members of a growing society.  After spending 10 years in corporate America, I decided to switch gears and become a classroom teacher.  I feel that my decision to change careers brought a different focus than that of teachers who had no experience in the business industry.  I understand the importance of technology and I wanted to not only instill an understanding and appreciation in my students, but I wanted to dispel the myths that technology was a threat.  I was able to fully understand why so many of my students were "afraid" of computers.  Many of my colleagues don't know anything about computers and they are intimidated by e-mail and any other means of electronic communication.  If an educator is not willing to continue his or her education in technology, how can we collectively encourage our students to embrace technology?  As a high school Fashion Merchandising and Business Law teacher, I am constantly designing lessons that allow students to explore using the internet.  I often find myself giving a lesson in computer applications or internet usage, however, I will do what it takes to make sure students are competent in technology.  If we expect to produce students who will excel in any area, we  must  do what is possible to make sure they are prepared.  Technology education will be a firm foundation for our students' success.  
      
</post>


</Blog>