<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The atomic bomb and the terror attacks seemed to be the right option to each party at the time. But that does not mean either or is the right descion. Each one can be justified differently. The atomic bombs being dropped on Hiroshima and Nagasaki was an extreme measure to end a desvatating war that was brought on to the United States by the Japanese. The terrorist flying planes into the twin towers was an attempt to destroy the United States&nbsp; economy or at least hurt it. In other words, terrorist attacked the United Stated for having a different religion and different culture than theirs. The attacks on the twin towers was not necessary, but for some reason the terrorist felt compelled to kill thousands of people to prove a point. But then again isn't that what happened in Japan when we dropped the bombs, to prove a point.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The&nbsp;&nbsp; environment in the U.S. during WWI and today's war against terror are similar in a few ways. The idea of being patriotis and the country pulling together as a whole to protect liberty and the American way of life is the same. The ACLU is still in affect! People need that reassurance that they will be able to have that freedom to picket against the government to show that they do not agree with that system. Even today people are shunned by other Americans when they do not agree with the descions the President and his council makes. People&nbsp;then and now&nbsp;are prejudice, and paranoid, towards the people of the ethnic background in which we are in war with. The citizens of this country who were from Germany and today that are Arabic pay a price for their heritage in war time. I am not saying that all Americans are racist against them but it is enough to make someone's life terrible! People also come to the conclusion that if people are not behind the war 100% they are not as American as they should be. I do have to say that most people today are a little more open to different&nbsp; ideas than they were 7o years ago!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Americans have this idea that the things they believe in are the ones that are right! Therefore, the ideas will be pressed to whomever Americans feel need to be brought to light, you can say! The idea of moving west for new opportunties and new way of life. The  American white man did not seem to care to much about hurting any person on there way out westward. It did not bother them that there were so many people already living and settled there. Americans wanted to storm in and change the way of living for these people. Take the Chinese for instance, they developed Chinatowns, Americans wanted these people to live like other Americans and leave behind their traditions. Since the chinese did not want to leave behind there traditions and values they were shunned by Americans, and the Chinese ended up at the bottom of the economic food chain! In todays world you can put Iraq on the list as a project for the Americans. Not that I do not agree that the Iraqi people did not need some rescuing from Saddam, but we, as in Americans, felt compelled to put our nose in their business and help "rescue" Iraq. Apparently, there are some people in that country that feel they did not need any help. There has been so many Iraqi people injured and died due to fighting. Americans need to sit back and ask themselves if we are really needed to put our nose in others business!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In today's society, labor unions do not seem to have the same meaning as it did when Americans were fighting for fair working environments. Today it is to be sure you have health insurance and availability to a credit union. Granite, labor unions are to regulate fair working ethics and to insure equal chances for people to have the opportunities to advice and have a fair options within the company. Sometimes the union does seem to fail to do its soul purpose when factory workers have to go on strike in order to get the raise in pay they should have gotten three years ago. I think labor unions should step in and help regulate more then they do today. Too many workers are being taken advantage of with lower pay then they deserve. Labor unions should step in and make sure workers are getting paid the ample amount workers should get paid. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The idea of welfare was a great thing! My personal opinion is that people take advantage of it. People are out there not trying to find jobs or trying at all to make ends meet! The people that actually need and would not abuse it can not getit in time of emergency. There was a time when I was younger that my father was out of a job...The company closed, so it was not like he quit and tried to free money from the government, which is not actually a lot. He was denied because my mom was working and made a whopping 7,ooo a year with four kids....How can a family live off of that? Finally, we got food stamps for a month...I mean the system would be a great one if it worked for the people that would use it when actually needed! None of that actually answered the question asked, but it is a touchy subject that I feel like the system is messed up! To try to answer the quesiton is that I think people tend to view people on warefare as inferior to them and others that can not afford things. I know that I was embarassed when my Dad was out of a job for a month or so and we did get food stamps, I felt like people looked down upon us. It all goes back to the issue of different classes in society. But then again I was around 15 and at that age when everything embarrased me. So it is not relivent to use that as how I do feel today about food stamps. Welfare can be a good thing to help people in situations like companied closing. It can help get people back on their feet again! But then again, when I think of food stamps and welfare I think of the lazy people of the world that do not make any effort to do anythign besides mooch off of tax payers like ourselves! So, I am support of welfare as long as people do not abuse it, but in all reality people always tend to abuse the good things and ruin it for everyone!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>