<Blog>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Way to go La Russa by keeping your team in check!&nbsp;  urlLink http://sports.espn.go.com/mlb/columns/story?columnist=rogers_phil&amp;id=1843755   It's amazing to me that players like Zambrano put themselves before their team and would single out someone like Edmonds which costed them the game and forced them on the road to 10 games out of 1st.&nbsp; Dusty you&nbsp;better muster up some team morale, pal!&nbsp; Have a nice day!  

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Salutations!&nbsp; It's been awhile since I've written, but I must make this blog brief.&nbsp;  urlLink http://www.drudgereport.com/kerryv.htm &nbsp;is all have to say today!&nbsp; The next time Michael Moore wants to rip on Bush for his vacation getaways, he should remember that the donkey party&nbsp;is guilty too!&nbsp; Especially when they miss 80% of the Senate votes!&nbsp; Talk amongst yourselves...    

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I agree with the fact that baseball is exciting when your team is winning... however, I feel this sort of emotion shouldn't make one feel like a fair weather fan.  As of today, the    urlLink Cardinals  are 20 games above the .500 mark.  They are definitely the most exciting team in baseball.  They have more wins than the Yankees (1 more win to be exact), who actually had $80 million more in  urlLink payroll  than the Cardinals for the 2003 season.  As a Cardinal fan, who cheered through both heartbreaking Game 7's in the World Series (85 and 87), I feel that I have earned the right to revel in the moment.  In the true sense of the word(s), I know that this city is not made up of many bandwagon jumpers.  This is a city that respects it's home players as well as the visiting team.  We have given standing ovations to players like Lou Brock (105th single season stolen base), Ken Griffey (500th career HR), Bob Gibson (20th game winner), Tony Gwynn (3000th career hits), and Mark McGwire (I won't even go there) when they've reached milestones in Busch.  In closing, St. Louis is engaged in a city-wide celebration of America's past time, so everbody should be involved, even the fair weather fans!  Play ball! 

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Blog... a funny word to describe someone's innermost opinions, thoughts, and everthing in between.  This is the world as we know it... a collection of influenced personal thoughts that I found worthy to blog.  I hope you enjoy and please feel free to send feedback.  Thanks!  -John 

						
</post>


</Blog>