<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's amazing how much shit you can accumulate in such a short period of time. With my move back so close, I've been going through everything I own in order to scale my vast collection of irrelevant crap down to a reasonably-sized, easy-to-move-around collection of irrelevant crap. I've kept letters, pieces of paper, a marble, a photo of some unidentified person's shoe, someone else's ID, collars of past dearly loved pets and train tickets, all for the sake of memories that mostly&nbsp;I cannot even remember.&nbsp;Going through all of this stuff made me realise how sentimental I am. But the time came, I had to move on, take what I needed, and bin the rest.  On a lighter note, Poe learnt how to say "fuck you hunny", in the gayest accent that a bird can muster, and that's kept me amused for the last few hours. Leaving him here will be difficult, but unlike my puppies, he can come up and live with me in another 9 weeks.  Peace, love and bad-mouthed homosexual birds,  Bethie xoxox   
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The young child next door has an imaginary friend. I often hear him outside speaking with it. The other day I realised that he was referring to it as "Mum", and I thought... 'stupid Beth, he just has a soft-spoken mother, and you cannot hear her respond'. However, recently I learned that his mother died a few years ago. It makes me sad to listen to him now, chatting away to thin air as if someone is lovingly looking on as he plays with pegs and toy cars. Peace, love and absent parents, Beth xoxox 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Your nothingness is my everything, your heart is my never-ceasing passion. Everything is broken. Feeding this corrupted, fitted puzzle. what you search for in confusion only makes more sense. Your black world, my white face, surrounded by this dissimilarity, they all become the same. Sharing opinions you all wish to find likeness. Where is your precious uniqueness now? All looking for pity, your insecurity, your suicide, your deadly attention. You say you refuse to conform, to disregard the drones. By doing so you join the outcasts, this labelled group who are so-called unique - unique is none the same, yet you feel as though you're joining something - you feel a part of something. This destroys your feeble attempts. Feeding off this darkness, you'll find that nothing satisfies. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that my cigarettes prefer to be smoked at night, when no one else is around. Well, at least that's how I enjoy them. With the faint shaft of light that seeps outside the backdoor from inside the house makes the cancerous smoke dance, and I stupidly imagine that it is my friend, flirting with my imagination like it's about to write me an intimate letter, expressing it's gratitude for my addictive loyalty in the air before me... but it never does. My deadly companion, I sacrifice myself for you daily, and you do not respond. You only make me smell bad. I crave you, and you float away with the wind, infecting others, with not so much as a thank you for my attention. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      -It is no surprise that a generation of children of divorce have grown into a world of extended adolescence, in which so many of them have slept with one another and remained friends, have put the conflicts of sundered relationships aside for the sake of maintaining a coherent life. Divorce has taught us how to sleep with friends, sleep with enemies and then act like it's all perfectly normal in the morning. - I have so much respect for myself but have very little respect for most of the people I sleep with, particularly my subs. Is it that I think I am closer to perfection and less susceptible to temptation than the 'typical chauvinistic males'? I have stronger grudges against women than men, but the biggest grudge I have is against myself. I am an actor, a dramatised projection of a few minor traits in my personality, and I use this facade to appear genuine. It works, but I never call them again. Should the guy be saying that? - Bethany is a dirty hussy.  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've always wondered about certain jobs. Especially those guys who drive the cars in front of trucks with a large yellow sign stating "Oversize vehicle ahead", with the flashing lights. It's like "Hey, what do you do for a living?" ... "Oh, I drive one of those cars with flashing lights that say "oversize vehicle ahead" "... I wonder how you'd apply for such a job... License: check, IQ under 90: check.  Everytime I see one, I cannot stop laughing. It's the same with people who lock the cemetary gates at night. "What do you do for a living?" ... "Oh, I lock the cemetary gates at night" ... "Oh, so you unlock them in the morning?" ... "No, I am not trained in that respect, but sometimes I get extra shifts and lock the public toilets at night... you know, clear out the random gays declaring the site as their new beat, or occasionally a corpse resulting from a drug overdose". It brought me to a thought... before I actually embarked on my shitty job as a Deli girl, I had never considered those people who served me at the supermarkets, just took them for granted. I suppose quite a few people feel the same way, as I am not treated as a person in my job, only by the occasional thoughtful senior citizen. Today was my last day (or should I say... technically, yesterday was my last day), and as it was a Sunday, my nine hour shift was particularly slow, and I found myself purposefully (and quite obviously) fucking up orders so that my time would be filled with something that to me appeared constructive. Through this job I have become so morbid. Moreso than usual. As I have never liked meat, it was expected that I would be bitter about such employment, but my mind has been playing nastier tricks on me. Occasionally if someone asks for "silverside", I swear they are saying "suicide". Not long ago I found a bacon rasher that looked like Frankenstein's monster. When opening a new packet of cocktail frankfurts, they are shaped like a noose. Every so often, the weight will come up as 66.6g, or the price as $6.66 (only with particularly evil customers), and it keeps me amused, otherwise I am calmly bitter/cynical/sarcastic toward customers, and find no joy at all in working in an edible mortuary. This all sounds stupid, trust me, I realise. But when stuck in the redneck shithole, little else amuses me. I move back to the city tomorrow, and aim toward finding a new job asap, involving serving alcohol to cockheads and sleazes. Again, I will instantly find issues with that, as well. I should get some intense training as a barista, then I would only have to hear customer complaints second-hand, and not have to bite my tongue to stop myself from articulately telling them to fuck off. Like chicken drumsticks, or cuts of gammon, I find myself comparable to the pristine frozen supermarket meat. But unlike the plastic coated innards, hearts which can be preserved forever, I am just a mass of stinking flesh As life rots me from the inside. Don't worry, I love myself (in a non narcissistic way, I just scribbled down some thoughts on a scrap of Deli paper one afternoon...) Peace, love and baby octopus, Beth xoxox.  
    
</post>


</Blog>