<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I love women who are willing to go out of their way to make the world a better place. This kind of girl is definitely a hero in my book. My book is small, because there aren't enough heroes, if you recall. If you want to see what a real hero is like, take this opportunity to view a rare gem of a site:     urlLink www.datetosave.com     Enjoy.      Then Comment.  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        For those of you who have not previously taken my advice on sites to visit, this one I am not mistaken on. I have visited many areas on albinoblacksheep.com and have enjoyed them all, the most recent of which is the following game. It is a challenge, but there are very few counties in Oregon where one can, without litigation, compete for distance in the newly popularized sport of Penguin Throwing. It's mostly eastern - too much rain on the left coast.    urlLink http://albinoblacksheep.com/flash/pingu2.php     And furthermore, I would like to thank all the nerdy folks for making games like these possible. Without nerds, I would play a lot of Parcheesi.   
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        So here's what's up. I'm not trying to slam Clinton, but frankly, he only cared about the prime minister of his pants. I walk around this area, and all I see is a bunch of people whining about what's in it for them, and somehow saying that all the consequences of everything bad is somehow because Bush lied about weapons of mass destruction, and I hate it when people would rather whine than do anything constructive. That's why I enlisted. No sense trying to convince anybody that peace can only be reached when order is established. I have always thought of peace as a goal, and sometimes war is the path to that objective. Sometimes a person like Saddam has to be removed from the equation to get the solution. Sometimes the Taliban or Al Qaeda need to be crushed to be at peace. But nobody here agrees, so I enlisted so that I could speak out loud without having things thrown at me by the very people who want to accept everyone.    How can somebody be "liberal" and "accepting" and "tolerant" and get so angry and offended about a worldview other than their own? Sounds more liberating to accept that there is a right and wrong, that relativity is an excuse and not a reason, and do the right thing. I don't care if everybody does the right thing, but I believe "the right thing" exists, and that "liberates" me to do it.    I thought I should publish this as a post, rather than a comment, so that it will be easy for everyone to find. That way everyone gets a chance to react and comment, and I like when I get comments.  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Regarding WNathan's comment on heroes: 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink www.explodingdog.com   I firmly believe that this is some of the cleverest animation ever. If you disagree, it is because you are not really trained in ninjitsu. Fans of this site actually submit the titles, and he draws pictures to represent those titles. Years of titles. Years of beauty.  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       What the world is lacking in most is people who are willing to sacrifice themselve, their wants and desires and dreams, to serve others. There aren't enough people willing to be like a good dog. There aren't enough people willing to die for something larger than themselves. People are too concerned with their rights, their benefits, their annual bonus or vacation time or privacy. Privacy? The more you need privacy, the more your privacy needs to be invaded! If you aren't doing something wrong, privacy isn't necessary! Shame is what inspires this. And if you are more concerned with others than yourself, you won't be ashamed. Not that I feel like everybody needs to be watched all the time, but it is good to be aware of each other. Back to being aware of others, rather than just aware of what we want for ourselves.   "For even the Son of Man did not come to be served, but to serve, and to give His life as a ransom for many."    There is a hero, a man Who can be looked up to as watching out for others. Big brother didn't have to watch Him, and he didn't bug everybody about His rights, even when He was being executed. He made sure that His mom and His friends had the things that they needed to survive, to thrive, to establish a worldwide church, and He gave Himself completely to saving the world instead of Himself.  Maybe I will get the opportunity to do that! 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I saw a GNARLY bumper sticker today. It is rare to see somebody who knows what they are talking about in Eugene. Most people just talk without research. Pity that this bumper sticker was only about a 2" square.  &nbsp;     10 Out of 10 Terrorists Agree:       "ANYBODY BUT BUSH!"         I would have to agree, shamelessly, that regardless of anything you want to say about G-Dub, he is willing to do what it takes to fight evildoers. If he got misinformed, he acted on it, not because he is corrupt, but because he believes it will make the world a better place. I think that Clinton made for a good representative of America because his values reflected those of our country. So when people looked at Clinton, they saw what Americans are like - we cheat on our wives and lie about it! On the other hand, I believe Bush is a good president because he does not represent American values. He is above that. Bush has the type of values that demand he does what is true and noble and righteous, which is what I would love America to represent! But we don't, which is tragic. But rather than an accurate representative, we have a righteous man who can lead us to becoming a more moral nation, as well as making the world a little more safe for our children by discouraging terrorism in the most ominous ways he can. I'm so glad we are able to do this! I am so glad we are able to take a stand for what is right, to deter the children of the Middle East from becoming terrorists, to stop many of those who have already chosen that life, so glad that I enlisted to be a part of it. It's a physical manifestation of my vote.  &nbsp;
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think that says it. No need to explain the  AWESOMENESS  of The Aftermath. It speaks for itself.&nbsp; You've been told. 
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          YAY!  The Aftermath ROCKS!  YAY!   And by " rocks ," I mean, probably isn't playing right now. As I said before, we are waiting for the opportune moment to strike. Apparently, we think that's later. Like, some day when I'm not deploying to Iraq. Or maybe they'll play without me. We'll never know until    The Aftermath is upon us.   
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I just want to plug this   TOTALLY SWEET   website about ninjas  flipping out  and killing  everybody . It gives me something to aspire to. If ninjitsu is an interest that interests you, this site is interesting. The hate mail is  way  sweet. Also, one  must  study the ancient tradition of seppuku, whether one is interested or not. It is the way of the ninja.   realultimatepower.net     However, if one were to run an image search on Google, they  may  not wish to look for images of hemorrhoids. It's pretty sweet  if  you spell it right. Everybody at work loves me now. I  strongly  recommend saving all the images of hemorrhoids to a new folder and set your screen saver as a slide show with that folder as the source.   Party Hard!     I suppose the same would be true of a large assortment of health impairments, but  this  rocks    the catbox!  As for the rest, they are all so workplace friendly.   
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I would like to thank Nathan for all the wonderful new dolls he has blessed me with! These dolls will go to wonderful use as Ben flicks them at my puters. That needs clarifying. Clarifying which I choose not to give. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Holy Crap of Evil Minions!  I  love  the Army! They gonna   PAY   me to run around  with a rifle!  You  gotta  try this!  Best job  EVER!   Better than selling office supplies or tacos, anyway! You gotta do this as well!  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well, my time has come. This August I am scheduled to go to my 2 weeks of annual training with the Oregon Army National Guard, but I got a call last Wednesday asking if I wanted to go to Iraq, and I was like, "TOTAL AWESOMENESS!" Because their women know how to behave.   On a  way gnarlier  note, as I was doing paperwork and getting punctured in my elbows and draining Jake into a cup and all those  glorious  soldier duties, we got notified of a  new  mission especially for  my  unit, as in NOT on a volunteer basis, to go and give the rest of my men in Baghdad the backup they requested a quick  5 months ago . So I may be going almost  immediately , and that would be  RAD!       Anyways,  for the one and a half of you who love me, I'd appreciate your support while I'm under fire. I don't know if I will have access to  this  site, but if I'm not blogging for a while, my personal warrior ninja email address is:    urlLink jesse.myers@us.army.mil    and I'd  love  to hear the sweet, sweet sound of your  beautiful  voice as it radiates in written form on whatever monitor we are issued.    YAY!  I'm super grateful!  YAY!       In Loving Service,                               Uncle Jesse  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        If you are sick of stupid commercials, I strongly recommend the following sites, where you can find GNARLY commercials from overseas! There is heap upon heap of   AWESOMENESS!   Such as a Ford tricking a cat or protecting itself against a bird. These need to be seen a few times by anyone who loves animals (or cats), whether you like Fords (or reliable vehicles).    Tyler is super cool because  HE  has a Ford and some kittens who like to eat my legs.   basementv.com/commercials/btv-com-008.html  urlLink http://basementv.com/vault.html     You need to enjoy this, or else Tyler's kittens will haunt your shins for all time and I will laugh a sinister laugh.  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't care  what  you say! We are still  gnarly!  And so are exclamation points !  And I still think you're cute!   YAY! 
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wanna see a wizard? You gotta see the   wwwyzzerdd!   He's the  best Wizard ever!  His magick would beat Harry Potter in his  stupid British mouth!  He'd be like, "Hey, Harry, I hear you got the magic goin' on," and that Potter wuss would be like, "You betcha," and the wwwyzzerdd would be like,    "SHAZZAM!"    Harry Potter's movies would all have to be prequels. He'd be crunchy Harry  toast!  The Potter would become the clay, and  dead , too! If you don't believe me, see for your unbelieving self!   If you dare!    http://www.yzzerdd.com/
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So here's the deal:  There are different ways of showing love, and different ways of receiving love. My way is getting comments on my blog. Only  then  will I feel loved and appreciated.  Please love me!   Nothing yet...  Still waiting...  Nobody loving me yet...    Darn my poop!  
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "So where does one get the inspiration to write such  amazing  music," you might ask. Well, let me tell you. It's from being olde skool,  hardcore , and from the streets. We live the thug life. It's the  only  life for us. And the music we play also reflects the music we listen to. If you want to see some of this music, I recommend the following site:  http://www.zophar.net/music.html  It's full of music that takes me back to my tormented roots, and expresses the true  agony  of life in  my  crib. Just close your eyes and dwell on the  sheer emotion  in the overtures. It's  powerful , yo!   If you can't open it, the programs for listening to it are at the link marked, "Proceed to NSF Players." This isn't players like us, it's just programs.  L8R.  Uncle Jesse
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yay!  The Aftermath is  good!   Yay! 
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is tough to rock when you can't afford food, and I am on my way to a massive layoff. So Uncle Jesse is looking for work, and that is rough, because it means I have to be all nice and humble and stuff. But I figured I'd check listings on the internet first, and to all you jobless losers out there, there is a magnificent site full of awe and wonder. Not as much as this site, but pretty full, I guess. Anyway, it's worth investigating. If you alter your name, it will alter your ideal career. However, they are all good suggestions. Mine have all been deadly accurate.  Jesse is a permanent temp(which I am, hence the layoff). Jesse Myers is a puppeteer. Jesse O Myers is a...who are you kidding, you work? Jesse Orion is a Second-Hand Car Salesman! Jesse Orion Myers, your ideal job is in a land far, far away! And...  Uncle Jesse is a Fluffy Bunny Trainer.  I recommend this valuable job resource to all you unemployed punks. Being misguided is a perfect excuse for doing something stupid. Do what I do: Blame the internet!  www.jobpredictor.com  PS: Give Tyler a shot. It's glorious! Tyler Hartley is an Air Sterwardess!  For those who care, Penis is Prime Minister, and the ideal job for testicles is a dentist.  
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Aftermath is so full of  awesomeness  which knows  NO LIMIT!  The  awesomeness  of The Aftermath is far beyond any known form of measurement!  Infinity  is not an awesome enough word to describe the complete and utter  awesomeness  of The Aftermath! Do not question the  Awesomnity  of this  rocking  Spitcore band, or the magnitude of their  hardcority!  If you question this, you are wrong, and must be punished  mercilessly!  And your mother should be  BEATEN  for not raising you properly!  SELLOUTS!  We haven't  SOLD  a single ticket!   PS: Nathan Rocks! If you don't believe me, you fail at life, and you should go to nathanrocks.blogspot.com! Be conformed to the loving of NATHAN!
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it appears that The Aftermath is currently waiting for a more opportune moment to strike. Due to being cool, we are, at this moment, not going to play for you. But just you wait! The Aftermath is still going to strike, and now you don't know when! Yay!
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My profile is better than yours, because it is supercharged with all the fiber your body needs! It is filled with wondrous filling stuff, and things such as these! See all the fillings? They are so full! Abundantly, if I do say so, and I do say so! Yay!
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Beware! The Aftermath is coming to Eugene, and more aftermath will ensue! Run away, shrieking like a mutilated kitten! Nothing will save you from the Aftermath! Jumping will not save you! Ducking will not save you! Blocking will not save you! Impending Doom approaches! All your base are belong to us! We are The Aftermath! And we love exclamation points! Here's another! And Another! When will it end? It won't!
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Two rules when making vows:    There is a story about a man, a war, a vow, and a virgin daughter. Perhaps you have heard it. It's in the Bible, and it is  not a parable , but a  historical  account of a    tragic    decision. But at no point is this decision to keep a vow referred to as a poor decision.       more to come soon...      1. Don't make stupid vows.     more to come soon...     2. No matter what your vows are, keep them.     more to come soon...  
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So as the report goes, my wife is trying to find out what my website is because she wants to find out what I have to say about her, because she thinks this is about  her , and not about me. Christina called me to warn me about it, and I didn't recognize the number on my  call waiting, so I answered it, and it was our maid of honor, acting like  she  wanted to see my blogspot. So when somebody who I haven't talked to for  over three years  tries to tell me she wants to read about my opinions on everyday things, I generally call her bluff, because I have   no pat  ience   for people who take no interest in me except to parent me. My   parents   don't do that. My   friends   don't do that. So I let her know,  rather abruptly , that this site is for people who   care   about me,   not   people who are digging for excuses to hate me, and she said that Christi doesn't hate me, but she's trying to marry somebody else because she isn't married and we got a divorce (  Christi   got a divorce -   Christi got everything   she wanted and anything she didn't want me to have, and she hawked most of it because it reminded her of me, and she only left me the things that would remind me of my failures, like the wedding photos) and I need to move on, too.  This is not friendly advice, this is an evil woman trying to mislead me .   I know.   
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Little Melissa comes home from first grade and tells her father that they learned about the history of Valentine's Day.  "Since Valentine's Day is for a Christian saint and we're Jewish," she asks, "will God get mad at me for giving someone a valentine?"   Melissa's father thinks a bit, then says "No, I don't think God would get mad. Who do you want to give a valentine to?"  "Osama Bin Laden," she says.  "Why Osama Bin Laden?" her father asks, in shock.  "Well," she says, "I thought that if a little American Jewish girl could have enough love to give Osama a valentine, he might start to think that maybe we're not all bad, and maybe start loving people a little."  "And if other kids saw what I did and sent valentines to Osama, he'd love everyone a lot. And then he'd start going all over the place to tell everyone how much he loved them and how he didn't hate anyone anymore."  Her father's heart swells with pride and he looks at his daughter with new found pride. "Melissa, that's the most wonderful thing I've ever heard!"  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Here is something for you read in your leisure time:  There once was a man named George Thomas, pastor in a small New England town. One Easter Sunday morning he came to the Church carrying a rusty, bent, old birdcage, and set it by the pulpit. Eyebrows were raise dand, as if in response, Pastor Thomas began to speak..."I was walking through town yesterday when I saw a young boy coming toward me swinging this bird cage. On the bottom of the cage were three little wild birds, shivering with cold and fright I stopped the lad and asked, "What you got there, son?" 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So anyway, during basic I wrote some of the best songs I have written to date. As in  most  aspects of the military, I had purpose and direction and hope. I had a  reason  to write, because I had a reason to be   awake  . If   The Aftermath   ever plays again, I know that   these   songs will be recorded. Of course, they are  much less entertaining  without the music, but enjoy them if you can. Writing them really just came naturally, and released   a lot   of what   needed   to be released.
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        remember that year when we both went to war 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        lost my life to my addiction 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So anyway, today David decided that the man his wife was given to would just have to   deal with it.   As in, when Saul first decided to kill David, he took his daughter back and gave her to another man, but now that David is king, he's like,  " Nah.  I don't think it's cool that you married my wife, so she's gonna be mine again."  Hand her over to my servants and go home and cry about it. And he did, because that's what good people do. They give the king's wife back. Is there a parallel here? I hope not, because David's first wife had another husband for a    long    time while he was off at war. But it answers my other question a little better. My buddy and his wife were asking me about moving on and remarriage and heaps of other crap that I    objectively  despise  , but    subjectively  desire .   The last of which being that if my ex were to be remarried and redivorced, would I still be willing to work things out? This is still a hard one, because now we have David who is married to a widow AND a woman who has been married to another man  (both after   and   before being married to David) ,   and he will later kill a woman's husband over an adulterous affair and a bastard in the belly. Then there is Hosea, who married a woman who became a whore, and he went and rounded her up to demonstrate forgiveness. I've always wanted to do that. I think that would make him a hero. Unclean, but a hero and a fine example of how to rise above the standard. I would follow the examples of either of these - with a few exceptions surrounding the adultery and murder - but there is also the question of the Law. Granted, it is Levitical and is directed toward a specific level of holiness, but why not aspire to holiness? "Be Holy, as I am Holy," right? And so here is the only verse that I have ever found that I thought resleased me from my covenant: If your wife marries another man and is divorced again, do not take her back. Is that land not much polluted?    (if you think about it, there's only so many times you can plow a field that someone else has planted weeds in. Those things are tough to get rid of.)   Why choose to take on someone else's chores? Why take over a project another man has chosen to forfeit?    Because I am Jesse, and I don't have to be selfish. I don't have to act like I am too good to keep my commitments, to accept that somebody has made mistakes. I mean, I make mistakes pretty consistently, but I would hope for forgiveness if I asked for it, which I do.  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        As of now, we have our orders. Tonight I go to drill to see all my buddies leave for Colorado. The 7th through the 21st, I will be going to the Armory all day, just like drills, and be off at night. So, basically a regular job, but in the army, for 2 weeks. On the 23rd, I leave for Texas for about 3 weeks, and then I land in Baghdad and get to work doing what I've been training for. So if you pray, pray for me. If you don't, fake it. I'd appreciate it. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I forgot to mention a small detail that could undo everything I said about David and all the smote raiders. That detail being that the person who tried to kill him on a daily basis was pretty much under his protection. He would not allow anybody to kill King Saul on the basis that he was the king, even though he wanted to slaughter David. However, that was a personal dispute, and the raiders were not a threat to him, but his wives. So does this create a contradiction, or a set of rules to live by? Let's apply this to the New Testament. Jesus would let His enemies kill Him, but would defend those He loved. Not necessarily with violence, but with diplomacy and brilliant teachings, inspired by the Holy Spirit. Fine. Let them kill me, but not my family. That is a Hero. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So glad you could make it. Enjoy my blog, eh. I hope you all enjoy my dumb little comments on life. I enjoy writing them. If you don't like it, read it anyway, and then comment on it. I like that. Really. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So. Yeah. Good news about the slaughterbot. I was signing a form saying that I am STILL volunteering, and that they can call me at any time they want and I will go to do the war thing. And as I filled it out, I was asking for details about what was going on. Amusingly enough, he doesn't know that much more than I've already been told. As I was standing there, he got a call from higher. Whoever was on the other end indicated a desire to ship by the 10th. Of this month. As in next week. Or Possibly the 19th. My next move is to go to drill Friday. At drill I will find out if I am supposed to go to Colorado or not, based on whether we will be leaving in the next couple weeks. If there is a chance that we will leave before the 21st, I will be staying behind from AT so that I can go to Texas instead of Colorado. So if I get to go and back up my guys, that would be great. Then I asked if there would be a chance I could meet up with Sergent Jaques, who is a super-hardcore airborne combat infantry vet and used to take out entire truckloads of the opposing forces at drills. He ran into me at the mall and gave me his cell number last Christmas because he wanted me to join him. I guess I won't. His truck got blowed up. The driver was killed, and the Sergent's coming home all beat up. They say he'll be okay, he just won't be on the battlefield for a while. So instead of going overseas, I could be on my way home on a stretcher right now. I don't know which I look forward to more.
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So I finished up I Samuel on the bus today, and I was amused by the input I got from it. Specifically, that David's wives were stolen by raiders. And did he get over it and move on like a  good  soldier would? That's what we'd  hope  for, right? Let people do what they are going to do because they have   free will   and there's nothing you can do about it, right? Nope. He took an army and put an end to their free will with a battle that lasted from dusk the first day into the  next  night. The way it's worded, they said   nobody lived    (except for 200 who fled on camels. How many people would have to die to make the 200 survivors look like nobody?)  Anyway, my hero got both his wives back and in  my  opinion, was  pretty nice  about it. All  he  did is kill them. That's  far more humane  than any of   my   recent thoughts.
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I just got a call from my roommate, encouraging me to seek the Lord, not necessarily concerning my wife, but concerning His Presence, to dwell in the presence of God, and let Him work things out in His own way, which is usually beyond our comprehension. I find a lot of people with no faith, or little faith in God. A lot of people believe in God, but think He basically observes the things we do and sometimes gets disappointed and occasionally smiles and blesses us. But those people wouldn't dare to venture out and say God could do anything that they couldn't do. I believe that my abilities are limited, but I have seen evidence that God's abilities are not. I believe He will bless me abundantly, and I believe that that will happen IN THIS LIFE! A great many people assume that because we must struggle sometimes, that means we will not have those things which God has offered to bless us with until we reach the Kingdom of Heaven. Seldom is this true, unless that is all we strive to acheive! We must seek Him, and He will find us when we do. Whether my relationship with God has anything to do with my relationship with Christi has been a subject of long, tiresome debate, which I have been on both sides of many times, but one's relationship with God is understandably reflected in their dealings with people. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       After months of neglecting the things I need to do, it's about time I do them. Not because I want to impress anybody with my holiness or anything, but because my soul needs it. I need to be accountable, and I have avoided it for one reason or another since I got back. When I first graduated Basic Training and AIT, I was doing great, and I knew I could deploy at any time. My unit had left for Texas shorthanded and I figured they'd send me as backup, so I spent most of my time with friends and family. After a few months had passed, I was gradually slipping back into my old addictive patterns, slowly enough that it didn't alarm me, but quickly enough that I didn't turn back.  Once I knew that I needed help, I was too ashamed to seek it. I didn't want to be accountable for my actions when my actions were inappropriate. My friends want me around, and I would rather be alone in my shame. That time has passed. Now is the time for war. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I received a letter from an old friend, who reminded me of the fact that I'm divorced. The way it was put, I feel kinda yucky. I think I've been burdening you guys with problems that are primarily in my creepy brain. I needed to write a bunch of stuff, because I couldn't exactly discuss it with customers, so, I dumped all my garbage on you. I posted my friend's letter as a comment under the "Creepy Robot Mongoose Stalker Dog!" posting. It cut pretty deep, and was something I needed to hear. I seriously need to worry more about myself and less about the choices of others. 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey, Folks!  Lots  of nifty things are happening. Most of them are concerning my ex-wife. She's kinda engaged or something, so I got a new burst of enthusiasm for doing   good   things. What better place to be a   hero   than in my family? What if I can rescue my wife? From what?  Anything but me!  The way I see it, the Bible is true. She says the same thing. So if the  Bible  is true, does that make the  words in it  true? I think it  do . I have heard arguments from perfectly decent people that the New Testament is  more  valid and applicable than the Old Testament, which I think is  so absurdly ignorant  that I wear (and will someday tattoo) a star of David. I mean, these people claim that Jesus' teachings overrule the Laws that God dictated in the Pentateuch, which has its merit as an  idea , except that Jesus taught that not one letter of the Law or the Prophets was to be left out. Jesus taught straight out of those writings, and people who claim to be Christians think those writings are  outdated . Currently, I am reading about David and his rise to power over Judah in I Samuel. There's a lot of stuff about killing Philistines, and people tend to think that doesn't apply to us and we need to avoid conflict or something, because apparently anybody who reads and understands the Bible is obligated to let Terrorists attack whoever they want,  free of consequence . If   that   is Scriptural,  I am a robot disguised as a mongoose dog.  But this is what my ex-wife believes. She also thinks that divorce and remarriage are to be taken as seriously as the braiding of one's hair. Right.  Beyond help , you say? Even so, I am not giving up yet!   Real heroes don't abandon their families.  
</post>


</Blog>