<Blog>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i woke up, ate, watched tv, cleaned, and talked to jo and kyle on-line. kyle read something he wasent supposed to about, and now im in the middle of it, and i wouldnt have it any other way. jo, im sry, i didnt want this to happen, i kno i just got done apoligizing to u in the IM but i cant say sry enough. i dont think u understand how bad i feel. now i think it would have been better if u didnt tell me, but then, would we still trust eathother as much as we do? or do u still trust me?i hope to god that u still do.but im sry to everyone else that this is so short, and ima go now. i love you jordan, pleez forgive me, and pleez dont stop trusting me. i'll talk to everyone else l8er! seyaz!  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hola! i tried to write last night but my computer froze and i wasent gonna re-boot the damn thing then have to re-write everything all over again, so i just went to sleep. but technaclaly(sp) it was this morning, but who cares! yup, and now its 2:14 in da morning and i should really go to sleep. people say that i dont sleep enough, but i really do, its just that wheni sleep it happens 2 be in da middle of da day. yea...and if anyone cares, bug jordan 4 her blog link. she has a blog now and claims that no one knows about it. so yea. anywayz, yea i was supposed to chill wit rida and lauryn and kyle and them, but my mom was bein and Biznitch and wouldnt let me go. damn her! o-well, yea, ima go now, seyaz  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         yea, im sry everyone! lonzo, sry for the comment on u and megan....hope i didnt bring up any bad memories...sry jenny for what i said in that one blog that u commented on...sry rida, for everything. and sry everyone else that i havent written in my blog for like a year! i am turning into ryan...shame on me! lol, yea, but im&nbsp;not as bad as him, he hasent written since the 13th, i havent written since the 18th! so im still kinda good. well, lately me and rida broke up, ryan came over and i tried to burn a CD of his but it didnt work, and im supposed to be going to daneilles house tonight...rida and lauryn, keep ur comments about her 2 yourself. i dont need to hear u 2 trashin her. ANYwayz! um, i just got 2 new cats last night! they are so awsome, they are reading this with me at this very second, they on my lap...one is sammy and one is cubby, i dont kno which one is which though, and if kt reads this before she gets home then im screwed! lol. yea, WE MISS U CHI2! lol, and i hope u havin fun with that da vinche book thing. i dont think it would be something i would read but im alex, i dont really read at all. yup, and if anyone feels like beating the shit outta danny kapost feel free. he could use it. and speaking of...me and him were going up to family video to drop off shit for our parents, and we passed ryan but he didnt see us....anywayz, we were on bikes and riding in the construction on sauk trail and it was muddy as hell so us and our bikes got trashed. then we went on the sidewalk (bad idea) i saw a peice of the sidewalk was missing, but it was 2 late, i was like O SHIT! and then i hit the corner of it as i tried to avoid the damn thing, and my knee smashed into the edge and now my knee is fucked up! and then a guy came out of the house cuz he heard us screaming and cursing and shit...(danny almost ran me over with his bike) and so the guy was like "r u guys alrite? and of course we said no, so the guy called some people and they put up some light thing so that people could see the damn whole...of course they couldnt do that before I got there...lol, yea, well, ryan left his geeeetar here, so ima go do that for a while...seyaz!    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       cho everyone! its been a couple dayz, and i just didnt really have time to update my blog, therefore i didnt, but now i can, and now i am...lol, yea, well, nothing interesting has happened the last 3 dayz, cept i went to my moms g-parents and then to my moms b/f's...or was it the other way around??? o-well, i finally updated my blog...be happy everyone! and erich, slow down on all the depression shit....its not healthy.....seriously, talk to someone...well, ima out! seyaz!  
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "yea, thats exactly how i feel, blah" quote from tori....lol, well, i woke up, only a lil' bit earlier and in a different manner than i normally do. i woke up to danielle beating me with her cell phone, then sitting on me, than reaching for my lower area, so thats when i decided that i would like to keep my manhood, and i got up. i took my blanket and ran in the bathroom, locked the door, and layed there. it was very comfy. so i got out of there and ran into my room. danny called jo and jo was alseep so danny was just wakeing everyone up! yea, so then me and her went down-stairs and sat and watched tv, what fun! then she went up-stairs to sleep, i wouldnt let her, so i turened the mattress upside down and sat on it/her. im sure she got hurt, due to the fact that at its me and i jumped off the dresser. man i wish she could read this...i would get a lot of kicks outta that! so then she left and i went to the pool. it was freezing. so then i played v-ball, than buried nacho in the sand, then went swimming again, then left. no fun, the me aaron and anthony found more robo "sticks" lol, no fun there. then i went home, ate and then went outside and played v-ball with kyle nacho aaron anthony rida lauryn and kt, then the girls decided to stop playing and then kyle said we should play football...with a v-ball, lol. then kyle hit the ball into a tree and i had to go in the tree...it was painful! lol. well, then i went inside and now im here, seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yup, like everyday, i woke up, went online, and then went to the pool. yay for me! then when i got to the pool i went into da pool and then i got out cuz i saw lightning. then me and everyone went to the sand place and played v-ball for a while. then the staff said that it was gonna be staff vs. patrons(us)and of course, we lost, DAMN U SEAN! DAMN U! yea i have plenty of anger towards him. yea, well, that was my day, tons of fun....SINCE WHEN DID MEGAN AND ALONSO GO OUT!?!?!? i never knew that....lol, yea, well, thats it for now, im out, seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cho yall! hehe, i said yall, how lame am i! lol, yea, well, today i went to the pool and it was atually fun as hell! we swam, had a bellyflop contest, and a whole bunch of races, mucho fun...then we left the pool, and then me and aaron and quick went to nightswim dressed as chickas...dont ask...it was a dare, log story....at the pool for nightswim i had to sit out for grabbin ridas ass....and then we all went home again, and then i went home and ate....then i went to ridas...kyle and quick and arron and sean were there, more mucho fun. yea, and then everyone left, me rida kt and aaron walked kyle home and then like 10 min ago i asked rida out...wouldnt ya kno, she said yes! lol, yea, HAPPY B-DAY JO!!!! well, i g2g, that was my day...mucho love rida! seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yea, i was gonna go to the pool today but couldnt cuz my dad is lame, this blog is gonna be short cuz i really dont feel like tyeping....but i sat at my dads and then ate turkey then went to my moms and i found out that kt and arron got jumped by a couple pussys who think they all big and bad but it took 2 to get my sister...and then i ate pizza, then i went upstairs and my moms door was open and i saw her and gary doin it! AHHHHH! anywayz, now im talkin to jo bek and ryan  and yea, im done now, seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i woke up and found out that my sister was gonna go to rida's and then go to the pool after then, so i thought that i should go as well. so i got up, had my dad take me to my moms, then went to rida. no fun there, once i got there we left, so i was pretty disapointed that i couldnt take a 5 min. break from that walk(though it was only a 2 min. walk) anywayz, when we got to the pool, we were hot and sweaty, but there was no one there, so it took us a while to decide that we were gonna get into the pool. so once we got into the pool, kelly showed up, she dont really chill wit us no more but thats her issue not mine. then josh and krystine, jenny, sam and kyle showed up. no one really cared about jenny krystine and sam bein there cuz they had there own little world. and kyle was with taimane the whole time so we didnt really get to chill wit him. and josh, well, me rida lauryn karli and linz hung wit him. so yea, it was a pretty fun and preductive day, though it was all at the pool so preductive might not be the rite word for that, but this is my blog and i can have what i want in it! for instance....lkahglhaw;gni9vh....see, i can have anything i want in here. anywayz, i got back to my dads and now im here, its o so much fun here!(and for the ones who havent been to my dads, that was sarcasm) yea, well, i ate, and now im typeing...well, im out....seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i woke up at about 8 after goin to sleep at like 4, i had to get up early to go to some nascar thing...it was called Pole Day, it was really boring, it took like half an hour to get up there and i almost feel asleep on the way there, then when i got there i had to go walk around and look at a whole bunch of tents filled with a sheit load of nascar sheit...nothing interesting, i wanted one hat that was orange and had the cingular wireless guy on the front, but i didnt have enough money...then from like 10 till 2 me rida and kt sat in the van, listening to the radio(nothing good) while my mom was at the track having a jolly good time. well, then at like 3 it started to rain which caused the track to get all wet and needed to be dryed...which took about an hour and a half, and we were supposed to be gone from the track at about 5, when the puddle of mudd concert started(which everyone was 2 tired to stay for) so by the time it was 6 my sister got really pissed and wouldnt stop complaining about leavin so she could go to the steger dance(which was canceled) so my mom got all pissed at her and then snapped on me....rida prolly injoyed all this...but then i got picked up from my dad on the way here he gave me and kt a lecture about how we shouldnt give our mother attitude, o fun...well, now im here, and that was my dad, 3rd day in a row without missing any....better than i can say for ryan...hehe, j/k, anywayz, and turkey/lonzo...your blogs seem very sofisticated...lol, i actualy read them, just cuz of your coment...lol, and ryan, you never did tell us how you got "Ryan is da Bome" see, now you HAVE to start updateing your blogs more...pchanzb.blogspot.com...dont mind that, just had to type it...well, ima out, seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i woke up around 12 and went on-line and talked to my buddy nacho...we talked about how i hit sean in the head with a rock and made him bleed...yea, fun, anywayz, then i went to the pool and had fun there untill i got out of the pool...very very cold...anywayz, after that me and kt and adir(rida) went home and got ready to go to some nascar fan fest thingy, pretty fun, we walked around for a lil' with my mom and gary(her b/f) then ditched them and went on some bridge just to look, it was one of those ones where the bridge goes up when a boat comes...drawbridge or somethin...the bridge went up and scared the sheit out of us...adir freaked out, it was HIlarious, she was so f'in paranoid...then we went and walked around for a lil' while, it was pretty awsome and fun....then we met up with my mom and we all decided to leave, then my mom met up with a friend then me kt and adir went to the car and blasted music and messed around, fun fun, then the parking lot police came up and yelled at us, it was fun as a mo', o-well, then we went home and listened 2 country music(o yay) then we just got home and i was on the phone with jo(jordan) when i found out that rida almost got skunkified by some skunk....lol, well thats my day, some fun, ima try to get a pic up hur but dont think ima be able to, well, ttyl, seyaz!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yea, this is kinda weird, this is the first time i have ever done this, but like they say, theres a first time for everything...yea, well, today i have sat here on the computer thinking of what to do, and i just got done reading ryans, linzs, erichs, and chi's blogs, and i decided that i wanted one 2....by the way linz, nice job with the burning of the pants, and be sure to kick ryan r's ass....just for the hell of it...yea, anywayz, i got nuttin to do, wow, didnt think i could be this bored that i could sit here, typeing a whole bunch of sheit that a whole bunch of people are gonna read and be bored with......o-well, cant wait till tommorow, when i can finally leave my dads house! YAY! and ryan, if you read this, be sure that we get into another fight soon, but also make sure im not so stupid to hit some wind chime thingy, lol, you know what im talkin about...yea, well, this is actualy pretty long for my first blog, and hopefully i'll update it everyday, and hopefully i wont be like ryan and say that im gonna do it everyday then dont..lol..yea...how bout that..ight yall, im out, seyaz!
    
</post>


</Blog>