<Blog>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things like this should happen more often. JK Rowling (author of the amazing Harry Potter empire) has been given an honorary degree from  urlLink Edinburgh University . They are honoring her for her contributions to the world of children's literature...and encouraging even the most unlikely readers to see what all of the fuss is about. It's stories like this that just make me happy. To go from struggling to survive, a single mother on the  urlLink dole  in England to a multi-millionaire for doing something WORTHWHILE is just so admirable. Let's hope that in the meantime, while waiting for  urlLink book 6 , these kids are using their new found admiration for reading...rather than just pining away for the next one, because after book seven, it's all over...  And, not to be a conspirator, but I do think  urlLink Harry will die .  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so apparently  urlLink Song  airlines is now offering in flight exercise. No, not your own aerobics instructor but some lame ass rubber band type 80's exerciser. Apparently, it's supposed to appeal to all the business travelers. I guess I am on  urlLink crack , but normally when I see those business travelers, they are doing business. I don't really think they want to use a  urlLink thigh master  next to some random stranger they don't know. How bizarre is this country that in order to get one to choose an airline, the option of exercise is a plus? C'mon, they won't even let you file your nails on the plane.  Do we really need to be  urlLink "feeling the burn"  on our commuter shuttle from DC to the city? I think not. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Ken Jennings won $14,000 and his 25TH consecutive game on the Tuesday, July 6TH edition of JEOPARDY! This unprecedented string of wins brings his total to $788,960."   urlLink Ken Jennings  started out kinda  urlLink dorky  looking. After about five nights, he started to grow on me. I now look forward to seeing him win again every single night. As an avid Jeopardy watcher, it's really exciting to see someone accumulate money for something worthwhile-rather than the usual feats of  urlLink swallowing live bugs  or marrying some loser you just met 6 days ago.   Can no one beat this guy? Seems not. Tune in tonight to see if he'll win again.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Again, being bored at work has brought me some new knowledge. There are an insane amount of links on the internet regarding the ever so loved haircut of champions, the Mullet.  Here are some of my favorite Mullet Haikus. If you want to read more check  urlLink this  out.  O! SQUIRREL brother, Your tail, my hair. We are one. Yet I must eat you.  Dogs urinate where they so choose. And so do I. Red and blue lights flash.  Teen runaway, I hate my dad. Yet I am one. Fly, thunderbird, fly.  Short for dad. Long for the daughter mom always wanted. Everyone's happy.  Dad likes my mullet. The nurse calls it a critter carpet. My head breeds.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG Hell has frozen over.  urlLink Nascar may be opening in NYC . Yes, THE city. As if there is interest there.   I am so annoyed about this I cannot even formulate the words to express my disgust.  Please,  urlLink Nascar , stay out of  urlLink NYC . I may be forced to hurt you...  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently, it's "history from the horses mouth."  Um, in my book, that's what's called  urlLink creepy .  They say all you need is one good idea and you can make millions. Personally, I hope that this Californian inventor, needs to hit the drawing board again. He has developed a new type of tombstone that has a computer chip and a touch screen, so that when you visit your deceased family member, you have a consoling video message. Um, does this strike anyone else is completely bizarre? Would you really have the foresight to put this type of tombstone in your will, make a video, then expect your family to pay for it?   Here's the  urlLink article , if you'd like to read it...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Six Feet Under , one of my favorite shows, is getting maybe a bit too creative. For any of you that watch it, I need to say, WTF is up with the excrement plot line? I mean, it was funny at first when the newleywed George received a  urlLink tupperware  full of crap, but in last night's episode, let's just say it brought new meaning to the word " urlLink dump truck "...  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you think I am joking? Or that perhaps, this is a witty title for my next blog?   You could not be more wrong. UPN has created a new reality show.  urlLink Amish in the City . It stars five 18-24 year old Amish guys and gals in LA. They live with several non-Amish people. Just imagine the real world cast mixing with the Amish.&nbsp; Throw in some bikinis and electricty. I bet we are in for a wild time.   Somehow, it's offensive. Somehow, it's brilliant. Just when you think reality TV could not sink any lower, they always do.   Somehow, I can't wait to tune in...starts July 28th, at 8pm.&nbsp; Who's with me?!   &nbsp;   urlLink Check out the article...    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Due to popular request, this week's analysis of Six Feet Under has arrived. (At least I know one person is reading my blog!!)   I finally got to watch  urlLink Six Feet Under  last night. What a strange episode.  First, we learn that people believe Claire to be "empty"...who would have guessed.  Second, we learn that Brenda's mom is getting reconstructive surgery on her, um, womanly parts because "no one wants to f*** a water glass". Youch.  Third, we feel bad for Nate, once again, as he tries to grieve with a bunch of 80 year old widows. Then, once he's releasing all the dirt and hurt inside, the fire alarm goes off. Go figure. Will he ever get a break?*  *As a side note to discussions on Nate, I learned that the lovely girl (quiet toddler) who plays Maya is a twin. I am shuddering with images of the Olsen twins...  Fourth, while Ruth is buying flannel to make her new hubby pj's, she learns that the disgruntled cashier/friend broke up with her boyfriend (who is also married) &nbsp;and then lit a bag of excrement on fire on the married man's doorstep. BINGO, we've found a winner...Ruth decides to try to set her up with George's son...the excrement plot line continues.  Fifth, Rico's involvement with the stripper is starting to get a bit scary. Did he not see this coming?  And finally, and probably most importantly, we get to see David go through utter hell with a guy he picks up who's out of gas. He gets punched, robbed, kicked, forced to smoke crack, plays dog catcher, gets drowned with gas, sucks the barrel of a gun, and is left for dead while his van is stolen. Moral of the story, don't pick up people on the side of the road and/or don't talk to strangers, otherwise you will die or see death quietly awaiting you. Poor David. I really do feel bad for him.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Susie needs a nose job, plus, she's pretty flat chested. Susie's parents can't afford to pay for her aestetic improvements. Sadly, the American public can. And does. Yes, today it's possible to  urlLink BE ALL THAT YOU CAN BE . I am referring to the Army here. I am also referring to the fact that as a new lure to join, one can get plastic surgery, for free.  Not talking about reconstrucive plastic surgery here-you know, when you break your nose during basic training. I am referring to  elective  plastic surgery. Apparently, the surgeons have to have someone to practice on. This absolutely infuriates me.  urlLink The American taxpayer is paying for plastic surgeons to master their trade in the Army . Again, let me clarify. I would not be so pissed about this if we were talking about reconstructive sugery to make these young soldiers look normal again after a severe work related injury. What I am so annoyed about is that Susie Flat Chested can go into the&nbsp;Army, and come out with new boobs. &nbsp;And a new nose. And liposuction. And, even a face lift.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Even though she's a fellow  urlLink Theta , I can't help but writing about this one.   Who would have known that while  urlLink Jenna Bush  was being primped to go on Daddy's re-election tour that the topic of sticking-one's-tongue-out-at-the-press-is-not-a-good-idea should have been in the handbook. Wow. What a great country we live in. The best part is, she was laughing while doing this.   " urlLink Look at me ! I am going to fuck up my daddy's chance at getting re-elected even worse! Hehe, look how big my mouth is boys! Anyone got a margarita!? I swear I am legal now.... "  &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had to tell you all about literally, the best dinner ever. I'm a big fan of Dallas restaurants so it's a big deal to tell you I have a new favorite.  Went to  urlLink The Green Room  on Saturday night and had " urlLink Feed Me-Wine Me "...it's 4 courses and 4 glasses of wine, paired to compliment your course. You just tell the waiter what you are allergic to and don't care for, and the rest is history! Needless to say, I was quite a bit nervous about all this. And, of course, my first course was  urlLink raw oysters  with some sort of vinegar pico de gallo/mignonette ...I almost died but decided, what the hell, I will try it. Loved it! :) Everything that followed was better than I could imagine. I even found that I enjoyed my red wine and I tried port! Yum!  Anyways, if ever in Dallas, it's a must. Plus, hitting the upstairs porch and watching the sunset is the perfect end to an awesome four-course-four-star dinner!  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gotta say, that I normally just love flying. However, when one is behind a 17 year old father with his 2 year old toddler, it's not a fun ride. This child would not shut up. Screaming at the top of his lungs "but I don't WANNA!" the entire time the father was trying to get him buckled into his car seat. When I say screaming, I don't think you can imagine the utter torture I am really referring to. It was so loud I started laughing uncontrollably.  Best part was, the father did not even appear to try to calm his child down. Was he not noticing the dirty looks from fellow passengers? Or was he just simply too busy grooming and shaping his baseball cap?  Point is, don't travel with your children if&nbsp;you can't even seem interested in trying to keep 'em quiet! Not to mention this was a 9:15 PM flight?! Don't kids go to bed early anymore? UGH.  Vent over.   
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do goldfish in bowls have a distorted view on reality? Do they go crazy? It is cruel to keep goldfish in bowls, and does anyone really care?  In Italy, they sure do. In a small town in Italy, goldfish will soon be banned from living in goldfish bowls...they need to be placed in aquariums with filtration systems.  When I first read this story, I was thinking, how crazy. What is the big deal about keeping goldfish in bowls? How is it really any different than aquariums? They still have ugly humans bumping their faces against the glass, pointing and watching. I mean, it just seems like a silly law.  However, the more I  urlLink read of the article  and the more I thought about it, it does make sense. It's apparently a move to make people more in touch with the needs and responisibilities of having an animal and taking care of it properly. While I do think there are more important animal rights issues at bay, I just thought I would share my thoughts on this wacky law. Maybe it's not so wacky.  As a side note, just for giggles, does anyone remember the episode of  urlLink Full House  when Michelle gets a goldfish and gives it a bubble bath? And it dies? And Michelle gets depressed because she killed her fish by trying to be responsible and keep it clean? Anyone remember this one? Anyone?  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Couldn't help but blog on this one. Check out the  urlLink world's smallest cat , Mr. Peebles. How cute is this thing? I want one.  As a side note, today my Kitty let me pet her while she was eating. She seemed to be enjoying it. Then, all of a sudden, she growled and hissed at me. It was not the usual hissing, this time it sounded as though she had bronchitis and was hissing. It scared me. I should have known better, that damn cat hates me. Grr. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why, yes, after all these years, a Simpson's charachter is  urlLink coming out of the closet .   My bet is on Smither's... ...but it could also be one&nbsp;or both of Marge's sisters...  Or perhaps Flanders?   Any ideas? Anyone?  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just when we think this place could not sink any lower, it always does.   I just read an article about Missouri police pulling people over for good driving habits. And giving them coupons for free ICE CREAM. Yea, you heard me right. PULLING PEOPLE OVER for driving the speed limit, using turn signals, etc. Um, shouldn't the police be focusing on pulling over the dangerous drivers from the road rather than giving Petunia, Perfect Driving Record a coupon to Ben and Jerry's?   And as one woman adds, when almost late for work because of being pulled over to get free ice cream, she doesn't think her boss would care that she was being pulled over for good driving habits...he'd care that she was late because the police felt like giving out ice cream.   To read more, click  urlLink here .   BTW, it would be fun to get some commentage going.   That's a hint, if you are reading this, please comment soon. It could be fun. It's painless. And you don't need to have an account on blogger to do so. Give it a try. You may even get an ice cream cone if you are lucky.   As a PS to this post, a good friend of mine recently told her aunt to get a few moles checked out on her back, as they looked suspicious. When said aunt went to the doctor and told him that her niece had encouraged her to get the said moles looked at, the doctor came back and said that she should get her niece an ice cream cone.  Why is ice cream such a reward in this country????   Of course, said doctor understood the term "niece" to mean "my 7 year old niece" not my "mid-20's niece". Oh well...     
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Of Amish in the City! I can't believe it!  But, never fear, it's on Friday night again!   Did anyone watch it? Comments??? 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, last night, after a long and tiring day at work...  I got a nice suprise! My bridesmaid's dress for Kimmy's wedding has arrived and it's just so beautiful! I love the color and the style, and it's almost fitting me perfectly! Yay!  Click  urlLink here  to see it!&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't talk loudly.  Don't talk loudly to your neighbor on a 9pm flight.  Don't talk so loudly that the person sitting diagonally behind you in the next aisle can hear your entire conversation.  Don't talk about why you don't like the ocean or  urlLink spider bites.   Don't refuse the delicious onboard cookies then ask your neighbor what they taste like.  Don't let your 8 year old nephew talk while he is listening to his walkman.  Don't read over my shoulder.   That is all. Stay tuned for Travel etiquette 201. Soon to come.    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week, on Six Feet Under:  Claire got high, dunked her hands in paint, wrote on the walls, watched her ex and 2 friends have a threesome, and exclaimed that "everyone should work with dogs!" Oh, and she played rolling-pin with Mena Suvari. Yipee.  Ruth had quite an emotional explosion at David's birthday. I just love her explosions. She's so repressed and subdued normally, it's so fun to see her character explode.  David celebrated a birthday...and he got a creepy gift from Ruth's new hubby. Some instrument that you place hot water in, and use it to clear your nasal passages with to prevent colds and sinus infections. Perhaps this is yet another not so hidden clue as to the fact that Ruth's hubby George is much, much weirder than we originally assumed him to be.  Brenda and her man go looking for a house, try for a baby, and then Brenda finds Nate and makes out with him. Brenda SO needs to leave Nate alone! This new guy is great and Nate is finally seeming normal again.  Unfortunately, there was nothing too exciting this week. Stay tuned for more SFU fun.     
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry that I haven't been blogging lately!   I have been away at Universal Studios...then yesterday I went home early because I threw out my back at said amusement park and was literally bumping into walls at work because of recent dizzyness. So, when I got home and crashed for a few hours, mommy gave me some Vicoden. At that point, it was probably best that I did not blog. Instead, I somehow managed to re-read 100 pages of Harry Potter, year 2 and proceeded to pass out.   Never fear, I will be back later to blog...once I can get my mind off of my back pain! :(  &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who could possibly even believe that Amish in the City was actually a pretty decent show?  Well, the first 10 minutes was all fighting...very much a Real World episode. However, later on things bucked up...especially during the time with the mentally handicapped and during the concert! Very cute.  The one true classic line of the show from one of the Amish, "I don't know of any Ray Gae. Never heard of the guy."  The one true classic line of the show from one of the ABNOXIOUS city kids, "Do you even know how to read?"  As a side note, do NONE of the city kids even have any grasp on the fact that everything they know is totally unknown to the Amish?! They act suprised when they don't know who Bob Marley is, don't know what a fajita is, and don't know what pasta is and that it comes in different sizes. Patience, my friends, a little patience. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read this: Then I have a story to tell you:  LONDON, England (Reuters) -- A British man was being treated for shock on Wednesday after he fell from a ladder while pruning trees, accidentally killing his wife with his chainsaw, police said. The 56-year-old man, who has not been named, was cutting back tree branches at his home in southeast London on Monday when he tumbled backwards from the ladder. The running chainsaw crashed down onto the neck of his wife, who was working in the garden below him. "The woman was killed instantly, although she was not decapitated," police said in a statement. "Her husband was taken to hospital. He is still being treated for shock." A police spokesman said the incident was being treated as a "tragic accident."  About a year ago, my dad did something similar. And, he's English (as you all know). This absolutely cracked me up. I read the story to my mom and she exclaimed, "that  would  happen to me! And  he'd  get off without a scratch!". Unfortunately, when this happened to my dad, he fell off the ladder with the running chainsaw and fell on top of it with his wrist. He's ok now...but what a scare!   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Try it. You may like it. Like eating bananas in pudding. I personally don't like that. But, it's an example of something that one may like if one trys something new.         Why do you read my blog?         I feel obligated.        I like to read.        I like to laugh and point and make fun of Nicole.        I think that Nicole is a talented and gifted writer, and she makes me laugh and completes my everyday boring life.        I have nothing better to do.        I don't read your stinkin' blog, so quit asking.        I have nothing better to do.        I like to hear about world events of much importance.        I'd rather stab myself in the eye than continue reading Nicole's blogs.              urlLink  Free polls from Pollhost.com        
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I read an article. It cracked me up. Please understand that I do not want to make this a political blog, but I just could not leave this story alone. All politics aside, this really did make me giggle. Apparently, at a rally for Kerry, some of the opposition began shouting "four more years", implying that Bush would be/should be in office for four more years. To this, Kerry's wife replyed to the crowd, "they want four more years of hell." Boy, that woman can speak her mind. Another lewd comment she made recently comes to mind, when she said "shove it" to the annoying press. Not sure exactly what to think of her quite yet, but I have to say, she does crack me up. I enjoy her honesty, even if it seems that she's unable to think before speaking...it could be a very interesting four years if/when Kerry gets elected. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week's Six Feet Under was fabulous! They are finally getting back to their strange, strange roots. I have much to say.  First of all, how cute was it when the Fisher children busted out in song to " urlLink I'm Just a Lonely Petunia in an Onion Patch " to Maya?! Adorable but that song was really kinda creepy!!!  Going along with the Petunia theme, Nate sees his dead wife in the sleezy motel room dressed as a petunia, in an onion patch, just after he has sex with his new dating partner from the  urlLink doggy day care . She tells Nate that he needs to move on and start a relationship with this person, to give her the chance that she never got. And she tells Nate to stop sleeping with Brenda. Then she proceeds to throw onions at Nate and when he exclaims, "that hurts!" she tells him that life hurts and to get used to it. I found it quite amusing.  Brenda comes clean with  urlLink Joe , sort of. She tells him that she has been sleeping with someone because she's confused about the level of feelings she has for Joe. When he asks if it's anyone he knows, she lies and says no. Joe, who I really like despite his bizarre sexual fetishes, tells her that it's over. She begs him to reconsider and start anew...but I don't think this one's gonna cave. I think it's very possible that Brenda is pregnant with his child and will go back to Nate and they will become one big disfunctional family.  Claire develops the photograph she took of  urlLink Mena Suvari  (Edie) and thinks it is her best work yet. While at a critique, an annoying art student gets enraged that Claire gets an A for taking an erotic photo of her girlfriend. When Claire tells her that it's not her girlfriend, she herself begins to wonder about the nature of their relationship. Later in the episode, Edie makes a move on Claire and she freaks out and leaves...the next day she decides they should just have sex and see how it goes...I am not sure if I truly think that Claire is gay, but it's cool that Edie is making her happy and more in touch with her artistic side. Edie inspires her, lets see how it goes!  Poor David has more panic attacks, one in particular that was a bit much. For all the kiddies reading, (yeah right) I will try to keep it clean. David goes home with a bartender and just as he's going to open his mouth, he gets a mental image of when he was attacked and had to suck the barrel of a gun. The bartender leaves while exclaiming, why do I have to pick the crazy ones!?  George watches a documentary on marbles. Personally, I think he's lost his. Oh, and he tells Cathy Bates' charachter the history of paper mache. Yipee.  And, in quite possibly the best scene in the entire show, Ruth imagines all of George's ex wives heads on display...they are all talking about George's secrets and when she asks why he's so secretive, they all laugh hysterically at her.  All in all, last night's episode has been the best in quite a while...but, dear lord, where has the excrement plot line gone?  And, do we think the Petunia in an Onion Patch plotline will continue? I certainly hope so. It's always a good time to see people dressed as flowers, throwing onions. Hey, it made me laugh...  Last but not least, I almost forgot to comment on Rico. Poor  urlLink Rico  ( Riiight ) finally decides to cut things off with the stripper. However, its a bit too late as Rico's wife catches him leaving a book for the strippers' daughter Nicole on the doorstep and she gets a glimpse of the charity case stripper that Rico has been helping. Of course, she jumps to the conclusion that they have been sleeping together (who wouldn't?) and confronts Rico and tells him to move out...which drives him right into the arms of the stripper and we get to see her fake boobs, yet again. Joy.  Creepy . I have to leave now and go puke. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Six Feet Under...  (I am dutifully trying to remember what happened as it's been 5 days since I viewed this marvelous show)  We find out that Claire just isn't that into girls, even though Mena Suvari is really hot. Rico sleeps downstairs in the morgue. I honestly don't think I could ever do that. I mean, c'mon Rico, you can splurge for the Red Roof Inn. Ohhh, and Rico's wife and sister have a great catfight with "Destiny" and wreck her pathetic car. Mama Ruth leaves a pot roast in the oven and almost burns the house down after some nasty fights with the hubby. She leaves without saying where she has gone, or for how long. What a drama queen, but good for her. She needs to step up and stand up for herself. George prunes one of Ruth's trees. It's actually Claire's tree that her dad planted for her. When I say prune, I really mean "slaughter". It was a sad day. David gets cheated on. And his man cheats on him with a famous celebrity, Celeste. Yes, a woman. Hmm. Oh, and Celeste then proceeds to FIRE him.  All in all, 'twas a good hour of escapist TV. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I am putting this out there after a nice convo with my dear friend (you know who you are).  I think that she is the only one reading my blog. If I am wrong, drop me an email. Let me know you are reading.   urlLink Nickisee@aol.com    Because if that's the case, I think I am just going to start typing personal notes to my one reader. :)   Oh, and you are highly encouraged to vote on my little polls. They don't bite.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just had to share, my alma mater has a new website design and it's simply FABULOUS. I love it!  Click  urlLink here  to view it!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When filling in your W9 form, don't abbreviate association with ass.  It's assoc.  Just wanted to clue all you folks in. Unless you like your checks going to Suzie Jones, Ass. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, we are at 49 hits currently...and I am anticipating my 50th hit! Wohoo!  C'mon people, read my blog! Make me feel wanted and loved! :0    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             If you could be anyone who would you be?         George "W" Bush        Kermit the Frog        Olivia (by Ian Falconer)        Eloise        Jesus        Yourself        Me        Julia Roberts        Julie Andrews        Julia Stiles                 urlLink  Free polls from Pollhost.com        
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You really, really like me. In the words of Sally Field...    Well, seeing as only one of my readers/friends answered my fun little poll from last week, it's unanamous that you think I am talented and funny and just all that!  Sorry I have not been blogging lately. Have been in a slump of some sort. I promise to write more and soon.  Six Feet Under analysis to come. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>