<Blog>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just kidding. I love Day Camp. Day Camp rockz. I have some friends now. Molly (of course), Amber, Hobbit, and Lindsey. Oh and I think Stephen nd Catherine aer sorta kinda my friends. I get the feeling Ian wants to kill me though. Anyway, Im going to create a new show called "Everybody loves Stephen". I might as well. Its true. -.-
Anyway. Yeeea. But camp was fun. Yea. Thats all I gotta say.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heres a poem I did a while ago. Well, just a year or two ago. But I talk about how people under the age of 18 are always looked at as "kids" and dont take us seriously, even though more of us are smarter than adults. I  really hope you like it and I hope I get some feedback about it.          ***                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   
I don’t get it anymore.
How does this work out?
I was overlooked by God.
I have more than I’ll ever need,
But still it’s not enough.
How did I get so unlucky?
How did I just get skipped over?
Like a page in a book.
They just don’t see me.
Hello? No one answers.
No one is there.
I’ve yelled the loudest I ever could and
Still
No one’s listening to someone like me.
I’m just a kid.
Just a god damn kid.
With no hope, no dreams, no future.
It was all taken.
What do I need for them to see me?
To kill myself?
Must I be suicidal?
Why don’t they listen?
 The younger the smarter, so why aren’t we up there,
Up in the spotlight expressing ourselves?
Why can’t they see the soul that lives?
That thrives of victory? 
Why can’t they believe us?
Karma is wrong.
Karma made a mistake.
How?


     

    
</post>


<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Try" by Nelly Furtado &nbsp; I do hate Nelly Furtado's voice. I really do. But this song does relate to my current situation, or one of them. Well, some of it does. Well, enough about me... (haha, just kidding!) This song is well written, and is uh... well, just ok. Not great. But I do listen to it, because I like music I can relate too. She is way too perky. Nelly F. would do well on a second remake 0f Painted Black. haha. Get the lyrics at:  urlLink http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/nellyfurtado/try.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Symphony 5" by Beethoven &nbsp; Ok, I admit, this doesnt quite fit with System. But the 'Hoven Man rules! I mean hes long dead and cold and his music is still played worldwide! I mean seriously, classical music people like myself admire Beethoven and all of his work greatly. I mean seriously! Mozart wrote twinkle twinkle little star.&nbsp; WHO GIVES A SHIT? Beethoven wrote Symphony 5 (my personal favorite) and Tempest. Tempest RULES! No singing- so no lyrics. :( 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Chop Suey!" by System of a Down &nbsp; I listened to this song in elementary school. I didnt know it was System, but now I do. And it rocks.&nbsp; System rocks. I love all their music. Chop Suey! is probably my favorite though. Its got its fair amount of needed screaming, andits got its meaning. You have to listen to this song. My friend first introduced me to System, but not to Chop Suey! Like I said, elementary school. Get the Lyrics:  urlLink http://www.systemofadownonline.com/lyrics/0206.htm  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Someday" by Nickelback &nbsp; I really like this song. Im not sure, but Nickelback sounds like they know what they're talking about. The singer sings with emotion, and the music video is phonomenal. Its got brilliant meaning and the music video makes you think. I live everything about this song. Even though the singer has a strange voice at times, when singing this song it doesnt even matter. I love this song.&nbsp; I keep ssaying that but I do. I normally am not fond of Nickleback, other than Hero. If you listen to it, you'll either love it or hate it. Get the lyrics at:  urlLink http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/nickelback/someday.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Imaginary" by Evanescence &nbsp; I love this song. It is very dramatic, but also very powerful. Its finally getting the recognition it deserves in the upcoming movie M.Night Shyamalan's The Village. (you may recognize Shyamalan's name from "Signs") The song is all about a person making up a new place to go when her life falls to peices.&nbsp; At least, that is what I got. This song has a great guitarist and Amy Lee has a great voice for these kind of songs. This is on the album "Fallen". Get the Lyrics:  urlLink http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/evanescence/imaginary.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "I am Human" the Smiths and "I am Human" by the Psychedelic Furs &nbsp; I love both versions. I think I like the newer version because its closer to my taste in music, even though they are both almost the same. I think both singers have good voices and are&nbsp; right for the song. Many of us know I am Human as the theme of one of America's most populare witch shows, Charmed. I believe this song was originally done in the 1980's, redone in 1997 by the Psychedelic Furs.&nbsp; I strongly recommend at least trying to listen to this song for people who are weird, like me, or obsessed with music. --lyrics unavailable-- 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "Pardon Me" by Incubus  &nbsp; This song is so cool. I like the words. I love he "effects" the guitarist makes with his guitar. They are a really good band, as far as I know. I listened to this song first in Little Nicky and went on a search for its name and group. I was amazed of how long I had gone without hearing an Incubus song until then. I find this song incredible and&nbsp;not many&nbsp;people other than me like it. I find it brilliant.&nbsp;&nbsp;I love the singer, he has talent in. He can think fast, I can tell, from his singing. I hope you enjot this song as much as I did. Get the Lyrics at the end of this page:  urlLink http://www.incubusonline.com/my.php  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, this is song #1. To explain, every now and then when I come by a song I have a strong opinion about a song or new band, Ill type about it here. Is there an Inside the Music site 1 or 2? I dunno. I just like the number 3. So heres an example of a Song Review--  &nbsp;  "Accidentally In Love" by the Counting Crows  &nbsp;  Well, I do to a certain degree,  like  the song. It is kind of perky for my taste but still. I guess some of us can relate to the lyrics. The singer does have a fairly good voice, while the band also gives a good performance. You can find this song on the Shrek 2 soundtrack, now in stores, and no, I dont work for Best Buy. I like the song itself, but I must say that the music video is absolutly dreadful!!! It was inevitably the stupidest thing I have ever seen! For a summary, it involves a giant rabbit with hair like the Crow's lead singer and a moron making pancakes. Its not funny, either. So anyway. The songs lyrics are good at some points, while at other points they just confuse me. Though I sort of like the song and respect the band, I'll give it a 5/10 and I think Ill stick to System. Get the lyrics at:  urlLink http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/countingcrows/accidentallyinlove.html    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>