<Blog>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow these past 2 days or so have been crazy.. i didnt like them well yesterday.. wow.. it was crazy..  Ive been sick lately so idk what is really going on..  But frank found his birth mom.. and he wants to leave to go with her.. so idk what is going on.. and let me just say that its not fair.  Brittney i love you. I am here for you always. WE are all here dont forget that..   well okay thats a bout it.. ive got some things to do today so yeah..    bye.
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Everything is moving so quickly Im trying to take everything in stride I realize that every day with u is a blessing and im blessed to have you.  Then it comes the time to say goodbye We both sit and wonder why? We both cry when we leave But we know we shall stay together indeed  Everytime I talk to you im in heaven My heart beats so fast I feel like im the best woman in the world,  when im with you.
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Name::Laura Lee Zerangue (Larva) >Birthday:: June 24, 1989 >Eye Color::blue >Hair Color:: brown! >Shoe Size:: 9 >Name of your school:: St. Louis >Do you Have braces?::nope not anymore! :) >Do you Wear contacts?:: somtimes. >Where were you born?:: This stinkhole >How much did you weigh when you were born?:: 4lbs 6 oz.  >Do you have a retainer?:: yes, but i dont wear it! haha  >Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend?:: yes >What color was your hair when you were born?:: blonde >Are your parents Married or Divorced?::married >How many siblings do you have?::1 >What are their names?:: Frank >Do you have any step brothers/sisters?::nope >Get along with your family?:: yeah sometimes >Parents :: Dad >Age difference between you and your siblings?::4 years  >Favorite cousin?::DYLAN.. omg i love him to death >Daddy or Momma's boy/girl?:: DAD >Do your parents spoil you?:: yeah. they spoil me ALOT i love it but sometimes i just think im to spoiled! >How many people live in your house?::3 >Do you have family get togethers?::uhh naw? >Do you like your dad or mom's side of the family >better?::i love my dad's side.. i HATE myu moms side..  >Does your older brother/sister boss you around?:: hell no he is never around anyways. >Do you like your family?::their okay >Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend?:: yes  boyfriend >What's their name?::DOUG >How long have you known them?::2 years >Your anniversary?:: uhh >Are you in love?::idk i think >Have you ever been in love?::no >Who have you been in love with?:: not going to say  >How many boyfriends/girlfriends have you had?::2 >Have you ever had sex?::nope >With who?:: ... >Do you want to stay with your current >boyfriend/girlfriend?:: yeah i do i really do, but he lives about 2,00 miles away.. but i do love him. >Do they love you?:: he tells me he does. >Held your breath until you passed out?:: nope >Wanted to die?:: no >Smoked weed?:: nope! >Commited a crime?:: naw >Saved someones life?:: yeah >Stayed up all night?::yup on the phone  >Been to another country?:: uhhh >Loved someone so much it made you cry?:: YES.  >Been cheated on?:: no  >Let someone else take the blame for something you >did?::yeah i have done that once   >Faked being sick?:: who hasnt?! >Been to the Astrodome?:: yes >Dyed your hair?:: yep in 8th grade blonde lol just to get OLQH pissed.. and it worked! :) >Hot/Cold::COLD >Sun/Rain:: SUN >Night/Day:: night >Guys/Girls::guys i love doug >Lust/Love::LOVE. >Car/Truck?:: truck >Laptop/Computer:: laptop >Goodie-goodie/Rebel:: Goodie-goodie >Dr.Pepper/Coke:: Dr. Pepper >Summer/Winter:: WINTER >Lake/Ocean:: lake >Prep/Goth:: prep? >Basketball/Football:: BAsketball > >Color::PINK. >Number:: 189 >Animal:: IDK >Web Site:: uh..blog? lol Food?::mexican >Football team?:: Broncos ;) >Thing to do?:: dance,talk,phone,dance. >Sport to watch?:: cheerleading i love to watch it on TV >Sport to play?:: SOFTBALL, DANCE, AND TENNIS! >Holiday:: Christmas i love when everyone is tog. >Friend:: Lisa/ Mels >Place to go:: Softball fields, lisa's, movies  >TV show:: uhh idk >Place to eat::CASA >How many pillows are on your bed?::  2 small ones and a body one >What color is your toothbrush?:: ITS A PINK AND PURPLE HELLO KITTY! >What brand of toothpaste do you use?:: whitenin stuff >How old will you be when you graduate High School?::17 >What is on your desktop?:: Orlando Bloom >Have you ever been to a tailgate party?:: that was a stupid ass question of course i have been! >Gotten kicked out of Wal-Mart?:: naw >Have you ever sat on Santa's lap?:: yes >Gotten money from the tooth fairy?:: yes >Do you have an online journal?:: blog >Do you love someone?:: yes >Who?:: Doug >What channel is your TV on?:: 54 >Do you Like George Strait?:: no >What time is it?:: 1:20 pm >What are you wearing?::im still in my pj's.. an angel shirt and frog shorts.. im sick haha  >How is your hair done?:: in a pony tail >What color are your socks?::im not wearing any! >Who are you talking to?:: i was talking to Lisa and nita >Who hugged you last?:: my mom  >Last word you said:: damnit >Color of your nails?:: pink >Do you have make-up on?:: nope none  >What color are your shoestrings?::pink >What's the date?:: July uhh? 12 2004 >What time is it?:: 1:22 pm  sry guys i love those things! ;)
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yesterday was a weird day. Me n Lisa went to Wal Mart so she could get a new bathing suit! It was fun lol so anyways we went to BlockBuster and then we came home cooked lunch and then we watched some of Monster and then Lisa's dad said that he is comming over in 45 mins to get her, so then i just gave her the DVD to watch.. and yeah.. then i went back to sleep.. cuz i didnt/ dont feel good.  And then i started to wonder about alot of things. Some good things some bad things. and i wondered how much i miss them now that they are gone. Bcuz now when i need that person the most they are like 2000 miles away.   Doug i miss you.
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have jet lag. and it sucks badly. lol evne tho my flight was only 3 hours.. haa   but anyways i think today is going to be one of those stay inside watch movies with ur friend day. and that friend would be lisa. haah i love my lisa. I missed her very much while i was gone. :)   Its really acutally funny, bcuz i bought this cowboy hat while i was in CO and everyone was like omg r u from Louisiana.. and they were all like say something and i sad like hey yall.. and omg thye freaked out.. its so weird.. lol    Later GanstERS. 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today i left from Colorado.  As much as i told myself that i wasnt going to cry i did. I was scared to wake up this morning bcuz i knew what was going to happen. So i wake up this mornin and find a note on the foot of the bed that says my name, so naturally im going to open it. and i did. and i balled for ever. :( so yes. this mornin sucked. and then i go downstairs to see that dylan was waiting for me to get up. so i went and hugged him and just cryed lol im such a baby. okay and then last night was super sad. I went to Phat City for like 3 hours and said bye to Addison, Mandy, Courtney and CHRIS. Man, i miss Chris alot. Addison- i miss you too lol oh and PRANK PHONE CALL lmao love ya! But anyways my flight went okay, and i dont even want to talk about what happened b4 i left cuz if i type it i will cry more. so ill ttyl guys.   Latuh.
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      im leaving today.   :( nope im not going to cry im not going to cry.
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today i am leaving. I woke up @ like 8:40 not willingly tho but only bcuz i have to. I put my make up on then i packed all my stuff. :(  and now im sitting here wondering about things, things that you only think about when you leave somewheres. I mean dont get my wrong yall I LOVE lake charles and ALL OF THE PPL IN IT.. but i mean im leaving my cousin and doug. thats really hard.    But yeah, im comming home tonight.. and hopefully lisa and sarah and her mom are going to come by to see me! lol plus i have gifts for them! haha !
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay so yesterdayyyyy i updated but im going to do it again haa  ok so we went to go eat @ Texas RoadHose which was really good.. lmao we all got a full slab of ribs, and i couldnt even finish a 1/2 haha  omgz in Colorado they have the HOTTEST guys working @ Texas Roadhouse.. if anyone comes here yall should definately check it out! ;) haha so anyways we ate then we came home and rolled some dice and then we all went to  bed fairly early bcuz we are going to ESTAS today! WHOOP! its a place where they have alot of shops and things... lol the only way dylan is comming is bcuz he gets a new knife! haha but anyways thats really it.. we should be home around 3 or 4 or so but ill talk to yall later! byes! :)   Latuh niggah.
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today i woke up @ like 10 or so bcuz last night was crazy, and i had a nervous break down. :(  So then i figure what is the point of waking up bcuz things just went bad today. So to make things worse, im sick. And then Dylan had to go to the doctor. Then doug came over which is a plus but i cryed the whole time he was here. Which isnt cool then me dylan and dee went Bowling i beat them. haha  thats about it.. Tomorrow i think we are all going to estas :) yay! that will be one of my last days with my cousin and doug. :(  Love isnt fair.  i love you.
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      last night was boring we didnt do anything. i woke up @ like 8:30 came down to the computer saw that melanie was on then made her explain why the fuck she was up that early lol  me n dylan and dee went downstairs and cleaned the basement me n dee went to Bed Bath and Beyond to get some furniture for donwn there called lisa to ssee how she was feeling!  oh and i got my moms b-day present and i got a light. haha yeah im leaving saturday yall. dude its really funny bcuz when i say 'yall' ppl FREAK out and are like wtf? omg ur a hick im like uhh okay w/e  ok now to explain the title so i come home from BB&B and nanny let those fucking farrots out and they bit the shit out of me..so then we go to Home Depot and she forgot to put them in the cage so they were out.. so i get home and the first thing i do is sit somewhres where my feet dont touch the floor.. lol so yeah.. it sucked. but anyways  now im just gettin ready for dinner tonite with doug dlyan and the neighbors.. it should be fun.. :) but yeah ill update later   Ashlee Simpson - Pieces Of Me Lyrics  On a Monday, I am waiting Tuesday, I am fading And by Wednesday, I can't sleep Then the phone rings, I hear you And the darkness is a clear view Cuz you've come to rescue me  Fall... With you, I fall so fast I can hardly catch my breath, I hope it lasts  Ohhhhh It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real I like the way that feels Ohhhhh It's as if you've known me better than I ever knew myself I love how you can tell All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  I am moody, messy I get restless, and it's senseless How you never seem to care When I'm angry, you listen When youre happy, it's a mission And you wont stop 'til I'm there  Fall... Sometimes I fall so fast Well, I hit that bottom Crash, you're all I have  [Chorus:] Ohhhhh It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real I like the way that feels Ohhhhh It's as if you known me better than I ever knew myself I love how you can tell All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  How do you know everything I'm about to say? Am I that obvious? And if it's written on my face... I hope it never goes away... yeah  On a Monday, I am waiting And by Tuesday, I am fading into your arms... So I can breathe  [Chorus:] Ohhhhh It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real I like the way that feels Ohhhhh It's as if you've know me better than I ever knew myself I love how you can tell Ohhhhh I love how you can tell Ohhhhh I love how you can tell All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me...   
      
</post>


</Blog>