<Blog>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is one of those stories that begins... "Y'all ain't gonna believe this shit..."  I met this young lady a couple weeks ago, so what the hell, I asked her out and we agreed to meet for dinner on Tuesday night. Dinner went well, it seems to always surprise me when a date arrives to a designated meeting place on time. Is it a power thing for women to keep a guy waiting?   Anyways, like I was saying, dinner was going relatively well. She mentioned quite a few times that she was single and not seeing anyone (isn't that supposed to be a good sign?) but she mentioned also that there are quite a few guys that are interested in pursuing her. (What the hell is that supposed to mean?) But overall, the dinner experience was pretty good. I walked her to her car and we were supposed meet back up at this nightclub a few blocks away.   Now, I have honestly never been to a gay nightclub before. But the word from friends is that at least on Tuesday nights, the salsa dancing is pretty good, so... Why not? Let's check this place out. Honestly, aside from the DJ seemingly intent on playing anything but salsa music and the blinding strobe lights, this really is an awesome place, ESPECIALLY the bartender in drag.   Back to the date... like I mentioned, it's a few blocks away from the restaurant, so we each took our separate cars and drove over. She arrives 30 minutes after I do. Said she was on the phone. A few of my friends show up as well and so, for the moment, things are normal, we're dancing, we're drinking... No worries.   Her ex-b/f shows up. Some guy from San Francisco. Now what the hell are the chances, especially here in Sacramento, for somebody to run into an ex from another city... especially one from SF? To top it off, the guy is a stripper, with the physique to go with it. Okay, as a guy, I'm pretty self-confident and secure, so this is NOT an issue. It raises eyebrows, but it's a minor ripple, the boat barely rocks.   They talk for a bit and they kiss. That rocked the boat... Not happy.   She comes over and apologizes (profusely...) and explains the situation. Which is how I got the aforementioned bit of information. Ummmm.... okay, annoyed, but the night is still young, let's just enjoy the evening and see how this thing ends right? I mean, my friends are here, we're in the club, if nothing else, the people here are pretty interesting.   About midnight rolls around and the music stops. Another drag queen announces in rapid fire Spanish about some show (mi espanol es muy terrible... as a good buddy of mine says) and so we get off the dance floor and watch. Wouldn't you know it but the ex-b/f of my supposed date is the one man show and strips for all the glory of humanity.   Now, I know that in the premises of a short story, this chain of events seems to be a logical progression. But this isn't a short story, this is real life. How plausible is it for me to ask a woman out, take her to a gay nightclub where she runs into her (supposedly?) straight ex-b/f from a city over 100 miles away who just happens to be a stripper and who... by the way, HAPPENS TO BE THE STAR OF THE SHOW? Do you see the overwhelming probabilities against all of these things happening at the same time?   All in all though, that kiss they shared was the thing that annoyed me the most. Everything else is just... well, a really good story. Of course, the question is posed to me as I am driving home and my cell phone rings... "Dude, so are you going to call her again?"  Should I? 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Call it an attempt to be constructive while venting my random thoughts that all of my friends and family that have grown tired to listen to. Anyways, this is my experiment to speak randomly to a wider audience.   So... hello. My name is Puck. And here will reside... random thoughts. 
    
</post>


</Blog>