<Blog>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhh, finally I've got a day off today from the joke I spend 60 hours a week at called work. I'm in the process of sending out resumes...again...  I really hate that I can't seem to find anything more than a dead end job. Finding a career isn't what I want either...but I need something that pays well enough for me to be able to live. Maybe I should just join a band that needs a good guitarist and cash in...but the problem is I like a lot of what's out there, but I certaniy don't want to play it...lol. It's too much like selling your soul to me.   I'm so stuborn...but it's got to happen on my terms in order for me to be able to live with myself...lol. It helps though that I'm going ahead in the right direction, even if it feels like it's taking forever.  That said, tonight I'm fixed on making some magic happen...I don't even know how yet..all I know is I'm going into the studio and it's going to come through.    Someday it's going to be to a point where I'm going to not be able to justify the waste of time my job is...and I'm going to be consumed by this thing we call music...I just hope by that point I've at least got a band together so I can play it...lol...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I first heard about "blogs" about a year ago. I'm sure at the time I swore I'd never have one, now here I am. A suggestion from a good friend and I steped right up...me and myself might have something to say about what "I" have done.   A year ago things were simpler. I had no idea what I was in store for. Getting laid-off, going back to school, losing people I never thought I'd see walk away. On the other hand I guess I didn't think I'd get to see my parents again for the first time in 5 years. I probably have more mixed feelings about that than anything...but I'll save that for another post...  So here I am. Somehow the world feels smaller every year. I feel like the boundaries society places on our minds through work and school has shrunk my mind and locked it up...I didn't feel this way a year ago...as if every year this world pushes us all one step closer to accepting the bull shit as normal...  I'm not normal...now I'm a blogger
     

    
</post>


</Blog>