<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       YESTERDAY ROCKED HARDCORE.  WELL MY MORNING WAS A WEE BIT HECTIC AND SUCKED BUT BY ABOUT 1 PM THINGS WERE GOING GOOD.  ME AND ANNA HOPPED IN HER CAR AND DROVE TO MARSHALL TO GET APRIL THERE WE MESSED WITH JOSH AND ANNA TOOK 40 PICTURES OF HIM. SPEAKING OF PICTURES I'M TRYING TO WORKING ON PUTTING UP SOME PHOTOGALLERIES SO IF YOU HAVE ANY SUGGESTIONS ANY SUGGESTIONS AT ALL PLEASE HELP ME. BUT ANYWAYS SO THEN WE MADE IT BACK TO MY HOUSE AND JESSI  WAS THERE THEN WE LEFT SOMETIME BETWEEN 3:30 AND 4:00 PM.  WE ATE AT WENDY'S ON THE WAY THERE (MMM... CHEAP CHICKEN NUGGETS) WE GOT TO THE CREEPY CRAWL AT ABOUT 7:10 AND WAITED IN LINE FOR LIKE 20 MINUTES TO GET IN LUCKILY WE BOUGHT TICKETS IN ADVANCE.  WHEN WE GOT IN SCATTERED FALL WAS PLAYING AND THEY WERE PRETTY GOOD THEIR SINGER WAS REALLY HOT AND LOOKS A LOT LIKE DAVEY HAVOK BACK WHEN HE HAD THE WHOLE DEVIL LOCK HAIRCUT THING GOING AND THEIR DRUMMER LOOKED LIKE NAPOLEON DYNAMITE.  AFTER THEY WERE DONE PLAYING ANNA AND I BOUGHT THINGS FROM THE LAWRENCE ARMS MERCH TABLE WHEN BRENDAN SHOWED UP TO DO SOMETHING AT THE TABLE SO I INTRODUCED MYSELF AND THANKED HIM AGAIN FOR CALLING ME ON MY BIRTHDAY AND HE GAVE ME A HUG.   THEN PIPEDOWN PLAYED AND WELL I THOUGHT THEY WERE GOOD AT FIRST BUT THEY WERE PLAYING THE THEME SONG FROM HEAVY METAL AFTER THEY BEGAN TO PLAY THEIR OWN MATERIAL I BEGAN TO REALIZE THAT THEY REALLY KINDA SUCK.  THEIR LEAD SINGER LOOKS KINDA LIKE A MONKEY AND WAS A MAJOR DOUCHEBAG TO ME AND ANNA.  THEN THE LAWRENCE ARMS TOOK THE STAGE ANNA APRIL AND JESSI WATCHED FROM A BACKCORNER WHILE I WAS IN THIS HUGE MESS OF PEOPLE I GOT A TON OF HOPEFULLY GOOD PICTURES AND I HAD TO ASK THIS REALLY BIG GUY TO MOVE LIKE 2 STEPS BACK AND ONE STEP OVER AND HE WAS REALLY NICE AND DID.  AFTER THEY WERE DONE WE WENT OUT THE BACK DOOR AND TALKED TO THEM AND CALLED FOR A RIDE.  WE WOULD HAVE STAYED TO WATCH TSUNAMI BOMB PLAY BUT IT WAS FRIGGIN PACKED AND I THOUGHT WE WOULD ALL DIE OF HEAT EXHAUSTION AND PLUS WE WANTED TO GO TALK TO THE LAWRENCE ARMS.  SO YEAH IT WAS AWESOME DESPITE ALL THE GROPINGS I GOT FROM STRANGERS AND THE WHOLE ALMOST DEHYDRATING THING.  ALSO I GOT PUSHED AND FELL ON THIS REALLY SHORT REALLY SKINNY GIRL WHO DIDN'T LOOK MUCH OLDER THAN 12 BUT SHE SORTA DESERVED IT FOR SITTING ON THE GROUND AND STRETCHING HER LEGS OUT ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING HOW PACKED IT WAS.      SO BASICALLY A GOOD TIME WAS HAD BY ALL EXCEPT MAYBE THAT GIRL I FELL ON.      SHUT UP SHARKY AND GO CATCH A DELICIOUS BASS!, TAGUE    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       LAWRENCE ARMS TOMORROW SO I WON'T GET BACK TO YOU FOR A FEW DAYS BECAUSE I'LL BE BUSY ALL DAY TOMORROW AND THEN SATURDAY I'LL PROBABLY GET MY PICTURES DEVELOPED AND THEN I'LL BE I DON'T KNOW PROBABLY WATCHING THE EVEL KNEIVAL MOVIE TO MAKE FUN OF GEORGE EADS (WHY DOES JESSI LIKE HIM, I MEAN I LIKE TO MAKE FUN OF HIM AND HE IS LIKE-ABLE AS NICK ON CSI BUT HAVE YOU SEEN DUST TO DUST WHERE HE PLAYS A FAKE INDIAN AND WEARS ZIGGY STARDUST MAKE UP AND CROWNED AND DANGEROUS WERE I&nbsp; SWEAR THAT CHICK HAS "SOMETHING SPECIAL" IN HER PANTS IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.)&nbsp; THEN PROBABLY I'LL SEE HAROLD AND KUMAR GO TO WHITE CASTLE BECAUSE CHRISTOPHER MELONI IS IN IT AND THERE ARE PROSTHETICS INVOLVED AND PROBABLY NAPOLEON DYNAMITE BECAUSE I AM INTRIGUED.&nbsp; OH AFTER I GET TOMORROW'S PICTURES DEVELOPED AND ANNA GETS THE ONES I WANTED SCANNED THERE WILL BE MANY PICTURES MANY WONDER, INTERESTING OR OTHERWISE WELL I'M OUT OF THINGS TO SAY EXCEPT I LOVE YOU ALL WITH A FEW EXCEPTIONS    &nbsp;  MASTER IS MY NAME AND THIRST IS WHAT I TAME,   TAGUE    &nbsp;  PS YOU CAN KNOW FIND ME AND MORE ABOUT ME AT MYSPACE.COM BUT THIS WILL BE THE BLOG I DITECT ALL TO.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       SO ANYWAY I AM FRIGGIN PSYCHED LIKE NONE OTHER TODAY IS TUESDAY WHICH IS ONLY A SHORT TIME BEFORE FRIDAY WHICH IS WHEN I GET TO GO SEE THE LAWRENCE ARMS!!!!!!!!!!!!!            [img urlLink http://www.thelawrencearms.net/band/images.php?page=4 /]      HOW CAN YOU RESIST?       SOMETIMES YOU FEEL LIKE A NUT ESPECIALLY AT JUDY'S BAT MITZVAH , TAGUE       PS CHECK OUT ANNAS BLOG     urlLink HTTP://ANNATALKSTOOMUCH.BLOGSPOT.COM  /    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       WELL MY DEAR PEOPLE AND CREATURES I AM WRITING TO YOU ABOUT 2 MAYBE 3 DAYS SINCE MY LAST POST AND WELL QUITE FRANKLY NOT A WHOLE LOT HAS BEEN GOING ON ME AND JESSI MADE A CD FOR OUR TRIP FRIDAY AND I PLAYED TRIVIAL PURSUIT WITH HER MOM AND BROTHER (WHO BY THE WAY GOT FRUSTRATED BY HIS LACK OF PIE PIECES AND QUIT)THE OTHER DAY I WON WOOHOO IT WAS VERY CLOSE I JUST HAPPENED TO&nbsp;HAVE A VERY LUCKY GUESS OF WHAT KIND OF WATER CAMERON DIAZ WASHES HERE FACE IN (ITS EVIAN).&nbsp;&nbsp;LAST NIGHT I DECIDED TO TAKE A WALK SO I GOT DRESSED AND WENT FOR A WALK AT 10 PM I LIVE A FEW BLOCKS AWAY FROM THE PARK SO I GRABBED MY HEADPHONES AND WENT THERE WHERE I JUST SAT THERE FOR&nbsp;AWHILE AND THOUGHT AND LISTENED TO&nbsp;THE ALBUM GHOST STORIES FROM THE LAWRENCE ARMS&nbsp;I HAVE THE FIRST "HIDDEN" SONG AT THE END OF TRACK 12 STUCK IN MY HEAD DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS CALLED BECAUSE I WOULD REALLY LIKE TO KNOW.&nbsp; SO THEN AFTER I WENT HOME I PUT ON THE SAME PAJAMAS I'VE BEEN WEARING FOR A WEEK ON AND ATTEMPTED TO FIND SOMETHING TO WATCH ON TV BEFORE DECIDING &nbsp;IT WAS TIME TO PLAY VIDEO GAMES SO I MADE MYSELF A CUP OF COFFE WHICH AT THIS POINT IT WAS ABOUT MIDNIGHT, AND STARTED PLAYING KINGDOM HEARTS WHICH I PLAYED UNTIL&nbsp;4 AM AT WHICH POINT I RETURNED TO MY ROOM AND WATCHED CAPTAIN PLANET BEFORE GOING&nbsp;TO SLEEP AT ABOUT FIVE AM CENTRAL STANDARD TIME TODAY I GOT UP AT 12:40PM BECAUSE JESSI CALLED AT WHICH POINT I STARTED PLAYING KINGDOM HEARTS AGAIN UNTIL ABOUT 2 PM WHEN I HAD A BOWL OF CEREAL AND&nbsp;A CUP OF COFFEE&nbsp; THEN I PLAYED KINGDOM HEARTS SOME MORE AND TALKED TO JESSI, THE A LITTLE BIT LATER APRIL AND THEN A LITTLE BIT LATER ANNA AND THEN GOT DRESSED AND WALKED HERE TO TALK TO YOU FOR AWHILE.&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       OKAY SO THESE GUYS ARE AWESOME AND I TOLD THEM I'D PIMP THEM LIKE CRAZY HERE.&nbsp; SO THEY START TOURING OCTOBER FIRST I&nbsp;BELIEVE AND YOU SHOULD GO SEE THEM.&nbsp;&nbsp;I LIKE THEM AND SO SHOULD YOU.    &nbsp;CHECK THEM OUT CHECK THEIR WEBSITE&nbsp;    urlLink  http://www.11minutesaway.com/     urlLink  http://www.purevolume.com/elevenminutesaway/      so check them out they are cool &nbsp;  also they need a logo.   &nbsp;  don't monkey with my buisness, tague   &nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       WELL BOYS AND GIRLS I AM BACK FOR A FEW POSTS TODAY AND IT'LL PROBABLY BE A FEW MORE DAYS UNTIL I POST AGAIN SO STAY TUNED BECAUSE I MIGHT JUST LOVE YOU FOR IT.&nbsp; THE REASON THERE IS SUCH A PAUSE IS BECAUSE I HAVE TO USE OTHER PEOPLE'S COMPUTERS BECAUSE OURS MELTED AWHILE BACK.&nbsp; NO I AM NOT KIDDING.&nbsp; I THINK IT GOT STRUCK BY LIGHTENING EVEN THOUGH WE HAD IT PLUGGED INTO A SURGE PROTECTER&nbsp; BUT THAT CAUSED LARGE SINK HOLES IN THE HARD DRIVE AND EVENTUALLY WE JUST GAVE UP ON IT AND THREW IT IN A DUMPSTER SOMEWHERE.&nbsp; THE PLUGS WERE ALL BLACK AND MELTED AND WE DIDN'T DISCOCER THIS UNTIL AFTER WE HAD GIVEN UP ON IT AND WERE UNHOOKING IT TO&nbsp;TAKE IT TO ABOVE MENTIONED DUMPSTER.&nbsp; YEAH SO THIS SUMMER BEWARE OF PEOPLE WHO LOOK LIKE&nbsp;B LIST CELEBRITIES BECAUSE THEME PARKS ARE PACKED WITH THEM, ALSO ANY RIDE WHERE YOU HAVE A PULL DOWN HARNESS THING BECAUSE THERE IS A LITLLE NUB AT THE BOTTOM THAT HAS TO GO OVER A LITTLE &nbsp;LOCATED IN CLOSE PROXIMITY TO YOUR CROTCH BECAUSE IF YOU HAVE TO BE A CHILD OR CHILD SIZED TO MANUEVER THIS CORRECTLY SO YOU CAN THEN BUCKLE THIS LITTLE SEAT BELT LIKE APPARATUS BECAUSE YOU WILL HAVE TROUBLE IF YOU ARE NOT A CHILD OR CHILD SIZED AND IS FURTHER COMPLICATED IF YOU HAVE BOOBS BECAUSE THEN THERE IS SOME UNPLEASANT SQUISHING INVOLVES SO THAT THOSE TWO NUBS WILL CROSS&nbsp;     &nbsp;  BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY............... DO NOT TALK ABOUT HOW HARMLESS OWLS ARE BECAUSE THEY WILL EXACT THEIR REVENGE AND THIS USUALLY IN THE FORM OF DROPPING A OPOSSUM ON THE HOOD OF YOUR CAR WHILE YOU HAVE COME TO A COMPLETE STOP TO AVOID HITTING IT.&nbsp; (THIS COMES FROM EXPERIENCE ASK ANNA.)    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  JUST WHEN YOU THINK&nbsp;YOU'VE GOT LIFE BY THE BALLS YOU GO AND TRY TO KILL AND INDIAN AND HE JUST SUCKS THE LIFE RIGHT OUT OF YOU,&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; TAGUE  
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       UMM. SO I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE FIGURED THIS OUT YET OR NOT BUT THE LAWRENCE ARMS ARE ONE OF THE BEST BANDS TO EVER GRACE THE FACE OF THE EARTH.&nbsp; OKAY MAYBE I'M JUST A WEE BIT BIASED BUT LETS JUST FACE IT, THEY KICK BUTT.&nbsp; AND EVEN MORE SO LIVE.&nbsp; THIS I KNOW.&nbsp; I SAW THEM BACK IN DECEMBER AT THE CREEPY CRAWL IN ST LOU.&nbsp; THEY WERE THERE WITH FEABLE WEINER (WOOHOO) AND A PICTUREBOOK OF SAINTS (ALSO A PRETTY GOOD BAND THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME I HEARD THEM AND THEY ARE PRETTY COOL GUYS THEY LET YOU LOOK AT THEIR JEWELRY WELL WE ONLY TALKED TO TOM AND DAVE BUT ANYWAYS&nbsp;THEY KINDA SOUND LIKE THURSDAY)&nbsp; BUT BACK TO THE LAWRENCE ARMS AND HOW GREAT THEY ARE.&nbsp; SO NOT ONLY ARE THEY SUPER TALENTED BUT THEY ARE ALL&nbsp;PRETTY EASY TO LOOK AT AND ARE ALSO PRETTY COOL GUYS.&nbsp; SO I HAVE AN AWESOME STORY INVOLVING THEM SO HERE IT GOES.&nbsp; SO IT WAS LIKE 2 WEEKS BEFORE MY BIRTHDAY AND I HAD DECIDED TO HAVE A LUAU AND MY MOM GETS THIS AWESOME IDEA.&nbsp; WHY DON'T WE SEE IF THE LAWRENCE ARMS WILL COME?&nbsp; SO WE BOTH EMAILED THEM AND I DIDN'T GET A RESPONSE I EVEN TRIED LURING THEM HERE WITH FREE FOOD AND CAKE BECAUSE WHO DOESN'T LOVE FOOD AND CAKE ESPECIALLY IF ITS FREE EXCEPT FOR MAYBE MARY KATE OLSEN.&nbsp; OHH HAHA I MADE FUNNY JOKE ANYWAYS.&nbsp; SO I WAS GETTING KIND OF DEPRESSED BECAUSE I COULDN'T GET AHOLD OF QUITE A FEW OF MY FRIENDS AND FOR SOME MY SUPER CLOSE FRIENDS WERE ACTING VERY STRANGE AROUND ME AND MY MOM WAS ALSO BEING VERY WEIRD AND SAYING SOMETHING ABOUT A SUPRISE AND IT SORTA FELT LIKE NOBODY WANTED ANYTHING TO DO WITH ME.&nbsp; BUT APPARENTLY MY MOM HAD SWORN THEM TO SECRECY AND ALTHOUGH THEY WERE UNABLE TO COME MY MOM HAD SOMETHING UP HER SLEEVE.&nbsp; SO ANYWAYS ITS LIKE 8:45 EVERYBODY WAS THERE AND WE HAD ALL EATEN SO WE WENT INSIDE FOR A FEW AND FOR SOME REASON WE ARE ALL JUST SITTING IN MY LIVING ROOM AND EVERYONE WAS JUST SORT OF STARING AT ME AND THEN THE PHONE RINGS AND ITS BRENDAN FROM THE LAWRENCE ARMS.&nbsp; OF COURSE BEING THE  IDIOT  I AM I DIDN'T BELIEVE HIM AT FIRST BECAUSE WELL I THOUGHT IT WAS LIKE SOMEONES COUSIN STEVE FROM IOWA.&nbsp; SO THEN MY MOM ATTEMPTS TO PUT HIM ON SPEAKER PHONE AND ACCIDENTLY HANGS UP BUT THEN HE CALLED BACK AND I&nbsp;ANSWERED IT ON SPEAKERPHONE BUT I COULD BARELY HEAR BECAUSE EVERYONE WAS&nbsp;LIKE PACKED AROUND ME BUT ANYWAYS IT WAS LIKE THE COOLEST THING EVER I WROTE THIS HUGE THANK YOU EMAIL LIKE TWO DAYS LATER AND SOMETIMES I STILL JUST LIKE SIT THERE AND GO LIKE "WOW BRENDAN KELLY FROM THE LAWRENCE ARMS CALLED ME TO SAY HAPPY BIRTHDAY HOW COOL IS THAT?" THIS WAS&nbsp;JUNE 27TH.&nbsp; I WENT TO TERRE HAUTE WITH TWO OF MY FRIENDS THE NEXT DAY WEARING A T SHIRT THAT SAID "BRENDAN KELLY CALLED ME TO SAY HAPPY BIRTHDAY"&nbsp; I DID THAT BECAUSE I AM A DORK I THINK BUT IT WAS KINDA COOL TO SEE PEOPLES REACTION BECAUSE THEY WERE LIKE WHO? BUT IT WAS COOL     SO YEAH THE LAWRENCE ARMS ROCK LIKE A LOT AND YOU SHOULD GO SEE THEM THEY ARE ON TOUR RIGHT NOW GO SEE THEM OR ELSE YOU WON'T GET A CHANCE FOR A LONG TIME AND YOU WILL HATE YOURSELF THAT WHOLE TIME.&nbsp; I'M GOING TO SEE THEM AT THE CREEPY CRAWL JULY 30TH.&nbsp; ONLY LIKE 8 MORE DAYS WOOHOO!!!!!!&nbsp; FOR MORE INFO ON THEM AND THEIR TOUR CHECK OUT THEIR WEBSITE     urlLink http://www.thelawrencearms.net      &nbsp;    &nbsp;   THIS IS A STRAIN FOR I AM DOING IT AS HARD AS I HAVE EVER DONE IT,&nbsp; TAGUE     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   P.S. DO YOU THINK THAT MAYBE I MIGHT HAVE SHAMELESSLY PROMOTED THEM A LITTLE TOO MUCH BECAUSE I DONT. &nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I realize that I have been sending lonely immigrants to my dear friend Jessi's blog but You will most likely not find the love of your life there.&nbsp; I also cannot find love for any angry lesbians as she said and I am sorry if you feel betrayed or mislead in any way.&nbsp; PS a certain horrid beast has been fired from CSI along with someone who may or may not be fired and lets just say that that is the root of the immigrant thing   &nbsp;  I love you all except for you (you know who you are), Tague  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So anyway&nbsp;I found this on the wall at the high school in Charleston Illinois.&nbsp; I know what you are thinking&nbsp; "She's totally lying to me."&nbsp; But would I lie to you?&nbsp; Well, yes but I promise I am not lying this time.&nbsp; So anyway here it is  .   &nbsp;      TROJAN UP!        TO ELEVATE ONES PERFORMANCE        TO COMPLETE THE TASK AT HAND.  
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       so i am pondering some of lifes little mysteries and if you think you know the answer email it to me at  urlLink TAGUESALOSER@truepunk.com  and maybe if your answer is good enough you win a prize.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  1. Seriously how much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood?&nbsp; Let's just say thatthis hypothetical woodchuck weighs thirteen pounds and has three hours to chuck all the firewood sized logs his little woodchuck heart desires?  &nbsp;  2. Why did the FDA approve a medication for&nbsp;arthritis, &nbsp; I think, if one of the possible side effects is tuberculosis?    &nbsp;  3.How can someone as gross and like deformed as Gwyneth Paltrow be allowed to be naked in movies?    &nbsp;  4.&nbsp;Why are they letting Juliette Lewis front a band because 1: she sucks&nbsp; 2: she isn't even like a reasonable facsimile of a human being and finally 3: ummm oh yeah thats right she sucks.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  well kids like i said if your answer is good enough you may just win a prize    &nbsp;  hey lookit lookit i'm devlin,&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; tague    &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       good morning sunshine and hello.&nbsp; note how i'm not even bothering with caps and grammar it is simply because i am lazy. so yeah umm as i mentioned under no likey i put the conservative punk people these people are mainly nick rizzuto and michale graves.&nbsp; this is because well first of all they are stupid hypocritical presumptious douchebags,&nbsp; if you have read the interview in alternative press you know what i am talking about.&nbsp; rizzuto just assumes that stiv bators of dead boys fame is on their side but&nbsp;stiv&nbsp;can't contest this because well he died in 1990 and he was creamated and snorted by several of this loved ones and even if&nbsp;he&nbsp;was a conservative&nbsp;he's been dead for 14 friggin years and a lot can change in 14 years.&nbsp; do they have any ides of how many people were conservative and now they aren't simply because of george w. bush?&nbsp; now that brings me to how rizzuto also claims they aren't urging people to vote bush but michale graves was been quoted as saying that if kerry is elected he will&nbsp;"help the enemies destroy us all"&nbsp;&nbsp;errrrrrrrrrrrr. i hate people like that if i have offended you with this too bad but my email address is  urlLink TAGUESALOSER@truepunk.com  if you want to argue with me or tell me i'm dumb or prove me wrong email me i'll get back to you&nbsp;&nbsp;stay tuned there is more to come&nbsp;&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So this is the first of what&nbsp;I hope will many posts.&nbsp; Just in case you don't know me and are curious I'll give a little information about myself.&nbsp; I'm Tague well my first name is Amanda but only like my parents, some of my teachers, and a few others call me that.&nbsp; Let's see what else is vital for you to know.&nbsp; I was born on the 27th of June in the year 1987.&nbsp; I live in Robinson IL.  Likey:  the lawrence arms, my pet mouse pepino, the fellowship aka the best friends in the world, buttons, chuck taylor high tops (the best shoes ever), law and order svu, the comedy lineup at adult swim,&nbsp;taking pictures, video games,&nbsp;lightening, and setting small contained fires simply for my own amusement. &nbsp;  No likey:  Dashboard Confessional,&nbsp;this town I live in, the movie The Pallbearer(possibly the worst movie ever made), getting suckered into going and doing the most retarded places and thing known to man, Juliette Lewis, the people at Conservative punk, George W. Bush and many many more. &nbsp; &nbsp; That's basic me info I hope to put up a site soon but it'll probably be away.   
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Remember about three posts ago when I said that things were beginning to look up? If you recall I also said it didn't look like the cat was going to die after all. Well my dad got home not that long ago from the vet. They had to put Travis down. He had a kidney and urinary tract infection and then he go pneumonia and he kept making this terrible noise because his lungs were full of fluid and infection. I just stopped crying so if you see me don't say anything because I'll probably start crying again and then you will feel bad because you will have made me cry. If I can get the disk to work I'll put a picture up on the Friends O Tague blog. That's it for now. I'm hella sad and it physically hurts like someone punched me in the stomach. I feel like I'm going to cry but now my eyes hurt because they are dry. I guess that teaches me a lesson about loving things that have a significantly shorter lifespan than I do. Also Adolf (aptly named because of her mustache, we aren't nazis, I hate nazis) one of our other cats keeps running around crying and going to the door because she thinks he's coming back. Travis was more of a mommy to her than her mother ever was and I don't know what she is going to do with out him.      Well I love you guys.      "I wish Lacee would turn into George Eads because then we could have sex."- Jessi to me on Lacee turning into George Eads., Tague       PS The Rock Against Bush Volume Two is out now it has been for almost a week. go buy it I don't remember who all is on it and my copy hasn't been delivered yet but its got an awesome Lawrence Arms song on it that is brand new. I heard it live July 30th, it rocked. Also, there is a free DVD with it. Even if you like bush the music is great so buy it now.  
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Lets see school is starting again in about 2 weeks and I couldn't be less thrilled. Oh well in May it will all be over until I got to college. Where and how and for what? I don't know. Perhaps the Tralfamadores do as they seem to know all since they are time travelers. If you've read Slaughter-house Five you'd know what I mean but if you haven't I'm not going to explain so you just have to got and read the book yourself it's great.      Anyways as i was saying. School. Don't want to go back. Hate it. Yeah so my schedule would be great if it didn't involve all the idiots and douchebags I will soon be forced to deal with once again.        1st Semester:      9:00-9:50 mwf Speech out at LTC.  (not bad at least I don't have to be at any classes until 9 instead of 8)      Art at RHS  (its on the 3rd floorstarts exactly at the same time that my LTC class ends hope the teacher doesn't care when I'm late 3 days a week)      Senior Home Ec  (with Jessi and I think Anna luckily not with all the preppy douchebags some of which have sex with the teachers)      Creative Expression  (a whole class devoted to creativity in all its form and its taught by Mrs. Ox who is great.)           All in all, it should be an easy semester. Two classes where I get to be the creative little weirdo that I am. One where I just have to talk in front of people and I have a big mouth so it shouldn't be a problem. Then there is Home Ec. It's really going to make me miss Josh a lot for we will have no cabin boy to abuse or play Naughty House Mormons with. I guess this class lets me create too. In regular home ec sophomore year, I don't think we ever followed the recipe right but our groups food always tasted the best and generally looked the most interesting or something that should not be in food was added in. Like the key we baked into our cake or well Josh's hacky sack ending up in the cake or the teal eggs and blue bacon. The scary thing is that Josh is now training to be a chef at some fancy steakhouse. I've cooked with that boy. I don't know how safe I'd feel eating at that steakhouse.                 Click on the link below for Armular.      urlLink http://www.myspace.com/index.cfm?fuseaction=viewImage&amp;friendID=2835790&imageID=17519345&amp;Mytoken=20040814124232          Oh Armular, how I do love thee so. I think maybe that it might be weird for me to be a wee bit obsessed with a fake Legolas from Simplicity Costume sewing pattern book. I really do just want to rip the back cover off that book so i can have Armular and do with him as I please. Seriously everyone should have a picture of Armular.      Anyways as usual more later.       All charades go on forever, Tague               
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Anyways yeah so some things have been on my mind lately and well now we have over 180 channels to kill that thinking part of my mind.  But anyways if you haven't figured this out yet it is friday the 13th and for once people didn't go rent all the copies of the Friday the 13th movies.  For once the people of this idiot town are not as predictable as they seem.  Oddly enough, there were several of the Halloween movies missing from the shelf.  Yeah so Jessi and I in our search for the best and worst old horror movies of all time rented The Witchery staring David Hasselhoff and Linda Blair which right now is my top pick for worst movie from the horror section I say from the horror section because well the Pallbearer is what I would call a horror movie because it features El Paltrow and the guy who played Ross on Friends.  That is what I would have to say is the worst movie of all time horror and otherwise.  Oh hell I'm getting off subject but anyways we also rented this movie called The Burning.  It has Fisher Stevens and Jason Alexander in it and you see both of their buttholes.  In the immmortal words of Napoleon Dynamite, GROSS!  I think it was made in 1980 and also features a killer named Cropsy.  Much better than The Witchery but by no means good.  Anyways I've been reading a lot lately.  This last week alone I've read Hocus Pocus and Slaughter House five(for the 21st time I think I've counted) both by the wonderful writer Kurt Vonnegut, A clockwork Orange(with the 21st chapter I might add which I didn't see why it was such a big deal), and A Modest Proposal by Jonathon Swift which I highly recommend.  It is about eating babies so if you find that offensive don't read it but I found it quite amusing. Oh and hers a treat for all of you.            Hey look its Armular.  Well if that doesn't show up I took a picture of him at Walmart today so I'll post it when I get it developed.      Anyways I'll post more later or you can find me at myspace.com a lot so yeah.      I'm like a carcrash you just can't keep from watching me happen, Tague  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So if you are wondering what I am doing, I am sitting here writing to you, writing a bit just in general, and browsing all the people on myspace.com. That's it. I'm kinda psyched now. We are getting sattilite(no way of spelling this looks right) TV back. Finally. Its been like 3 years on cable. Also the cable people are much more douchey than the sattilite people could ever dream of being. I really don't like cable. I think it might be because we got sattilite for the first time when I was like 5 and thats about when I started watching TV. Then we had it until I was like 14 when we moved into town and switched to cable. Also with sattilite you get like twice as many channels for like half the price. and the sattilite people are nice and not doucebags and don't break your VCR. Here's a tidbit of Tague trivia for you, the day we got sattilite TV hooked up for the first time was also the day I learned to ride a bike without training wheels.  Well thats about it for now as I am getting bored with writing this and I hope this one doesn't make anyone cry. I'm okay guys it's just that this is a depressing world and i was letting it get to me. Maybe I'll do something with this thing I;m writing afterall. Like maybe put it up in a blog of it's own or perhaps turn it into all those lyrics I've been trying to write but haven't known how. Well anyways I love you guys and have fun but not sex with Gwyneth Paltrow.      "Now you will put me in your mouth because I am Delicious!"- Jessi to various poor souls on the internet who have that Baxter song she wants, Tague     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well boys and girls I am still in a shitty mood so it would be in your best interest not to mess with me because I'll mess you up. Okay I probably won't mess you up because I am too lazy/depressed to do so since our cable is still off and I am left with nothing to do but read and listen to music. Both of those things make me think. Some of the best thinking I've ever done was in my car, back when it still worked, with the Lawrence Arms's album apathy and Exhaustion playing just driving around out in the country at like 11 o clock at night. but now my car doesn't work so I don't get to enjoy that luxury anymore. Anyways I don't really know what the hell it is I'mm talking about. Oh yeah I remember, I've been doing a lot of thinking lately and when I think a lot i tend to get depressed becausee I never think about happy things when I'm alone and there is no one to talk to. I generally think about life and the world which are two very depressing things. The upside to this is that I have been writing. A lot actually. It's all just sorta coming out weird right now. I just have like four pages of notebook paper with my thoughts written on them. I don't know what I will do with it though. It's just so weird the way it comes out. Sometimes it's sort of like I'm talking to the paper or whomever might eventually read it. Which at this point no one is going to except for me. Don't even ask. If you are reading this you are probably Jessi or Anna and guys I love you both and you are two of the very best friends the world has to offer but I really just don't like people to read my stuff and I don't trust anyone enough to let them read it. Chances are that everything I'll write will be burned in my kitchen sink or in my bedroom or I'll spit gum into it and throw it out the car window just like everything I've written since I was 14. I kinda regret that though because there were a few good lines and ideads that are now lost forever. I say good because they still make sense to me now even though they did get me in trouble with the guidance counselor in 9th grade. Since then I've been a lot more guarded in respect to what I write because well it generally changes peoples opinions of me or makes them think I'm weird and enough people think I'm weird as it is. I don't know what I'm going to do with it if I don't dispose of it. Anyways I'm rambling and the good news is that it looks like the cat isn't going to die after all.  Oh yeah that whole distress thing....  I have no clue what I am going to do with myself in five minutes from now much less a year from now or five years from now and people won't get off my ass about it, even though I have discovered that some of the best things I've ever done have been the spontaneous things.  Lazer tag, that came from a last minute idea after other plans fell through.  I think maybe I just want a little bit of direction.  What the hell should I do?      Do the otter dance, Tague  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay so the old photo album i had at like taguespictures.blogspot.com or whatever was not allowing me to use Hello Blogger bot any more so i have created a new one using the same account as my Larry Arms and Feable Weiner page.  It is now at  urlLink http://friendsotague.blogspot.com       Enjoy.      Ned me boy carry on the Kelly name,  Tague  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I got all my Lawrence Arms pictures up on  urlLink http://larryarmsfeableweiner.blogspot.com       ENJOY, Tague  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It really wasn't anything to spectacular.  Umm.  Yeah Jessi and watched a lot of movies.  I didn't play any video games or run about in my underwear.  The video games I just wasn't in a videogame mood.  The underwear on the other hand is because I didn't realize that my cousin would be home and that his friend would be there all the time so I wore pants all weekend and well to be honest except for the 12 hours I spent sleeping I wore the same pants.  Okay so I am still wearing these pants but i like them a lot even though they are falling apart.  Okay so we watched the new Ned Kelly.  The only good part was Orlando Bloom's attempt to be Irish.  Oh and the fact that he spoke Chinease and made a servant girl giggle with embarrassment.  We also watched Aladdin and casted the live action version.  The next day we watched The Stuff which is this great horror movie from the mid-80's about this product that comes from the center of the Earth and is sold as a yogurt like food and it takes over people and eats away their insides and makes them crave only the stuff.  Anyways i don't think it would have been near as good if The Stuff weren't a creamy white substance called The Stuff.  Then we watched the Jabba Forensic Files.  Then we tried to watch Ed Gein and fell asleep.  The next day we went to Taco Bell with Tanner and then went to see Collateral.  Ummmm.  Well if you like to watch people get shot by Tom Cruise than this movie is for you since that wasn't something I enjoy it was not for me and I got pissed off because some douchebag not only forgot to turn off his phone but answered it and began to carry on a conversation.  Not just any conversation though since it was an action movie the man had to talk very loudly for the man he was talking to to hear him over the shootings.  Yeah so anyways that was my weekend.       The taste that makes you come back for more... The Stuff,   Tague  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       OKAY I GOT MY BLACK AND WHITES BACK ON TUESDAY SO I AM ADDING THOSE AT THIS VERY MOMENT AND FOR THOSE OF YOU TOO LAZY TO SCROLL DOWN AND GET THE LINK THEY ARE AT  urlLink http://larryarmsfeableweiner.blogspot.com   IF THIS LINK IS WRONG THEN YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO SCROLL DOWN ANYWAYS.   MY MOM REALLY HATES THAT ONE OF ME AND CHRIS WHERE HE'S LOOKING AT ME AND WE'RE BOTH SMILING.  THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT NO ONE LOOKS LIKE AN EVIL DEAD WELL THERE IS ONE PICTURE OF NEIL WHERE HIS EYES LOOK COMPLETELY WHITE BUT UMMM YEAH.  ALSO WHILE JESSI AND I WERE IN TERRE HAUTE WE SAW NAPOLEON DYNAMITE AND WELL IT WAS PERHAPS THE FUNNIEST REAL MOVIE I'VE SEEN BESIDES WEEKEND AT BERNIES 2.  NOTE I SAID REAL MOVIE NOT CRAPPY GEORGE EADS EVEL KNEIVAL MOVIE JESS!  BUT ANYWAYS GO SEE IT ASAP.  TO SEE THE ADDED SCENE THOUGH YOU HAVE TO SIT THROUGH THE CREDITS.  THE THEATRE WE SAW IT AT WAS SORTA CRAPPY AND AS A RESULT THE HEADS WERE CUT OFF ALL THE CHARACTERS.  ALSO THE "DELICIOUS!" SCENE WAS NOT IN THE MOVIES. OH WELL I STILL LAUGHED A LOT AND  IT WAS GREAT ANYWAY AND I ALMOST PISSED MYSELF DURING NAPOLEON'S BIG DANCE NUMBER.  I WON'T GIVE ANYTHING ELSE AWAY.         OH AND IF YOU WERE WONDERING WHAT I WAS LIKE FROM  THE AGES OF 4-8 JUST IMAGINE NAPOLEON AND DEB HAVE A FEMALE BABY AND WELL.........  I REALLY WAS LIKE THAT,  I HAD VERY DEB-LIKE HAIR (YES, THERE WAS THE OCCASIONAL CRIMPING AND SIDEPONYTAIL ALONG WITH PIPPY LONGSTOCKING BRAIDS THAT ACTUALLY STOOD OUT), I THOUGHT I KNEW VARIOUS FORMS OF MARTIAL ARTS (THANK YOU POWER RANGERS), I REALLY LIKED NUNCHUCKS, I HAD A FEW DRESSES AROUND THE AGE OF 5 WITH BIG PUFFY SLEEVES, I DREW TONS OF UNICORNS AND OTHER HORSE-LIKE CREATURES WINGED AND OTHERWISE, I MADE KEYCHAINS AND VARIOUS OTHER TYPES OF CRAFTS AND ATTEMPTED TO SELL THEM ON MORE THAN ONE OCCASION, AND WELL I'M GOING TO STOP WITH THOSE DETAILS BECAUSE WELL THOSE WERE MORE THAN ENOUGH AND WELL I DON'T WANT TO LOWER YOUR ALEADY LOW OPINION OF ME.      IT'LL BE A FEW DAYS UNTILL I POST AGAIN BEAUSE MY PARENTS ARE LEAVING FOR A FEW DAYS AND I HAVE THE HOUSE TO MYSELF FOR THE MOST PART AND I'M GOING TO ENJOY THAT.  SO INSTEAD OF COMING HERE AND WRITING TO YOU I WILL BE AT  HOME IN MY UNDERPANTS DRINKING A BUNCH OF COFFE AND PLAYING VIDEO GAMES FOR 2 DAYS.  OH YEAH I THINK MAYBE JESSI IS SPENDING FRIDAY NIGHT SO I GUESS I'LL HAVE ON PANTS THAT NIGHT.      BIZARRO I LOVE YOU, TAGUE  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am about half way finished with getting all my pictures I wanted up online. As of know I have one spot where it is just friends and well there are 2 of Feable Weiner that are on the other one but I am only halfway done with one so if you do not find yourself don't be offened it's a work in progress. That address is   urlLink  http://taguespictures.blogspot.com   .  The other gallery i have up is devoted to Feable Weiner and the Lawrence Arms. I am going to add a lot more Lawrence Arms after I get my film developed which should be any day now. This address is   urlLink  http://larryarmsfeableweiner.blogspot.com     I do need to add the ones of me with Chris and Brendan from back in December but if you must see those I think they are up in my myspace.com photos. If you go there go into search and type in TAGUE it has to be in caps or i don't show up.  Maginot, maginot, maginot!, Tague     
    
</post>


</Blog>