<Blog>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my girl is  j .  i prefer to call her my girl.  she's there for me in ways i don't even ask for.  and i've only known her for a month.  but when i'm stressed she knows how to help me keep my head from coming undone.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i don't know the answer to that.   i can only think of bad things to come from letting myself blog.   it goes something like this...  i'm working 10 hrs a day, coming home to having only 3 hrs to take care of household chores, e-mail, bills..etc, leaving little time to actually wind down and spend time with  B .   now i feel distant and seperate from what my life was before (nothing to do BUT spend time with  B .  it used to drive him crazy.  but he's THOROUGHLY enjoying the time our lifestyles are lending him to spend alone. so am i actually.  even when we're in the same apartment together. don't get me wrong, i would sell my soul before letting him go.  we just seem to be enjoying our solitary states of mind right now.  this is all very familiar.  but i digress....  in my outer spaces i'm the happiest i've ever been.  but with such a seperate-feeling life, giving myself the chance to blurt out whatever i'm feeling, whenever i'm feeling it, so somebody or nobody or anybody can read it...  well, that would just be bad.  i would get addicted to it.  i would be up on a soapbox 24/7 with blogging fever and wouldn't know WHEN to shut up.  EVER.     my boss, who can never handle being wrong, taught or one up'd, (although, neither can i lol) would just lllOOOOOOve the soapbox, don'tcha think? :O)  i can't help myself.  when i'm into something, i'm into it and live with blinders on until i'm on to the next thing.  so back to the question,...  why blog?  or for that matter, why eat that cake? why smoke that bowl?  (i think we just answered the cake question.) why do anything that you know is going to ..damage you?  anyway, let's see what happens. 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for my first post i will copy and paste an e-mail i just sent to someone.  i'm a little compulsive about reading over e-mails that i just sent and when i read this one, i wanted to record it so i could go back to it when i needed to.  ..so here i am blogging.  "hey cutie!!!  how are you?      things in GA are good.  i'm all moved into my new apartment with bill.  it's a small one bedroom and i think my mom's basement was bigger than it but i love it here.  it's been a long time since i've felt having and paying my own bills to be a privledge.  i'm working for a different chiropractor now.  they started me at a great salary so i don't stress about money anymore.  now i just stress about losing my job (so i wont lose the money lol).   i don't think they've given thought one to firing me.   it's just how i get when i have something i think i am beneith.  you'd never know it from how i act there tho.  too comfortable lol.    have you ever heard of VAX-D?   it's a spinal decompression thing.  we do that there.   i get it done too.  i actually went in for my first exam with my resume cuz i knew they were hiring. seems to be the right thing for me for now.  i've made friends with the girl i work with in the office.  she's one of the most normal females i've met since i've moved to atl.     hmmmmmm..  what else has been going on?...  oh yeah, i turned 34 (pronounced thirty FUCKING FOUR!!!!!) a couple of weeks ago lol.  not too happy about that really.  but i had a great b-day.  it just seemed that everyone really made a big deal over me in lots of little ways.   normal thoughtful ways.  my other gf in atl., (she's sort of normal for a jew from NYC like me lol) and her husband took us out to a nice dinner then we strolled thru the small town center and window shopped, browsed a small art gallery... , a few days later my mom took us out for dinner and pool (that was my idea lol), i came home from work on my actual b-day to find that bill had covered the ceiling with helium balloons and ran me a tub with rose pedals...   it was nice.       things are good in GA :0)   ...."    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was a pain in the ass.&nbsp; literally.&nbsp; my piriformus muscle, located basically in my butt, has been A PAIN IN THE ASS ALL FREAKIN' DAY!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; makes it difficult to sit for long periods of time.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp; i am of course dealing with the 'secretary spread' already, so my pain has lots of ground to cover. &nbsp; &nbsp; my bosses went away starting today.&nbsp;&nbsp; and everything that could go wrong, did.&nbsp; hello murphy, how are you? &nbsp; i have realized why people decide to give up their possesions.&nbsp;&nbsp; have you ever thought about the word possession?&nbsp;&nbsp; possess.&nbsp;&nbsp; it doesn't sound good.&nbsp;&nbsp; it sounds greedy, narcissistic, .....affected.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp; i am AFFECTED.&nbsp; i love my STUFF.&nbsp;&nbsp; but i have to go through hell to get to it.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; is it worth it?&nbsp; i dunno.&nbsp; i'm having a bad day.&nbsp; feeling unsure of my job, insecure, fat, ugly...and so the cycle starts.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; let's see where it goes.&nbsp;&nbsp; if i have a good day tomorrow, i might feel like the ultra-mighty modern-day yuppie i feel like i'm becomming.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; i think i drove  j  crazy today.&nbsp;&nbsp; she did make my butt feel better for awhile but the pain came back.&nbsp; it's back again.&nbsp; she will have to work on me before we leave today.&nbsp; at least we get to leave early.&nbsp;&nbsp; i am not touching the insurance payments until tomorrow when i hopefully stand a chance of not royally screwing things up.&nbsp;  &nbsp; i'm going home. 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the apartment is a mess.  i have to clean it tonight.   and tomorrow i get to quit smoking?  maybe.    i need a vacation.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i almost called in sick today.  would've been my first time since i started this job just over a month ago.   glad i didn't.  the bosses are going away for a week starting tomorrow and they would've flipped thinking that i wouldn't be able to come in while they are gone.   but who knows.  my tonsils feel like golf balls, dimples and all.   i better go get that prescription filled that i've had sitting at the pharmacy for 8 months.   ...sigh.  i wanna go back to sleep.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "just because someone paints an arrow, doesn't mean they know where the hell they're going".....    the voice in B's head when he sleeps. 
    
</post>


</Blog>