<Blog>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to my cousin’s funeral. Her name is Maria. I never met her and I never met almost anyone there but there all are my family. I met my great uncle Agusto, My grandfather’s brother. He had gray eyes. My family genes include a whole bunch of different colored eyes like gray, blue, green, and brown.  Anyway I felt a little odd meeting all these people but it was nice to know hey this my cousins. But like always there either too old or too young for me to approach them. A couple of cousins were crying. No one really knew me and if I had to introduce myself it had to be: The son of my grandfather’s daughter. Why you ask? Well people only knew you as the head of the family, example some of my cousins introduced themselves as kids of other people who are more above in the family tree which I call the heads. My grandfather and his siblings, which are about ten and they had about ten more kids. Just imagine how many kids that is. This was my mom’s father’s family. Yes complex like any other family tree. I never knew this side but I was part of it. I knew my mom’s mother side I’m always with them. I know my father’s father’s family and I even know my father’s mother’s side but never my mother’s father’s side until know. Zapata, Cepeda, Escoto, and Henriques that’s what I am. Later we went to Charro’s place. (Charro is a girl; it’s some weird nickname.) They made a lot of food but we already ate. So they drank coffee, smoked cigarettes and talked. Leytta is a family favorite. Martha’s introduced her to everybody already and beside Leytta’s pretty so it all works out. I came with a nice sense of the people that no matter what I’m a part of. I’m really happy that I met my great uncle Agusto, because he’s my only connection to my grandfather since my grandfather died two years ago and I never met him. Well I met him when I was so little that I don’t remember.  Rest In Peace Maria HenriquesMy beloved cousins whom I would of loved to meet for her charm and loving attitude. The heavens will accept you with out a doubt. Because that is where god wants you 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Black Eyed Peas Song: Lets Get It Started Rating: 5 out of 5 Comments: I just love this song it makes me want to dance but I bet you didn’t know that it’s original name is “Lets get retarded” and instead of saying “It started” they say “retarded” they probably did that for the video and radio edit. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Ashlee Simpson Song: Unreachable Rating: 4.5 out of 5 Comments: I really like this song it’s has a really nice guitars and nice drums but with a sad medley and nice vocals. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came from Kevin’s house right now and my mom I think didn’t expect me because she locked the door and she also asked me what time I would be back, I really was unexpected sorry to crash your party. The guy who calls my mom is here at this moment. It’s all. All right I like him for her. I wish they wouldn’t be so shh shh about it. But what can I do? Anyway the guy doesn’t look me in the eye. He thinks I don’t like him, which I didn’t but he’s All right now. I feel so excited for my mom. Maybe there are just friends but I’m not sure what they are. I still think it’s all exciting. I like the idea of being a group of three. Anyway I ordered lasagna. I’ll be all right for now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I slept over at Wanfi’s house yesterday and Helen woke me up and we had to go to my house. But of course there were other stops then home. But on the way there Helen talked about Tarah. I know some things but I don’t know what Tarah feels if I know. Did she want me to know? She didn’t mention it. So you I know. I wish Tarah would of told me but all right. &nbsp;I went to the dentist office today and in two weeks my braces comes off. I’m so happy. Today they broke the metal things that were on the top back teeth. Drilled those babies right off. And broke the teeth guard on the back of the front teeth. Then I had to get a new imprint. This means tasteless pink stuff pushed on your teeth to make a make this way they can make a retainer. Good thing this time it was only on the top teeth. My mom and me went to Bedford café and ate club sandwiches. (Yummy) then we crossed the street to the supermarket. When we got home my I decided to choose my clothes for Walt Disney. I have a nice luggage. 7 shirts 5 pant 5 boxers 1 sneakers 1 sandals 1 bathing suit. That’s about it. Since my mom doesn’t let me put on new clothes until the trip she noticed she had too much clothes so I can put clothes I’m not taking with me. Crappy thing Michael left today to Florida. I mean he could have lived here but he rather roams free in Florida. I talked to Jessica today she’s really annoying me, I’m not calling her anymore. I talked to Kristina today instead. I miss talking to Kristina, her and her boyfriend and their problems. Not really problems but anyway we talked for a long time mostly about nothing but it wax nice. She’s leaving to D.R. Monday and she’s a little afraid of planes and turbulences and this is beside the point she doesn’t want to leave her boyfriend but he’s going over there too so I don’t see what’s the problem. I really like Tarah and I’m telling her in an email. I think she likes me too 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After the long wait. (O.K I wasn't really waiting but)    I got Ashlee Simpson's Cd Autobiography! 
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today I had an appointment and it went fine last time I had to get (naked) now play the drum music. Anyway It went fine I was told I had a odd heart beat that went ta dum ta dum ta dum ta (whistle) dum. But he said it normal for adolescents. So I'm alright. Anyway I need to get a blood test tomorrow ad I'll be fine. I went to Michaels house today (both actually) and here I'm, typing. I post my story it's forty pages. And well i guess my blogger lookers can see it. I'll post it in four sections. 10 pages each just to leave you wanting more. (well it's not great but I think it's o.k) anyway my highlight of my day&nbsp;I got an Email from Tarah. I'll make sure to keep in touch. with her.     !Happy Birthday Kevin!  
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and My cousins (Micheal, amanda, Quenia, and her boyfriend Randy) went to six flags. first we went to the superman ride after being split up me micheal and the rest. I found Audriana, her sister, her cousin, her mom, her father, kevin, amanda, randy, and quenia all in one ride at the same time and trust me this was not planned or even expected. but it was good. Now time for my ride review!   Superman    Time waiting: 1 hr and a 1/2     Fun:4/5  Fast:5/5 Puke Factor:3/5 (the lower the better) Coftablity: -2/5 (and why you ack I got a cramp and it hurt really bad) Notes : Good and fun hate the lines    Scream Machine   Time waiting: 1/2 hour  Fun:3/5 Fast:3/5 Puke Factor:1/5 Coftablity:3/5 Notes: It's allright but really I won't go on it twice...   Nitro   Time Wating: 40 minutes (we had fast passes by now)  Fun:5/5 Fast:5/5 Puke Factor:1/5 Coftablity:4/5 Notes: This one is the best ride and trust me we went back for more! It's really good I mean  good.  Best ride ever.   Skull Mountian   Time Waiting: 7 minutes (This was a fast pass thing)  Fun:4/5 Fast:4/5 Puke Factor:2/5 Coftablity:2/5 Notes: besides the fact that this ride is just dark and that I had to run from nitro to get there it was alright   Batman the ride   Time waiting: 55 minutes  Fun:3/5 Fast:5/5 Puke Factor:4/5 Coftablity:2/5 Notes: I got a horrible headache after this ride it's alright just let this one go and try chiller.  We later saw a show Batman Catfight.   Batman:Catfight   Time Waiting: at 7 pm  Fun:5/5 Fast: well it's not a ride Puke Factor:alright I should just cchange my system  New System  Time Waiting: at 7pm Fun:5/5 Realisim:3/5 (They really weren't hitting each other.) Action:5/5 Eye Candy:4/5 (So many things happeing at once) Notes: I thought it was good especially the begging I won't tell because that destroys the intro but they were lip syncing.  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;I went to Ivan and Sara’s House last night and well today we went Belmonte. (It’s some beach that’s in jersey but it’s kind of far.) Let me tell you what happened in the ride there. First we were riding relaxing and I’m looking to the right and there is these two white guys listing to Lloyd Banks “Fire” and they’re really into it. Moving there body with it but it was so funny because they act so ghetto but in such an “well you live in your mother’s house and have two cars but still” ghetto way. It’s hard to explain let’s just say anyone else would not do that like them. I start to stare and then move my body down and start laughing. They get pissed and stop doing it. Second we were almost there and Ivan’s talking about his job. Ivan does something do to with moving boxes and organizing and stocking I’m not exactly sure anyway he works with inmates. Well not with inmates but at the end what he piles and moves goes to inmates. And then the radio goes “locked up” we all start laughing. Anyway we get there and we walk a bit. The place is about 3.5 miles long one way. We walk to some point and then Ivan goes by himself and runs in both directions, 7 miles or more. Sara and me go to subway, which is right there, and order sandwiches. Then we take a quick seven eleven grab and get drinks. We hang around the car but every time we were next to the car someone would ask for parking. So we sat in a bench. Sara had to pee and right and that moment Ivan just comes back. We go get tickets to et in the beach. And we chill for a while and eat. There were a lot of condo’s and nice houses. Anyway later we decide to go in the water. It was really wavy. Sara couldn’t go in because well you know why. She’s pregnant. (Oh yeah that’s the pregnant woman from the title duh) anyway Ivan and me got in. the wave’s were so much fun. It would come and we would have to swim away fast it was great. Sometimes we just let it hit us but sometimes they were so big you had to run. After we went back and talked relaxed got tanned and we were deciding what to do but we just decided to go back because it started to rain. I have to admit this was really fun and would die to do it again, even just the same thing all over. (Well I’d prefer just going again) Sara wants to name the baby Nathaniel if it’s a boy and Ivana if it’s a girl. They don’t exactly know if it is a girl or boy. I really don’t mind what the baby is but Sara said that Elaine had a boy then a girl and so did Ariel. This trend might just happen again. Crappy thing though is that Nathaniel or Ivan is going to be young compare to the rest but the baby always get the most love so its not that bad. I’m really happy for the grandkids though because they have 5 first cousins and if they have another one and Iseli have one that’s 7 first cousins. That would be so cool. I have two first cousins. The L’s Leytta and Lana. Bad thing though is that I’m so old compare to them. Leytta is 6 and Lana 6 months but that’s not so bad you get to have small baby cousins. Well when we went back to the house we watched some TV and my godmother called and it she said she was going to take me home in the morning and had to be there by tonight. I left Ivan’s house kind of sad that we didn’t spend more time with him and Sara but I guess it was back to my world. Well I got there I learned we were leaving tonight just because of traffic. Nikki, Her dad and my godmother took me home. We bought pizza on the way back. I noticed something though. When I was in Ivan’s house he said that in his mom’s house that there was too much greasy food. And my godmother said that they don’t eat much. I’m sorry I don’t know who’s side I’m on here because my godmother does it wrong but Ivan eats much healthier. O.K I got Ivan’s side. When I got home I said hello to my room. My dad left me some shoes. There is Nike Tennis with deep green color on the side. Thanks Dad. My mom had finished her butterfly puzzle, which it’s oddly shaped like a butterfly. I’m happy to be home. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a stomach ache and man it's horrible. I'm just little stressed out. Erik is (pause) really a tough kid deal with... He's only six but damn I hope I wasn't that annoying when I was young I mean he's not that bad but sometimes I can't stand him. Anyway I love Ashlee Simpson there I said it. I'm buying her CD when it comes out July 20. I saw the show and man it's a great idea for promoting herself. I already have an idea of which songs she is going to make singles. First "Pieces Of Me"&nbsp; then "Shadow" and finally "Autobiography".&nbsp; We're going to this water park place today and tomorrow I'm going with Ivan and Sara to the mall or beach who knows. (But they are Beach freaks so..) Now that I think about it Duke did a hole bunch of songs for Freq games. He did about 10. That's about 10/55. (you do the math on the percent) Anyway I was thinking about Terrah. I think destiny showed me her and was thinking "Here Steven here's someone who doesn't like the same music as you doesn't have to many things in common but this is the person you will like" and man it worked. Destiny is grinning saying "There you go, you're likeable you don't need Jessica" and I agree. It was only about four days or so but I really liked her. (I mean I  really liked her)    We ended up going to the pool anyway. I was relaxed and got my swimming skills back (Somewhat) anyway later we went home took baths and got ready to go to Keysburg it's a fair like place. Me and my cousin Nicole rode all the good ones but she didn't want to ride the one in which you fly up and tit takes you back down really fast. Anyway by then she was sick. There was a arcade there and there were some really craze DDR (Dance Dance revolution)&nbsp;fans. I'm trying to say a gay guy with extensions a midget with a amazing DDR skill and a freaks tall guy with a funny laugh. I didn't play DDR I really want to but it's fine. I met this girl on the last ride I didn't want to ride by myself&nbsp; so I got to sit next to two girls. She told her friend on the way up the ride the second time. "I like him more than then the other guy we met" we were on the Power Ride and if was just a little loose you'd fly over. It was fun but it made me a little home sick. It reminded me of my friends. I wanted to be there with my friends.&nbsp; I imagined what my friends would say.  I'm in Ivan/sara's house now and we're going to the beach tomorrow.        
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         They upgraded the blogger tools and now it's even better!        &nbsp;   Well first I awoke and watched "Real World S**T they should of shown" for the thrid time. Today nothing was planned&nbsp;which was good. We ended up going&nbsp;for a ride around the car. We went to a lawers office to thank her for getting my&nbsp;uncle papers and got mcdonalds. This Mikki D was new and&nbsp;the bathrooms were clean. I ate a ten piece chicken mc nugget meal with some lemonade. (Minute Maid of cource). Getting there was a blur since i was sleepy and needed to pee. Anyway when er got back I got on the computer and registerd myself to Ashlee Simpsons&nbsp;website. (She's hot) My&nbsp;cousins I&nbsp;have no clue what they were doing but i was looking&nbsp;some sex info on the net. I like this site they give reliable facts and answer guestions. It was  urlLink  www.teenwire.com     .&nbsp; I went downstairs I became a kid again. I played with my cousins&nbsp;for a while then my cousin's neighbor&nbsp;told me his computer was&nbsp;going slow. I went there and twicked it a&nbsp;little to try to fix it. It's a great computer&nbsp;it's just really slow. First to many downloaded crap. (You now click here free download crap)&nbsp;It has great&nbsp;hard drive but it needs a faster DDR. I guessed it was 256 and i was right he needs at lease 512. &nbsp;      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I left around nine and went to play a good old fasion cops and robber.     &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink "Lamb Gabriel (Symbion Project Remix)" Symbion Project   urlLink "Synthesized" Symbion Project  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello    Here is another version. I'll use this one for my profile since the other one looks blurry
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is the beat cartoon picture of myself I could get cool huh?  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://illustmaker.abi-station.com/index_en.shtml 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some bands I like:   urlLink www.freezepop.com    urlLink www.garbage.com    urlLink www.symbionproject.com    urlLink www.ladytron.com    urlLink www.lifestyleland.com    This is where I get my amplitude remixes:   urlLink www.freqremixes.com    some Bloggers I like to check out:   urlLink http://standingonthebox.blogspot.com/    urlLink http://www.bizstone.com/   &nbsp; some other links:  urlLink www.teenwire.com     
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I woke up at around nine I think. We went to Chukie Cheese today (not my favorite place I prefer a place with DDR) I was with my cousin Nikki, My Godmother, Elaine, Erik, Brianna. I had my 360 song CD in my CD player and was looking at my CD's auto ranking and it showed me this: 1."I Love You" Faith Evans 2."Stupid Girl (Techno Remix)" Garbage 3."Bills, Bills, Bills" Destiny's Child 4."Breath" Finkl 5."You know" ???: It's the song that Overnight Celebrity stole the beats from 6."Can You Keep A Secret?" Utada Hikaru 7."Everytime I Look" Blink 182 :I'm not sure on the title but it's the song in American Pie 8."Bomb" Kim Hung Yung 9."Queer" Garbage 10."Excuse Me Mr." No Doubt  Anyway after we left chukie cheese and thought man it's hot lets go to the pool. It's been raining all week and the sight of the sun was a beautiful thing. So we went home, changed and went to the pool. Bad luck strikes revenge! The pool had a dead rat in it. The pool staff took it out and threw it away. There was nobody there since most people come only on weekends. We still got in. (Yes in the rat pool.) but let me tell you that it was really cold! But after you wither in it you get use to it.   Bad Lucks not done.  After about an hour and a half it starts to cloud up but good thing we were on the way out. We went home and my cousins friend/neighbor came over. Her names Karina. I think my cousin is really mean to her but I try to tell her not to be so mean and i asked her why doesn't she like her she tells me "She's one year younger than me" I say "well my best friend is three years older than me." she looks away. Oh well i tried right? Then later they get bored so they want me to make a game. I make up a time challenge game with me as a dark voiced host. They had to find three items one was a cellphone, a baby doll, and a spongebob ball. They had 2 minutes to find them. I asked them if they want me to go easy or hard they said hard so that is what they got. Nikki found one item and ran out of time. karina found two items and ran out of time. Erik did the same as Nikki so i had to make a tie breaker. Erik won by finding one item in plain site in 27 seconds. Then I made them spot multiple items of certain colors in the basement and because nikki lost she had to up the stairs. (Not really I just said that with the dark voice) Karina won she had to find 8 Purple items, 12 black items, 6 blue items and 55 green,pink and gray items in 2:34:04 (minutes,seconds,milliseconds) minutes. They got bored again and decided to rent a game. They rented Lilo And Stich for PS and then went to dunking donuts. (really in NJ your always hungry  unlike in NY I was never hungry like this all I want is water in NY but in NJ it's food and juice...) I bought the new caramel swirl latte with two French crullers and said latte like ladday. The caramel latte was fine maybe it's because I'm not hooked on Coffee...   I like it here in NJ (and not just the fact of DSL internet) I feel more cofmtable than the city. It's surburban and calm but you need a car to go any where. I like just being in a house, but don't get me wrong I don't want to move here or anything but it was nice just being somewhere different for a while. Oh yeah   my mom passed the drivers test!!!!!!!!    finally she gets a car and I can drive it yeah hurray. O.k enough excitement.  I got the picture with me and terrah. It's a nice picture except that i got headphones around my neck...(I forgot...) man I was really happy in that picture. Terrah why do you live in Canada?
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today's was a long day. First I ate some Cinnamon Roll things damn they're good (I'm going to be fat...) anyway I later I took a bath to go to the mall. I went to my second home. Hot Topic. I'm thinking of buying a wallet maybe the Nintendo one or the three chain one who knows.  Second we went to the Skating place YMCA. (Trust me their are a lot of those everywhere including NY) I had fun for the only hour that we (me and my cousin) we're there. And they have Dance Dance Revoultion there for two tokens. Tokens are four for a dollar so it's only 50 cents can you believe that, in NY it's 1.00 to 1.50 what a rip off in the City. I haven't skate in a while but I picked up quick and got skating away with only two falls! (This one is a record) the first fall was me trying to avoid a kid. (There was some summer camp there) and the second time I made a sharp turn. (but the fall was fun) and by the end I already mastered the skates once more and was going preety fast and as good as some of the people that worked there.  Thrid We came back ang started downloaded some music and then thought about the Freezepop Remix Contest and I started to look for the Sony Acid to download but all I got was a demo but it was fun I'll buy it later.  Lastly I played outside with some neighbors (see this is what I mean by the oldest of the youngest and the youngest of the oldest it's really an advantage) I got tired and started to play with Acid program for about two hours and that was my day.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listen to this freezepop song  urlLink Plastic Stars . I just love this song so listen to it.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well What um did I do?...Ph yeah I slept late so give me some time to recuperate.           I woke up at 9 or so and well I was at my cousins house and they woke up because there was thunder but I didn't remember so it doesn't matter what did matter was that it was raining and it is going to rain the entire week. (Bad luck just likes me). Anyway I tried that spongebob game with the nose as the controler. And then found Final Fantasy 7 and noticed that those graphics are so bad after looking at the recent Final Fantasies. (Man they don't even play it they should give it to me... I feel bad for the game... it wants to be played) well it was fine anyway...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm in the Great Garden state of New Jersey. My cousin's house right now. My summer has been normally boring but now I see the light called not-boredom. We're going to go to the pool later this week. hey Maybe I'll get a tan.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got pictures to work!   urlLink    Here's My Cousin Ellaine. (Dazzeling!!)&nbsp; urlLink     
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I knew about Garbage for a while but I wasn’t addicted yet. Then amplitude came out (Sequel game to Frequency) and I got more interested in all the artist in the game but garbage had something more appealing (I don’t remember exactly) anyway I went to their site and got quickly hooked. Then I was in Sam Goody and their was Beautifulgarbage and I thought what the hell. And bought it and loved it. Later I got more into old garbage songs and I liked them even better. (The old songs are great!). Garbage is making a new album working title “Hands On A Hard Body” I’m defiantly buying that when it hits stores.  Here's A Pic Of Garbage   urlLink     &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just graduated from middle school and these are my final grades: English: 94 Social Studies: 98 Math A: 92 Earth Science: 97 Music: 95 Physical Edu: 90 FINAL: 94.3  I’m in an advanced class and I took the regents this is what I got: Math A: 87 (The highest score in my class was 97) Earth Science: 79 (Highest Score In my class)   State Test Scores: (these go by 1-4) three being good and four being great English 3 Math 4  The Awards I got this year are the following: Certificate of achievement In Academic Excellence in 03-04 Certificate of recognition In Science Certificate of recognition for excellence in English Membership for Arista Society Certificate of award Betsy Gotbaum Award (oh this one’s fancy)   And of course there was a diploma but you can imagine what that’s like 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Nirvana Song: Smells Like Teen Sprit Rating: 4.4 out of 5 Comments: One of my favorite Nirvana songs and one of their best songs. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I heard about Freezepop first in Frequency and fell in love with their electronic song “Science Genius Girl”. On the game frequency I would play their songs so many times and eventually went to their site and heard other great synth-pop songs. I emailed them and they responded (I was so happy that day!) I still have that email copied to a word file. I continued to hear more of their music and downloaded some. (Sorry Freezepop…). I always want to buy their CDs but they’re hard to find. (They’re in an Indie Label) I’ll order them eventually  Here's A Picture Of Them!    urlLink     &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Freezepop Song: Bike Thief Rating: 5 out of 5 Comments: It’s really a five not because I’m a Freezepop fan. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Listening to: Utada Hikaru Song: Deep River Rating: 4.5 out of 5 Comments: Its soothing sounds are great and peaceful. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (My Best friend) Kevin’s Birthday is on the 21 of this month. He made a list of games he wanted and he left it in my house. I got to get him something. Here’s the list  -Legend of Zelda. The Wind Waker -Onimusha 3: Demon Siege -Resident Evil Outbreak -Onimusha Blade Warriors  -Max Payne 2: The Fall Of Max Payne   -Dead Or Alive Xtreme Beach Volleyball  -Project Gotham Racing 2 -Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles -DDR -DDR Konamix -DDR Disney mix -DDR Ultra Mix  The ones I highlighted in are the ones I might buy for him. Only one not all…  I’m leaning towards an Xbox Game 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From: fanmail@freezepop.net  View Contact Details   To: "Steven Zapata"    Subject: Re: I can't find Ultra Funky Fresh...  Date: Fri, 9 Jul 2004 22:33:10 -0400        Hey Steven,  Yeah, I doubt any big record stores are going to be carrying our CDs  since  we're just a little indie band. Your best bet would be to order it from  our site  (you can always mail-order it if you don't want to do the PayPal  thing), or if  you know of a record store that's a bit smaller, you can ask them to  special- order our CD from our distributor, Darla.  And yes, the Duke is Symbion Project.  cheers, Liz E.  ------------------------------------------------------------------ Well freezepop didn't let me waiting for long and they E-mailed right back. Only problem is this CD maybe I'll money order... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cousin's name is Lana. She's about 6 months old and she is so cute. Anyway today was her baptism. She cried when they put water on her head but then she fell asleep which was good because we were able to take pictures without her crying. We took a lot of pictures (digital of course...) and then we went to the reception it's real close so no worry. They played a bunch of old music but it soon got better and I danced. I talked to Terrah the most. She's really cool. Some of the little kids were annoying and I locked one in a room. (Well he started to cry and had to let him go, but you don't know what he did so don't go cussing me out, o.k I'm sorry...) Well he started saying perverted things and being a pain for a nine year old... Anyway.        Well I continued to talk to Terrah she's actually really nice. (My friend will kill me for using "nice") and well I like her ..........But she lives in the great  Canada!  well there's not much I can do about that. But it was nice to know that I could like again after the 2001-2004 tragedies. I'll get more into detail later about what I'm trying to say.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    O.K this is Plural who sang a song in the Ampltiude game called "Cool Baby" Now I love that song and Plural looks nice in the game but this picture she looks like a hooker&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ------------------------------------------------------------------------Date: Sun, 4 Jul 2004 12:59:40 -0700 (PDT)  From: "Steven Zapata"    View Contact Details   Subject: I can't find Ultra Funky Fresh...  To: fanmail@freezepop.net        Dear Liz,  It's zapata2424. (I doubt you remember...) anyway I want to but ultra funky fresh but i can't order it and i've tried to find it on tower records but so far no luck...   Do you know where i can buy your cd without having to order it?                                Your fan for ever and ever and ever,                                                     steven zapata   P.S I loved the sampler! and If you could, could you put my new  email on the mailing list. garbagefan2424@yahoo.com (i tried putting freezepopfan2424 but it din't work...) oh just one more thing is Duke also symbian project? ------------------------------------------------------------------------ well this is my first email i'll share if you want to learn about Freezepop go to  urlLink www.freezepop.com  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm posting my Emails for you to read so far i sent one to freezepop.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spelled my name wrong somewhere on the main page and i tried fixing it in the Profile but no luck... it's  Steven Zapata 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I made this Blogger so I can Convey thoughts and meet people. So Hiya rest of the Blog community!
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I started my Blog. (What you’re reading right now). I’ve decided to tell limited amount of people that I started a Blog just people I won’t see again and a couple of my in touch friends that way they now what's up with me when we’re not in touch 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mom found a person who teaches music.  I called her today. Her name is Lori. She lives near my house and it is really cool to learn how to play keyboards and violin. I told her my name. She a little expensive but music lessons is expensive. She sounds really cool and she knows to play everything and teaches various things. Anyway here are her rates: 	Musical Instruments: 	1 Hour		$35 	10 Hour	$300 	350 Hour	$350  I asked about multi learning like Violin and keyboards but I wonder if I can just learn both for one month. Now I’m hooked on it and I want to learn so badly! I hope this works out…  I’m calling Lori back at around seven. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I was still in my uncle’s house today. I played with my cousin. Her name is Lana and she’s six months old. Wanfi got a new computer and I’ve been copying all my CDs to Atrac 3 plus format to fit lots of songs in one MP3 CD. I ate two croissants with some orange passion fruit juice. (Yummy). The tourist wanted to go to the Bronx Zoo, which is a small walk from where we were. I got ready and talked to Terrah and her mom. Her mom is so different from her daughter. On Sunday she passed some man who was smoking a cigar. She went saying “BAD BAD BREATH, BAD BREATH, BAD BREATH” and the man wasn’t even that far ahead. He kept looking at the group. Helen told me that they were thinking that the man might throw them something or follow them. Well none of that happened… 	When we left the Bronx Zoo we came with seven and left with six. Josephine was upset and tried and took a shortcut. (Not really a shortcut but whatever) she got home later that day and we went to palisades mall. We didn’t buy much it was more for the tourist. I really like Steve & Barry’s I mean not as much as I like Aeropostale. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did nothing much today. The tourist left real early I reckon (Maybe you got that…) anyway I stood in Wanfi base and hung around. We went to Costco I think that’s how it spelled and well did nothing interesting. Later that day the tourist arrived. (Drum roll please). I talked to Terrah some more and then went to sleep. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to my uncle’s house. There were tourist there from Canada my aunts family. Let me describe them. Josephine is the oldest. She’s quiet and well intellectual. Her husband is Rowdell. (I think that’s it’s spelled…) He’s a web designer. Their kid is Robert he’s like an anime with funny impressions and Josephine’s sister is Rosy. She is really funny. I’ll tell you some of the things she does later. Her daughter name is Terrah. (Say it like Terra from FF5) She’s really different. Quiet and fun. On Monday we went to Liberty Island. (Where the statue of Liberty is) We couldn’t go upstairs to the crown but I still had fun. (I’ll post pictures later). I tried talking to Terrah during the boat ride there she’s quiet. It was my first long boat ride. I had been on boat rides but there weren’t that long. That night in my aunt/uncle’s apt I tried talking to Terrah. We talked and told stories she’s really cool. I kind of like her but I don’t know + she’s leaving on the sixteen of this month. So forget about it 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today I didn’t do much. You know listen to music, play games and work on my RPG maker game. But really that’s all I did. I talked to Jessica yesterday we really haven’t been talking. She’s mad at me and well I let her be for a couple of days I don’t think she wants me as her friend, I called her earlier today she said she’ll call me back so I’m not planning to call her back and I think she won’t call back. Jessica and my cousin Michael (garbagefanscus.com) are talking and I think he likes her. I mean not in love with her but I just fell badly because I don’t want him to waste his time on her because she’s not worth his time. It’s hard to explain but it won’t work. (Or so I think). On much better news, I told Tarah I like her. (Crappy though since she lives in Canada) but I don’t know if she likes me back. Oh one more thing for people who read my Blogger feel free to send me email too but just label something like “After I read your Blogger I started to hate the color tea green autumn” something that let’s me know that you’re a reader. Which just to let you know there’s not a lot of you’s (yes improper grammar) but hey I want to know what you think. Give me advice. I like any feedback. O.K next order of business, I’m playing Dark Cloud 2 again. It’s not too bad but let me tell you I really wasted my money on Megaman anniversary collection. Please save yourself and DO NOT I repeat DO NOT get Megaman anniversary collection It was a waste of money.              I had the funniest dream last night. Jessica went to my house and she hated my room and I laughed. (yeah laughed) and her whole family came over and wanted her, her cousins and me to go to some ice skating place. I told them that I didn’t want to go. I’m not exactly sure what this means but it was kinda weird but hey.              I know I’m jumping from topic to topic but I can’t just can’t wait for UTADA to make her make here in the States. I just love her so much and now in English Utada’s even better then ever. If you want to listen to her music go to  urlLink www.utada.com  but the server sometimes doesn’t work. You can also try her Japanese site  urlLink www.utada.jp  and click on now playing to hear “Easy Breezy” already a hit in Japan. Her original site is  urlLink www.toshiba-emi.com/utada.com  the first two were for her English CD. Her CD comes out October 8 here in USA. I’m so excited but if your desperate like me you can download her first English single on iTunes. Too bad I don’t have iTunes… ((Weep, don’t worry I’m (blow nose) fine)).              I’m trying to get my cousin Alyssa to go to my middle school. I loved it there. Well let’s get some things right. My program I loved, some of the other ones are kinda crazy. Anyway she has to be my protégé there keep good grades and eventually make it to a specialized high school. One of six, anyone really. I just want her to go to a good school cause the schools around her place (zone) is really bad. But um I think she’ll get in. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today I didn’t do much. You know listen to music, play games and work on my RPG maker game. But really that’s all I did. I talked to Jessica yesterday we really haven’t been talking. She’s mad at me and well I let her be for a couple of days I don’t think she wants me as her friend, I called her earlier today she said she’ll call me back so I’m not planning to call her back and I think she won’t call back. Jessica and my cousin Michael (garbagefanscus.com) are talking and I think he likes her. I mean not in love with her but I just fell badly because I don’t want him to waste his time on her because she’s not worth his time. It’s hard to explain but it won’t work. (Or so I think). On much better news, I told Tarah I like her. (Crappy though since she lives in Canada) but I don’t know if she likes me back. Oh one more thing for people who read my Blogger feel free to send me email too but just label something like “After I read your Blogger I started to hate the color tea green autumn” something that let’s me know that you’re a reader. Which just to let you know there’s not a lot of you’s (yes improper grammar) but hey I want to know what you think. Give me advice. I like any feedback. O.K next order of business, I’m playing Dark Cloud 2 again. It’s not too bad but let me tell you I really wasted my money on Megaman anniversary collection. Please save yourself and DO NOT I repeat DO NOT get Megaman anniversary collection It was a waste of money.              I had the funniest dream last night. Jessica went to my house and she hated my room and I laughed. (yeah laughed) and her whole family came over and wanted her, her cousins and me to go to some ice skating place. I told them that I didn’t want to go. I’m not exactly sure what this means but it was kinda weird but hey.              I know I’m jumping from topic to topic but I can’t just can’t wait for UTADA to make her make here in the States. I just love her so much and now in English Utada’s even better then ever. If you want to listen to her music go to  urlLink www.utada.com  but the server sometimes doesn’t work. You can also try her Japanese site  urlLink www.utada.jp  and click on now playing to hear “Easy Breezy” already a hit in Japan. Her original site is  urlLink www.toshiba-emi.com/utada.com  the first two were for her English CD. Her CD comes out October 8 here in USA. I’m so excited but if your desperate like me you can download her first English single on iTunes. Too bad I don’t have iTunes… ((Weep, don’t worry I’m (blow nose) fine)).              I’m trying to get my cousin Alyssa to go to my middle school. I loved it there. Well let’s get some things right. My program I loved, some of the other ones are kinda crazy. Anyway she has to be my protégé there keep good grades and eventually make it to a specialized high school. One of six, anyone really. I just want her to go to a good school cause the schools around her place (zone) is really bad. But um I think she’ll get in. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cousin's blogger  urlLink www.garbagefanscuz.blogspot.com  Sometimes I post things that happenned in the past and post it under the day that it happened so you might see some new post that happen in the past. Get it right? Like I post July 24 on july 27 but july 24 will be on july 24 so you might want to llok back every now ans then 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>