<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        i spoke to my mother inlaw yesterday and she told me since i wans't doing a lot here in the US..i should be writing a journal..she said it might help if i record daily events no matter how boring my day will be...  then i recall writing my first journal when i was thirteen. i told myself back then that i should start recording my experiences since am a teenager already. i religiously wrote my experiences everyday for more than 10yrs and stored all my journals in one big memory box.   there were times  i opened my memory box and read some entries...some made me laugh, some made me cry, other entries made me mad..while others made me recall the times i fell inlove! oh boy!!! i never realized how much i've grown to be mature not until i browsed thru my journals. my writing improved, my grammar, my ideas changed...friends came and went...while others stayed...i read my decisions..some fair, some good...every little thing was recorded and i cherished those journals for years!  Before i left for the States, while i was cleaning my closet i came across my memory box...my hands were trembling as i tried opening my box...inside i saw ME! who i was and what i've become..i read thru the pages once again and this time all i did was smile..i smiled because for more than 10yrs i recorded the story of my life..it was indeed lived fully! as a teenager and as a young adult.   after putting back the last journal back to the box i thought it's time for me to move on to the next chapter of my life...in the US with my husband....it just came to me....i started buring one journal then the next...next.....then came the last one..it was the hardest one for me to let go because it contained memories of my mom who past away three yrs ago (from today). it took me awhile before finally accepting the death of my mom...with my act of burning it was also my way of releasing the pain i have been keeping for years...it was time to let my mom go and leave her in peace...ill only be holding all the memories in my heart...  Apparently, i've stopped writing but maybe pretty soon i'll write my journal again..this time it'll be in a different place.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I spent my first 4th of July in Romeoville, Illinois with my husband, Gus and some friends.  It felt so strange considering that Iam a Filipino celebrating an American holiday. I felt more guilty considering that i haven't really celebrated Independence Day in the Philippines like i did here in the US. Does this mean Iam less a Filipino? Does this mean Iam still chained to our once colonizer? Humm?!   Yes we surely had a blast in Romeoville seeing the best fireworks in my entire life. Everybody drank and ate. Everybody laughed and enjoyed the night like no other. It was indeed one good experience for all of us...especially me. ( i just arrived in the US 2months ago so practically everthing here is new to me).  Inspite of the experience i felt that something was lacking, then BANG-- i realized that no matter how fun the event or party is, without one's family it will never be complete. Then i realized how much i miss my own country ( my very own CEBU province) despite it's imperfections. I miss the very place i call HOME. I miss the food- "lechon", green mangoes, dinuguan, palitaw..the list could go on. i miss the beautiful beaches... the mountains..i miss the people...i miss HOME!  My 4th of July experience has liberated me in a way...i realized so many things about being what it takes to be free..IAM a FILIPINO and IAM FREE! i miss home terribly and i promise to be  back pretty soon and embrace again the gift, the one place my heart calls home- the Philippines.  by: Hazel N. Basa 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>