<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It looked so out of place  Like a black rose among tiger lillies,  She sat on a green moss throne  Alone with a frown on her  red  lips,  Beauty all her own,  Looking at the overflowing creek  As though she was undergoing  A great internal struggle   Wind blew her crown of thimbles Off her  golden    head    Lightening lit the  neon &nbsp;silk of her flowing princess gown  And blended with the  ice blue  of her sad, glowing eyes  She let her sorrow out with a tiny sigh  Like a whisper it was heard  An icy tear leaked from her eye  Falling down her  snowy  cheek  It joined the rushing water by her feet   No love to come and wake her soul,  No warming lovers gaze  She clings to herself for warmth,  No companion there is to laugh with  Only her farmiliar tears of ice,  No family who cares  Too busy consuming power,  No comfort in her skin  It crawls with chill and sadness,  No way to get away  Trapped&nbsp;in a web of pain and lies   Thunder called her name  It shook her   saphire   wings,  Wind tossed her rain soaked hair  As she slowly rose into the air  Her delicate jeweled wings  Picked her off her throne of mossy  Riverside rock,  They led her to the sky,  A bolt of lightening  blue   Met her painful cry  "Free me from my prison-hell"  Lightening struck her being  As bright as her eyes  She saw no more corruption  Felt no more pain  Lighening&nbsp;awoke &nbsp;her fairy-princess soul   &nbsp;  This probably sucks but it somehow is a way for me to vent.    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       She never mentions the word addiction&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    In certain company&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Yes, she'll tell she's an orphan&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    After you meet her family She paints her eyes as black as night now&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    She pulls those shades down tight&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;She gives a smile when the pain comes&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    The pain gonna make everything alright&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Chorus:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Says she talks to angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    They call her out by her name&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Oh yeah, she talks to angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;Says they call her out by her name &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    She keeps a lock of hair in her pocket&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    She wears a cross around her neck&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Yes the hair is from a little boy&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    And the cross from someone she has not met&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Not yet &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Says she talks to angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    They call her out by her name&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Oh yeah, she talks to angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Says they call her out by her name &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   She don't know no lovers&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    None that I've ever seen&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    And to her that means nothing&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    But to me it means, means everything &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;She paints her eyes as black as night now&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    She pulls those shades down tight&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    She gives a smile when the pain comes&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    The pain gonna make everything alright &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Says she talks to angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    They call her out by her name&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Oh yeah, she talks to angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Says they call her out by her name     &nbsp;   I love that song.  &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I reach out and touch my cold window   She's fading, going faraway   I can't see her anymore   Gone, she left through fog outside   You won't see her anymore   Consumed from darkness in her head   Eyes are dead and not her own   China dolls mock her life   For they live more than she            She tries to see who she was before   But the before was always laced with lies   She can see that now   Her happy wasn't really happy   Just some mirror playing tricks   A circus of jokers telling jokes;   She was vulnerable and believed   Little girl got bigger    The innocent white veil was lifted from her mind      She saw what was right in  front of her suddenly     Like solving a riddle after years and years              The hurricane clouds rolled in to cover up the sun       All her hopes were fed to the vultures         They had a feast on those,     Her chances long since blown away            Along with the tumbleweed,    Her faith was left neglected       As a forest without life,          She sits alone looking out her cold window       Wiping away the raindrops falling from her eyes         
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sorry doesn't cut if   If you never try to change,   Your apologies bounce off of me   Like they were never said,   I've built a wall around myself   Made of stone, fear and curling ivy,   Noone can break through    No matter how much that I want them to    &nbsp;  Anger flares inside of me   Like a human candlestick,   Anger controls my mind   When I see her stagger by,   It masks my hurt   Like her clouded eyes  
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      walls groan  rain washes the windows  and all your curses  are drowned by the thunder,  lightening creeps across the gray-painted sky-  strikes the ocean  and lights your face,  illuminates your rage  like a shadow of a monster   you scream and shout  and i try to block out  all the sick things you say i am,  i can't help feeling i'm the reason  you act this way  wind throws trash cans  across the street  mom throws lamps  at my feet   i'm sick of all the fear you give me  i'm tired of always hiding it  i'm done wishing i would die  and hurting over you   the trees do a fitfull dance  outside in the wind  kinda like my emotions  always swaying back and forth  sad-happy-mad   you want me to pretend it's okay  but i can't do just as you say  see i've gotten a little older  now i know it's not alright,  to treat me the way you do  i'm leaving you and this house  for a better life   you wonder why I can't hug you  why i'm so unconfident  or why i have these scars  but if you look alittle closer  deep inside yourself  you'll find the storm which i have seen  and maybe try to calm it 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dream Angel  she flies above city lights sending hope in the form of a dream one dream is all it takes to give hope to a child that there's something more than the crime of the streets  or the lonliness of an orphanage  she mixes in her glittering dream dust  an ounce of will,a pinch of faith and a song of courage- with a voice as delicate as angel food cake  her silvery dream concoctions float through the tiny window cracks, as silent as a secret through the moons dim glow in dark alleys filled with shadows, a sleeping baby breathes it in  then she flies away high like a dolphins smooth glide to anothers restless cries- there's others in need of a simple dream 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this i wrote when i was thinking of England and for some reason this just came into my head... can't I find a place somewhere? a place for me that I can have in someones eyes that love me too have his soul,could I? and call it mine and mine alone? a place protected from groping hands; icecycle fingers threatening a chill a warm ocean draft,I dream a key to unlock the secrets of his masked eyes such sweet and sour seductiveness what key better then my heart? ready to unfold and unfurl all dark ready to stop hiding in myself and find a pleasant burrow inside of him  and for him to find his place in me like a lone hotel abandoned,haunted and dark I wait he'll walk in and turn the light on and start a newness in me like freshly baked pumpkin pie sitting warm beside the turkey; safe from November wind and with a place 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this isn't the geatest, I know but I was just sittin' thinking about this and decided to write it down to ease my mind a little.  I will never taste the burnt dinners I will never see that protective stare I will  never hear that encouraging advice I will never touch that warm belonging deep in my heart I will never speak the word "father"  That's just what I was thinking about today....
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my poem and fav songs diary :-D.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its been five mons since you went away you left without a word nothing to say when i was the one who gave you my heart and soul but it wasnt good enough for you noo so i asked god Chorus: god send me an angel from the heavens above send me an angel to heal my brocken heart from being in love cuz all i doo is cry, is cry send me an angel to wipe the tears from my eyes  and i know it might sound crazy but after all that i still love you you wanna come back in my life but now there's something that i have to do i have to tell the one's that i once adored that they cant have my love nomore my heart cant take nomore lies and my eyes are all out of cry's soo god  god send me an angel from the heavens above send me an angel to heal my brocken heart from being in love cuz all i doo is cry, is cry send me an angel to wipe the tears from my eyes  now you have me on my knee's begging god please to send you back to me i couldn't eat i couldn't sleep and you made me feel like i could not breathe when all i wanted to do was feel your touch and to give you all of my love but you took my love for granted want my lovin' now but you can't have it ohh god  god send me an angel from the heavens above send me an angel to heal my brocken heart from being in love cuz all i doo is cry, is cry send me an ange to wipe the tears from my eyes  seend mee an aaa-angel send-- me an aaangel-oh god send me an angel-ohh god 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just for this night   Come alive   Put your feelingless gaze aside   Relax without your pain   Or memories that linger      Hold my hand tight,   I'm not expecting   More than you can give   I just want to give you a chance   To let yourself loose without fear   You've been caged with barbwire,   Rusted and sharp   For so long,   Let it go   For just this night   Don't think of it      And I won't manipulate    Your insecurities   I'll hold them close to me,   Make you feel safe and burdenless      Just for this night   I'll see the soul    I've always known   Was there   All along     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hurt me     Break me     Make me feel     Give something to regret     I want to see your dead eyes      Looking over me     I want to feel you consuming me     Hating me      And loving me     In the most twisted way        
    
</post>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *yawn*  Can I borrow someones bed?  I don't want to sleep here tonight.      BETH  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I am absolutely and completely bored. I actually hope Beth sends me 10 boxes of JollyJohn's free condoms. Atleast then I could enjoy some humor. Oh My God. My mom rented another movie and left it here. Guess when it's do? Today. Guess what time it is? 7:01 p.m. I have to rush upstairs to grandma and tell her we need to hurry to take this movie back. I  hate  when my mom does this. Grandma's going to be pissed! If mom went to work Tuesday in the shape she was in I bet a dollar they fired her. It just discusts me to no end. Kill Bill is a good movie. I want to see Kill Bill volume 2 now...  &nbsp;    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          As I lay in my bed with the covers all around me, comfortable as can be and drifting off to sleep once again my kind mother comes barreling into the house. "You had better be ready! I mean it!" I jump up angrily disturbed from my cozy little half-sleep and she continues with her rant"Where are you? I mean it! You had better be ready!" As you can imagine I am confused as hell about what the hell she's going on about so I&nbsp;ask &nbsp;irritably "What the hell are you talking about?" And she respondes "Your dentist appointment, why the hell did grandma come over yesterday if she wasn't going to tell you when your appointment was?" So, I get up somewhat forcebly thinking to myself 'she asked you when my dentist appointment was and you responded "August 28th", so, either grandma didn't hear you right,which I seriously doubt, or, you were so high you didn't know what month it was. My bet goes on the latter.' Although, I didn't say anything of that sort out loud because I was way too tired to&nbsp;start an argument. I got up and got dressed and grabbed my tooth brush and comb and shoes and did all that in the car on my way to the dentist. I do not recommend brushing your teeth in the car, by the way I just&nbsp;remembered I left my tooth brush in the car. Damnit. That's cool cause the dentist&nbsp;gave a new tooth brush, some floss, and a little tobe of Crest toothpaste :-D I feel happy, I got presents today. Anyways, I got to the&nbsp;dentist and sat in the scary dentist chair and looked at all the scary dentist equipment and kept thinking 'Seneika is behind this.&nbsp;Seneika has got these dentists under her paycheck. They are going to do all kinds of evil Nazi experiments on me. They hate Jews... Wait, I'm not jewish.'&nbsp;I did think&nbsp;Seneika was paying the Nazi dentists under the table, all ... I did think they were&nbsp;going to do&nbsp;mad-evil-scientific-torture experiments on me and then I got to thinking of evil and evil reminded me of mr.McDonnel and McDonnel reminded me of a lesson to do with the Holocaust he had taught.. Or it may have been mrs.Beck-I don't know the point is I was reminded of the Holocaust and then I got scared cause I started thinking the dentists were Nazis and see how my mind wonders? It just got worse from there. At first she stuck some plastic thing in my mouth and arranged it in it way that when I had to bite down on it(I was required to bite down on it)it hurt and stabbed my cheek and tongue, I think she was taking x-rays but the whole while I kept thinking'Krissy!! Come save me! Make Andrew come get me! Beth! G! Chelsea I want out of this torture seat!'. Then she cleaned my teeth. Okay, the only bad part about that is the paste stuff gets on my lips and dries them out and I don't have any chapstick cause I'm too poor to buy chapstick. After that she used some kind of sharp metal object that she referred to as a metal toothpick to scrap my teeth, I haven't the foggiest idea why, but it scared me cause it doesn't feel right to have a metal object scrap between and across your teeth. After that she flossed my teeth. That was the weirdest thing. I'm not used to having peoples fingers all up in my mouth and she was ALL up in my mouth. Okay, last thing she did was fill this blue thing that you put in your mouth and bite down on with this purple flouride crap just for my teeth. That stuff wasn't very good and I had to bite down on it for about 10 minutes and you know, after awhile your jaw gets tired and the sucky-thing wasn't suckying in the place it should've because I had drool runnin' down my&nbsp;chin&nbsp;. Nasty.&nbsp;Again I thought 'save me all my friends!' and actually&nbsp;made a noise but&nbsp;nobody heard because I had that thing in my mouth, plus noone was in there at that time.&nbsp;Then after she took out the nasty blue thing I waited for the doctor cause the x-rays of my teeth had gotten back. I waited in there for quit awhile but I didn't care because the dentist woman let me play with the sucky-thing. Doctor came and told me my wisdom teeth are coming in but that was the least of my worries. I have scrabble teeth. If you do not know what that is I will tell you even though I don't know what it is but I'll tell you what's wrong with my teeth. My teeth are fairly straight it's not like I need braces or anything but I have ONE tooth that's kind of crooked, not very much but you cam tell. I thought 'oh-well big deal it's just ONE crooked tooth, that's okay' but the doctor said it wasn't crooked. Meaning it would have been totally straight IF it wasn't for my one canine baby tooth right beside it. I have ONE baby tooth left. One. And it seems as though the big tooth that should have been grown out by now is growing on the inside and pushing against the one tooth and that's why that tooth is crooked. I have to have surgery. I have to go to Charlottsville to get an ortho consult so the doctor here can operate. What&nbsp;he wants to do is take out the baby tooth and then pull out the grown up tooth that should be there in the first place in it's place. I'm not going to be missing a tooth or anything&nbsp;so everythings cool. I just haven't been in surgery for years and I'm kind of nervous about it. &nbsp;        
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey People,     &nbsp;  How is everyone doing?&nbsp; Good here.&nbsp; I'm really bored.&nbsp; Its 3.30 in the afternoon and everyone I know is sleeping but me.&nbsp; and shelly.&nbsp; Shelly isn't sleeping.&nbsp; I tried to sleep but every fricken person in Harrisonburg decided to walk on my porch.&nbsp; Which, by the way, if you try to sleep in the living room and anyone makes a noise on the porch you'll here it like its RIGHT BESIDE YOU.&nbsp; No fun.    &nbsp;  I'm cranky and I've read all my library books.   BETH  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I was reading one a blog and came across an entry that had another link, so, I clicked on it. It was site for a little 5 month old&nbsp;baby girl, it was titled Save Julia. She has a rare disease called SCID. She needs a bone marrow transplant and her recovery depends a lot on what hospital she is at and that depends on how much money they have. I wish to give some money, though I don't have much at all($12) but I thought we might raise some together. It doesn't have to be a lot, just a little. For more about this go to  urlLink http://jerusalemgypsy.blogspot.com  and then go to&nbsp;an entry titled The Millionaire Next Door and scroll to one of the bottom paragraphs and find the orange thing&nbsp;   -This &nbsp;.   It's called This and is orange. Thank You.  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          As I was reading I came to a paragraph in my book that especially caught my attention and made me go "ewww"(the good ewww, remember the bad ew is "ew" the good ew is "ewww"). From the book  Resurrection  by Tolstoy is the paragraph talked of in the first sentence that made me go "ewww"-    One of the most widespread superstitions is that every man has his own special definite qualitites: that he is kind, cruel, wise, stupid, energetic, apathetic, and so on. Men are not like that. We may say of a man that he is&nbsp; more often kind than cruel, more often wise than stupid, more often energetic than apathetic, or the reverse; but it would not be true to say of one man that he is kind and wise, of another that he is bad and stupid. And yet we always classify mankind in this way. And this is false. Men are like rivers: the water is the same in one and all; but every river is narrow here, more rapid there, here slower, there broader, now clear, now dull, now cold, now warm. It is the same with men. Every man bears in&nbsp;himself the germs of every human quality; but sometimes one quality manifests itself, sometimes another, and the man often becomes unlike himself, while still remaining the same man.    To &nbsp;say that I agree&nbsp; may well be &nbsp; hypocritical. I do not care. I agree. I think that a lot of people feel this way but still classify someone as being stupid or kind and I think that that's okay as long as they realize(this includes me)that there's more to them than&nbsp;just stupid or just kind and I think that a lot of people know&nbsp;that. I just like the fact that Tolstoy brought it up and&nbsp;wrote about it because it seems like such a&nbsp;small thing that loads of&nbsp;people know in there&nbsp;minds but never bring it up because it seems like everyone knows this.&nbsp;I could be completely ignorant &nbsp;and have no idea what I'm talking about, though. That be the case- I'm sorry if I have offended anyone.         
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hehe I said pizzel.    &nbsp;  Today went alright even though the realization of how far behind christian school put me, keeps clicking in.&nbsp; My dad is taking me to talk to the counselors tomorrow about my classes.&nbsp; I'm nervous.&nbsp; I know they're going to have to look at my grades from last year and I shouldn't have failed.&nbsp; I passed everything with flying colors and I know there is a reason why they won't let me have my end of the year exams back.&nbsp; I know what you're thinking:&nbsp; Man is she paranoid.&nbsp; Typically I'd laugh and say 'You're right, what am I doing?' but christian school is screwed up in too many ways and its definately a possibility that they failed me because I wasn't coming back.&nbsp; The teachers would constantly ask me 'are you coming back?' no.&nbsp; I'm not you crappers, and you wanna know why biotch?&nbsp; Guess.    &nbsp;  Anyways, I don't feel like talking about this because I get mad beyond all recognition and then shut myself in my room for days.    &nbsp;  Catch you all tomorrow,    BETH  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Recent statments have been made about one of   OUR   dorks by a   fellow   dork. It so appears that a certain Dorkerer is   NOT   the Dork of   guitars  . Rather, he is the Dork of all music. So, I hereby declare(with the approval of all Dorks) that&nbsp;Dorkerer&nbsp;now become Dorkerer, the Dork of all music.   Please send your coments of approval   IF   you approve of this sudden change. Many thanks.   I had fun yesterday playing with the giant frisbee. I don't know if it's actually a frisbee, it's sort of like an oval balloon type thing that you throw as a frisbee but it isn't made of hard plastic.... I'll have to find out it's name... It amuses me.  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey everyone, I hope you all had a great day.&nbsp; I know I did     &nbsp;  You know what people?&nbsp; I love life (no I'm not on any drugs, despite what you may think)&nbsp; I don't know why I love life.&nbsp; I just do.&nbsp; You guys do too, trust me you do...&nbsp;     &nbsp;  I had an oreo milkshake tonight     &nbsp;  I didn't see any good looking guys today.&nbsp; I saw some mediocre looking guys and some old men.&nbsp; They didn't suit my fancy.    &nbsp;   I like big butts and I cannot lie...     &nbsp;  I'm turned in all my vacation cameras today at Walmart.&nbsp; Yay!&nbsp; I tried to take some really good pictures but I don't know how they'd turn out because it was a disposable camera...&nbsp; very low quality.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Tomorrow=Church.&nbsp; Wish me luck.&nbsp; Its like a freakin' battlefield out there.&nbsp; Bodies torn apart and ragged left for dead in the feilds of sorrow...&nbsp; Okay so maybe it's not that extreeme...&nbsp; but you know, its not heaven either.&nbsp; Huh... isn't that interesting... church isn't heaven.&nbsp; Okay, I have to go.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Bed time for Bethy.    &nbsp;   You otha brothers can't deny, when a girl walks in with an ittybitty waste and a round thing in your face...       &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This was very weird...I just took thisquiz thing somewhere, I don't even remember how I got it but it was a quiz to tell me what kind of self mutilator I was. My results-"You are a cutter, you can be moody as hell and probably don't even know how your feeling half the time. Despite this, you pull yourself together with a lot of strength and aren't to be messed with".      weird...      Am I supposed to feel proud?       If draging a big needle over my arm is supposed to be&nbsp;my inner strength, I would hate to&nbsp;see my inner weakness.... &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hello! how are you!?    -That's 'hello! how are!?' in webding. Hehehe.    I want to talk about something and yet I find myself in a position where I have nothing to say. I've been reading this book   Nana by Emile Zola  &nbsp;and I really really like it. I recommend it . I want to go to&nbsp;JC Penneys and shop but I don't think&nbsp;I'll be able to because noone can take me because my grandpa had a stroke and he's not allowed to drive and grandma's at work.&nbsp;The other day my mom asked me to dry&nbsp;off the dishes and I ignored her [partly because she asked me and partly because I would be doing them beside her. I know that's horrible but I can't stand doing things she asks me to. Also, the other day she asked me to&nbsp;go to the pool and the only reason I said no&nbsp;was because she would be wearing a bikini, her bikin's are more revealing than mine like she wears the kind that looks like a bra and underwear. If you have ever seen my mother&nbsp;you would understand why that is&nbsp;a VERY bad idea.&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm back all my wonderful friends.    &nbsp;  I wrote about vacation in my other blog, so check it out if you are feeling bored. ( urlLink Http://www.angelfire.com/freak2/twizzledazzle/bloggy )    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  It was weird that when I checked my email that Chelsea inquired about which converses she should get, because my mom and I were talking about school clothes this week and she said "I am trying to figure out a way to get the money for those converses you want."&nbsp; I love my mom, she's so rad.&nbsp; I don't love her because she wants to buy me things, I love her because while I was screwed up last year... she never gave up on me and even though I did a million things to hurt her she made sure that I came back as Me.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Anyways, back to the converse dilemma.&nbsp; I can't decide whether I should get green, red or classic navy.&nbsp; If I can get them at all.&nbsp; I can always dream, right?&nbsp; I'm obsessed with Kelly Green.&nbsp; My favorite shirt was Kelly Green and I found it at goodwill.&nbsp; On vacation I bought a kelly green watch.&nbsp; So, typically I would go for the green.&nbsp; BUT....&nbsp; RED.... red is so...&nbsp; Evil.&nbsp; It says "Theres a little bit of hell on my feet."&nbsp; We all like the dangerous side of red.&nbsp; OH NAVY.&nbsp; Navvvyyyy is so... classic.&nbsp; You can  never  go wrong with classic.&nbsp; Rush is classic, Queen, AC/DC, Black Sabbath,&nbsp; Zepp....&nbsp;&nbsp; its all so good and  classic. &nbsp; What do you guys think....    &nbsp;  Now that I have killed you with my spear of boredom I will leave you to die in your computer chair.   BETH  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Well I'm going to leave in about 2 hours, so I won't see/ talk to you until I get back, and that will be on the 31st.&nbsp; So I will talk to you all later, and I'll miss you all while I'm away.&nbsp;&nbsp; ( And I'll take mental notes Shell!!)....L@8r &nbsp;     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Bubbles may very well be the most exciting things there is-well besides sex and I should really not talk about sex because I'm inexperienced with that and I'm rambeling,what was I saying?Oh yes! Bubbles! I love 'em! I was blowing bubbles with Luke(my 4 year old cousin) yesterday on the porch and grandma brought Maddy over(my 1 and 2-3 mons old cousin) and I started to blow them and she got this look on her face like :-o, I do it too when I'm excited about something and there's more then one thing I want to do because I'm so excited so I try to make myself be in more then one place and as you know that doesn't turn out too well. But anyways she got that look on her face and started running towards the bubbles and poking at them and popping them and it was so cute!    :sigh: The good times.   I love my cousins and I love bubbles!  
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to meet a guy! I really want a guy!!!! :whine: I'm lonely. I want a guy that doesn't think my sense of humor is weird or bad... I want a guy that cares about me... I want a guy... I want to meet someone that's kind of like me, and I know that sounds weird but I want to get along with him and I know that opposites attract and that is really true for a lot of people including me but I want a guy that isn't totally opposite,you know what I mean?... I want a freakin' man..
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am still cruelly being forced to spend time with my stupid, ugly, disgusting dad. in a cold climate. we went to the beach today and there was this guy lying right across from me and right as i was about to take a big gulp of ice tea i noticed him staring at me. i lowered the can. stared right back at him. and shrugged my shoulders. he smiled. and i took my big gulp. and started reading my book again. and the asshole stared at me the rest of the time. it was okay the first time... and he wasn't even remotely bad-looking. but even his friend told him to stop staring. that has to be saying something. &nbsp; ANYways. i dunno what else to put here. &nbsp; hope you all are having a better time than i am... 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everyone!!!! I might not be on for the next couple days so don't worry, I'm at Kissy's grandma's house. One of my friend got bit by something or she was having an allergic reaction to something cuz one side of her face swelled up a little and her eye got puffy and the awelled part is rock hard so she's going to the doctor today. She hates docoters but I'm glad she's going cuz we need to find out how to treat it.  Yesterday I stepped on a slug... Krissy said I would have the feel of the slug under my foot for the next three days... I think she's right....
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I starting to see that boys suck.  Okay not all of them, but some of them.  Maybe it's just me, but I hate the way they leave you hangin'.  And you try not to think about it (whatever "it" maybe), but you end up doing it anyway. (Did that come out right?)  So than you wonder why can't the be more understanding about things and try to see something from your P.O.V.  But do they? no.  And why do they get so mad when things don't go their way???   Anyone w/ me on this??
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "It is a tidal wave of children who have lost one or more of their parents,"Carol Bellamy, the executive director of the U.N's childrens agency UNICEF, told Reuters. "Fifteen million globally"she says"It has the possibility of destablizing societies quite dramatically".-Patricia Reaney,Reuters. AIDS has tacken a parent or two from 15 million people.  15 million people.  It goes without saying it has increased the number of orphans. The 15th International AIDS Conference released a report that stated an estimated 18.4 million children would lose atleast one parent by 2010 to the disease.  People are more interested in finding a way to control the disease and finding a cure and I'm not saying they shouldn't be but orphaned children because of Aids are being somewhat neglected and aren't getting as much attnetion they need(and deserve)and that pisses me off. 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hope I didn't sound bitter or unhappy for all my dorks in the below entry because I'm really not. I hope that Beth has unforgetable fun despite the trip being created because of various evil reasons. I hope Chelsea has a great and knowledge-filled time on her cruise . I hope G's remaining time in Turkey is exciting and eventful(the non-boring and good kind of events). I hope Krissy's stay at her grandmothers in Elkton is peaceful and relaxing.                        *HOPE YOUR ALL WELL*
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dorkenya is gone on her trip for various evil reasons, Dorketta is in Turkey, Dorkster is getting ready to go on a cruise, Dorkerella is in Elkton and I, Dorkengerine, am stuck in Harrisonburg,sweet ol' H'burg. I am so lonely;(. The only company I have is the television. I've become rather interested in The West Wing. Why? I'm not exactly sure. I think it's because I really want to know things about politics, I hate being ignorant in stuff like that, I hate how ignorant I am. Atleast I'm not ignorant to the fact that I am ignorant. Anyways, I really like The West Wing but I don't fully understand what they talk about and that's partly becuase they talk to fast about important things. I don't know I'm just rambeling probably, nobody really cares about my ignorance... But since there's noone here for me to do stuff with I'm stuck home watching soap operas and reruns of Dawsons Creek, The West Wing, Buffy the Vampire Slayer and Angel.  :sigh: Woe is me... And on that mockingly dramatic note-
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish i could watch I love the 90s. I LOVED the 90s... I have to spend at least a week with my dad and today I called my mom to tell her something and she started randomly yelling at me ...  this is turning out to be a reaally crappy summer. and i was so looking forward to it.   i'm staying at this medieval place now... so don't expect me online again for at least 5 days...  as the SECOND DAY with my DAD ends....
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you have not seen The Blue Collar Comedy Tour you must absolutely beyond a doubt see it. It is hilarious. I don't care if your not country or redneck you HAVE to see it. It's a fix for depression too. Here's a little tid bit out from the 'you may be a redneck if-' "if someone says you've got something in your teeth and you take them out to see what it is,you may be a redneck" "if your idea of fastfood is hitting a deer with your truck at 65 miles an hour you may be a redneck" "if your momma says your lying through your tooth, you may be a redneck" And here's a bit from 'here's your sign'(retard sign i guess) "the airport has lost my luggage and you go to the lost luggage place and the person working there says "has your flight landed yet?" and i reply" no they just dropped me off by parachute. There's your sign" "I went shopping and went up to pay for them,i dropped them on the counter by the cash register and the lady working there goes "you buyin those?" i replied "no i'm gonna steal 'em i'm just lettin' you see 'em first. There's your sign" It's great you've gotta see it.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMFG.I'm going to fucking cry because the motherfucking hairdresser does not know how to fucking cut any goddamn hair. UGH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I'm gonna cry;-(:whine: :whine:.......
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm getting my hair cut today! YAY!!! I want to get a trim and get sweep away bangs and if the hairdresser does it right this time it should look really good.  :sigh: My mom is taking me.... I have to tsepnd some quality time with the wicked witch from the west wacked out on drugs..... Oh-well.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...Be happy! JK :-D  Anyway, don't worry shell, I got your comments and your's too G.  If you're wondering shell, when you post comments they're not going to show directly on the screen.  They'll appear on the link that says "comments".  I hope that didn't sound mean.  I didn't want to to, I was just telling you incase u forgot or didn't know...
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello everyone I was just seeing if the blog will view this post....
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for some reason this blog is not publishing my comments.....i wrote one to chelsea on this blog and another on her other one and then i wrote g one on this blog and another on her other blog...and it won't even let me on beth's blog....i'm confused....
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all dorks. I'm still desperately hanging on to my mom but... pleeeeeeease don't make me go. we just went to a beauty salon thingie... and wow... waxing has to be the worst form of punishment. but maybe it helped a bit because my mom was talking to this person who was like... 'oh, she's BEAUTIFUL...' :makes face: i don't see it. anyways... oh shellliii help me. i dont wanna goooooooooo...........   - desperate dorketta  
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I really want a tattoo.  So I figure that I'll get one when I'm 18.  But I think one time my mom said that I'm not going to get one as long as I'm living under the same roof.  But I've talk to her before about getting one in front of her and she never said anything bad about it.  So I dunno.  But anyway, when I'm 18 I'll be a senior and - That's perfect!!! I'll get my little black star and then I'll get a blue streak to remember all my friends.  So u all should come w/ me when I get that, so it will be extra special.  And why does everyone look and me when I say that I'm going to get a tattoo and think "YOU!!!????... YEAH RIGHT!!"... 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I FINALLY DONE IT!!! I'M ON HERE.  YA GO ME.  I FIGURED IT OUT ALL BY MYSELF (SORTA) JK, but really, I'd like to thank all the people that got me here.  shel, beth, and finally G.  Thank you...
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all my dorks! I am going to miss you Dorkenya :snog: I hope you find a way to have fun during your...um trip for various evil reasons. Dorketta I'll help anyway I can when your staying with your dad,I mean I hope I can help-You've helped me so much with my mom by just being there. Of course I'm here for your if you need me, your my Dorketta! What makes people think they have superiority over anyone else? I'm talking about racists and sexiests. What makes them think they have a certain "specialness" that say someone of the another gender or someone of a different color could not have or does not have? This is just how I feel, skin color is not a reason to dislike or hate someone. Hate is what kills people which just leads to more hate and eventually that brings along pain in however order you wanna put that. It never solves anything and never brings love,kindness or happiness just more hate and pain and evilness over and over and it never stops.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I taught my cousin Maddie(15 mons old)to dance in the rain today:-D. Omg I'm soo happy, she was so cute out there in her little pink tee-shirt and diaper dancing in the rain. I just hope she doesn't get a cold or anything. I feel special:-D. 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone.  Yes... it is saturday and I am awake BEFORE one oclock in the afternoon.  Whats wrong with Beth, one might ask themselves.  Well... I am very excited because my sister is taking me out this morning.  Usually she is gone with her boyfriend by this time in the morning (9:59 AM) and she does not come home until midnite or after.    Anyways, other than the fact that I'm spitting flummery at you... I'm actually quite happy this morning.  I'm wearing my "Llamas and Pirates and Cheese OH MY" shirt.  This one guy came up and hugged me for wearing it.  MWAHAA he was good looking too.  I found my toe ring.    Obviously you guys can tell I'm bored and I just WANT TO POST SOMETHING WITH ANYTHING IN IT.  Oh... I won't be here for a couple weeks for various evil reasons.  Don't worry I'm not dead.  Wait a minute... I MIGHT BE A VAMPIRE WITH VAMPIRE NAILS.  My sisters leg hurts.  MWAHAA.  Catch you later you guys. DorkenyaBETH
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, all dorks. today i dyed my hair this really dark brown - its like black and i got it layered and i got my bangs... i think my hair looks pretty now - just the rest of me looks crappy. im with my mummy in the capital of turkey and my DAD is forcing me to spend a week with him at this other place and i REALLY, REALLY don't wanna go... i haven't gone to the isolated beach so I will be able to get online... so you guys are gonna have to help me through this...   i visited my old elementary school and my old house today. i'm going on a steady downward spiral.   YEEEEEEEEEES dorkenya itd be awesome if i could spend spring break with all you dorks and my mom said i might be able to come to the USA early since there's no place for us on a plane on august 15. hanging out with you guys - if i can, that is - is the only thing i have to look forward to.  CIAO... oh sorry about the long boring blog... i'm BORED...
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...okay never mind the post that was telling you to sign your name b/c it already says who wrote it,i just didn't see it because the print was so small...
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm in love with you all my little chicas.   Penis.   Sorry--I'm REALLY tired and can't move my fingers very well... OH! YAY!  RUSH IS ON THE RADIO!  Hell... fluffing... yea.  DorkenyaBETH
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I(Dorkengerine) wrote the last 2 entries called 'England' and 'I am a dork and a member of the very special dork family' and G(Dorketta) wrote the first entry. Don't forget to sign what entry you have written so nobody gets confused.  -Dorkengerine-
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of these days I'm going to go to England with my dorks. We are going to show up the old British women who think Americans are unable to speak proper English. We are going to spit at all the british girls and steal their hott english boyfriends. We are going to ride the humungous ferris wheel and look upon the stars. We are going to dance in the rain and laugh intill we have to take Dorkkenya to the hospital because she forgot to breath between the bursts of laughter. We're going to walk into the shops that are so obviously made for just the rich and wealthy and sneer at the employees as we try on their expensive clothing. I am going to England with my dorks and find the dark prince of my twisted fantasies. I even wrote a "cheese poem" for him. can't I find a place somewhere? a place for me that I can have in someones eyes that love me too have his soul,could I? and call it mine and mine alone? a place protected from groping hands; icecycle fingers threatening a chill a warm ocean draft,I dream a key to unlock the secrets of his masked eyes such sweet and sour seductiveness what key better then my heart? ready to unfold and unfurl all dark ready to stop hiding in myself and find a pleasant burrow inside of him  and for him to find his place in me like a lone hotel abandoned,haunted and dark I wait he'll walk in and turn the light on and start a newness in me like freshly baked pumpkin pie sitting warm beside the turkey; safe from November wind and with a place   
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I don't have much to say right now but except I really really want to go to England......
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE DORKS...  Rachelli - Dorkengerine (Dork of Tangerines) G - Dorketta (Dork of Sleeping Beauty) Krissy - Dorkerella (Dork of Cinderella) Beth - Dorkenya (Dork of Kenya)  Chelsea - Dorkster (Dork of Monsters) David and Andrew - Dorker and Dorkerer (Dork os Guitars and King of Dorks)
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa. I am really excited. Nirvana just came on. WOW. David has a lip ring. I don't even know. You know what? No. No, I don't even know. "...I'm so happy cause today I found my friends.. Their in my head.. I'm so ugly that's okay cause so are you.. light my candles in a daze cause I've found God.." DAVID(DORKERER) BOUGHT CARE BEAR BOXERS AND SUNGLASSES!!!! OH MY GOD!!!!!!! Why do you insist on being so forceful little carrot? Doesn't matter what you do I'll never do you..... Man.. Those guys at the mall were sooo hott :dreams: one of these days I'll actually talk to them... Well only if they talk to me first.....  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My fucking grandpa is cancelling the internet. I don't know when. If you want to contact me you'll have to either call me or write me a letter-Phone # (540)433-9620, cell phone #(540)435-1850. Address-708 Stuart st. Ugh, why does he get the computer and then all of a sudden take it away? Why get it in the first place, man, it pisses me off. I need it not only to talk to my friends but for school. In Loughrans class if we didn't type our writings(poems and stories and projects) we got points taken off.  Who's to say another teacher won't be like that? I also need it to research things. Talking is not the only thing I freakin' do on the damn computer! Ugh, he pisses me off.   Oh, and after awhile he's cancelling the cell phone too.   Damn him.  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm jealous of you G. Why can't are school have a photograph glass??? This sucks...!!!   ( I'm not mad at you, I'm just jealous)  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I'm wanting another and newer SN for AIM.  I've got some ideals, but I want to know what you think I should put??  OHH, I just thought of this, what about Dorkster8???    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey G, I noticed that you put  urlLink Anna Karenina  as one of your favorite books?  Is it really good?  What's it about???? 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LOL, I've FINALLY posted the 1st part of my vacation stroy.  If you don't know the link, just click on this :   urlLink www.theotherdorkster.blogspot.com   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I think I could be one of the happiest people in the world!!! I got Loughran again for english, so I'm happy.  Who do you have shell and beth?  G, I wish you hadn't moved!!!!   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was really an OK day. I went and got signed up for school. I made sure I knew where all my classes were. Grandma(yes, I made grandma come with me, I wasn't about to go with just my mom)met some people at school, Dale and Virginia, they're janitors and since grandma knows the kind of work, she decided to say hello, it's a way of saying thank you, somehow. But I always so "hi" or smile when I see Dale in the halls, he's really nice and so is his wife(Virginia). It's so cute, they always where matching shirts. Didn't see anyone I knew. I managed to get my mom away from the PTSA(whew! that was a close one)so she didn't sign herself up for any colunteer crap. If my mom was not a drug addict I would've cared less how many things she sined up to do, but she is. The last time she signed up for that kind of stuff was in elementary school. It went as follows: She came into my third grade class to help us paint Christmas knomes or "Holiday" knomes. I don't remember if she was high or not but I think she just coming off of something. Anyways, you were supposed to make two and paint all of it one color(red or green) and leave a little circle for it's face. I forgot to leave a circle. Big mistake. My mom flies off the handle screaming at me at the top of her lungs-"YOU STUPID! FOLLOW THE FUCKIN' DIRECTIONS!" blah blah blah and so on and so on. I look around the room at all the faces looking at us. I start bawling and run into the bookbag place(you know the place that was like a closet that you slide the door open and put your coats and bookbag? that thing). And I refused to come out. It was sooo embarrassing. Mrs. Lile, one of my favorite teachers by the way, finally got me to come out and I can just remember everyone s eyes on me and how hot my face was. So, you can see my desperation to avoid her volunteering at all cost.    I had a nice little wrestling match with Luke and Logan upstairs on the floor. Haven't had one of those since.... I can't remember, but it was kinda like a way to lose myself. I was happy. It felt nice. Me and Maddy played peekabo. :-D. She would put her hands over her eyes and I would go-"Where's Maddy?" in my stupid little kid voice and she would put her hands down real fast and I would act surprised and go "AHH! There you are!" and she would giggle and do it again. I love my cousins. Cousins are grand.  
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished watching The Blue Collar Comedy Tour, and you're right shell, it is funny!!! 
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I went to Hillandell park today with the kids(Logan and Luke) and read while they played on the playground thing. There was a cute little girl down there, she was blind. It was sad because she was feeling around everywhere so she would know where to go.    You know there worlds going to end when you see a country singer wearin' a rap shirt.   Gentry of Montgomery Gentry had on a G-Unit shirt... Odd.   Odd rhymes with... Wait, what?  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am excited. I got advanced profiency on my World History SOL's. I only missed 5 questions.    On my Math SOL's I wasn't so lucky. I got 39 out of 50 which is pass/profiency.   I'm not tryng to brag or anything, I'm just happy.   :-D.  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today is a very pretty day. I am happy to be alive today. The sky is extra clear. It feels like September or October. There's a cold breeze. It feels so beautiful, cold but I've always liked the cold when the sun is shining and the sky is so clear... Like it is today.    I got up at 7:50 a.m today. Why? You ask. My grandma walks in as I'm trying to fall back asleep and informs me she's going on a walk. I mumbeled "... okay..." and she pauses for a second .."would you like to go?". This is the strange part, I said yes. So, I get up and find that it's very cold so I have a good excuse to wear my new jacket without looking like an idiot. We had a nice little walk. I like the weather today, even though when I got back and took a shower it was colder when I got out then usual. I'm not use to that. One of the things I'm not looking forward to when it gets cold.  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently I'm not going to be a social worker. Apparently I'm not going to college. Apparently I have no common sense. Apparently I'm not going to amount to anything. Apparently I'm some weirdo hermit that never does anything. And apparently I'm going to end up like my mom. Says grandma and grandpa. Well thanks a fuckin lot for having faith in me O'Family of mine. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm bored. I can't think of anything to research...    I was watching a Red Hot Chili Peppers video and the lead singer looked kinda hott with a mohawk.. He's probably old now but I don't care. My ears are hurting.. These head phones used to not hurt... Odd.   Odd rhymes with ... I don't know.    Hey! Dorkster! Guess what I got you? I got you a/the/an- I'm not saying! HaHaHa! Was that as fun for you as it was for me?   I wish grapes were hot pink and this color pink. Then they would taste like bubblegum. I wish I saw a neon green sky. I swear I'm not on anything.   (Not that I don't like grapes the way they are(not discriminating against grapes)I just want to eat a hot pink grape that tastes like bubblegum)  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Life just isn't what it used to be.      But what it will be is going to be the best.    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        :Sigh:      I went to CiCi's the other day with my grandma,pappap,aunt,Luke and Maddy(cousins), and my mom even though I didn't eat but one piece of pizza and I didn't want to go at all but since grandma thinks I have problems with eating, I went. Needless to say my mom manipulated this dining arrangement to spend time with me. I went to look around at Kohl's because I got $10 from the yard sale and they were having a sale. She tried to buy me clothes because I guess she thinks she can buy me back. Noooo, she can't. I was going to get a pair of jeans that were on sale and a care bear shirt and a cordiroy coat because it was 50% off and my old one was kind of shrinking at the sleeves and it's sort of difficult to find a cordiroy jacket that's 50% off. That's what I was going to get and I would be done with shopping for school clothes but she wanted to get this sweater/shirt for me that was cute but it was $14.99 and in my opinion that was still too high and I knew what she was taking me shopping for. I didn't want her to get it so I begged her to put it down and she wouldn't and it pissed me off because I knew I was going to end up feeling guilty. Sure enough. I feel guilty. I HATE when she does that. I love when I get new stuff but I hate what else it costs me.         
    
</post>


</Blog>