<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday night I dreamed of myself in a new house (nice, medium-to-large family dweeling). I don't know exactly how I came upon the house, or exactly how I came to own the house, but there I was, feasting on all the newly-gotten stuffs at my disposal (the house was fully furnished, down to the last night-stand trinkets). Specifically, I remember starting in a sun-room, which was right off the backyard. I was looking outside at a nicely groomed, yet semi-rough and wild, back yard. There was a shack for storage on the left side of the yard (looking out) with a little path of stone meandering towards it from the back door. It looked like a nice backyard. The inside of the house...I guess morphed regularly...at time it was older looking, at time very modern, and I do recall a few instances where it was my current apartment itself. Anyhow I digress to the main action of the dream...  Part I - K-dig was there, enjoying the company of our 3rd roommate (some chick I think was one of K-dig's old girlfriends). But this 3rd roommate, I knew I had had the experience of knowing intimately, but carnal sounds were coming from K-dig's bedroom and I knew they were "hittin' some skins". I wasn't pissed or anything, actually maybe I was kinda proud of my boy. It was all good, but I just wanted to sniff a little of her sweet stuff as well.  Part II - There was a little house-warming party underway at the new digs. I don't remember anybody clearly at first, but I knew I wasn't too interested in being the social butterfly. I went out to my backyard. I like to be outside, with the smell of fresh grass and earth and trees and life, more than I like the company of most people. In my humble opinion, enjoying the full spectrum of what the mother earth offers is more important than making 1 or 2 friends (which is also important, but for different reasons). Anyways, I was outside for awhile (did I hear trouble?), but finally I went back inside, only to see my nana and papa waiting in the foyer area and my uncle scott and his crew already pulling out the driveway and down the street. I saw uncle scott's face, he didn't make eye contact but looked pissed. As usual, Papa stood quietly behind nana, who as usual, was very forward with her emotions. She said I was outside for over an hour and that was very rude of a host. She cried. I complained that she was being silly, being unreasonable, that I was only looking around the backyard, but they decided to leave. And, the dream was over.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's Monday morning...blog time should be done on work time...wouldn't you agree? The weekend was a self-inflicted wash (as usual). Did I leave the apartment at all? Ha ha haaaa. I love my damn C.Z. (comfort zone) too much, admittedly, and I've had guests (sorta) in my apratment the last two weekend in a row (alison 1st, k-dig's moms 2nd). That said, I was happy to sit on my phat ass and do a whole lotta nothin'. Would you like a detailed account? Smoke, video games, eat, shit, smoke, drink, sleep, web page updates, smoke, watched some not-so-hot dvd's (this weekend was Jeff Rush in Quills and DeNiro in the King of Comedy), watched tv, reconciled my checking account, did dishes, a little shower laundry, and (ta-da) actually cooked a meal (pork chops, beans, and potatos au gratin....mmmmmmmm, auuuu graaatin). That pretty much sums it up...
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, it's Friday night...getting late. Had a long evening of video games and bong hits, followed by this here blizog. I just got the expansion pack for Sid Mieir's Civilization III (Civ Conquests). Same game as before, but I'm diggin' the various, uhhm, conquests available for play...right now, i'm vying for control of the middle east (of course, i played through the feudal era Japanese scenario...sweet). So, besides the VG & BHT, I read a little more of Neil Gaiman's "American Gods", which is shaping up as a not-so-bad read (I definitely bow down to the god of the internet). Anyway, maybe it'll earn a place on the current top 20 list. I'm out.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here I am...at work...Friday afternoon. Nothing but thoughts of play on my mind. Far removed from all the hassles of the job. Oh, you need something sir? Kiss my ass and wait till Monday!  Gonna go take a smoke break with my hottie Asian friend. 
    
</post>


</Blog>