<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       OK, kiddies, ready for some free association, random train of thought kinda stuff?&nbsp; No?&nbsp; Too bad.    &nbsp;  I would like - I would like, I would like a trip to Europe - I would like to introduce myself.&nbsp; But I won't.&nbsp; Instead, I will hop up and down on one leg.&nbsp; Of course, it would be difficult for me to just hop up on one leg, wouldn't it?&nbsp; I mean, on this planet or any other, if you hop up, you will come back down, gravity and all that.    &nbsp;  Speaking of which, wasn't Stephen Hawking losing his bet about black holes somehow supposed to cause the complete annihilation of all matter and energy in the universe?&nbsp; I thought it was.&nbsp; Luckily, or perhaps unluckily, it wasn't.    &nbsp;  How many contractions have I typed so far?&nbsp; Why am I asking you?    &nbsp;  I like ice cream.    &nbsp;  Isn't there some way to take all the money from people like Bill Gates and Warren Buffett and Teresa Heinz Kerry and just divvy it up amongst all of us lowly peasants?&nbsp; Oh, wait, now I remember, there is a way.&nbsp; It's called either communism, or the Democratic Party platform - I always get those confused.    &nbsp;  Speaking of the Democrats and Kerry....&nbsp; Nah, let's not speak about them.&nbsp; I'll fall asleep on my desk.    &nbsp;  Hold on - gotta read an e-mail.    &nbsp;  OK - I'm back.    &nbsp;  Like Donald Fagan said, "It's nasty weather for July."&nbsp; Where the hell is the summer, dammit?&nbsp; Not that I can enjoy it anyway (ref. earlier posts re: wife's accident).    &nbsp;  No more for me thanks, I'm driving.    &nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Another day, another couple of dollars.&nbsp; As previously noted, I'm dead-dog tired (apologies to the dead-dog-loving crowd).&nbsp; Hopefully I'll have a chance to relax by and in the pool this weekend, although I suspect that Jean will want and need to catch up on sleep, leaving me to watch over both kids yet again.&nbsp; Well, what're ya gonna do?     &nbsp;   Today's quote: "The sky had a baby from my cereal box!!!"          
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       All righty, then.   Is anyone else as sick of this whole working-for-a-living thing as I am?&nbsp; Dragging oneself out of bed, getting proper child care, commuting, making money for someone else, doing something that means diddly-squat in the whole scheme of things - doesn't this all suck eggs?  Now, I'm not really the kind of person who just puts in his hours each day (nine, in my case) and goes home.&nbsp; I do try to do my job to the best of my ability and to make myself upwardly mobile.&nbsp; However, more and more, the thoughts creep into the front of my head (they're always hanging out in the back of my head, drinking tea and eating Drakes' coffee cakes), "Hey!&nbsp; What the hell are we doing?&nbsp; What impact are we making on the world?&nbsp; Why can't we be home taking care of the kids instead of selling advsrtising positions in sales flyers to power tool companies?"&nbsp; And more along those lines.&nbsp; I don't actually know who "we" are - my wife's the one who has&nbsp;multiple personalities, not me.&nbsp; At least I don't think I have them.&nbsp; I'll get back to you on that one.  So what's a person who thinks such thoughts to do?&nbsp; Unfortunately, we happen to live in a society where one requires money to do more than subsist, and such money generally doesn't fall from the sky or multiply like rabbits inside bank accounts.&nbsp; No, those of us without a healthy trust fund must slog through fifty years or so in the work-a-day world of working each day (huh?).&nbsp;   Of course, I fully intend to become financially comfortable and moderately well-known through the commercial sale of my literary endeavors.&nbsp; Now all I have to do is get someone to pay me about $100K a year for writing blogs.&nbsp; Any takers?  ETH NED  Today's TV quotes - deep existential questions: "Lemon curry?" "With a melon?" "This is a cheese shop, isn't it?" 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I knew that being the sole childcare provider, housekeeper, etc., in the wake of my wife's injuries from the accident would be tough - but this is ridiculous!    &nbsp;  I'm already exhausted, after less than two weeks.&nbsp; I'm physically wiped out, from doing everything, stress, and lack of adequate sleep.&nbsp; I'm mentally drained, and emotionally edgy.&nbsp; And let's not even talk about the spiritual - I haven't been to church the last two Sundays.    &nbsp;  Yes, I know, eventually everything will be OK - Jean will heal, I won't need to be SuperDad/Husband, and we'll likely be compensated financially.&nbsp; But for now, this really sucks.    &nbsp;  On a lighter note...    &nbsp;  Today's movie quote: "You will never find a more wretched hive of scum and villany - we must be cautious."&nbsp; (No, not from someone attending the Democratic National Convention.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate driving.&nbsp; Simply put, but true.&nbsp; Now, I don't mean that I dislike driving, or that driving on certain roads gives my agita, or that I'm not fond of my current motor vehicle.&nbsp; I mean, I  hate  driving.  I live on Long Island.&nbsp;&nbsp;It may not be the traffic capital of the world, but it does seem to have more than its share of bumper-to-bumper slowdowns (and stops), as well as a plethora of bad drivers.&nbsp; Such things used to just annoy me, back when I first became a commuter lo these thirteen years ago.&nbsp; Over time, as conditions became worse, they began to really piss me off, and now they have succeeded in frightening me.&nbsp; I will admit that much of my current state of mind is due to my wife's recent accident (see last post).&nbsp; However, in driving about a hundred miles a day for much of the past two years, I have seen drivers do things that...&nbsp; well, frankly they defy any reasonable explanation.  I take that last bit back.&nbsp; The things that a lot of drivers do are actually easily explainable.&nbsp; Plainly put, they care neither about the law nor about anyone other than themselves.&nbsp; And this, gentle reader, stokes in me the belief that this country is well on its way to hell in a handbasket.&nbsp; I will expound on this in future posts (here's a napkin to wipe up your drool).  In the meantime, if you are the type of driver who speeds like the highway is your own personal ractrack,&nbsp;tailgates so close&nbsp;that you're in the other driver's back seat, slams on your brakes for no apparent reason, rubbernecks, etc., please... STOP.  Today's movie quote: "This IS Seti Alpha Five!" 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Aloha, all.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Thus starts my first blog post, nearly two weeks after I registered here at Blogger.&nbsp; Why the delay, pray tell?&nbsp; Because some chick from Hawaii broadsided my wife's car&nbsp;after going through a red light, that's why.&nbsp; She's basically OK, thank God, but qualifies under NY law as being "seriously injured" with a broken shoulder blade and some cracked ribs (with a partially collapsed lung, to boot).&nbsp; So I was out of work almost all last week, this morning, and will be part of Thursday, et cetera and so on.&nbsp; Oh, and when I'm home, since my wife can't use her left arm, I get to do all of the child rearing duties - you know, changing diapers, feeding and stuff.&nbsp; In short, I have had zero time for myself, which is actually only a small reduction from the miniscule amount of time I had for myself before the accident, and add in that I have only a crappy NetZero internet connection at home, and that's why my blog has been blogless until now.&nbsp; OK, so that wasn't short.&nbsp; Sue me.&nbsp; Hey, that's what we're doing to the chick from Hawaii!    &nbsp;  And now, gentle reader, come my hopefully-humorous addenda.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Today's movie quote: "I would like to have seen Montana."  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>