<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Reality TV....can't stand this...it's making me hate my first love (Television).  I hope the madness ends soon, because I'm actually starting to read books and go outdoors again....crazy!  Low-Carb Dieting.....this is the stupidest thing the human race has ever embarked upon.  Carbs are the enemy??? Carbs are the enemy if you sit on your fat ass all day eating a bowl full of deep fried potatoes covered in pasta and cream sauce, and then wipe the bowl clean with a sugar coated sourdough baguette......c'mon people...carbs aren't the problem....sitting on your lazy fat ass is!!!  Being Not Trendy....this is the trendiest thing since trends began back in the stoneage when everyone started wearing those furskin ponchos....people who try really hard to show how alternative they are belong to the trendiest and most hipocritcal group of trendsetters in our society.  You want to really be alternative???  Subscribe to every trend...because no one does that...wear clothes from the Gap, while talking on your cell phone while watching reality television while snacking on a low carb candy bar while wearin a trucker hat and listening to top 40 music...now that would be some crazy alternative shit!  late,  DrunkMitch
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. Dudes that drive convertable roadsters 2. Wild On E (not pissed about the hot chicks and partying, just pissed that I can't be there - really pissed!) 3. Direct TV only offering 4 HD channels 4. Charges for using random ATM's 5. Still using the random ATM's, even though I know I am getting charged 6. Beautiful babies that don't want to skrog me when I stare at them 7. Actresses that call themselves actors 8. Wynona Judd 9. Country Music Awards 10. Cribs - Because I don't understand where they get all that money? 11. Kids that ride a skateboard, but can't ride a skateboard 12. The lady that sits on the other side of my cube, with her nasal East Coast accent. I hate her! 13. Bad Diet Coke mix from the Rotten Robbie on the way to my work 14. Margo Kidder 15. The death of Bradley!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, today I was greeted by a new neighbor in my row of cubes. I spent the last three hours training her how to use various systems and programs and reports... and the whole time, all I was thinking about was the outline of a G-string I could see in her slacks. I am way overdue for something to distract me here at work - so, "Bravo, to you!" hiring manager. Of course, she has no idea how to use any of the systems I trained her on - and - she can't use Excel to save her life... but, it really doesn't matter to me. I have been working with a bunch of idiots for four years now - so, a little G-string action is well deserved.  I'm sure, at first, she will find me clever and engaging and will giggle at my stupid jokes and innocently flirt with me... but eventually, probably sooner than later, she will see me staring at her dirty spot... and then the gig will be up.  But, until then... daddy's home!  Stay Classy San Diego!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       As of 8:47 AM   Cups of coffee:  3   Minutes spent screwing off at work (let's see i've been here 47 minutes):  45   Shoes I wore to work today:  0   Surfing Monkies in my office:  1   Holes in my jeans:  5    Nothing interests me.  And I'm not saying that no thing interests me.  I'm saying..."doing nothing" interests me.  It's my goal.  I want to wake up in the morning with no agenda, no schedule, no appointments.  That would be wonderful.  Don't get me wrong, I'm pretty close to doing nothing already, I've got it way easier than most, but still, I must strive for the ultimate goal of nothing.  Of course, this takes money...people don't realize how much doing nothing costs.  It costs a shitload!  You're not doing anything to generate income, which means you need to have income already.  I suppose you could start a business that requires no work, like putting ATM machines in convenience stores, starting an interenet porn site, etc.  But still...at least one day a month you would have to maintain this business and collect money from it....which totally negates the principle of doing absolutely nothing.  Now, this doesn't mean that I would do nothing...it just means that I wouldn't be required to do anything.  I might get up one day and be active all day long, accomplish things, workout, help others...but this would be totally my choice...not planned or required.  Other days, I might never get out of bed except to get food to bring back to bed, and possibly to put in a new DVD to watch.  Anyways, I'm gonna go for it.....my goal is nothing.  Nothing could make me happier than nothing.  Thank you for your support...god bless.  Out,  DrunkMitch   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have recently noticed that the frequency of when I laugh "out-loud" has been on a steady rate of decline, ever since I can remember.  When I was young, I laughed at everything... and smiled all the time. Was it because the emotion of laughter was new to me then, but now it's getting old - sort of like seeing a movie over and over. Was it because I was young and had less on my mind? Was I less disturbed by the world? I'm sure things weren't funnier then than they are now, so why don't I laugh as much as I used to? I can't remember the last time I caught myself laughing at something on TV. Is TV not funny anymore? Or, was it not funny then, but I was too stupid to know the difference? Am I getting old and laughter/smiling takes too much energy? Am I too lazy to laugh?  When I was young, was I generally happier?   When I get really old, will I even be able to smile? Or, will I just sit around frowning and moaning? I see a lot of old people frowning and moaning, so maybe that's just how it's supposed to be?  Or, as I get older, I could just get drunk more frequently... so I could smile and laugh out loud all the time! Yes, I have decided to drink more, especially when I am very old.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This morning has been the start of what will be a very smelly day. I drank a 64 ounce Diet Coke on the way to work and apparently the ingredients are not mixing well with the remnants of BBQ spare ribs that were already in my digestive tract. The gas is absolutely disgusting, even by my standards. I would describe it as a mixture of sulfur and Ajax gently sprinkled on the rotting body of the Sloth dude from Seven. By all accounts, it is causing extreme discomfort for my coworkers and lending to my already diminished standing amongst my peers. I have decided I will grab a Guinness and some hard boiled eggs for lunch, so I can take it to the next level. My short term goal is to be ostracized - long term goal is that they are forced to give me an office with a door that closes.  Wish me luck!  - Fetzer
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ken (the guy from Jeopardy) TV Shows/Movies/Music:    Crime Drama:   CSI: Ken Law and Order: Special Ken Unit NYPD Ken Miami Ken Ken Street Blues    Situation Comedy:   Ken of Queens The Kensby Show  That 70's Ken Friends...........of Ken Ken and Grace Kenson (the new Benson) The Facts of Ken Two Guys and a Ken    Reality TV:   The Real Ken Who Wants To Beat The Crap Out Of Ken For Love or Ken Ken Factor Ken Swapping Ken Bachelor Kenster Garage While You Were Ken    Movies:   The World According To Ken Apocolypse Ken The Ken Hunter The Ken Mutiny Kens In The Mist Kenfather The Unbearable Likeness of Ken Farenheit Ken My Left Ken Bridge Over The River Ken Ken Fiction Reservoir Kens My Best Friend's Ken Fried Green Kens When Ken met Alex You've Got Ken  I could go on, but at some point today I've got to get to the bars people!!! More to come...  out,  DrunkMitch
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       As of 9:00 AM this morning...   Cups of Coffee:   3   Boobies Looked at:   17  (i know that's an odd number, but one woman I only looked at from the side so I only got to look at one...by the way...yes, I'm a loser)  Curse Words:   73   Thoughts About Women/Sex:   296.5   Pissed off:   4   Songs on my Ipod:   836   Countdown Lists:  1   Ran out of things to countdown:   1   Was funny:   0    Lates,  DrunkMitch    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, as Drunk Mitch would say, "Stop looking at me Swan!"   So,.. Blogging? What The F#@k?!?! I have often wondered just what kind of loser actually spends time posting thoughts in a Web Log? Now that I am one of them, I guess I still don't understand...?  I think I will limit myself to things that piss me off and amusing anecdotes about stupid people... eventually working my way towards lengthy diatribes and conspiracy theories.  Also I will write about tits, beer and movies, whether they piss me off or not!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You can't make this shit up!  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I friggin' hate this guy on Jeopardy Ken.  It's not just his little troll body, and beady little eyes either.  It's the way he answers questions like he doesn't know the answer and somehow he pulled it from his little Hobbit ass.  Or the way he answers questions about foreign names or countries, in a half-assed accent of said country....that really pisses me off.  And last but not least...the way he only bets enough in Final Jeopardy to raise his total to the next 10 thousand mark (34,500...he bets 5,500 for an even 40k)...hey Ken...the game is called Jeopardy, not "Big Pussy", grow a pair buddy!  The only thing I like about the whole situation is how he has become Alex Trebek's arch-enemy.  Alex, can no longer smugly say the answer as if he knew it all along and wasn't simply reading it off the damn card in front of him.  Alex, can't wait to get this guy off the friggin' show, and I like that whole dynamic.    p.s. - If this guy Ken gets any kind of TV show after this, like some reality tv show (Who Wants To Marry Ken) or a friggin' forensics drama (CSI: Ken), or a law drama (Law And Order: Special Ken Unit)....if anything like this happens, I will officially boycot television forever (with the exception of TNT, TBS, USA, FX, A&E, Discovery, and The History Channel)  See ya,  Drunk Mitch
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So Kobe asks the Clippers to play games in Anaheim if they sign him, so that it will be closer to his Newport Beach home.  I love the Lakes, but what an asshole!  He also asked them to change their name to the Kobes instead of the Clippers, and to buy his wife another 4 million dollar diamond so that she would get off his back about the whole "rape thing".  What the f#@k?!?!  He'd better resign with the Lakers or I will officialy be on the warpath.    Other things that have pissed me off so far today:  1.  PT Cruiser with Personalized license plate.  Is that a requirement if you own one of those p.o.s.'s  I hate that shit, makes me want to pull the driver from his car and shake him furiously until he/she steps back into reality.    That's actually it for things that have pissed me off so far today....pretty calm morning so far...  out,  Mitch
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This blog was created Today July 9th, 2004 in order to keep my head from exploding.  As thoughts and emotions of all different types (funny, sad, disturbing, drunk, immature, hilarious, ingenious, brilliant, idiodic, etc.) come slamming into my head, it is important that I excrete them in some manner other than getting shit faced drunk and blurting them out to unsuspecting strangers.  Well, I guess it's not that important, as that system has worked for me for several years now, but i'm doing this anyway.  So welcome, enjoy, comment, whatever...  Laters,  DrunkMitch
     
    
</post>


</Blog>