<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, its 5:25 am in the morning! AM STILL AWAKE! i have bags under my eyes AAAAHHAHAHAHAH BAGS!   So like i feel SO loved! Today me mum came home, and me and my sister were just chillin in my room. She comes down to my room, hugs my sister and says she loves her and then she leaves my room. Thanks MUM i love you TOO! bleh!  I must show you another picture of my beloved boyfriend    Okies so hes not my boyfriend. We all know that. Right? BUT It sounds so wicked cool just to say you got a boyfriend! (or so the people around me make it seem like bleh on them) Walking down a street, go up to a random person "yo man, i have a boyfriend" and then you walk off leaving the random person confused, and thats when you  know you completed your mission.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1:02 and yes am still awake... oddly enough am not sleepily Am telling you its the drugs. Am not on drugs. At least i think am not. But who knows what my mum been putting in my dinner. Last i heard she's been trying to kill me...... 0.o o.0 anyways .... my sister chased me around the house. Then i tackled her and she kneed me in the eye  @.0 yeah, ouch.  Then i get told that i was JEALOUS please...me? jealous ...of chantell and nick? .....theres no words.... Who knows if she was lying to me! AND she told me to GROW UP! (ok so i do need to grow up but thats not the point) That little GIT!   OOO ^_^ i'll post a picture of my  boyfriend MUAHAHAH    Isnt he dreamy? Nobody is aloud to touch or i slap their hands! AND send dogs after them! OR make them spend the day with Tasha ^_^ JK TASHA!  I WUV YOU!!!!!!!!!! I DO! *huggles*   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, am suppose to be cleaning my room...but...eh..its  my room and i'll leave it a mess if want too! *hopes mom didnt hear me*  So yeah, my blog is GAY i can't see any new entries or comments until like a day later what the dog is up with that?  Anyway, check out this new siggy that i made!    Pretty groovy!  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         LOOKIES AT WHAT I MADE! heheh...so bored... nothing to do... nobody to talk... BORED BORED BORED BORED BORED  BORED BORED BORED BORED BORED  BORED BORED BORED BORED BORED  BORED BORED BORED BORED BORED 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So i got a blog but what the  HELMS DEEP am i suppose to do with it? its.... what do i do with it? is it a journal? do i write...er... "type" my feelings down... or...make fun of people... so confussed..... anyway you guys....(who ever may that be) must see my sexay BOYFRIEND with his new hair color    AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAH 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, i totally forgot that i had a BLOG hehe how dim witted of me....VERY anywho..... So nothing much is happning lately excpect this girl got so mad at me she deleted me from her buddy list and her Live Journal List and so on and so on ...apprently am not suppose to live my life with out her....0.o o.0 very ....scary. School is about  to start! YEAH! JOY! NOT! but i did get this new handy dandy bag! am just a little sad, a  friend of mind is moving and she wont be joining with me for drama 3 this year! *cries* shes going to CALI! so far! but thats ok i plan on going to college  there any way, or NY doesnt matter. So i was at my cousin's house she has fishes! lol it was soo funny. This fish suddenly let out this sting of turd ewwww lol and it was stuck to it. so he swam in little cricles till it fineally came off as the sting of turd was falling to the bottom  of the fish tank he swam after it...to a bite of it and then spit it back out and then other fishes started to do that.... fishes are weird...very....weird.... anyway i want ice cream. i hadn't had for a while now! I played goldfish with my sister...i lost HOW CAN I LOST TO GOLDFISH!?!?!?  stupid game anyway. I rather play tig. Very cool game MUAHAHAH So anyway, yesturday my sister and her fat friend came over. We did a little play  called "The dinosours" it was ...short... i was the director! muahaha the only bad part they wouldnt stop laughing when i told them  to feel the anger.*shakes head* stupid little twat they are! but they are cool. Okies i'm going now, only cuz i can LATER 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>