<Blog>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         It is certainly an art to enjoy yourself at any given moment at any given place. Majority often thinks - man, all these people at 'blah' doing 'blah' are definitely having a kickass ass time, if only I was there with them surely I'd be much happier. As one of the side effects of this thinking comes the insecurity in your own decisions. If only I have studied, if only I have known, if only I have bought instead of sold. Rarely do you hear people say - it was the right choice at the time and under those circumstances, it was my decision and I stand by it even though things didn't exactly work out to my liking. There is always someone else to blame, or you weren't in your 'right mind'. It is a lot harder to deal with the consequences and accept the outcome of your actions if the blame is solely on your shoulders.  I wish I didn’t sell...
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These pictures seems every photographer takes but it doesn't make it any less fun          
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My plans never work. If you are superstitious you might call it lack of luck, if you are one of those meticulous nuttcases you might say I don't plan well enough; but the fact remains - nothing ever goes according to plan. As a matter of fact things work out better and more fun if I don't plan at all. Certainly I have an idea what I have to do today and that I have a doctor's appointment Friday morning or what bills are due to be paid, but those are more like rough drafts. Maybe it has to do with crushed expectations. You don't remember the plans that do work out but the ones that don't annoy the shit outa ya for days to come. I read in another blog that people, being the strange creature that we are, often are very drastic - the all-or-nothing way of thinking. So seems to me the solution is - don't make plans. Of course that can result in sitting home on a saturday night (which by the way I don't mind at all) but not stressing it usually results in a more harmonious outcome...at least for me. That kinda thinking could backfire at times in a more inconvenient way than a quiet saturday night. Like procrastinating to call your relatives to pick you up from an airport on the other side of the world could result in a Homer DOH! moment....I'll let you know how it turns out though   
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend of mine, in finance, noted not so long ago that he gets paid way too much in comparison to his doctor mother, and that's not right. He does not create anything feasible or provide any obvious service to society. Say you are a doctor, the best surgeon in the world. You have a terminal cancer patient on your hands, who is in terrible pain and is begging you to end his suffering. Would you go for it? Would you put him out of his misery? So what do you say? No? Since you are a true doctor and by law you are not allowed to kill a patient even if the patient is begging for it no matter what horrific pain he is experiencing. Certainly that's an option, but I pray you not to be my doctor or the doctor of any of my loved ones. But what if you do help the terminal patient? You get caught and never allowed to practice medicine again. Now, being the best surgeon in the world but unable to practice how many lives could you have saved? How many children could you have brought back to life? Now back to our parasite trader. One of his clients is a middle class family man, whose investment pays off enough to put his kids through college, something he would never be able to afford otherwise. Of course, I am not saying a trader is a more morally rewarding (for lack of a better word) profession than a doctor, neither am I questioning who contributes more directly to the society's well-being....just saying it's not that simple
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    All you need is Love
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So from the beginning of time people have been searching for that 'special someone' to hang around the rest of your life, and since the rest of your life usually means quite a bit of time the choice seems to be sort of an important one. People are completely convinced of the existence of that elusive but perfect mating partner somewhere in the population, but blame the difficulties of locating the victim on not being able to get their hands on enough samples to choose from. But the boundaries are once again broken by the all mighty World Wide Web. You can purchase your lovely spouse on the internet through numerous dating sites and dating chat rooms. Yes, even Love can be made a product, and the price can be a hefty one. But who in the world can be penny-pinching when it comes to Love??? I ain’t sayin’ I have a solution. I just find amusing the clever marketing and simplemindedness of an average consumer. 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    heheh
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You often hear people say that they  believe in destiny and so, at the end of every step there awaits some event that was chosen for this particular person at this particular time. I used to think that it might be partially true; there is some force out there that places us in certain situation 'by luck', but I also believe that 'luck' gives you a shot, but what you make of it is totally up to you. So lets say the force above is sitting up there, looking down thinking: "There is Alex walking down the street, he is walking on 40th street, and so to get to work he is gonna have to walk to 5th ave and then make a right and walk down to the office. So now that I have it all figured out, lets make Alex bump into his destiny (whatever the hell that might be) on the corner of 40th and 5th." But instead, I end up making a right on 6th and hence completely avoiding my appointment with distiny and hopelessly missing out on the happiness that was awaiting me on the corner of 40th and 5th.  The reason this strange thing poped into my head is that lately, I've been having this feeling that I keep making a right when I should make a left...don't know what to make of it really
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    To curb speculations on what alexey goz looks like
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For a long time I wanted to have a place to drop a thought down or a frustration out, but due to my very lazy nature I haven't got around to it up until now. Of course the internet is not the best place for your sometimes intimate thoughts because of the privacy issue but since my lazy nature is also a not-care-very-much nature, the conveniences of the internet overpower the lack of privacy.
    
</post>


</Blog>