<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks to Samantha for being the only one to suggest names.&nbsp; Although as of last night, around midnight I'm the proud parent of a new baby boy, "Loki".&nbsp; Named after the Norse god of mischievousness.&nbsp; Oddly I hadn't read Sam's suggestions until just now.&nbsp; But we were on the same wavelength, par for the course I'd say.&nbsp; We always seem to think similarly.   Loki, being the mischievously cunning bastard that he is thus far.&nbsp; Decided he'd like to play 'hide the sound output'.&nbsp; Apparently there's something about the onboard sound in the motherboard and running XP that makes it not want to output, so I'll have to grab a sound card donated by the famous Steve.&nbsp; Not you Exo, someone much cooler.&nbsp; I'm still currently using my old computer until the problem is solved, and I transfer / install the mandatory get me by programs.   I haven't been doing much at work this week.&nbsp; Mostly because the boss is out of town, and the entire department kind of shuts down without supervision, it's kind of sad that we are like small children like that.&nbsp; But I actually have no work of my own to do.&nbsp; Which isn't the case of everyone else here.&nbsp; My only unfinished task that was assigned to me at the beginning of summer is to train 3 other people in how to continue doing what I've done all summer with all the tools they release.&nbsp; I imagine an hour meeting next Monday, and maybe a couple hours with each of the 3 lucky volunteers would pretty much cover me for that.   Speaking of work, there's this chick in IT that has been curiously wandering around the engineering department occasionally.&nbsp; She's the same woman who installed all the garbage programs on this computer for its use as the company whore when I leave.&nbsp; A bunch of digital camera software, some rendering software, FTP, etc&nbsp; Anyway, I don't know how old she is, but I think she's got a little work crush on me.&nbsp; Being a guy, and lonely from not being in a relationship for a long while, I may be misreading signs, as I swear all men do.&nbsp; We're just dumb, remember that ladies.&nbsp; But I think it's mostly the way she walks around our department, which is all the way on the other side of the building, and only says 'hi' to me.&nbsp; She's all smiles too.&nbsp; One of those innocent smiles too.&nbsp; I'm a sucker for a cute smile on a female.&nbsp; We'll see if this persists, but with only working here for another three weeks.&nbsp; I honestly can say I don't think it's worth pursuing.   On the errands I said I was going to do&nbsp;yesterday, little got done.&nbsp; I was all pumped up to get my haircut&nbsp;at work, and 45 minutes later I was just minutes from home, and I said screw it.&nbsp; I just didn't feel like getting my hair cut yesterday.&nbsp; It's funny the way the human mind can just tell your body it doesn't want to do something.&nbsp; I just got a sudden bout of apathy towards the haircut.&nbsp; Don't know why.&nbsp; Didn't really care.&nbsp; But that's apathy for you.&nbsp; I did however make it to the computer store, and purchase a couple needed items for Loki, to get him out of the PBA.   On the work front again, I got an e-mail from Ford yesterday which really irked me the wrong way.&nbsp; The intern on the other end said he had finished everything I'd sent over for the summer.&nbsp; Which I thought was impossible since he said he was only doing like 10 a day.&nbsp; Come to find out Ford seems to think I've only sent 250 parts over this summer.&nbsp; When I mailed them a disc with over 700 parts on it.&nbsp; Not to mention all the files I've transfered via the web.&nbsp; The total on my end is closer to the 850 mark.&nbsp; There's nothing like an intern on the other end trying to cover his own lazy ass.&nbsp; Pass some more blame on the hardest working intern in the tool design industry.&nbsp; By my standards, I think I really impressed the company I work for.&nbsp; They all seem happy that I wasn't like their last intern.&nbsp; He got the job because his daddy is some big wig over at GM.&nbsp; They tell me he didn't do a bit of work all summer.&nbsp; Now I've taken more 'days off' than most interns, and quite frankly, more than I like to, this summer.&nbsp; But I don't get paid days off.&nbsp; So the opportunity cost of time off is great for me.&nbsp; I basically have to pay through the nose for it.&nbsp; But despite all my time off, I've ran the company out of work for me.&nbsp; This makes me 3 for 3 on the work-a-holics list for summer internships.&nbsp; If I only would have gotten that job last summer at Harley-Davidson, but I try to block that out of my memory it was a bad experience.&nbsp; I lost pretty much all respect for their company as a business for it too.&nbsp; I'd like to think that after 2 phone inteviews, and the company flying me out, and renting me a car for the day for a plant tour, and a 3rd interview, competing against 3 other people, that they'd at least contact me whether or not I got the job.&nbsp; But after 3 weeks when I e-mailed, and called, and e-mailed, and called (I know I put this down more than once.&nbsp; It was intentional.)&nbsp; They still never returned any messages to my question of whether or not they had come to a decision.&nbsp; Even if they changed their mind and weren't going to hire an intern for the summer, I would have at least liked to get some sort of contact saying so.  Alright, I've just ranted my way into a much needed coffee break.&nbsp; I could either blow off this steam, or I could drink it, and piss it out.&nbsp; I chose the later. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, we are in the process of assembling my new computer.&nbsp; The case is as high tech as it comes, and with it some minor difficulties.&nbsp; This monster of a computer lacks the one key ingredient that makes my computers...Well...Personalized.&nbsp; I like to name my computers.&nbsp; they are like my children.   My first child - The Overmind; after my favorit'est of games.  My second child - Sheman; as vain as I am, this one was named after me.  My third child - Gengar; the ghost with the most, I think so!  My fourth forbidden love child - Batman; this is the one I'm using right now typing up this Blog.&nbsp; Like&nbsp;the good servant of Gotham he's protected me, and kept me within a safe and warm loving embrace since day one.&nbsp; (Batman will be sadly missed, for about 5 seconds after he's gone)&nbsp; At least he's going to a good home.   My newest creation though.&nbsp; Remains nameless for the time being.&nbsp; Simply unable to come up with a compelling enough name to satisfy my primal need to procreate.&nbsp; I simply haven't thought of a name yet.&nbsp; There is plenty of time though.&nbsp; As with all the problems we've came across assembling it in the last 3 hours it seems like it's going very slow.   Now don't get me wrong.&nbsp; Slow is no where in this computers name,&nbsp;it is the antithesis of slow.&nbsp; It is slows most bitter enemy.&nbsp; This computer is wiser than the overmind, more vain than even myself, more diabolical than the ghostly Gengar, stronger and faster than Batman.&nbsp; This computer is the destroyer of eternities, the swallower of souls, the eater of babies, the flame that burns the unburnable, and the breaker of myths.&nbsp; It is beyond me of a name.&nbsp; That is why I ask, no plead to you, my blog viewers, to please assist me in naming this contraption.   Something masculine, something strong, something with so much cock in the mere saying of it's name that will make it bow down before me, it's master.&nbsp; (Please post name ideas to me via AIM, or in the Comments section below)   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I'm in Halifax still.&nbsp; I haven't killed anyone or gotten killed myself.&nbsp; Which is always a plus.   The party was pretty lame with only about 80 people showing up.&nbsp; So I switched out of "Try to get laid" mode, and into "Let's fucking tear it up and get hammered!" mode.&nbsp; I was one hurting unit by 4am, and decided that I'd pass out on the couch.&nbsp; Then again, I did finish off an entire&nbsp;fifth of vodka, some jello shooters, and a couple other drinks that I nabbed out of coolers come the time people started leaving.   Steve, as it turns out, isn't as much of a ladies man as bragged up to be.&nbsp; With his myriad array of underage poon that he invited.&nbsp; Only 3 girls showed up and they all slept with his buddies.&nbsp; Sorry Steve, maybe you need to work on your game a little.   The trip has been great so far though.&nbsp; We've been taking some footage with his Sony, and will definitely get that online for those interested in viewing it.&nbsp; The party footage is really just Steve walking around way too intoxicated to speak.&nbsp; He mumbles to himself a lot, and apparently had a fascination with filming my crotch while I was passed out on a couch.&nbsp; Strange fellow that Steve.&nbsp;   The only problems I have with Canada is their freaking ridiculously priced cigarettes.&nbsp; over 10 bucks for a pack of smokes?&nbsp; No thanks.&nbsp; But as I'm an addict, I keep buying them regardless of the cost.&nbsp; It's almost as much of a habit for me to just purchase them as it is to smoke them.&nbsp; I think that's one of the biggest obstacles to me quitting.&nbsp; Not going into convience stores where they are proudly displayed.&nbsp; I need to avoid this, people that smoke, as that makes me want one really bad too.&nbsp; Big Italian style meals are also a problem, any place where you gorge yourself until your super full, then after all that I just want a cigarette.   My new computer should be completely in at Mike's place when I get back.&nbsp; I'm pretty pumped up about setting that up.&nbsp; New games coming out this Fall will hit my pocketbook a bit too.&nbsp; There's about 3 that I can see myself playing quite a bit.&nbsp; World of Warcraft (MMORPG), Dawn of War (RTS), Resident Evil 4 (Gamecube).&nbsp; All these games look sweet, and with my new system I should be able to run them all flawlessly, and still have power to spare.&nbsp; I really like games when they are fun to play, and there's tons to look at.&nbsp; If the developers put sufficient time and effort into the graphics, then they'll be rewarded by a great game.  Well that's about all for today.&nbsp; As we have other stuff to do on my last night in Halifax.&nbsp; I think we'll head out around town again today.&nbsp; After all I don't think I did enough walking up and down big fucking hills the last couple days.  Until I get back home.&nbsp; Shop Smart, Shop S-Mart!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Actual conversation today with Larry Hessanian, who I've nick-named "The Macabre Clown".  &nbsp;  Me - "Damn, I've got something in my eye". *rubbing eyeballs trying to get it out*  Larry - "Yeah, it's your finger, and it doesn't seem to be coming out."  &nbsp;  That gave me a great chuckle this morning.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I don't know why, but my chair at work seems to stretch my legs so that they get really sore when I stand up for while.&nbsp; Maybe they are designed that way to keep me in it for a longer period of time, working.&nbsp; Speaking of which, my vacation starts this Thursday.&nbsp; I'm going to Halifax, Nova Scotia for my buddies Big Beach Blast.&nbsp; Indoor beach, palm trees, free booze, what's not to like?&nbsp; I leave D-town at 6am, which&nbsp;is kinda convenient, as I'll have to be there around 5am, which is about the time I normally get up for work, and Mike's normally getting home from work.&nbsp; This trip marks the 4th of my DOH Gathering stops.&nbsp; Meeting the guys I've basically grown up with, has been quite memorable, except Edwin (Trix) because he wouldn't make his mom cook me Chinese food made by real Chinese people!&nbsp; Not&nbsp;that restaurant processed crap that I love so much.&nbsp; He at least went to a really upscale nice Chinese restaurant in town though.&nbsp; After meeting James (Zerocool), Edwin (Trix), Axire (Axire, dude I don't think I even know your real name.&nbsp; As far as I'm concerned your just a figment of my imagination anyway.), Ed (Fission), Joe (Destroyer), James (Xenon).&nbsp; I've concluded that I have been blessed to have known, and grow up with these gentlemen and scholars of whom I still haven't met in person most of them.&nbsp; But as long as there's the DOH forums, and I still keep posting, I'll make it a goal to see the ones I've known (and liked, because I won't ever visit BrianBond007, Fuck that guy!&nbsp; LOL).&nbsp; So Steve (Exodus) you better be ready for the PBA.&nbsp; Because it'll catch you when you least expect it!&nbsp; And it will be recorded, as the 11th PBA I've handed out to one time or another DOH'ers.&nbsp; So get ready to party, and let loose the original PBA&nbsp;Monster in your hometown.  &nbsp;  We've been LAN'ing it up at Justin's house the last couple days.&nbsp; Apparently while I was either at work, or asleep after work, Justin decided to do some electrical work in the house, and shut down all the computers, and in the process of throwing the breakers back on, fried my power supply.&nbsp; I was fortunate enough that he had an extra one that even had an additional 20 Watts of power *Woohoo, minor upgrade* which worked fantabulously when installed.&nbsp; Just played some games, after my 6-9 nap, and passed out again around 1:3am, just to wake up around 5:15am to go to work.&nbsp; It's kind of strange, I'm actually getting used to getting very little sleep again and getting up really early in the morning to be functional.&nbsp; My normal insomniac lifestyle during school is stay up till 3-4am, and sleep till 8am or so then get up not having to leave till about 9am.&nbsp; Although, I must say that I'm getting quite bored with my drive to and from work, and the amount of time I spend away from my friends and family.&nbsp; I figure I work 8 hours + 45 minute unpaid lunch + 90-100 minutes of driving both ways to work + occasional gas stop / check cashing / errands.&nbsp; I'm generally busy 'working' from 5am till 5pm.&nbsp; I use the term working loosely, to include all the other activities involved in my trips to and from work.&nbsp; Add my sleep schedule to that, which is about 4-6 hours a night, and I'm basically only spending 6-8 hours with my friends.&nbsp; Some of which is sans Mike, because he leaves a bit earlier for work.&nbsp; I guess the overall question that needs to be asked is; Is it worth it?&nbsp; Hell yeah it is.&nbsp; I figure when I graduate college there's no telling where I'll be working, shit I could be in Florida, California, Las Vegas, the dreaded Wisconsin, etc.&nbsp; I might not be able to visit my good friends on a month by month basis for much longer.&nbsp; Their company would be dearly missed.&nbsp; But I'll stop talking about the future before I start to cry.  &nbsp;  So with both of the projects they had me working on for the summer winding down, and me with only a month to the day left of working here.&nbsp; I look back and ask myself what have I accomplished this summer.  &nbsp;  - Made money (Which was really needed after spending a good deal on Spring Break, and various other things throughout the year, while not working)  - Learned a new CAD program, SolidWorks.&nbsp; Normally in college you have to pay for a class on how to use something like this.&nbsp; So that's a definite bonus, and something to put on my resume.  - Made more business contacts for employment after graduation.&nbsp; With the job market still looking a little dim for graduating engineers, even from MTU, I need all the help I can get.&nbsp; And I've even heard a few people say that with the job that I've done here they'd probably hire me back next summer, or even after I graduate.&nbsp; Which would be awesome.&nbsp; I like a lot of the people I work with here.&nbsp; And I know that a few will be soon retired, and a couple who are transferring out of the department.&nbsp; The location kinda sucks, as it's pretty far from Mike's house, where I'd spend most of my after job hours presuming I did get the job.&nbsp; But many other employees here drive the same commute I do.&nbsp; And the increase from intern pay would also help offset the gas cost of the longer drive.&nbsp; Besides I could also split the distance and live somewhere in between work, and Mike's.  - A few contacts at Ford.&nbsp; Now Ford is the solid money spot.&nbsp; Closer to Mike's with divisions within 5, 15, and 30 minutes of Mike's house the location is better suiting.&nbsp; The pay would most likely be higher as well.&nbsp; I've talked with a few guys that work there, and they seem to think that I'm a damn good engineer here at SPX, and might even try to headhunt me out of college.  &nbsp;  Now living and working in the greater Detroit area after college is a good thing, and even possibly worth a significant cut in starting pay to do.&nbsp; Based on the fact that I'm kind of already established here.&nbsp; But first things first, let's get through college and get the resumes out in the working world.&nbsp; We'll see who comes knocking on my door.  &nbsp;  My trucks been running well.&nbsp; Needs an oil change soon, and since I've gotten rid of a lot of the garbage in the back, I think I'll pull everything out and let them have a go at vacuuming up some more of that glass.&nbsp; It's like it comes out of no where.&nbsp; No matter how many times you think you've gotten it all, it jumps out of places you wouldn't expect and litters the back again.&nbsp; I might even go as far as to have the interior detailed.&nbsp; As there's a few stains on the seats and floors that I could do without, and a good protective finish couldn't hurt the dash.&nbsp; This is just a thought though.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Wow, I've spent way too much time into this post.&nbsp; I guess it is warranted as tomorrow I'll be packing for Halifax, and the following few days will be in Halifax, and probably won' update till Monday, or most likely Tuesday evening.&nbsp; So until then Bat-Fans.&nbsp; Adios, and Mahalo.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a delicious BELT today.&nbsp; Fresh crisp bacon, crisp lettuce, just the right amount of Mayo, and toast so mouthwatering I can still taste it.&nbsp; Like any carniverous human being, I love bacon.&nbsp; I'd have to put a good few pieces of bacon almost as delectable as a sirloin steak.&nbsp; I like dead cow as much as the next REAL MAN (TM), but the little piggy that did in fact go to the market, after having his roast beef, is mighty tasty.&nbsp; Enough salivating over today's blog entry.  &nbsp;  So after having a fun filled weekend I do what any normal sane person would do.&nbsp; I stay up all night having fun, until I look at a clock and realize, I'd best get home to clean up for work.&nbsp; Well in the rush of scrambling to gather clean clothes, shave, and grab a quick bite of breakfast (Sorry Jew Lee, I ate your Berry Blast cherish) I realize now mid-day that I missed a few spots shaving.&nbsp; Now they aren't exactly noticeable, but I can definitely feel where I missed.&nbsp; Getting 5 o'clock shadow before noon is definitely unwarranted for the scrutinize care I tried to give my beard region this morning.&nbsp; The clothes I grabbed, mostly black, and of course the sun is beating down like a step mother on her red-headed son.&nbsp; The boss is out of the office this week, which means even less supervision and consequently my will to finish up my project.&nbsp; Oh well I got plenty of time to do it before summer is completed, and it's not like Ford has gotten too much further.&nbsp; I've already buried them under about a half year of work according to their calculations.  &nbsp;  Talked to my folks again today.&nbsp; In preparation for my Halifax trip, I wanted to make sure my financial aspect of my schooling was in check.&nbsp; Of course my dad is having surgery on his throat this week and couldn't do anything else...Like file his taxes which are very late...AGAIN!&nbsp; Now, it doesn't really matter much because I can always front the money for college, and when he gets them done I get reimbursed, but if the last few years have been any indicator, this would be around November.&nbsp; Meaning I get to live for 4 months on the super poor route.&nbsp; It's a shame there isn't much I can do about living exposing and food, since that money is paid up front.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I re-ordered my new computer.&nbsp; Hopefully that will be here in the next couple weeks, and I'll have it up and running in time for college.&nbsp; Speaking of college, this summer of love, has turned out to be a summer of spending way too much time on the road to and from, and shit even AT work.&nbsp; Not that I mind getting paid well for doing practically nothing.&nbsp; I just get bored with doing the same damn thing day in and day out.&nbsp; I guess it'd be better if I wasn't an intern here.&nbsp; I'm not doing entry work, but I sure as heck feel like a line worker.&nbsp; General feelings of apathy towards my project.&nbsp; I have to take a day off from it here and there just to keep my brain moving.&nbsp; Being as tired as I am right now doesn't help either.&nbsp; A bunch of the parts just kind of meld together on my screen, and I have trouble remembering how things went together by the time I open, save and transfer 40+ files over to the machine where the real work gets done.&nbsp; So I instead mill about setting up files for the next day / week by running these really long searches on the drive where the files start for their locations.&nbsp; I first thought this would be a bad idea, but it sure does save time over haphazardly guessing where 50+ files are that could be listed under different names.&nbsp; Oh well only a week or so more of this project and I'll run them out of work just like I did my last 2 internship.  &nbsp;  I finally got to see  Dodgeball .&nbsp; Man that's a pretty good comedy movie.&nbsp; Been a while since I've laughed at a movie like that in a while.&nbsp; Next will probably be  Anchorman , and  The Village.     &nbsp;  I came in to work today all tired, expecting e-mails from Sarah to cheer me up.&nbsp; And I get nothing today.&nbsp; I mean I had to call my folks up and talk for about a half hour each just to get my eyes away from the computer screen for a while.  &nbsp;  While talking to my Mom she said that she had a weird dream about me the other day.&nbsp; That I was a baby and I was burning up with a fever, so she put me in the freezer, and forgot to get me out.&nbsp; She as asking the doctors if there was any way she could warm me out of the block of ice.&nbsp; They told her I was hopeless because of the thick ice checks all over from the experiment gone wrong.&nbsp; My mom lighted thou.&nbsp; I didn't find that funny at all.  &nbsp;  I think that's it for today's workday ranting:  Until next time TV Land;&nbsp; Same Bat-time, Same Bat-channel.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It seems that an entire summer of burning the candle at both ends has started to get to me.&nbsp; All my friends work nights.&nbsp;&nbsp;And the ones that don't, want to hang out till around 1am, where I draw the line and say I gotta get *some sleep*.&nbsp; When my insomnia doesn't kick in that is.&nbsp; Sometimes I just stare at the ceiling for a couple hours and then say screw it, because really if I'm not able to fall asleep after two hours of lying down, am I really going to after 3, 4 hours?&nbsp; And what good would it do?&nbsp; I have to be up at 5am everyday.&nbsp; Gotta get to work by 6:45am and that's about 45 minutes from here.&nbsp; Now I'd normally sleep in the afternoon if I wasn't getting enough sleep the night before.&nbsp; But this is really the only 'fun' time I have to spend with my friends.&nbsp; I usually overload my weekend schedules too.&nbsp; What with the GLWL, and this RTT coming up.&nbsp; Next weekend on be in Halifax, a vacation at last.&nbsp; Taking 3 days off work, Thurs-Mon, will be nice to not have to get up early in the morning.&nbsp; But even still I can't sleep all day on vacation.&nbsp; I'll be visiting a friend I haven't ever even hung out with, in a town I've never even been too.&nbsp; Shit, it's even a province of Canada I've never been to.&nbsp; The good and bad news of this is my flex time.&nbsp; As a temporary summer employee, I'm not allowed to work overtime at work.&nbsp; But yesterday, the IT department decided to come to my desk right at 3:30pm, not normally I'd be out the door and ready to go, but I was finishing up a task.&nbsp; I've never been one to quit inthe middle of something.&nbsp; Anyway, my flex time schedule allows me to apply the half hour I stayed over to any day during the week, so that I can leave early.&nbsp; So I've got a half hour for today that I can stroll out at 3pm.&nbsp; Only problem is, by the time I get home (3:45pm) I'm going to have to nab a little extra shut eye to make up for my late nights, and lack of sleep all week. &nbsp; I have crammed a lot of fun into every weekend.&nbsp; A lot of plans have been made, and I never disappoint.&nbsp; I'll be there with bells on.&nbsp; I'll enjoy myself that's not the problem.&nbsp; I guess the problem is my health.&nbsp; I haven't been feeling well in the mornings.&nbsp; Now it's not like I think I'm sick, just I have never been a morning person, and I think the lack of sleep decreases my immune system.&nbsp; I hate doctors, and I've never been a big fan of medicine.&nbsp; Funny that since my sister, and my mom are both nurses, my dad used to be a teacher at the hospital too.&nbsp; All these medical personel in my family and I don't like to use their services.&nbsp; I'm not a hypochondriac, or get sick all the time.&nbsp; It usually boils down to once a year that I get something so wrong that I have to go to the hospital.&nbsp; Be it appendicitis, back spasms, etc.&nbsp; Usually something so unbearable that I go there just to get away from it.&nbsp; I think spending 3 weeks in a hospital with no food or water when I had my appendicitis did this to me.&nbsp; I mean I was in pain, always hungry, and yet I didn't really even want to move out of the bed.&nbsp;  &nbsp; On to a brighter note.&nbsp; Ford e-mailed me today.&nbsp; They've mysteriously gotten&nbsp;a bunch of the parts to work yesterday.&nbsp; Although they couldn't explain why they were working other than, grim determination to make them work.&nbsp; Now isn't that a crock of shit if you've ever heard one.&nbsp; I bet it was all the solutions I gave them but they never tried.&nbsp; And since I went there on Tuesday afternoon, and changed all the settings in their shit.&nbsp; Anyway, I guess I should be getting going to work now. &nbsp; As for what I'll do when I get home, we'll see when I get home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thinking happy thoughts didn't save me from wanting to strangle some Ford employees yesterday at the meeting.  Somehow they couldn't access the burnt disc that I had brought.  It just wouldn't open on any Cd-ROM they had.  I found that very strange, as they dodge quite possibly my best failsafe that I had to cover my own ass.  But seeing as how those dodgy bastards managed to find a loophole in my system I also found a loophole in theirs.  Threw the shoe ont he other foot, and then kicked it at them.  It worked.  Although we are still at square one with our problem.  They can get 66.66% of the parts I've done in, but I find out that they can't even get them all the way through their system.  I found out a couple other errors they've been having that they just never told me about, and I fixed those as well.  Funny how little things like switching to Assembly mode, when trying to load up an assembly works wonders.  THE SYSTEM IS DOWN!  I wasn't escorted out of the building this time.  I could have pulled some serious James Bond shit and stole some top secret Ford documents, but I didn't.  I figured I had my hands full with my stuff as it was.  Got to make it home slightly earlier yesterday too, seeing how as I was already half way home, and I would have wasted another hour driving to and from work to work 30 minutes.  I still get paid for the full 8 though.  Anyway, time to begin another fine day at work.  With the only silver lined cloud being the fact that it's Coney Day at Lefty's.  I love Coney Day!  I love Coney Dogs.  And I really like the fact that by the time I'm done eating my coney dogs, it's more than half way through the week at work.  Oh yeah, I get to beat the snot out of that cheater guy in the GLWL too.  It's going to be so funny that I'm bringing along my rules lawyers, who aren't fucking around, their packing heat!  It's not hockey night in Canada, but it'll sure feel like it when I'm done bringing the pain to his lame army, and even lamer list.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well off to the job once again.  Today I get to take a special visit to Ford.  For those of you who don't understand what exactly it is I do.  My job is really quite simple.  I take a model of a part on a computer, open it up, save it as a different format, FTP it to a UNIX computer, open it up, re-constrain it (basically put all the screws and joints back into in the part), save it as yet another format, FTP it back to a Windows machine, and then transfer it to Ford.  Doesn't sound to difficult does it?  Well Ford seems to be having problems opening the work I've been doing for the last 6 weeks.  I tried to tell them they should be checking files from day 1.  Now I'm over 80% done with the entire project, ahead of schedule I might add, and they hit problems.  Well technically to give them the benefit of the doubt, I got the first call at just beyond the 50% mark, but still.  I tried opening the files on our end; reversing the process.  Worked fine.  I tried to phone them how to open them as I did to get a working model.  They couldn't get it to work.  They stop calling me with problems for a week.  I continue on, get another 30% done, then they e-mail me, and say they still haven't gotten anything to work and that we should fix it.  Now I normally wouldn't have a problem with this.  But basically what they are doing here is saying that we should do their end for them, I'd do that, if they were paying me to do so.    There is an intern on the other end, basically the only guy there I'm dealing with.  His name is Shannon, which I find odd, because I thought I was talking to a female before he called me up.  So based on Ford's incompetence to finish my project, and my great desire to get it done, I'm going to take the helm at today's meeting, all by myself.  I'm going over there to sit at a table with 10 guys from Ford, by myself.  I'm marching into enemy territory armed only with my knowledge of the project, and the vast feeling I'm being suckered into doing more work than I really need to.  I've came to one conclusion.  People who work at Ford must have to force themselves to have problems so that they can say that their job is warrented and they don't need to be eliminated.  When I took over the project the guy before me had only 1 guy on the other end of the phone.  If there ever was a problem, he'd just fix it on his own.  Unfortunately, he only ran through one test case that worked flawlessly with Shannon, and now their process is jumbled.  On the bright side, I get to be the superhero I always wanted to be!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am weak willed in the ways of staying out of the crowd.  Like a herd of cattle I simply start a blogger to post my inner thoughts of the day.  It's almost mind blowing as to how many strangers will probably read this, and all my friends of days old and days new, tehy'll be here too.  Sort of like being in Downtown Detroit, in the bad area of town, without a weapon to fight back.  Go on ladies and gentlemen, rob my mind.    Well, a good friend, Dennis came up from the Navy this weekend.  I'm calling in to work today.  Stayed out late last night, at Cedar Point.  And besides could be the last time I see him for a long while.  Man hard to belive it's been a year since the last time I got to see him, and that was for his going away party.  The lives of man pass quickly in this world of ours.  I have to wonder, if calling in to work is worth seeing him for what is probably the last time in a even greater while.  College, and the working world beyond is kind of scary like that.  I have no idea where I'll be next summer, and a year after that, I could be someplace else working overseas.  I just don't know.  And quite frankly, I've have nightmares about not staying in contact with my friends who love and care for me like no one else will.   Albeit it's not like I'm just going to give up and quit.  I must press on, through all the hardships that pass my way.  I am strong, I will not give up.  I will never succumb to the little voices in my head that tell me what I don't want to hear.  Everything has a strange way of working itself out in the end.  You can't kill what you did not create.  I AM ETERNAL!  Nicoli
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well another long week without a post in my blog. I apologize for those of you that want to stay informed. It's been quite a rough week though. Lots of stuff going on in my life. Between the funeral, work, driving, picking up Dennis from the airport, hanging out with Dennis for the short time he's here, etc. A lot of time has been chalked up in the time well spent category, but at what cost to my sanity, and my free time? Answer, a huge chunk of free time has been well spent doing the above things. Would I do it again, in a heartbeat.  The funeral service was very nice for Joel. His band mates came in and showed his mom the matching tattoos they got. All on their inner calf, a red star with a black outline. Inside the star was Joel Douglas Bedore, his birthdate, and his deathdate. Joel had this same star on his forearm. Very touching to know that his bandmates cared that much about him to immortalize him on their person. I thought it was a great idea, and showed a lot of commitment to their dear friend. Joel also had many friends drive up from Southern Indiana to the funeral. His immediate family held up quite well. As my Aunt Mary said, "With all the crying you've (to the deceased's mother) done at the hospital, you've shown great resolve to substain it here." After all how much crying can you do for 6 days straight. My Uncle Doug was taking it quite well. He's normally a fairly silent guy. During the break in the viewing he took a walk along the coast to watch the powerboats come in. A little something to kind of get away, and alone for a little bit. My cousin Kyle, 27, was in the anger stage of coping with loss at the beginning of the viewing, and said some pretty mean things to my sister. They've always had their spats, but being my sister's maid of honor at her wedding, and not spending a whole lot of time with her was a little nerve wracking on my sister. They've made up every time, as they are about as close friends as each other has. But Kyle's words hurt my sister at the viewing, although later she apologized, and we told my sister that her anger was probably about the loss anyway.  Saturday, we held a kegger at Josh's. Sort of a coming home Dennis thing. Or was it the housewarming part deux? I took the time to kind of drink in solemnity in wake of Joel's death. I've always preferred that way of mourning the dead, by partying and having a good time. In fact that's the way I want my funeral to be. I'm leaving 100$ for a keg of beer, maybe more for some hard liquor in my will to be used for my wake. I would rather people celebrate my life, and their thankfulness that they are alive, than to mourn my death. Although I know that my parents would not approve of such a wake, it is my wishes. I'd also probably ask to keep the viewing short, only a single day or the better part thereof. And have the funeral either that evening, or the following morning. That way relatives and friends are stuck being shacked up in a hotel for a long period of time.  Sunday, hung out with friends a bunch, as Dennis leaves tonight (Monday). I got to bed way later than I would have wished, and woke up later than I would have liked to as well. But I made it to work, and started the process of logging my hours, because I think I was underpaid for the summer. Something about my last two checks being for under 60 hours, when a typical check logs me for 80. Although I see that I've only actually worked one 80 hour period though. A couple of 72's (day off), the vacation to Halifax work week at 57 (56+1 overtime, 3 days off) and a 64 (2 days off). So I took 7 days off this summer. Although I don't technically get any vacation time, and am supposed to work all 5 days every week throughout summer. I "buy" my days off, by not getting paid for them. All in all, I'm out $840 gross for all my time off this summer. BUT, I've had a great summer, probably better than my past summers with internships.  Today: Dennis leaves today *tear*. Sad to see him go so soon. I was busy for almost 2 full days of his 4 day stay. So I got 50% less Dennis time than everyone else. But that's alright, as the other things I did were deemed adequate usages of time determined by myself. I might go to the Heart concert tonight with Julie. I haven't decided if I want to drive out there or not. It is only $5 though, and would be the 4th (?) concert I saw this summer. Which is above average, but when you only blow $5 a pop plus gas on them, it's a great deal. I enjoy going to concerts a bunch, as long as I get to go with good friends.  I'll try to be a bit more diligent about filling out my Blog in the future while I'm at school. Just remember, I do it for the fans! All of you blog readers who digest my every day with voracity like a rabid wombat! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have some sad news folks.  My cousin Joel has died at the young age of 24. He was driving his sister home from Indiana where they had spent the weekend hanging out with old friends. He dropped his sister off in Grand Rapids, and continued on his way to New Haven. Around 3am on Sunday morning, a drunk driver crossed the centerline and hit Joel head on. He suffered a broken aorta, and massive hemorrhaging in the brain. He was airlifted to Grand Rapids hospital. The doctors were unable to operate on him due to the condition he was in. He was unconscious from 3am till around 10pm last night. His family, with the doctors recommendation that there was nothing they could do to save him, decided to pull the plug on his life support and donate his organs.  His sister begged him to stay the night with her at her place. But all he wanted was to sleep in his own bed that night.  If this happened to my sister. I don't know what I'd do. I've never had a direct family member die. But I've had way too many young people in my life taken before their time. With so much left unaccomplished in their life. So many good times yet to be had. All lost.  I guess this just goes to prove why I don't believe in religion. Too many bad things happen to good people. People who have so much left in their life to accomplish not only for themselves, but for the good of others. Why would God deprive them and the world of their existence? He doesn't. Because he-himself doesn't exist. When you die, you get buried or cremated (your choice) and you sit there and decompose over time. I'm not sure when, if ever, they'd dig you up. Because eventually many zillions of years down the road we'd run out of earth to put them in. But the point is simple. There is no human soul. Well there is, but when you die it doesn't continue on, it dies with you, and it takes a bit of your friends, and loved ones souls as well.  Now I've always been a rock when it comes to emotions. I don't cry, much. I don't get mad or angry, or jealous. I'm really just trying to stay happy in light of all bad things that fall upon me while I'm alive. I figure that if I do one thing that makes me happy everyday, then no day will go by that I think was wasted. ***Some of you probably don't want to hear this next part, so if your timid, just scroll down to the next paragraph.*** If I got fired from my job, my car broke down, my dog died, and my house burnt down. I'd still be happy at the end of the day just rubbing one out. Because it makes me happy. Even if just for a brief moment of the day.  Although, it's not all I do to make myself happy. I could go for a long drive in my truck (probably not anymore, at least for a while), get drunk, play some games with friends, visit an old friend, eat a nice meal at a sit down restaurant, buy myself something I thought I've really deserved and wanted over the last month, year, week, whatever. There's plenty of stuff in this life that makes me happy. And I alone have control over when I do them to compensate for a shitty day. Most times I do them on a regular basis. I figure that as long as I never go to bed thinking I've wasted a day of my life in sadness, misery, heartache, anger, and any other negative thoughts. That I've done damn good for myself that day. I've made the most of what I had, and I had a good time with it. Regardless of anything bad that could happen in my day, short of death.  I do however, not tell my family, and friends that I love them enough. I'm one of those people who just don't call my parents, they usually call me. Same with my sister. My friends, I generally keep in great contact with, through E-mail, IM's, phone, even snail mail if I have to. Most times I often live with them for long periods of time, but still have trouble telling them often how much I enjoy spending time with them, and just in general being a part of their life.  Remember to cherish your friends and loved ones everyday you get with them could be the last. And remember to make the most of what little time you are alive on this Earth. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Where to start...I'll try from the beginning.  Thursday - I played a couple games of Warhammer for the GLWL league. Went 1-1-0 losing to Chris's High Elves, and lucking out against Mark's Daemonic Legion. Only one game to go, and Mark kind of already crowned my division champion. Which means that I'll have to come back down for the tournament around the 2nd or 3rd week of school to play some more.  Friday - Worked myself to the bone, came home and got a good 8 hour nap in, before getting up and realizing I had slept much longer than the 2 hours I wanted to. Did some random errands and passed back out after only 4 more hours. I guess that's what I get for not getting much sleep during the week.  Saturday - Josh invited a bunch of us over for alcohol, and euchre. I chipped in about 50% of the money and by the time I got back to Josh's. I didn't feel like drinking. Oh well, I guess I kind of owed them a bit, I did drink a lot of beer at their housewarming party. Loki is 95% operational, he's only missing a couple of installs that I've been too lazy to do, and one bug that makes it so I can't log onto AIM via Trillian. Oh well, I still haven't fixed that garbage, I'll get around to it sometime.  Sunday - I woke up, played a bunch of videogames, because I wasn't feeling well. Then come about 6:00pm it was time to go to the concert with Julie. We went and saw a full orchestra, and a 5 piece rock band play Led Zepplin tunes all evening. It was a kick ass show. They played all my favorites. And their rendition of Stairway to Heaven, was fucking fantastic! After the long drive home we decided that we were both hungry for Nachos. I love nachos, Julie loves nachos. Together we are a nacho eating team! So a late night trip to Taco Bell before hitting up the house to eat. It was a fun time. I don't do nearly as much with Julie as I do with Mike. And I kind of regret that, because although they are like family to me, I seem to spend more time with Mike. I don't like to play favorites. It's not that I love them any less (Julie and Mom) I just have more in common with Mike I think. But I digress, it was a blast as always hanging out with Julie. And we need to get together and see some more movies. We haven't did that in freaking forever. We saw a guy with a bi-hawk, proving that my haircut was not just a fad, and that it was cool. Only I did it way too long ago, so now I don't know how cool it would be to have a bi-hawk.  Monday - Work was long and tedious. I had to do my normal days work, prepare and train 4 people on how to use software they've all but forgotten how to use, or never even knew existed. All this so that when I'm gone my job will still get done. I was playing catch up for them for the past 7 years, while this crap load of work accumulated. And in one summer I've shoveled that pile of shit down to the grass. I even combed out all of the little cling-ons to the blades of grass with a magnifying glass. Went home and slept, because I didn't sleep much the night before. I hate insomnia.  Tuesday - Hey I did some more tools. Yeah pretty boring day in my life. Mike and I went to Quizno's for dinner. I had a tasty Chicken and Bacon club. My first time eating there. That is much better than Subway, and for the cost I could have gotten 24" of sub for the cost of my one 8" sub and a cup of soup. You see, quantity and a little quality can always beat up quality and a high price in my book anyday. Besides I like Subway, after working there for a whole month while at school, I know how to make some pretty damn tasty subs by mixing sauces. I've always been a sauce fan. The more sauce, the more flavorful the sandwich. I guess that's why I'm one of the few people who actually don't mind bologna and cheese sandwiches. I just slap some mustard, and mayo (For those of you that don't know, Miracle Whip is not mayonnaise. It is salad dressing. And a much inferior product. I loathe it with all my being when it comes to sandwiches.).  Wednesday - Whew. Finally caught up. Well sort of. I know I've been telling people that I'm heading home to get my haircut many times this past couple weeks. But there my hair sits, still growing on top of my head. Why is it that every time I get almost home, I suddenly don't feel like getting a haircut anymore? I mean, I know it's getting bad on top of my head, I see it everyday. Sticking every which way by lunch, and being really annoying at the length where it just barely touches my ears in that bothersome way. I've been debating spiking my hair up again. Give me that I may be going bald, but I'm still a badass dude look. But I probably won't. After all school is right around the corner. I've found that even though a teacher can pick you out of a 300 person class because of your hair. If your hair is a problem they automatically don't like you. Dr. Pass-Or-Fail-O thought so. Since I was borderline, he decided that since I had more hair than he did, and it looked cooler, that I was a failure as a student. Me and 100 other people in that class.  I've been working on ideas for my army for this weekends tournament. If my Dark Elves come in. I'll most likely use them. But I've been getting mixed feedback about my lists. That and I've only played them a couple times. So I might be a lot shaky when it comes to trying to get them to do what I want at the tournament.  Well I think that's it for today. "GL HF DD FU ALL" = Good game, Don't Die, Fuck You All! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>