<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, let's see, today I woke up around 12-ish, had my daily cup-o-tang and a pop tart, sat my ass down in front of the tv, and started to watch Spiderman. Then my g/f called, she sounded irritated (I told her I would call her as soon as I woke up, oops :$). It's her grandma's b-day, and well, she doesn't want to go, maybe that's why she's irritated.  around 2:30 I called the airport to ask what time my friend's flight would arrive, they told me it would arrive at 4:15. The plane was exactly on time, however it took forever for them to get through customs, something about smuggeling a drive shaft or something, I dunno...  Afterwards me and my friend, let's call him Jason, we went grocerie shopping, that was hillarious. Word of advice, don't get in a car with him. He takes a corner at 60 MPH, that's just phsyco... We drove around for a bit, scaring the shit out of ppl by the way he drives, and then came over to my house, to talk and play counter-strike. That was pretty fun.  Tomorrow I'm going to my g/f's house, hopefully she'll be in a good mood. After that we're going to watch a movie or too, and I'll prolly spend the rest of the night playing games, prolly nfs hp2 (I know it's an old game, but it's still fun).  Right now I'm going to do the dishes and go to bed.  until we meet again
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's up I just finished watching Timeline, the movie was pretty okay, nothing really special about it. But nothing really is after you've seen the Lord of the Rings trilogy. Obviously I'm a LOTR fan. I also Like the Matrix, but that's not half as good as LOTR. I've seen the LOTR trilogy tons of times, and I'm still not fed up with it. Come to think of it, there aren't many movies I think are worth watching twice, except those phsycological movies which you have to see like 2 or 3 times before you actually get it.  Earlier this evening I watched "The Butterfly Effect", that one was really horrible. I mean, the idea of being able to change the past is awesome, but the movie hardly delivers. I thought of it as something to keep you busy for almost 2 hours. Yesterday I saw "Secret Window", which I actually did kind of like, but the story wasn't that fucked up that I have to watch it twice to get it.  Well let's see, tomorrow's monday, My best friend is coming here on vacation, from Holland. Yes, he has also left to attend College there. I hate having friends who are older than me, they always leave, and I have to make new friends, that sucks ass. What sucks even more is that my girlfriend is leaving for Holland soon, and I won't get to see her till december. Fuck it's gonna be hard without her.  I hate to see my friends go, but what sucks even more is if they fail there exams and have to do the whole damn year over. Now that's not such a bad thing if ur not in the final year, but they were, and they have to go through the same shit all over again.   I've been down that path, but I was in 3rd grade (of the 5), which isn't half bad. It was quite fun actually, I only failed in a couple of courses, mostly french and spanish, but I also didnt perform well in history. The second year in the 3rd grade was a breeze, I still remembered all the crap from the year before, and cheated on all my french and spanish exams. As for history, that year we got different topics, topics that I was actually really interested in, like WWII and Vietnam. so I passed with flying colors.  Right now I'm heading for my final year, I think I'm going to pass, well I hope so... 4th grade was pretty easy, so I don't see why 5th grade should be so hard.  After that, I'm heading straight to Holland, never to return again (well, maybe on vacation or that sort of thing). I'm going to study either system management, or computer consultant, eitherway, something in the IT industry. I love working with computers. I'm also into gaming, it's like an addiction, can't keep my hands off it. I often go to LAN party's and try my luck there.   Well it's almost 2 'o clock here, and I think it's bed time, I just have to do the dishes and off to bed!
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so I woke up today, and said to myself "hmm, let's make a blog an let everybody read what's going on in my life", but then I thought "Why, nothing cool ever happens to me". And well, after a while, I decided to do it anyway, just for the heck of it. Maybe something cool will happen, you never know.  Ok, so let's start at the beginning.  It was very dark, I couldn't see anything at all. I also couldn't move much, like I was trapped somewhere, and there was noone there to help me. I was wet, but somehow felt warm. I have never expirienced this feeling before. After a while, I heard a woman screaming, I had no clue of what was going on, I was afraid. Then I saw a light, I started moving towards it, struggeling, still unable to move my arms and legs. The woman was still screaming. I stopped to rest for a while, and coincedentally, the woman stopped screaming... I slowly started moving towards the light again, inching my way through the narrow gap, until finally, I reached it! I was born.  Ok, laim joke...seriously, My name is Ryan, I'm 16 (for a month or so, turning 17 in august :D), and I live on a rock some people call Curacao, I like to call it hell. For those of you who've never heard of it, it's just off the coast of Venezuela, doesn't ring a bell? Maybe you've heard of Aruba. Yeah, it's right next to that... The reason I don't like this place, is there's nothing to do around here (for me at least), the island is filled with druglords, and phsycho killers, and on the entire island, there's not one decent computer store. Don't get me wrong, it's not all bad, We do have some nice sunny beaches, and there are tons of hot chicks here. and well, the laws aren't that strict here (which is why there are so many murderers and dealers). Moving on, we are a dutch colonie, therefore our native language is dutch. But ask any native, and they'll say it's papiamentu, a dialect created by slaves in the 1800's to communicate with eachother so their master could'nt understand them. Papiamentu is a mixture of allot of languages, mainly Spanish, Dutch and English.  Most people love it here, tourists want to come live here and natives never want to leave. Well I'm different, I never really fit in here. I can't wait to leave, and considering the lack of educanional facilities, I have to leave to go to college. I'm going to move to Holland in exactly 12 months and 17 days.  It's a quarter past eleven now, and I'm going to watch a movie (for all of you wondering, I'm going to watch "Timeline", and hope it's any good)  I'll be checking back here after the movie. 
    
</post>


</Blog>