<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
            hiaz... today got choral... so sianzz... somemore tml got performance liaoz... then after that i still got tuition... wah piang... so stupid... im so stressed... so stressed... i wanna complain foereva!! *diaozz*    hiaz... dunno why... not in the mood to lame myself liaoz... hiaz... bb!       
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
            heyZz, i very long nv blog liaoz cuz i lazy...*heehx* and i dunno howta do my blog properly... i HTML stupid... so dun hav to worry... they are like alien language to me... *lame*    hiaz... aniwaes... today we played SOFTBALL!! finally after 2 weeks of rain.. and we are going to learn gymnastics! *omg*    hiaz... i so wish they would stop saying bad things bout ppl... i found a song tt really actually is an encouragement song...    beautiful by christina (chorus):   words cant bring me down...im beautiful, in every single way, and words cant bring me down... so dun u bring me down today.   &nbsp;      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
                hOhOhO!! so lAme todAy!! angie canT hit me!! yay!!  *lame*  i feel like sianging wai (thinking crooked) hiaz... so boring... i gone crazy liaoz... really got mood swing today... awhile so cheery heehx... then a while so bored... then awhile so pissed off...&nbsp; wah piang!! aniwaes... got nth to write liaoz... bb    write people's misdeeds in sand where the wind would blow it all away. Carve ppl's gd deeds on stones and remember it forever.                           
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
            toDay quite boring... lata got piano... and then these few weeks like very bz liddat...hiaz... (im not photogenic) *yawn*     tml needa go sch again liaoz... so fast... i still wanna play... hiaz... so boring... hohoho... (merry christmas) *lame*  aniwaes... i finished my journal on the trekking one liaoz!!yipee!! *lame*  stupid la... cant be crazy at home... so go sch beta... go sch liaoz dun wanna come home... so xianz... my new blog gd anot? abit lame... but nvm... im lame... gtg aniwaes... nth to write liaoz... remember... if u wanna buy crass phote plz bring $3 for small one or $6 for big one... its the same for fun shot lorx... of cuz can buy bth la!!      make urself sensitive to other people's feelings and try not to hurt them - jamie (me la!)         
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
       urlLink    heehx... i tink i dun wanna post so much photo today but this is really cute!! enjoy!! &nbsp; urlLink   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
            sry horx... this is my new blog... im HTML stupid... so i didnt noe wad i did to the web and it was ruined... hiaz... my fault... *lame*    todaY went for the bike for bible... it was quite fun... and cute... there was a nice scenery there... woah... too bad cant stop to take photos... (we were running late) our coy... those who nv bike one got prize!! soo gd... heehx... juz loved it... except the mozzy part... they will stick to u one lorx... u shake also no use... as a result i went and smacked one.. and it died... *ke lian*    pulau ubin is a nice place to go... juz remember to bring insect repellent... and the coconut is a muz try!! so sweet and fresh and delicious... ( at least after a long biking route it is nice! ) hiaz.. gtg write my journal liaoz... bb!!         That friendship will not continue to the end which is begun for an end. --Francis Quareles  
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
            its now raining siaz... at first the lightning like strike liaoz then thunder straight away... so scary... [ me scared lightning] i kiase... *lame*    today is so boring... tml still got maths test... wad the * rite.... and then somemore i failed my knowledge test... *i wanna cry* but nvm... whole squad fail lehx... *even worse* ppl like ginny who got study also failed... hiaz... i feeling so sad for them...     heyx... me dunno wad to write le... heehx       
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
       aHhhH!! sO lonG didn't blog in liaoz... heehx... my mum change the password to the comp... cant get the play the comp anytime liaoz... *wail* but hiaz... nvm... everyday stay in sch until so late... also the same... xinmin rawks... heehx... so fun... today got drill practice... tough... but not as tough as last time.. keke... im lame...   eh... bout the stayover at blk 684... care centre how? who wanna bring wad... like... pot luck? wad do u all wanna bring... beehoon? chicken wings? sushi!! u all decide la horx... i think the notice will go up on thurs or fri liddat... muz check board ar!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
       heyz... today so boring... stayed at home and rotted... *jay chou's new album rox* okie... aniwaes... yeah!! skipped all the boring lessons... gd! i so happy... heehx... me like the neoprint we took when we went to watch the village... see lar... me from eng pro *bhb* to eng shit...    aniwaes... today like got nth one... hiaz... bb... dunno whether got food bio tech...  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
        today discussed bout the teachers' day audition thingy... so sianz... in the end decided on a skit...    *heehx*      then the guys are so wad lorx... we gals discussing.. then they playing soccer... trying to endanger lives... hiaz...then sok loon kena hit lots of times...  so scary... i sway... kena hit on the back of my neck... luckily the impact not so great cuz hit the wall liaoz then drop on me... so sway... stupid clement...  jkjk... lata ppl angry...   then in the end i like got   ball phobia  ... i already got   swing phobia   lehx... swing too high i will go screaming!! i siao one...  hiaz...    heyz... i still dunno how to link ppl... wah liaoz... can some one juz teach me...hiaz... nth to write liaoz...   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
           today is fun day... and we had to go there to help out... we were spilt into groups where some sold drinks... some emptied the bins... some pumped balloons... blah... actually i was in the sell drinks place... then ms sherilyn asked the sec ones tending there to go help in the balloon part... so we went lorx... then in the end i was the only one left there... so poor thing... put pumping the balloon was fun... we got to use the helium thingy... so cute!! aniwaes... nth else liaoz... bb      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
            wEnt to wAtch  thE viLLAge  today... wad the... we went PS then there full house so we went cine... woah... the village the ending quite lame... but its quite scary also... i like the plot... they teach some morals also... cuz is like sometims money can make ppl wicked thes kinda thing... its also quite funny la... some parts... heehx... the  bad colour  is  red  and the  safe colour  is  yellow ... hiaz...    lEt the bad colour not be seen...    i forgot the second one liaoz... heehx!!    heed the warning bell for they are coming...         
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
             kon ban wa!!     hiaz... all bcuz of the minister coming to our sch... they got 2 new swings... wah liaoz.. then they repainted the places where the minister is going to walk... jian horxx... so jian.... they even corner off the foyer and decorated the canteen... wad ****... and then today during recess... i forgot the foyer kena cornered off then i like... slow run into the foyer... then the SLsss on duty go say"eh... wad u doin" then i "orh orh" and went back... lame horx... then when i was going to sch tt time... then i heard ppl saying this " wah liaoz... one staircase four SL guard lehx..." i heard liaoz was like wah piang!!    aniwaes... today got back geog and physics test paper... so lan... actually the poins quite gd la... and today got JAP!! so fun... we learned the mins liaoz... now is so fun... aniwaes... gtg...       
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
       urlLink    can't we be friends forever??&nbsp; urlLink   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
      todayzz...hiaz... so boring... hiaz... did duty today... clean the windows... it was so dirty... i made it clean!! :) *diao* i crazy... aniwaes.. why does everyone have to pick on one person... and no. 10 is a nice no. lorx... they so bad... so idiotic... i hate them... so idiotic and bitchy... idiot... jerks... hiaz... so idiotic... everyone has feelings lorx... so bad... so idiotic...  IDIOT!! aniwaes... gtg liaoz... doing maths hmwk... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

 
       today... so xianz... during assembly... we got the xinmin da xing xing... then while watching the performance... wah piang... one gal taking the whole thing down was standing there and blocking the whole 1e5 class the view... stupid... so inconsiderate... no brain... everyone behind her all cursing and swearing liaoz... hiaz... so idiotic... i tink our class the performance was quite nice... heehx....    and today... on the 156 bus... the bus driver very funny lehx... upon stopping at the red light... he took out a newspaper and started reading it lorx... lame ritez?... today i saw ranma half... so nice... its on AXN frm mon to fri 6-7 in the morning and evening.... muz watch arz... *-_-lll* hiaz... the stupid stories from asia the comic i haven do...   yay!! on 6 aug got half day!!*duh* so fun... it will be a fun day!! yay... im so happy... im over the moon liaoz.... heehx :)     urlLink  aniw@aes    ... live life to the fullest... ~n~ dun ev@ give up!!  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>