<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       .  my friend margaret stitched this fine lobster. to view more of her stunning stitching magic visit:   urlLink http://community.webshots.com/user/mg6000   yes!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i have just discovered&nbsp;that waterbeds are wonderful. i don't know&nbsp;what else to say.&nbsp;i'm a pickled onion. another cuppa tea methinks... and look at this festering blog of greatness:   urlLink  http://festerthegreat.blogspot.com  &nbsp; p  l  o  p  :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       this weekend i was banished to the black hole several times ;)   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    little pig after he fell in the bath. he's much cuter than puss in boots!&nbsp; urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     boiling my head, by tatanka-man &nbsp; urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      shark molester!   ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!!! &nbsp; urlLink       
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     this is my friend oily. he dropped off in my room and we decided to play a modified version of buckaroo on him. he just wouldn't move.  &nbsp; urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yesterday i did something odd. i decided to trust the universe (just a little bit), so i put my bank details on this blog for 10 minutes. it was quite thrilling. if my account had been drained, i could only blame myself. i could only laugh at my stupidity. at least it wouldn't kill me. i have no idea how much of a risk i took but i have survived! thank you universe for not getting me. yet!  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      does anyone else think ronnie o'sullivan is delightful? i know of at least one other person (VR).  we like ronnie lots!   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i hope you weren't lonely. i think you understood. i was an only child too. i gave you  green  spider and i had  orange  ted.  orange  ted is brill!!! :)    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i look very happy in the photo below. my head is bigger than the eiffel tower! i jest. silly fran.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is me in paris. my plait is now much longer!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       tom pearce, tom pearce, lend me your grey mare  all along down along out along lee  for i want to go to Widdecombe Fair  with bill brewer, jan stewer  peter gurney, peter davey  dan'l whiddon, harry hawke  and  old uncle tom cobley and all  old uncle tom cobley and all  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i'm on the right&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       pax    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    at work yesterday they had a bundun and i got a mehndi so i scanned it. it should last 3 weeks.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       the clouds are having a long, hard mutter on us and it doesn't look like its going to stop for a while. english weather is weird! last night i tried to go to grantham to practice driving for my test. ironically i only got as far as dry doddington. it was torrential and my windows steamed up so i couldn't see. poor me, are there higher forces trying to stop me driving in grantham? last week when i tried to go i had a puncture. when i eventually got back to newark, beaconhill road had become a river. as i ploughed into the deepest part of the road the door of a parked car to my left opened and a lady waded out. there was nothing i could do to stop my tidal wave utterly drenching her. i looked back and it was the sunday school teacher of the local evangelical church. when i was an innocent defenceless child i attended the sunday school for a while and she told us all lots of ridiculous happy clappy nonsense about the holy superstar saviour of mankind. i must admit it was a delight to see her soaked. shit, i hope i don't go to hell. it was an accident! ;)   its still raining buckets.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       summer arrived this weekend!!! i have been full of beans... i went camping in some nettles and to an all the bass party around the corner. portaloodledoo!  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     you can all jolly well leave my jolly tshirt jolly well alone! RAAAAA!   you can all jolly well leave my jolly tshirt jolly well alone! RAAAAA!   you can all jolly well leave my jolly tshirt jolly well alone! RAAAAA!   urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     my wallace & gromit tshirt is now 9 years old! my friend clare gave it to me at school. it is my favourite tshirt. now it has got many many holes including a big armpit hole but i still love it. my mum says it is disgraceful but i don't care. i am going to wear it until it disintegrates! i have worn it all over the world in five continents. its a truly amazing tshirt. happy birthday tshirt!   urlLink    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>