<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        went to watch I,Robot juz now wif Cindy.. nice show.. the action was cool.. altho didnt realli understand the ending.. will smith was great in the film(didnt know he was so muscular..lol).. but the startin of the show makes u think that he's tryin to do advertisement for Converse n JVC.. but overall.. i think i will gif it a 4 star****..hahaz. recommend u all to go and watch oso.. dun b so stingy for that 7 bucks lar.. my movie waiting list still got brotherhood, ella enchanted, kind arthur.. quickly after the guitar concert den i can go watch this movies liaoz.. but den oso must go ask ard 4 ppl to go wif mi.. haiz.. by den every1 would hav watch at least once liaoz.. sianz.. nvm.. wait n c ba.. anyway.. guess today is quite an enjoyable dae afterall..havin the half dae n the movie.. altho the guitar prac spoiled some of the fun.. but nvm.. i chose to enjoy my dae n be happy..^^      joke of the dae(continuation of cunyang's blonde jokes, from jokes.com)         A blonde, a brunette, and a redhead are crossing an enchanted bridge in Magical Fairyland when they run into a fairy. The fairy says that they can be granted a transformation if they jump off the bridge and call out their wish. The brunette immediately jumps off the bridge and yells "Eagle!" She turns into a beautiful bird of prey and flies away. The redhead jumps off the bridge and yells out "Salmon!" She turns into a gorgeous shimmering salmon and swims upstream to spawn. The blonde is at this point so excited that she jumps off the bridge without thinking of her wish. She panics.      "Crap!"      
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       another dae of guitar prac.. going to cannot take it liaoz.. hope the concert quickly over so i can co ncentrate on my studies.. results gettin poorer n poorer.. haiz.. play so long every dae.. make mi almost c the guitar wanna smash it(of coz i wun lar.. they are my "wives"..LoLz) btw.. the ajc guitar n harmonica concert is next fri in the ajc auditorium for those who r not aware of it.. hope to c all my frens there, but not enuff tix leh(kevin.. wads my no on the waiting list ar?).. haiz.. but the one i most wan to c isnt goin to b there that dae.. but nvm.. hope she would gif me a chance one dae.. think thatz about all.. goin to pia my tutorials le.. guys cya in sch next mon.^^    joke of the dae!!(got inspired by cunyang's lame blonde jokes..btw all jokes r fr jokes.com)     						A blonde went to eletronic store and she asked, "How is much is this TV?"       The salesman said, "Sorry, we don''t sell to blondes."       The next day she came back as a brunette. She asked the salesman how much the TV was. He said, "Sorry, we don''t sell to blondes."       The next day she came back as a red head and asked the salesman how much the TV was. He said, "Sorry we don''t sell to blondes."        She replied, " I came in here as a brunette and a red head. How do you know I am a blonde?"    "Because that is not a TV,  it''s a microwave." 					         
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heard this song a few days ago on yes9.33.. den i started searchin it on the web.. finally i found it!! altho the quality is bad{realli bad, u can heard a lot of "background" music).. but i realli cant find another 1.. those who wan it can d/l it at this  urlLink site .. happy listening..=)btw the song's name is  .. and the release date of him next album is on 3rd Aug.. every1 rememb to buy his original CD hor!! =)
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       so tired todae.. guitar prac until so late.. no strength to write liaoz.. nitez every1.. zzZzZZzZZZzz...   
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hai~ lost again in vollyball.. 3 times in a row so far.. sure "dian di" liaoz.. feel sad for panther house.. no sch team players how to win.. still rememb last fri vs couger house.. got 2 1.90m+ sch team players lor.. liddat how to win.. they smash dun even need to jump lor.. den today vs jaguar oso sad case.. they got a sch team player(altho this time not that tall).. but still kena thrash.. hurt my hand summore while tryin to stop their meteor like serves.. den squash oso.. 2nd last.. try our best tho.. is the other houses too pro liaoz lor.. now the onli hope lies on the panther soccer team liaoz.. altho they lost the 1st match, but todae at least got w1n(1-0 vs cheetah).. go Ethan u're our onli hope.. ok.. mayb not..hahaz.. anyway all the best to those who still got interhouse games.. btw guys that was a great game todae!    Joke of the day~    10 Things In Golf That Sound Dirty    1. Look at the size of his putter.  2. Oh, dang, my shaft's all bent.  3. You really wacked the hell out of that sucker.  4. After 18 holes I can barely walk.  5. My hands are so sweaty I can't get a good grip.  6. Lift your head and spread your legs.  7. You have a nice stroke, but your follow through leaves a lot to be desired.  8. Just turn your back and drop it.  9. Hold up. I've got to wash my balls.  10. Damn, I missed the hole again.   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        this is the third time im writing this same blog post.. coz he last 2 couldnt upload and the server crash on me.. stupid lor.. den now hav to rewrite all over..-_-" aiya.. 4got wad i wrote juz now liaoz.. firstly.. b4 i 4get.. cunyang if u r seeing this ar.. i juz wanna tell u that the "easy"  urlLink "mary had a little lamb" by SRV    u recommended wasnt that easy lor.. that stupid shedding song.. spolits the original song.. den wad ar.. oh.. hey guys, i failed my GP wahha.. feeling so sad(do i?).. sianz.. wad can i write ar.. i think many of u guys out there think i very boliao.. copy ppl write blog like nothing else better to do.. but actually.. u're rite.. wahaha.. im so proud(to b a copycat??).. btw.. frens.. pls drop mi a msg if u r viewing this site, so i noe sum1 is actualli visiting this site.. thx        Here are a number of very lame(yet effective) methods of keeping unscrupulous surfers from stealing your HTML source:     1. Use the   tags around the entire document.     2. Use the DONTSTEAL attribute in the tag.     3. Ftp to your server, select all files and directories, hit "Delete".     4.Put every existing copy of every file on floppies, place them in a shoebox and bury them in the backyard. There is another version of this method which involves placing the floppies in a plastic bag and hiding them in a different sort of hole. Both are equally effective.     5. Password protect your entire site and make sure no one has the password, not even you.     6. Employ a small but fanatically loyal and well-armed band of mercenaries to guard your site.     7. Start>Run>format C:\     8.Use any version of Microsoft Frontpage to create your site. (This won't prevent people from viewing your source, but no one will want to steal it.)     9. Don't put your pages on the web.      &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahaz.. im writin this crap again.. wasting my time.. i shd b studyin and doin tutorials now lor.. haiz.. so sianz.. has been tryin to record the "tears in heaven" song by eric clapton juz now.. sounds like shit..(click here if u wanna listen urlLink 1    urlLink 2 ).. got back all my results le.. not very gd sia.. B B B C.sianz.. sure tio parents meetin liaoz.. hope all the best for my GP lez..=)
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      erm.. wad should i write todae..? haiz.. so sad.. tryin to learn the srv song by eric johnson.. damn hard.. guitar players out there try it its really nice..  urlLink http://www.ultimate-guitar.com/tabs/j/johnson_eric/srv_tab.htm  hahaz.. actualli im juz tryin to test the functions of this thing.. dun think any1 will bother readin this.. =) btw..can this help to improve my GP??
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      testing the blog.. btw wads a blog?
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey ppl.. the guitar concert has being over for abt 3 days le. those hu went can gimmi a brief reply on whether the concert is gd or not?i will upload some of the pics once my frens send them to me.. btw if u got any nice pics on the concert can send mi? i'll be so grateful.. anyway all the best everyone!! =)  Joke of the dae(fr jokes.com)     One day a blonde finds out from her friend that her boyfriend is cheating on her. So one day she goes out to the mall and buys a gun. After that she goes to her boyfriend's house. She busts down the door and points the gun at her head.      "What are you doing?'' says her boyfriend.       "Shut up! You're next!"  					  
    
</post>


</Blog>