<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Wow... That last post? Pure stupidity. But enough of that, I'm posting about my fanfics.   FANFICTION.NET     STATUS  : TLOTES- currently working on the third chapter. I am slugging through and I will certainly not finish by the end of the summer. I hate summer school, even if it does get those stupid half-credit courses out of the way... New fics: I have a HP/YGO fic titled, "Those Japanese Weirdoes" currently in the makings, but who knows when that will be up...-_-U   DeviantArt  : Stupid scanner won't work...   I mostly hang around GaiaOnline...     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first post here on this Blog site thing...I have another one floating around on a different site, but that involves a more personal aspect of my life, though I mostly post ramblings there.    Places to see if you are in the neighborhood...   http://www.fanfiction.net/~dhasn  http://dhasn.deviantart.com  www.fictionpress.com/~dhasn   I'm going to get my own website up soon, it's just that I don't have enough time and that I'm lazy.   I realize that this is short for a first post as many others put gobs and gobs of information about themselves and their lives, however, I happen to not be that type of person. I happen to be very different in what other people believe.   It is important to also know that I have no happy medium. I have extremes.&nbsp;One of them&nbsp;happens to be the "serious, quiet bleep who makes bleeping good grades and who can actually play *insert musical instrument(s) that you think I play*". This side happens to be, or at least appears, very sane. This usually occurs during 11:00 AM to around 4:00 PM or when something very serious or very depressing has happened. This can also happen after a large and extremely stressful test. Keep in mind that I am  not  depressed. I just appear to be. Me being depressed is saying that Neptune has banana chocolate Pocky. See? I rest my case.   The other extreme is hyperness. Sometimes, especially after consuming a sugar packet, I become hyper and talk really fast. This will most likely&nbsp;lead on to rants and stupid plots. Talking about anime or manga that I know will also transfer me to this stage, even if I appear to be in my "serious, quiet bleep who makes bleeping good grades and who can actually play *insert musical instrument(s) that you think I play*" side". This extreme usually occurs during the time period of 10 AM to 10:55 AM.    Note : Just because I seem serious does not, I repeat  does not , mean I am. I may be thinking insanely random thoughts that go "Whee! Sugar Packets! I am stupid! Fear my incompetence!". Yes, that has happened before. No, I will not explain, because it is best for you to figure that out.   Thank you for taking the time to read this pathetic entry.   Maybe next time, I might be in a better mood.     Maybe .   ~DHASN 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eh... Ok, I now have a "website" [ urlLink http://dhasntheinsane.tripod.com/ ] thing up...it's so stupid, I don't even wanna look at it... Anyways, I won't be updating as much I would like to, which isn't much at all since school is starting soon. >_  >_  !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Fear mah inferiority!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! >_  ~DHASN the very stupid   
    
</post>


</Blog>