<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are quite a few stray cats in our neighorhood, and Saturday afternoon I arrived home to find a small orange kitten hiding under our fence. One of his eyes looked pretty bad, so I took a can of wet catfood and sat outside for awhile until he got brave enough to get near enough to me where I could grab him. DH says no more cats (we already have two), so right now we're essentially fostering him until he gets well enough to go to a shelter (there's a nearby no-kill shelter that we like, and is actually where we got both of our cats).  We took him to the vet yesterday, and he's about 8 or 9 weeks old, with fleas, worms, conjuntivitis and a cold. Whee! So he's going to be staying with us for the next 7-10 days while he gets better. In the meantime, we've named him Finn, because he's a little orange kitty, and so of course is Irish (Finn MacCool, anyone?).  "His song" is now "Poor Old Michael Finnegan", only he's "kitten finnegan".  Here he is curled up in a cat carrier, taking a little nap soon after I brought him in.    He is a hungry little guy! We knew he was hungry when he started eyeing Syd's food...    ...so he got his own kitten food...    ...but still, Sydney's water seems to taste better.    He's quite the cuddler, and enjoys curling up on DH's belly while he watches TV.       Ahh... to be this relaxed!    Of course, being within arm's reach means he gets the dreaded tissue wiping every time he sneezes!    Sydney has taken a keen interest in him, and seems to have nominated himself Finn's babysitter. Here he is keeping a close eye on him while he hangs out in a cat carrier...    ...and staying close while Finn roams the house...    ...and napping together in the dining room.    The cats are less happy. Syd supervises while DH checks Finn's ears, and Boo-Kitty comes in for a closer look.    Rembrandt wants to know what the heck is going on while Finn snuggles up in the back of one of DH's speakers.    Just an idea of how small he is...notice the small box of pop-tarts above him? (This is his new "hiding" place)    But all in all, Finn's been quite helpful. Here he "helps" DH work on the computer.    And assists me with my knitting (a poncho for one of my cousins).    Finn seems to be very laid back about it all. He has taken a liking to Syd, and lets him lick his butt (ew!) and follow him around. He seems to want very much to be friends with Remby, and will walk to within four or five feet of her, and then just sit down and watch her. If he gets too close and she hisses, he just lays down and waits. Smart little guy :)  And best of all - he uses the litter box! In fact, he starts wandering back to that part of the house himself when he needs to use it. Not a bad deal :) It's going to be hard to give him up, but I'm sure enjoying it while he's here.
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This blog is being created to add some ease to posting pics to my  real  blog, Aussie Knits. 
    
</post>


<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend, for the first time in a long time, we got to help out on an Aussie transport.&nbsp;Mick was&nbsp;an incredibly sweet ARPH dog going to his forever home in Mass. He slept&nbsp;most of&nbsp;the trip, but he made sure to nap with his head on the center console so I could pet&nbsp;his nose.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  urlLink   &nbsp;  urlLink http://aussierescue.leepfrog.com/   &nbsp;  On Sunday we went to&nbsp;a UCC church that is about&nbsp;four minutes from us. I'm pretty&nbsp;excited about it. Everyone was really friendly, and they have a book club, a knitting group, and a kayaking club! Plus it was okay to laugh and applaud during&nbsp;the service, which&nbsp;I like. They&nbsp;guest minister was given by a girl who is studying to become a minister, and&nbsp;in her sermon she likened one of the old testament prophets to Spiderman. Can't beat that!  urlLink http://uccredeemer.org/index.html   No real work on the never-ending sweater, but we did buy two (!) air conditioners yesterday, so hopefully it'll keep the house cool enough that I can knit comfortably.  &nbsp; The air conditioners are my one-year anniversary gift from DH. Since I'm home all day, it is the sweetest gift he could have given me. ::glow:: 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I connected the sleeves to my sweater, and today I started on the decreases on the yoke. I have been working on this stupid thing for so long, now that an end is in sight, I've started getting a little obsessive about working on it. The dog doesn't need to be walked! The house doesn't need to be cleaned! The bills don't need to be paid! I'm knitting!  It doesn't help that I took it with me when I went to visit my aunt and mother today, and they both ooh'd and ahhh'd over it. I want it done so I can wear it! Or, considering the warm weather: I want it done so I can show it off and then wear it in two months.   And I finally decided on and picked up hubby's anniversary present yesterday. I'm so excited I do a little happy wiggle every time I think of it! Can't post here because he might see it, but trust me, it's fabulous. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh. What a crappy day. Miserable, wet, drizzly weather, a million phone calls to make, and no ambition. Plus, I started  and  finished  my latest book on c.d. yesterday ( urlLink Skipping Christmas ), so I have to trek back to the library for a new one.   The upside of this is that I got a lot of knitting done yesterday on my raglan sweater.  urlLink     This is my first real attempt at intarsia, so I'm pretty proud of it. Not that I want to attempt anything like it again any time soon.    I only have a few inches left on the right sleeve, and then the almighty yoke. And I'm pretty sure I won't have enough yarn for it (I'm on my last skein), so a trip to  urlLink The Yarn Barn  is most certainly in my future. Checkbook, beware...  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My hooligan of a cat - Rembrandt
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spend far too much time on the internet. Having recently become unemployed (I prefer the term "Kept Woman") my surfing habits have worsened. My husband refers to me as "his little obsessive Sammie."  Two days ago I discovered knitting blogs. Yesterday I discovered web rings for knitters and knitters with dogs. Today I have my own blog.  After all, I have to put my pics of WIPs, FOs and write out the list of all the things I want to make  somewhere ... even if I'm only talking to myself... 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are quite a few stray cats in our neighorhood, and Saturday afternoon I arrived home to find a small orange kitten hiding under our fence. One of his eyes looked pretty bad, so I took a can of wet catfood and sat outside for awhile until he got brave enough to get near enough to me where I could grab him. DH says no more cats (we already have two), so right now we're essentially fostering him until he gets well enough to go to a shelter (there's a nearby no-kill shelter that we like, and is actually where we got both of our cats).  We took him to the vet yesterday, and he's about 8 or 9 weeks old, with fleas, worms, conjuntivitis and a cold. Whee! So he's going to be staying with us for the next 7-10 days while he gets better. In the meantime, we've named him Finn, because he's a little orange kitty, and so of course is Irish (Finn MacCool, anyone?). "His song" is now "Poor Old Michael Finnegan", only he's "kitten finnegan".  Here he is curled up in a cat carrier, taking a little nap soon after I brought him in.    He is a hungry little guy! We knew he was hungry when he started eyeing Syd's food...    ...so he got his own kitten food...    ...but still, Sydney's water seems to taste better.    He's quite the cuddler, and enjoys curling up on DH's belly while he watches TV.       Ahh... to be this relaxed!    Of course, being within arm's reach means he gets the dreaded tissue wiping every time he sneezes!    Sydney has taken a keen interest in him, and seems to have nominated himself Finn's babysitter. Here he is keeping a close eye on him while he hangs out in a cat carrier...    ...and staying close while Finn roams the house...    ...and napping together in the dining room.    The cats are less happy. Syd supervises while DH checks Finn's ears, and Boo-Kitty comes in for a closer look.    Rembrandt wants to know what the heck is going on while Finn snuggles up in the back of one of DH's speakers.    Just an idea of how small he is...notice the small box of pop-tarts above him? (This is his new "hiding" place)    But all in all, Finn's been quite helpful. Here he "helps" DH work on the computer.    And assists me with my knitting (a poncho for one of my cousins).    Finn seems to be very laid back about it all. He has taken a liking to Syd, and lets him lick his butt (ew!) and follow him around. He seems to want very much to be friends with Remby, and will walk to within four or five feet of her, and then just sit down and watch her. If he gets too close and she hisses, he just lays down and waits. Smart little guy :)  And best of all - he uses the litter box! In fact, he starts wandering back to that part of the house himself when he needs to use it. Not a bad deal :) It's going to be hard to give him up, but I'm sure enjoying it while he's here. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, to my delight, I discovered that there truly is something wrong with me. Wahoo! For the past two years, I have become quite the obsessive napper, to the point where I can't hold down a real job because of my need to sleep an additional 2-3 hours during the middle of the day. Not that I mind being a kept woman, mind you...  So Wednesday night I went in for a sleep study at Yale, and was awakened at 6am with the information that I have  urlLink sleep apnea . Yay! I'm not really faking it or just plain lazy! I'll find out more in two weeks, but until then, I just feeling vindicated.  Now off to clean the house and hide all the baby books: my in-laws are coming for the weekend. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>