<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Monday, November 10, 2003 - All-Region Band Music I don't remember if they gave us the music on the 10th or 11th, but who cares. Ms. F gave all of the All-Region band members the music that they're supposed to learn before the AR Concert. You're supposed to learn this music by yourself because some time on January, there'll be this huge band rehearsal with your AR band and you'll practice the songs there. Of course, they won't teach you the rhythms because you were supposed to do that by yourself, but whatever. I didn't look at the pieces at all. That's right, folks, I was  sight-reading  on the rehearsals because I didn't want to look at that stupid music. What music was it? Here it is: Sons of Liberty, Arranged by Larry Neeck ; Music From CARMEN, Geoges Bizet but arranged by Richard Saucedo ; A Song of Hope by James Swearingen ; and Under an Irish Sky by Larry Neeck. Though, just two days before the "Big Rehearsal," they decided that we weren't gonna play Under an Irish Sky, so they decided to switch that to Nevada Expedition by Alan Lee Silva, which was a much harder piece to learn. It didn't really matter for me, though, 'cause I hadn't bothered to look at the music. Well, yeah, I looked at it, but just to number the measures. w00t, I rock. The All-Region concert was gonna be some time in January.  Friday, January 16, 2004 - All-Region Band Clinic 'Tis the day of the AR Band rehearsal... or clinic, whatever. It started at about 4.30 or 5 PM, and it lasted to about 8 or 9. The Symphonic had it on the auditorium of Reed Middle School, and the Concert Band on the band hall. Oh... my... fuggin'... goddess. What a pain in the neck was to rehearse in this place. We played for a whole lot of time, and we only had breaks of 5 or 10 minutes. Can you believe that?! They were trying to kill us! Of course, like I have said before, I was sight-reading the whole time, and sometimes I didn't even play. =P My butt was aching the whole time because I couldn't stand up. Oh... the horror. The percussionists sucked (Shaw-san and Erica-san would have kick arse) and the saxophones didn't have a good sound (here's where So-Young would have been the star). I was so fuggin' tired at the end of the day. We sounded kind of good, but to me it wasn't good enough.   Saturday, January 17, 2004 - All-Region Concert This is where you find out that the AR Tryouts and making it to an AR Band is not worth your time nor your effort. Before the AR Concert we had another rehearsal, which was about 5 - 7 hours (a pain, eh?). We were the second band to play (the concert was at around 7 PM in the Alexander Auditorium), and lemme tell you this: the Concert band played way better than us. But I guess it's reasonable, since their music is easier than the one we have. Our concert sucked. In Songs of Liberty the flutes weren't playing at all in this part where they had the melody with clarinets. There was only one clarinet playing at that time, which was Elias. Then Sarah B came along, then Ciarra, Michelle and so on. It was horrible. Ms. Payne, the director for the Symphonic band (she was a really nice director, by the way, too bad we couldn't give her all of our energy), kept humming the rhythm so that a flute could come in, and she finally whispered, "Sarah, someone come in!" And that's where Sarah B caught up. What a shame. Some of the songs were good, though, like Music from Carmen (oh my goddess, that song rawked!), Under an Irish Sky and parts of Sons of Liberty. Nevada Expedition was ok, but at the end we sucked. Of course, what can you expect when the AR people throw you a piece of music which is uber hard and they expect you to learn it in two days? Not much.  We finished the concert and we headed back down the steps. As we were exiting, this lady was pulling patches out of this bag. Patches. We got patches for being on an AR Band. After all those months of working hard and preparing for the AR tryouts, endless chair tests and yellings from your band director, then wasting two fuggin' darn days sitting on your darn butts on a fuggin' seat for most of the day playing some stupid music, we receive a fuggin' patch that says this: ALL-REGION BAND, JHS/MS 03-04. Darn you all. Darn you all stupid and moronic fools who came up with this bullcrap known as All-Region Tryouts. First of all, this patch doesn't even tell you what band you made. What about the chair that you got? Nope. How about at least your initials? Nothing! Not a darn thing about what you made on AR or about you was on that pathetic excuse for a patch! So, as I looked at it with disappointment with my friends, I said, "This? This is what we get after our hard work?" Then this lady came up to my shoulder, who obviously was eavesdropping, and said, "And it's worth every penny." Screw you, you fugtard! It's not even worth a darn penny to tryout for this crap. She doesn't know what pain and trouble we went through in this AR crap, so she thinks that we, or maybe I should speak for myself, are satisfied with some crappy patch. Darn you all. I pity myself for having worked hard on trying to beat Michelle on AR tryouts. Why? It was not worth it, and now I'm kind of glad that I didn't get a better chair than her. Maybe I wouldn't have pushed myself so hard and wouldn't have been disappointed if I knew that my reward would be a crappy patch.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah I'm still feeling lazy so continue reading this "editorial." Continues right after Part I.   And it was true. We had to go to a room, and I saw gray shirts everywhere! Yes, our band director told us to wear the Reed Band shirts, and Reed flute players were invading the room. Boo-yah. The second phase consisted of playing half of the fast etude (which was the whole thing that we learned), and the second part of the slow etude. I still had some hopes that I could beat Michelle, but the bad thing was that she went before than me. When I heard her play... holy crap, it was so good! She didn't mess up once, her tonguing was perfect, and her sound was just incredible. My chances of beating her were just 2%... but I didn't give up. I decided to try my best. Of course, I didn't do as well as her, but I was so fuggin' good at the slow piece, so I still had some chances.  The bad thing was that I was so fuggin' sleepy, and I think I was falling asleep while other people were playing. Heh, there were still a lot of people that... well, weren't playing very good. So it was my turn to play again... the slow etude. As I was starting, I messed up. Bullcrap, I thought. My chances of getting a better chair than Michelle-chan were just smashed into little pieces until there was nothing left. But I continued, and the rest was fine. I had done pretty good, though, compared to most of the people in that room (not counting Reed flutes, of course).  Once I was done playing, I went back to my sit and fell asleep. Was I tired or what? Sally-chan woke me up and told me that we had to go to the cafeteria because we were done with the second phase.  I was kind of upset with myself on how I had played during the second phase. I didn't play near as good as I had done on the first phase. Maybe it was because I was tired, or maybe it was because I had heard Michelle-chan play first, and that had caused my hopes to just burn. Either way, it didn't really matter. I was still sure I'd get like 6th or 7th chair... possibly 8th on the Symphonic band. I was hoping Sally and I would be sitting next to each other. XD  So my friends and I sat down on this... ledge-kind-of-thing near where they post the results. I'm telling you... I was trying to fall asleep in any place and at any time as I could. I took a walk of "disappointment" around the school that we were in... and I think I walked around twice, maybe three times. But no one cares a crap. When I came back, the results still weren't posted. So, I decided to sit down where my other friends were, too. I was still thinking of my performance in the second phase and how not-so-good I had played. I was trying to take that off my head, so I asked Yaqui how her performance had been. She told me that she did good, but the monitor lady had told them (Veronica, Sheniece, and Brittany S) to quite down a few times because they were making a bit quite of noise and were talking. Then she told me that since they were continuing being "loud," the monitor went and whispered to the judges, looking at them. I said, "Y'know, that's not good. You do know that you get points deducted for talking during the try outs, right?" She nodded, and she was starting to get a little nervous and worried because of that.  Y'see, our band director, Ms. Fedynich, was putting too much pressure on Yaqui-chan because Ms. F wanted for Yaqui to beat this guy from our "rival" school, Byrd, known as Elias (whom for some reason always looks angry). What? Ms. F had absolutely no right to put such pressure over Yaqui. I was hoping that she wouldn't beat him, because that'd be just too ironic and maybe Ms. F would learn to not tell kids what to do. Maybe that had jinxed Yaqui, 'cause the results were just not what I had expected.  A couple of minutes later, they posted the Percussion results. Some flute players went over and checked just for the heck of it, but when they told me that Erica H hadn't made it to neither of the bands, much less an Alternate, I was just shocked. What... the... crap?! I quickly looked over and I couldn't see Erica-san's name anywhere. What the fug was wrong with those idiotic and moronic fools that dare to call themselves judges?!? Erica's just an awesome percussionist, and whoever thinks otherwise must be shot right now. I could see that Shaw-san was right next to Erica-san, comforting her because Erica-san was crying. I could understand... I would have done the same if I was her. Then I noticed something that just made me drop my jaw to the ground: Shaw-san, another excellent percussionist (I'm serious) didn't make it to the Symphonic band, but to the Concert band... 1st chair. Now I just knew for sure, with no doubt at all, that those judges had been smoking while "judging." I know that those two girls are just amazing players, and that they could have easily made it to the Symphonic band. But what had gone wrong?  To make things worst, Jack P, a 7th grade percussionist from our school, had made it to an Alternate. No, I'm not trying to say that I have anything against Jack for being an Alternate and Erica-san not even being one, but when this happens, you know there's something wrong. Maybe Erica-san and Shaw-san got nervous, but who knows. The only understandable reason is that the judges were fugged up!  Every time a lady with a piece of paper would post something where they post the results, a bunch of brainless losers would run up over there. Of course, when they posted the flute results, I didn't stand up at all. Instead, I told Sally to tell me what chair and band I had made. I had heard that Sarah B had gotten first chair on the Symphonic band (well, of course... what else could she had expected?) and Ciarra second chair on the same band as Sarah. Instead of Sally-chan telling me what I had made, Michelle told me that I got 10th chair, and I had made it to the Symphonic band. 10th chair. I, dany the dot, had gotten 10th chair. There was extreme disappointment inside of me, but I didn't want to yell out and scream to let my rage out. What happened? I was expecting at least 8th chair, but 10th? I just sighed and said, "Oh well..." But I wasn't thinking of that exactly. I was so upset I could break a glass with my hand. Blast these stupid AR tryouts! What kind of idiot would have come up with this, anyway?! And I still think that these tryouts weren't worth at all. You'll see what I mean when I tell you what they gave us for having gone through such crap and pain. Morons.  It broke my heart when I heard Michelle-chan made 3rd chair. "Maybe she is better than me," I thought. Oh well, so what? The thing that made me feel better was when I heard that I'd be sitting next to Sally, for she had gotten 11th chair. It cheered me up a little bit to know that the person next to me would be someone I knew and considered my friend, not some other person that I had never seen before. See? I told you that we would always end up by each other! XD This was just great.  A couple of minutes later they posted the clarinets result. Yaqui was nervous, I could see, so she made Michelle go and check what chair and band she had made (hehe, poor Michelle XD). Yet another disappointment. Disillusions were everywhere in this stupid place. Yaqui-chan had gotten 11th chair on the Symphonic band. Blasted judges! When Michelle told us this, I had to go and check for myself. Maybe she was just making a joke or something, but I went up there and I saw that she was, unfortunately, right. Now, let's think about this. Yaqui told me that Veronica, Sheniece and Brittany S were talking and had gotten in trouble for talking, right? Well, these 4 clarinet players are one of the best clarinet players there is, and they could have gotten high chairs on the Symphonic band if they wanted to. But, the result was worst than they thought. All of those 4 fantastic clarinet players had gotten low chairs, and I'm pretty sure it was not because they sucked, but because they were talking and they had deducted points for that. I just knew that it wouldn't turn out well. What did Elias make? Second chair. Hurts, doesn't it?  So, yeah, I saw Yaqui's face and all I could see was big words written all over it that said, "DISSATISFIED". Not really, but still. I just wanted to get out of this heck of a place. I don't remember what time it was when we left (I think it was around 4 PM), but it was getting dark. We got into the bus and I sat by myself. I didn't feel like seeing anyone, much less talking to anyone. I was trying to sleep during our way back to RMS. Though, without an intention, I eavesdropped and heard a little conversation that Ms. F was having with Yaqui. I didn't hear all of it, though, much less remember the whole thing, but I do remember this, "Are you upset because you didn't do as well as you thought you would?" Darn straight, lady. Mr. Williams also talked to me. He congratulated me for making 10th chair, and to Sally and Michelle, too (they were sitting behind me). I just told him, "Thanx," and that I was expecting a higher chair than 10th. But, for some reason, Sally just... made me happy. Sitting next to a kick arse friend like her is the best thing that can happen.  When we got to RMS, I didn't even see Yaqui leave. I guess she really was angry. I went inside the band hall because I had to call my parents to pick me up. As I was waiting for someone to finish talking on the phone, I heard that Jack P was playing an etude for percussion. Shaw-san was right behind me, and I heard her say, "Who in the world is playing that song...?!" For some insane reason, I felt like laughing, but I didn't because I knew Shaw-san wouldn't find it funny. Since it was a Saturday, I told my parents all about that had happened on AR. I decided to get "drunk" to forget this horrible day. It sucks that you have to do it every year.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wrote this "editorial" (note the quotation marks)&nbsp;a long time ago. And since I won't be writing in this blog for personal reasons, then I decided to post it here to at least make it look like I wrote something. There'll be 3 parts to it, since it's just so fuggin' long, so it'll take up the space of three days. It's actually entertaining to read,&nbsp;and it kills&nbsp;time.&nbsp;Behold! My AR "editorial"!  Saturday, November 8, 2003 - All-Region Tryouts Phase I  Worst. Day. Ever. A pain in the neck, and those AR tryouts were not worth at all. But I'll start from the beginning. Since these tryouts were on a Saturday, it ruined my whole weekend. I put my alarm to wake me up at 7.20 'cause I had to get to the band hall at 8 AM. Of course, I woke up earlier than that because I was nervous. I always get nervous before a contest for some reason. Some time before we went to the AR tryouts, Ms. Fedynich and the band made a promise that 32 of the whole band would make it to an AR spot. We had to get to Mensfield at 9 o clock, and I think that the tryouts started at 9.30 or so. Once we got there we had to warm-up a little bit, then we had to find out what room we were supposed to play in. For those ignorants out there who don't know what the All-Region tryouts are, I'll tell you: they're crap. Ok, so they're not crap most of the time, but usually they are. I'll explain what they are.  Some time in September, your band director gives you these two pieces (three if you're in high school) which are called etudes. They give you a fast etude and a slow etude (a medium etude if in high school). You have to learn the etudes before you can go to the AR tryouts. I really don't know if they're mandatory or if you can decide if you want to go, but Ms. F made us go anyway and we didn't have a choice. Anyways, when I was gonna try out for an AR band (8th grade), they didn't make us learn the whole piece. We just had to learn half of it. I'm guessing that if you're in hs, you have to learn the whole thing. Learning those two etudes was a pain in the neck. We had chair tests over those, and heck, it was a lot of hard work. The etudes that the flutes got were: fast etude - Bourrée Anglaise (Sonata for Flute), written by Bach. The tempo of this etude was quarter note equals 80-92. The slow etude was Selected Studies for Flute, C Major written by Heinze. Tempo was quarter note equals 72-90. Of course, we had to play it at 72 because a slow piece is not supposed to go at 90. That's just too fast. Not only do you have to learn those two etudes, but in middle school you have to learn the 7 major scales and the chromatic. Out of those 7 major scales, the AR people will choose 2 scales, and you'll always have to play the chromatic. The scales have to be memorized, and you have to tongue them up and slur them down.  Once you try out and the judges decide what chair you're in, you're put in a band. There's two kinds of bands: a Symphonic and a Concert band. If you get placed in the Symphonic band, then that means that you kicked arse during the AR tryouts and you were one of the best ones. If you got into the Concert bands, then that means you played good, but not good enough to be in the Symphonic band. That doesn't mean you suck, though. If you didn't make it to either band but the judges think that you played good, you'll be an Alternate. If someone from the Symphonic or Concert band can't go to the rehearsals, then an Alternate will be picked and you'll play in their spot. Once it's been confirmed on what chair and band you're in, you'll receive this folder with pieces of music that you have to learn before an All-Region concert. But, I'll explain more about that later.  Depending on how many people of your instrument try out for an AR spot, it will determine if there will be one phase or two phases. Instruments like the flute and clarinet had to have two phases, because there were about 300 people from different schools competing. Bigger instruments like the tuba and bari sax only have one phase. The first phase will consist of playing two scales, the chromatic memorized, and parts of your fast and slow etude. Once you're done playing the scales, you have to play the parts of an etude that the judges choose. If you play the tuba or a bari sax or a bigger instrument with not too many people for competition, you're done for the day. You go outside (by outside I mean the "cafeteria"... we were in a school-sort-of-thing) and wait for a lady to post the results to see what band you made it to and what chair. But, if you play the clarinet or something like that, you have to do the second phase. Once you're done with the first phase, you have to go outside and see if your letters are posted up to see if you made it to the second phase. Now, let's talk about the letters...  As you can see, this AR stuff is really confusing and it takes a while to get done. When you arrive to the place where they're gonna held the All-Region tryouts, you have to look for the room that you're gonna be in and play off your stuff. In each room there's a monitor. You have to talk to that monitor, give him or her your name, and she'll give you two letters on which you'll be known as. The letters that I got were DE. When you're playing your scales or whatever to the judges, they won't know your name. The only thing that you're known as to them is the two letters that you got. Of course, the judges will be behind some kind of curtain so they can't see who you are.  Now that everything has been explained, let's go back to my crappy day. As usual, I was nervous and I couldn't warm up. I guess I was excited. My stomach felt weird, but I knew that this day would be over. I was trying to get a better chair than Michelle. Yes, folks, I was competing against her. I was determined to beat her on AR since she had beaten me every single time that we had a chair test in our school.  My good friend Sally and I play about the same level. As I have mentioned before, 89% of the time that we had some kind of chair test, we'd be sitting right next to each other. Sally-chan told me that if I did good on the tryouts, she'd do good. If I did bad, she would do bad. Who knew that would be true at the end?  The only person that I had in my room and that I knew was Sarah B. The other people were just... unknown to me. I was the first one to play my scales. I thought I did awesome! Of course, I had to wait for everyone to play their other scales. Then the second part of the first phase started. Now I was the last one to play. Yet again, I though I kicked arse. I have never played so good before... If I kept this up, I would easily get a top chair. I was so happy right then.  By right now, for a lot of people, AR tryouts were over. What made me upset the most was that Regi didn't make it to any of the bands, much less an Alternate. What? But she's a good player! I could see that she was disappointed. Goddess dang it! I'm sure the judges were fugged up, 'cause I just know that she's a kick arse player. To make things worst, Rona had made it to the Symphonic band. No, I'm not saying that I didn't want her to make it, it's just that Regina had some competition with Rona... she wanted to beat Rona, but it turned out she didn't get a better chair than her. Dang it! >.  I had also found out that So-Young, the best saxophone player you'll ever hear, hadn't made it to the Symphonic band, but instead, she had been first chair of the Concert band. What?! I was sure that she'd made it to the Symphonic band but... I mean, Concert band? I now knew for sure that the judges were extremely fugged up to the max! Ugh... I was just... shocked that she hadn't made it to the Symphonic band... She seemed kinda disappointed, too, and I remembered she said, "Yeah... well..." I know it doesn't say much, but dang it, I could see she was upset. What the heck was wrong with these idiotic judges?!  If you didn't make it to the second phase or you were done with the AR tryouts, you had to take a bus with your director that would take you back to your school. I anxiously waited for the results. When I saw a lady go and post a piece of paper where they post the results, I ran over there to see if I had made it. Boo-yah, I made it to the second phase. By now it was around 11.30 AM or so. Maybe 12 PM... I was starving. So I decided to eat. I was so happy that I had made it to the second phase. Sally, Yaqui, Michelle, and other people made it, too. Most of the flutes did pretty well, and a few had to take the bus back to school.  I don't remember when the second phase was gonna start, but they gave us quite a long break. Once I had finished my lunch, all my happiness was gone. I felt tired, and I wanted to go home. I was sick of all this AR tryouts crap. My back was hurting and I was sleepy. At that point, my excitement to play was somewhere else. I was starting to think that I will not be playing as good as I had done while in&nbsp;the first phase.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        There's a little bit of insanity in all of us. There's just a higher concentration in me. -Kaden  &nbsp;  Since I had lessons today, Ms. Callaway told me about the band camp crap. Ugh, band... the last thing I wanted to hear about. She told me that next week we're gonna get started. I'm gonna be there every day for two weeks. The first week (this is what I understood) I'm gonna be there for around 10 hours a day: morning, afternoon and night. We'll finish at like 9 PM. These people are insane. They must be really traumatized with band and music. Then the second week we're only gonna go morning and night... or something like that. Ms. Callaway doesn't know where we're gonna do this camp stuff. Supposedly we were gonna do this in the high school, but since it's just a mess because of all the construction going on, then she has no idea. She told me that last year the section leader called you and told you info about the band crap, so I hope they do that this year.   The only good thing I can think about that's gonna be worthwhile about this band camp crap is that I get to see Mikey and all of my friends. I haven't seen Michael-kun or any of my friends for a loooooong time... Except Michelle. I see that girl every Tuesday, and her maturity level is still really low. Ha-ha, silly girl. XD So practically, after this week, my summer's over. Bummer. I better get going with reading WtLD.   My mom also told me that she saw Yaqui-chan as she was going inside to her lessons. My mom said that she had her hair straight or something like that. Whoa, that's something I gotta see! =P Oh, and also... Brook Mays is moving to Cedar Hill.&nbsp;I don't know why but they just are. Ms. Callaway told me they were moving because it was a dump in that place. She said once she found a roach and she could hear crickets and stuff. Bleh.   And to close off, Kosovar's returning back to the US on August 11 and hopefully be able to fix the ZP Boards and not have to go to those temporary forums anymore. He also said that he's working on a new skin for the ZP main site, and that's good since the one they have right now isn't very high quality... and it isn't the best skin ever. So w00t for Koso and his returning-ness! Of course, anyone who's not familiar with ZP has no idea what I'm talking about, so boo-yah all of you Non-ZPers! The OoT Community, which includes Goddess Din, Mike, Kaden, Groucho, and I,&nbsp;is making an 3V1L PL0T to take over the General Chat once the old boards come back. Ah, yes. Our head leader is Goddess Din, but if we fail, then we'll blame it on Mike AKA Link2004. =D Behold! PH34R T3H OoT Community!   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hey, listen to your elders, you kids. *crazy eye* -Goddess Din   Well this sucks... I was gonna buy WtLD to start reading it but they said that they ran out... Sucks. I have to order it and it'll get there on the first of August. Procrastination pwns. So, yeah. All this band camp stuff is gonna start soon... sigh. School's getting closer, too. I don't know... I'm kind of scared. It's not that I'm scared of going to the ninth grade... it's just that all of those goofy 7th graders won't be there... not to mention that So-Young, the spiffiest girl you'll ever meet, won't be with us in our first high school year. Also, I'm not so excited about the marching band. It's gonna be of annoyance to me, instead of me enjoying it. I still don't know why I'm in band if I don't like it. Probably I will... but I doubt it. Eh, too many doubts and worries when school hasn't started. Life rocks.  I'm kind of ashamed... I haven't written to So-Young in a long time. What the heck? I adore her to death, and I don't wanna lose her friendship... even though we're just e-mailing each other. Yeah, but still. She's so awesome you wouldn't believe. Anyone who knows her must agree with this, because you know it's true. Dang, how much I miss her. =\ But anyways, I don't wanna talk about that because it's just way too depressing for me, so I'll stop here. Yeah, I haven't written on a while, and this is a short entry, but what the heck.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Uruguay VS Brazil 1-1, Penalties: Brazil 5, Uruguay 4. Yes, Uruguay lost. Fug Brazil. They suck. What the heck? Every team that I wanted to win lost. Yeah, Colombia lost against Argentina, so now the finals is Argentina VS Brazil. It's always the same fuggin' story. I bet that Brazil is gonna win. Fug them, I say. I'm sick and tired of Brazil always winning. But man Uruguay was playing so good on the first half. They were controlling the ball so amazingly. At minute 22 they scored, but 10 minutes before that they had another chance of scoring. I mean, Uruguay was less than a meter away from the goal and then they miss it. Sigh, what a shame. But you should have seen Brazil when Uruguay scored... they were so fuggin' mad! They were pushing, kicking, smacking... they were trying to do anything they could so that they could get the ball. It was hilarious.  On the second half, though, Brazil scored in less than a minute. Bad stuff. Then Brazil started to control the ball now. So in other words,  Brazil still sucks.  They didn't win, they just won by luck. I hate penalty shots. It's not fair to win like that. It all depends on the goalie to stop the ball.&nbsp;Brazil is not the winner, they're just winners by luck. I hate them now. So now Colombia is going against Uruguay, and the finals is Argentina VS Brazil. I don't know who I want to win between those. I mean,&nbsp;I hate Argentina, but now I loathe Brazil, too. But I guess I'll have to go with Argentina, since they didn't beat Mexico. So... yeah. Go Argentina, I guess.   urlLink  But Uruguay kicks anyone's ar s e!    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        There are 7 billion people in this world, but only one of them is me. Does that make me unique? -Groucho  Yesterday I bought FSA and I've been hooked up to it since last night. It's a pretty kick arse game. This is like FF: CC: it's meant to be played in multiplayer mode. But like FF: CC, I still enjoy the single-player mode, so screw anyone who thinks that FSA sucks. Idiots. I've been having a lot of fun playing it, even if I'm just playing it by myself. Cool thing is that I got a GBA Cable for free. w00t. I sold my Wavebird Wireless Controller because it wasn't working anymore, but just for 8 dollars. Yeah, it's not much but that's the most they were gonna give me. Err.  &nbsp;  FSA is a lot like ALttP. There's ALttP songs, enemies, items, and much more. Just like in ALttP, you have to rescue the maidens that are trapped in crystals. I find FSA's style a lot like FF: CC, and it's kinda spiffy. I love both of those game, even though a lot of people didn't like them. Well screw 'em. There's also a few TWW stuff, like bosses and crap. Overall, it's a good game. I forgot to mention that I also bought a new controller 'cause none of the ones that I had were working, like I've mentioned before. Right now I'm Near the Fields (L4), and I'm gonna start on the first... place-thingy. So, yeah, that's it for my "report" of FSA.  &nbsp;  I also heard that the Nintendo DS, the most spiffy portable system there will be known to mankind, will be released in November (or some time before 2004 is over). Crap. I gotta save up for the Nintendo DS or I'll be behind  everything.  The bad thing is that Maetroid Prime 2: Echoes is also coming out in November, which is another great game. Oh goddess, too many games, so little money. >_   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A couple of minutes ago the match between Mexico and Brazil was over. Before I tell you who won, lemme tell you some stuff that was not even fair. You could have easily seen that the referee was against Mexico and was with Brazil. There were supposed to be several penalties against Brazil, but no. And even one penalty could have changed the results easily. One of them was clearly seen that it was supposed to be a penalty! But no, fuggin' referee has to say it isn't. You know how many faults Brazil made over Mexico? Twenty five. Yellow cards? Two.&nbsp;You know how many faults Mexico did over Brazil? Around ten. Yellow cards? Two. That's not good, or fair.  &nbsp;  I know that O. Sanchez is a good goalie, but the defense of Mexico wasn't so good. I don't think it has ever been. So every time that Mexico gets far in a cup, they lose. Don't get me wrong, Mexico has won several cups, and the most recent one has been the Gold Cup (which was in 2003, I think). And guess what? In the Gold Cup they went to the finals against Brazil, and they won against them. Brazil's not a tough rival to Mexico. Mexico could beat their arse any time they wanted. The result was 4-0. See? One fuggin' penalty could have changed everything, because when there was supposed to be a penalty, it was on the second half, minute 20 or so, and the score was 2-0. It could have been 2-1 and change the route of the game, and maybe Mexico could have obtained a tie, and possibly even win. But whose fault was it? The darn referee's. You could easily see that the Brazil player went straight for the Mexican's legs inside the penalty area&nbsp;just to get him away from the ball. Fug the referrees. Always cheating and getting money for that. Referrees usually are the guilty ones for making a good team lose, and that's because they're not doing a good job at it. You should have seen the face when the score was 4-0 and he gave a yellow card to a Brazilian. He was fuggin' happy, and so was the Brazilian player. Fug them. I hope Brazil loses.  &nbsp;  But enough of that. The good thing is that Uruguay won against Paraguay 3-1. Maybe this is what I get after wanting for Paraguay to lose. I only wanted them to lose because I remember Regi told me that her cousins hated Mexico and they were with Paraguay. So that's why I didn't want for them to win, and I was happy when they lost. I bet Regi's cousins were happy when Mexico got kicked off from the cup. So now Argentina is going against Colombia and Uruguay VS Brazil. Here's how I want for it to end. It doesn't matter if Argentina wins or not, but I want for Uruguay to kick Brazil's arse. Though, if Brazil wins, then I wish Colombia could win 'cause I just despise Argentina. So the finals could either be (teams in parenthesis are the ones I want for them to win):  &nbsp;  Uruguay VS Argentina (Uruguay)  Uruguay VS Colombia (Doesn't matter, but I'd want for Uruguay to win the cup)  Colombia VS Brazil (Colombia)  &nbsp;  If it happens to end up as Brazil VS Argentina, then I want for Brazil to win, though I hope the finals don't end up like that. Uruguay deserves to win, so... GO URUGUAY! And anyone who disagrees must die right now. Fug Brazil and Argentina. I hope they're burning in my closet. *Ice Beams them* Haha, losers. But even though Mexico is out of the cup, Mike makes jokes about Brazil that just make your day better and make this cup a thing of the past. If anyone gets this, then you're so darn spiffy:&nbsp; (brazil) ¬ &nbsp; But enough of that. If I heard right from my aunt, I think I'm getting $170 dollars from her. I could either be insane or insane. I was half-listening, but she told me that she's gonna give me that much money because she didn't buy me anything while she was here. Also, I had told her that I'm saving up to buy a GCN game (yes, folks, I didn't buy FSA this weekend because my parents didn't have "time" to take me to the mall). So... yeah. If you don't count the money that my aunt is giving me, I have 50 dollars (my other aunt gave me 10 bucks), plus whatever money I get by selling MoHAA. This is good stuff, folks. I love my aunts. So, yeah, they're leaving on Tuesday at 5 AM. Sadness. I have nothing else to write about so I'll close here.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Look, is a secret so listen carefully, you can make a secret more of a secret if a secret is told secretly to that person and in secret...secretly. [SECRET]Hair dye![/SECRET] -Goddess Din  Yesterday my mom felt a very strong abdominal pain at around 11.30 PM. She said that it hurt really bad so we decided to go to the Methodist Hospital of Dallas. My aunts and I went with her, and my dad and brother stayed home. As we were driving to the hospital, I could see that she was about to cry, but I didn't look, 'cause I hate it when people cry.&nbsp;I&nbsp;just feel terrible, and I'm sure other people feel that way when they see one of their family members cry. The good thing was that my aunts kept making her laugh and stuff. We arrived at the hospital's emergency room&nbsp;at like 11.45.  We had to sign in and stuff. I hate hospitals, they're such sad places to be in. All those sick people and all. It was so fuggin' cold in there, but I was feeling warm, surprisingly. They called us twice to put my mom's data and all that crap, and we had to pay quite a few dollars just to check. My mom didn't have the money that they were asking for, so she just gave the lady the money she had. Then we went back outside. I think it's really stupid that they ask you your data and all that crap when you're just dying of pain. Isn't it called  emergency room ? I mean, my mom was really suffering from the pain, but it was quite a few hours before they called her in to check her. Fug that. I know that they attend the other people who are worst than&nbsp;you, but&nbsp;heck, if you don't cry&nbsp;when you&nbsp;go in that emergency room&nbsp;then you have to wait. Bull.  &nbsp;  Since it was extremely cold in that place, it was making my mom feel worst. I was getting soft so I asked the lady if they had a blanket. They didn't. So I called my dad to bring a blanket for my mom. I waited outside for my dad and while&nbsp;I was waiting a made a little conversation with a doctor that was outside. Nice. About five or ten minutes later my dad arrived with the blanket. He gave it to me then he left. I came back in and I noticed that they still hadn't called my mom. Blasted morons. My aunts still were inside and kept making jokes and laughing, but then my mom told them to be quiet since they were the only loud ones. Then thirty minutes later my aunts couldn't stand being silenced so they went to grab some coffee then went to the car to "sleep," but they were just talking and laughing. I sat next to my mom to warm her feet since they were really cold. Know what's stupid? She was feeling better already. See, this is what I'm talking about. A few hours ago my mom was dying from the pain, and they were asking her questions when she was feeling really bad. Fuggers. Now that she had gone through the pain and a bunch of stupid moronic questions, she feels better without the help of any doctor. Ugh. I mean, there was this lady that just by seeing her face you could see her agony and that she had a really bad abdominal pain, but they took a really long time before they called her in. Once they called her she was feeling better (w00t for eavasdroping). _ _;;  &nbsp;  At around 2 AM they called my mom, and she didn't have the abdominal pain anymore. They took us to this room and a few minutes later this nurse came in to ask her more questions, then she left 'cause they were gonna get a doctor or something. It was even more cold in that room, so thank goddess that we brought a blanket with us. My mom was lying in this bed with the blanket while I was sitting in a chair. She kept asking me if I was cold but I told her I wasn't. A while later this doctor came and didn't ask that many questions about the pain, but he told my mom that she was going to have to take stronger medication because the one she was taking wasn't helping. He said he was going to write a prescription so we had to wait in the room until he was back. A couple of minutes later my mom noticed I was cold so she made me sit next to her with the blanket. Forty-five minutes passed and the darn doctor still didn't come with the prescription. My mom was getting desperate and kept sneezing, 'cause you can't imagine how fuggin' cold it was in there. So I kept roaming the halls to see if I could find the doctor that had attended us, but since I didn't see him I decided to ask the nurse who had come inside before. She told me we had to wait for it to be written, and that's all she said. Err.  &nbsp;  It was almost 3 AM and still no prescription. I went outside again and found the doctor I had talked to before while I was outside (he called me Ms. Spongebob 'cause I was wearing my Spongebob PJs). He asked me if I needed anything and I told him about the prescription and all. He told me that it was already written, so they were gonna take it to my mom's room in just a few minutes. The nurse came and explained everything, then we went back to the car. The whole ride back was just a whole bunch of laughter, but I couldn't laugh because every time I did my stomach would hurt. Once we got home and we were going to the apartment we couldn't walk because one of my aunts was just making us laugh so bad. We had to sit down for a while. Holy crap, it seemed as if though we were drunk! Hilarious stuff. I didn't go to sleep until 6 AM and woke up until 3.45 PM. Great night. Since this was yet another long entry, I'll write about the quarter finals of soccer tomorrow, even though no one cares except me. =P Hehe, 'tis all.     
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You know you're addicted to the computer when... you turn sideways to smile. -Unknown  Dang, I'm so fuggin' tired right now. My parents woke me up from playing their loud 80s music at 11 AM, so I had no choice but to get off from my bed. ;_; Then my dad asked me if I wanted to go to the Center of Dallas to give my aunt a tour around it and stuff. So I went (yes, I actually went outside). I had fun, actually, but it made my poor little feet ache. We went to this place that had a bunch of stores inside this building, and we bought a couple of souvenirs for my aunt.&nbsp; I wanted to ride the DART Trains to see where they would take us, but we didn't know how far they'd take us and if they would ride back to Dallas. w00t for ignorance. So we didn't. Darn. We walked around some more, but it wasn't the time to do so 'cause it was so fuggin' hot and I was starting to get a headache. We decided to go to the aquarium just because. Holy crap, the line was huge! But we didn't have to wait for long because the line was moving fast. My sister kept being annoying and she wanted to be in my dad's arms the whole time. We can never have a fun time when my sis is around. Always ruining the fun. &nbsp;  &nbsp;  I haven't gone to the aquarium for a long time. I think the last time I went was 3 and a half years ago. Yep. It was quite different from when I last went. I think they're gonna add sharks to it or something. But anyways, we saw the&nbsp;ginormous (© of Sally)&nbsp;crocodile. It looked kinda fake, but then I saw it move. Oh my fuggin' goddess... you wouldn't believe how huge it was! It was just standing there, but still amazing. It's an endangered specie, and it's called the orinoco crocodile. Eh, yeah, that. And then there was another elephant-walrus-kind-of-thing, called the antillean manatee. So, yeah, I had fun. &nbsp;  &nbsp;  I was hungry because I hadn't eaten anything for breakfast. My parents took us to this restaurant they had gone to before called T.G.I. Friday's. I had heard of it before but I had never been there. I ordered this plate that looked like orange chicken, but it was more sweet. It tasted so fuggin' good, but orange chicken is still better. ;P We were sharing and trading food, so more fun. Wheee. &nbsp;  &nbsp;  We finally went home at 3.45 PM. Ah, at last, relaxation. As I was reading one of my favorite xangas to read, I find out about something that just made me so angry.&nbsp; Click  urlLink here &nbsp;to see what made my jealousy come out of my veins. Of course, if you're not a Conan O' Brien fan, then you'll just say, "What the heck is this?" Well dang it! Just look at that girl's face! 100% garden toolness! She doesn't deserve to see Conan backstage! Dang it! And just look at her xanga. No one can understand that crap! Horrible spelling and grammar. But anyways, I already took my anger out with Sally. Meh, hopefully we'll get to see Conan backstage, or even be on the show. Anyone can always dream, you know. ;P Funny thing is that on the first picture, that girl looks like Katie A. X_x;; No offense! XD I'm just saying. Sigh, curse you, girl-who-went-to-see-Conan-backstage! ;_;  &nbsp;  I just finished watching the soccer match between Peru VS Argentina. Darn, Argentina won 1-0. How come all of the teams that I want them to win lose? Uruguay VS Argentina: Uruguay loses, Paraguay VS Brazil: Brazil loses. And now this game. What the fug? Mexico better not lose against Brazil, or I'll Ice Beam someone. I think right now Colombia is playing against Costa Rica. Meh, not gonna watch it. But! Tomorrow Mexico plays, so of course I'm gonna watch it, same thing with Paraguay VS Uruguay. w00t! &nbsp;  &nbsp;  Also, I drew a picture of Mike S and I with the Ice Beam and Plasma Beam... he has the Plasma Beam and I'm holding the Ice Beam. Looks kick arse. You can click  urlLink here  to take a look at it.&nbsp;&nbsp;Whoa, this was a long entry. I think I'll stop here, hehe. XD Tomorrow I'm gonna go buy Four Swords Adventures, hopefully a new GCN Controller if my dad's in the mood, and the book When the Legends Die. Blah, boring book.    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        If life gives you lemons... throw them at the idiot who gave them to you instead of the oranges you asked for. -Mike  I've never had so much fun in a message board before. What&nbsp;am I talking about? &nbsp;In the  urlLink ZeldaPower Temporary Forums , there's a  urlLink forum of Ocarina of Time . Holy crap. There's five members there that just keep the OoT forum alive: Kaden, Goddess Din, Mike (aka Link2004), Groucho, and of course me. =P Seriously, I love those guys. They're just so fuggin' funny, and I just love going there to have a good time. We make a lot of inside jokes, and as of right now there's one of my closet being hell. Supposedly Mike's soul is there, and we just make fun of it and have a good time. If any of you guys are reading this, then I just wanna say that all of you rawk! =D&nbsp;  &nbsp;  But tonight was crazy. I spent  8 hours  talking to Mike S. Holy crap! That's like a day of school! O_O If it were a friend of mine like Yaqui,&nbsp;I would have gotten tired of talking to her. But I was talking to Mike for 8 hours! That's insane! We didn't go to sleep until 3 AM. Hehe, funny. Mike just pwns. We kept making inside jokes. I love inside jokes. I have the most with him. Lately we've talked a lot about Metroid Prime (and I've laughed so hard lately with him, too!), and we made an inside joke of the Ice Beam and Plasma Beam. Y'see, every time we get "angry" at each other (we really don't, but we're just playing around) or one of us says something stupid, we Ice Beam or Plasma Beam each other. He uses the Plasma Beam and I use the Ice Beam. It's kinda funny, but of course, no one else would think it's funny because it's an inside joke. =P So if you're reading this, Mike S, then take this! *Ice Beams Mike for no reason* Mwuahahaha! >=D I don't wanna forget this conversation that we had about Metroid Prime (MP), so I'm gonna put it up ("dice" means "says" in Spanish, not the dice you roll!). Hehe, those were the days...    dany the dot dice: "No way! You have got to hate those Power Troopers... or at least the Space Pirates. Stupid song! Gets you humming it."  mike dice: lol  dany the dot dice: hahahahaahha, im gonna download that song  mike dice: =o good idea, that song is cool  dany the dot dice: ITS ANNOYING!! WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!?!?! omgs, i hate you =P  mike dice: =(... its cool but evil  dany the dot dice: AMEN TO THAT  mike dice: XD  dany the dot dice: IIII FOUND IT! but im downloading phendrana drifts first cause that song rocks  mike dice: w00t, yep, phendrana and magmoor are my favourite places  dany the dot dice: phendrana and tallon for me, magmoor creeps me out from those... flying pirates. eh, why did i buy mp if it creeps me out? XD  mike dice: lol XD one charged blast from the plasma beam kills them or if you freeze them  dany the dot dice: or a power missile  mike dice: yep  dany the dot dice: well you can freeze them then fire a missile, that kills them too  mike dice: yep, but plasma beam is kick ass, so is the ice beam  dany the dot dice: i like the flamethrower, boom boom booooooom  mike dice: flamethrower?  dany the dot dice: theres a flamethrower  mike dice: oh  dany the dot dice: if you use a missile with the plasma beam, it transforms into a flame thrower  mike dice: ooh, i don't have it  dany the dot dice: =o NO WAY, MIKE!  mike dice: XD  dany the dot dice: GO BACK AND PLAY MP RIGHT NOW!!!  mike dice: ok =P  dany the dot dice: hahahahahaha, hehe, i saw that space pirate song and now i cant find it  mike dice: =o bummer  dany the dot dice: found it, now im downloading it  mike dice: shweet  dany the dot dice: ooohhh its gonna bring back painful memories >. mike dice: XD you got killed?  dany the dot dice: in the space pirate thingy in phendrana drifts, where you get the therm visor... OMGS, THAT PLACE WAS HARD, I KEPT GETTING KILLED  mike dice: same  dany the dot dice: then i stopped playing mp for a while  mike dice: not me  dany the dot dice: then i got mad and decided to try again  mike dice: lol, that happened to me in LTTP  dany the dot dice: there were space pirates in there?!?!?! ...:wink:  mike dice: yep =P  dany the dot dice: hahahah  mike dice: LTTP was hard  dany the dot dice: no seriously, i would start SCREAMING when i saw one, and i'd continue screaming while shooting at those space pirates, then when i'd beat them, i'd start laughing insanely and laugh at them, and when i saw another one, i'd do the same thing  mike dice: ........... xD why?  dany the dot dice: XD CAUSE THEY JUST POP OUT OF NOWHERE AND HECK, IM TELLING YOU! THAT SONG IS CREEPY!  mike dice: lol, send please =D  dany the dot dice: of course, it's 56%  mike dice: oh, i assumed it was done XD  dany the dot dice: and my bro would only make it worst cause he'd say, "SHOOT! SHOOT! THEY'RE RIGHT THERE! OH NO... THEYRE BEHIND YOU! SHOOT I TELL YOU!!!" @_@  mike dice: XD was he laughing?  dany the dot dice: no  mike dice: oh  dany the dot dice: we took turns, we were MP-maniacs then... yep *ice beams mike* ...for no reason  mike: showdown,victory 2/4 and triumph pwn dice: XD its teh ice beam xD  dany's maniac killer scream dice: xD AHHH, IM PLAYING THAT SPACE PIRATE SONG AND IM SCARED... IM SOOO PATHETIC xD  mike dice: xD  dany the dot dice: oh no... you know how it starts all secretly?  mike dice: yeah  dany the dot dice: like... yeah, and then it starts more devilish  mike dice: >=D  dany the dot dice: hehe, it feels like im playing the game @_@  mike dice: XD  dany the dot dice: I HATE THAT SOOOOONG, GET IT OFFFFF  mike dice: >=/ =P .... XD  dany the dot dice: hahahahahaha, man, i dont think im going to be able to take MP2: E  mike dice: =o that's just... not cool XD  dany the dot dice: im gonna FAINT  mike dice: XD =P suure  dany the dot dice: i know, but i WILL buy it  mike dice: w00t  dany the dot dice: @_@ :fear: and i'll use my technique: i'll start screaming and screaming until i kill them all  mike dice: XD its dany's maniac killer scream  dany the dot dice: HAHA, DUMB MIKE!! i was drinking juice and i started laughing, and it came out of my nose!  mike dice: XD xD  ============================  dany the dot dice: lets see if my scanner works  mike dice: ok, to draw something? whoa  dany the dot dice: hahahaha, yeah, i made a crappy sketch so i wanna scan it  mike dice: ohh  dany the dot dice: BUT IT WONT WORK!!! +@ UGH!! *ICE BEAMS MIKE*  mike dice: *is frozen*  dany the dot dice: ugh, stupid thing, lemme restart the computer and see if it works  mike dice: ok  ....  dany the dot dice: HAHAHA! YOU PUT THAT IMAGE?! XD  mike dice: MWUAHAHAHAHAHA XD  dany the dot: xD i should have put the green sweater... =\  mike dice: XD lol  dany the dot: AND&nbsp;w00t THE SCANNER WORKS! BOO-YAH  mike dice: w00t, if i still had my scanner, i'd terrorize the net with my horrible drawings >=D  dany the dot dice: hahahahahaha =o  mike dice: MWUAHAHAHAHAHA XD  dany the dot dice: :fear: *ICE BEAMS MIKE AGAIN* stop terrorizing the townsfolk  mike dice: *plasma beams at the same time*  dany the dot dice: X_x ... Mr michelson Thu Jul 15, 2004 8:49 pm Posting a message... PREPARE YOUR GUNS!  mike dice: *pulls trigger on Plasma beam*  dany the dot dice: *freezes her arm with the ice beam and cant move it* dang it! =x  mike dice: XD but now you can whack people with it  dany the dot: YEAAAH!! >=D  mike dice: lol  dany the dot dice: a-hah! HE LEEEEEEEEEEFT  mike dice: break out the champaigne XD  dany the dot dice: HAHAHAHAHA! FUNNY!!! XD&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;  To close this entry, I'll leave you with a turtle hug made by Kao from ZP.  &nbsp;   urlLink Turtle Hug.     
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We went to the bus station in the metroplex to pick up my aunts. Whoa, they look the same since I last saw them. As we were going back to the house, I spent the ride laughing at the funny stuff my aunts were saying. Fun.   When I got home I watched the soccer match between Brazil and Paraguay. It didn't really matter who won, because they were both qualified for the quarter finals. Paraguay won 2-1, though I wanted for Brazil to win. Dang it. So now there's gonna be 4 matches coming, and I'm gonna watch all of them except one, which is Colombia VS. Costa Rica. Here are the matches, and in parenthesis is the team that I want for them to win:   Perú VS Argentina (Perú)  Paraguay VS Uruguay (Uruguay)  México VS Brazil (this is obvious)   So... yeah. They show those matches on Saturday and Sunday. w00t, 'tis gonna be a weekend of soccer. I love soccer, even though I haven't played it for a long time. I always used to be the goalie, and I was a pretty good one. I'd play with my cousins and we would always have fights. XD Yep, those were the days. Darn you, time.   I went to sleep at 2 AM, and one of my aunts was upset because I was still up. I guess she didn't know that once I stayed up until 6 AM on the internet. Heh. She told me she was gonna wake me up early tomorrow, and heck she was right. I only got 6 hours of sleep, and as of right now I'm so tired. I feel like going to sleep but I can't. Most of the time I spent talking to Mike S... heh, he's so fuggin' funny! He's the one that I can talk to about anything and anytime, and I think he's the one that I can relate to the most. He's always saying some hilarious stuff, and most of them are random. Mike rawks.   Even though we cleaned the carpet yesterday, it still looks dirty and my mom's upset. Oh well. Plus, we cleaned my room for nothing, 'cause supposedly my aunts were gonna sleep in my room, but they ended up sleeping on the living room. Darn, I guess cleaning the carpet didn't help  at all.    Now here's the part that annoys me. Yesterday I sent an e-mail to all the people who send me forwards telling them that I didn't want any kind of forward unless it was a really, really, really but   really   cool, funny, entertaining one. I also put the headline as "Read this carefully." So, this morning, I find out that I have two e-mails for me. I was hoping they would be some interesting e-mails, or newsletters from the many sites that I go to. What do I find? Two fuggin' forwards, and they were forwards from the people that I told not to send any kind of forward unless it was a really, really but   really   cool, funny, entertaining forward. What was it about? The same darn crap, "If you send this to 'x' friends, you'll get good luck, if you don't you'll have bad luck in any kind of rela--" Bullcrap! I'm getting pretty sick of them, and if I keep receiving forwards, then I'll make a new e-mail that no one except&nbsp;four people (maybe 5) will know about. Keep it up and you'll see my rage. Rawr.     
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You can do 1000 good things and no one will ever notice, but when you do one thing wrong, you'll get the whole world against you. -Groucho  Today someone told me the funniest thing ever. Here it is:   Me: I didn't do anything today. =P  Her: As usual, I did. I went to this candy fair.  Me: Gross.  Her: You loser, you're just jealous because I actually did something. =P Unlike you.   Yeah, I'm so jealous of you because you go to uninteresting places and eat candy. I like candy, but I wouldn't like to go to a candy fair. Completely boring. Why would I envy someone else's life? I like my life... my computer life. Just because I don't go to places doesn't mean I'm bored. Haha, I'm jealous of you because you go outside while I stay here on this fuggin' seat cracking up, making some stupid but yet funny jokes with Mike Stag and visiting my favorite websites. Oh yes, jealousy is in the air.   But anyways, enough of that. My mom made me clean the carpet of our room with sponges because two aunts from Mexico are coming over and stay in our apartment until Monday. I never thought the carpet was  that  dirty. Darn, my hands are aching and they burn a little bit now, not to mention they smell like bleach. >_  I'm so excited to see my aunts... One of them I haven't seen in about 4 years. Tomorrow I'm gonna go shopping with them, which is kind of weird because I rarely go outside, much less go shopping. Ew. XP I've been wasting the whole summer doing a whole lot of nothing. I haven't even bought the book I'm supposed to read for Pre-Ap English: When the Legends Die. Sally says that's it's a fuggin' boring book, and that it takes place like in 1940 or something like that. Dang it, why couldn't they have assigned us a good book like the one last summer? And Then There Were None was a kick arse book. The first chapter is confusing, but then it gets better. Like Sally said, the reason why many people dislike reading is because the teachers assign boring books.   But apart from cleaning my apartment, that's all I've done today. I never do anything and it's great. Haha, my life is just wake up, eat, computer, eat, computer, TV, games, computer and goes on. See a pattern here? My life's so interesting. I should write a book about it.   [sarcasm]Keep those forwards coming.[/sarcasm]     
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yesterday I watched the soccer match between Uruguay VS Argentina. Argentina sucks. They cheat just darn too much and they play so dirty. I mean, every time that Uruguay had the ball and they were going to score, some idiotic Argentina player would run up to him and push him real hard, which, of course, would cause the Uruguay player to lose the ball. Also, the Argentina guy would get a yellow card, but I thought he was supposed to get a red card and get kicked out. This happened a lot of times. Argentina also fakes most of the faults and pretend that an Uruguay player pushed/kicked them. Blasted morons. I was so mad! Then of course, they get a free-kick. Dang it. The bad thing is that Uruguay lost 4-2... they were playing good for just having 10 players on their team. I hope Argentina loses their first match on the second round and get their butts kicked by some kick arse team. I never liked the Argentina soccer team. They're just cheaters and (I'll never stop saying this) play dirty. Curse you!  Blog Spot rocks... I like it because it's more simple and clean. I loathe Xanga, it's too... "fancy." I think it's complicated, too. Plus, I like being the oddball. Almost all of my friends have Xangas, except me: I have Blog Spot. And 96% of my friends have AIM, too, but of course, I don't. I use the best IM there is up to today: MSN. I hate AIM and everything that has to do with gAyOL. It's so low-quality, and AIM is not even near MSN's quality. I mean, AIM's smilies suck, and that annoying sound that it makes when you receive/send a message can't get more annoying. I don't know why my friends use AIM or what they see in it. MSN is so far superior and better. All of the versions that AIM makes are the same, unlike MSN, because they keep adding some cool features to it, like on version 6.0 (I have 6.2 right now, and yes, there is a difference between 6.0, 6.1 and 6.2... go figure) you can add your own customized smilies. Plus, MSN's display pictures are bigger than crappy AIM Buddy Icons, and not to mention that you can change your background picture and background color in MSN. I could go on forever on why MSN is better than gAyOL, but I'll stop here. My goddess... MSN pwns.  There's another reason why I hate gAyOL and AIM, but you can see that by reading Kasuto's editorial about it by click  urlLink here . It explains everything there.  But enough negativity. I think I'm forgetting how to speak Spanish. It sucks. One day my brother and I had forgotten how to say "stage" in Spanish. It was the worst thing ever. Of course, I had to look it up in the dictionary that we have. I don't wanna forget my native language. I told my mom about this and she was so fuggin' upset. Then one day we went to this store and they had newspapers in Spanish. She made me read them out loud, 'cause she thought I had forgotten how to read it. I was nervous because I hadn't read in Spanish in a long time. I messed up two or three times, but I read pretty well. I wasn't even thinking of what I was reading, but I was worried that I'd mess up while reading. Weird. I think my mom is gonna buy me some Spanish books so I can start reading them and so that I don't forget how to speak it, read it, and write it. I hope I buy one soon. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I had lessons today. Bleh. Most of the time Ms. Bentel (aka Ms. Callaway) spent talking about the chances of me buying a new flute because... uh... I don't remember why. She was telling me all these reasons, but I wasn't really paying attention, just nodding and saying, "OK." Maybe we wouldn't have talked about all of this if she knew that there were some chances that I wouldn't be in band anymore. Holy crap, if I told her that, she'd probably give me some kind of lecture about not doing so or asking me why. Oh well, who cares. XP The day that I get out of band will be the best day ever. Maybe some Smirnoff to celebrate. ;P  I've been getting a lot of crappy fuggin' forwards lately. Oh my goddess... how much I loathe them! Stupid moronic and idiotic e-mails that just fill up my inbox with useless crap. I wonder if the people who send them really believe in those things, or if they just do it to annoy people. I mean, who's gonna believe that stupid forward can actually bring you good luck and/or it can make your crush fall crazily in love with you? That's just insane. I got a forward entitled, "I'm not superstitious, but w/e," and it said that Dr. Seuss's hat had visited you, make a wish, and, I quote, "Send this to 10 people within the hour you  read this. If you do, your wish will come true. If you don't it will become the opposite." Yeah right. Well, if you're not superstitious, then why the heck send this forward?! Wasting my precious time. ¬¬  They also give lame examples. I remember I got one that said that the chain letter had been going since the 1950s. Yeah right. The internet didn't even exist back then, so how the heck did they send those stupid forwards? I mean, did a geeky person sat down on a desk and wrote that mail a bunch of times to send it to people and annoy them to death? I wouldn't do that. Not to mention that they give the same examples  every fuggin' time!  To close this entry, I'll leave you with an idiotic example. Curse you all chain mailers! >_   "CASE 2:  Take Katie Robinson ...  She received this poem and being the believer that  she was, she sent it to a few of her friends but didn't have enough e-mail addresses to send out the full 10 that you must. Three days later, Katie went to a masquerade ball. Later that night when she left to get to her car to go home, she was killed on the spot by a hit-and-run drunk driver."  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        When I go to the ninth grade school I'll follow IFM's advice: don't suck. But if I happen to suck, I promise that I'll suck in a whole new and exciting way. -me   So today was the first day of my high school life. Uh, not so bad, I guess. I got there and I talked to Sasha. When school started I saw Veronica-san and I followed her to Portable 1, 'cause that's where I had to go for my homeroom and get all the crap that they were gonna give me. How utterly annoying. So I went there. I only had a notebook, one pencil, one eraser, and a permanent marker. People were carrying around backpacks and other crap, but whatever. They're not gonna give us the books today, f00s. ;P  The teacher gave me my schedule and I quickly looked at it. Since I'm stuck here in my house instead of being at the marching band stuff, I'll post my block schedule:  1)  Freshman I Band ; Mr. Brandon  (hehe, might change...) 2) World Geography ; Ms. Dias-Schindle 3) Bussiness Computer I ; Mr. Williams (no, some other Mr. Williams) 4) Pre-Ap English 1 ; Ms. Smith 5) [1st Semester] Health ; Mr. Moore, B 5) [2nd Semester] Speech ; Mr. Duncan 6) Bioligy 1 ; ? Bentley 7) Geometry Pre-AP ; ? Hanes (oh no...where's Ms. Fritz?! ;_;) 8) French 2 ; Mr. Adam  I have like 4 classes with Sally-san, two classes with Michelle-chan, about three classes with Yaqui-chan and only one class with Michael-kun. (all of them counting Band except Mikey). Wait...someone's missing... Gasp, yes, indeed, So-Young's missing... ;_;! This majorly sucks... Sigh.  After that we had an assembly at the A Gym. Y'know, this highschool might look big, but it actually isn't. I even think Reed's even bigger than this stupid NGS (Ninth Grade School, for those ignorant folks out there). Oh well, can't complain. While in the assembly, I saw Ms. Adams. Holy crap! Ms. Adams used to teach 8th grade Math back in Reed Middle School (best school ever!). I saw another RMS teacher but I don't know his name, so whatever.  After the assembly we went to first block. Band. I was hoping that today I'd get a reply from Mr. Williams, but I didn't. Fug...how am I supposed to live like this?! I feel that my life is so unorganized because I'm not sure if I'm in band or not. Tomorrow I'll talk to Mr. Brandon about my situation, but I'm gonna feel a little uncomfortable since I don't know him. Oh whatever, it's time to step up and stop being a stupid coward. I need to take care of my darn bussiness. I can't change my schedule until next week, but I already e-mailed Mr. Williams, so that's taken care of. I wonder if he even read the stupid thing. Pfft...  Today at 6.15 the band folks were gonna have a practice until 8.45 PM. Guessed it, I didn't go. I don't wanna go to any marching crap until I receive an answer from SOMEONE. I feel so desperate. I'm scared to go because I'll feel out of place...not knowing what to do and stuff. Plus, this will be my  fourth  marching practice I've missed. Am I even in band any more? I sure don't think so. It feels so wrong not to go to marching practices and yet still have band. Heh, I'm an idiot. =D *stands tall and proud*  World Geography is full of troublemakers and idiots. This is what I get for choosing it as an academic class. The good thing is that the teacher seems really nice, so that's ok I guess. There was this Mexican guy that just came to the U.S. and didn't know any English, so I offered to help him. It reminded me when I got to Duncanville...all lost and stuff. But he won't have to feel like that as long as I have him for that class, I assure.  Bussiness Computer I is gonna be the best class of A Day, me thinks. I have Sharde "Taylor," Michael-kun, Sally-san, Yaqui-chan and Michelle-chan. I also have them all for my lunch, which is B Lunch. w00t! I didn't bring anything to eat so I didn't eat anything. Oh well, wasn't that hungry.  The first day of Pre-Ap English and we already have a project due Friday. It's about our ten most important virtues in order and crap. Gah. It has to be in 3-D and it has to reflect our culture or something like that. Boo. I have Sally-chan and Jessica-san [M] in there, along with Krasynthia-san and Reyna-san, so w00t w00t. Tomorrow I'm gonna go to my next four blocks, so that's B Day. The good thing is that I don't have my two Pre-Ap classes in one whole Day. Talk about lucky. =o  Now, about my Random Quote of the Day... It's true! Here's what IFM said:   ...I mean, who the [fug] stands in the middle of a ramp and plays with their friends? Welcome to high school, you incompetant turd. Chicks play with their friends in the hall, not guys. Perhaps these wads had some sort of sexual identity crisis, because they looked like any other dweeby grade 9.    What's that you say, ye of little faith? "I was once a grade 9 too"? Sure, I was a grade 9 too. But there's a difference: I DON'T SUCK. These kids are begging to be beaten up, and I like to see it happen to them. I didn't get beaten up because I was too smart to get beaten up by some nigger, which is the only person who would want to beat me up.   So please, don't suck.  As I was reading my e-mail today, I had gotten one from So-Young. I sent her an e-mail telling her everything about what happened with band and stuff, and explaining some other things. I also told her that  we  would never forget about her.Like I promised,  I'll never lose contact with her.  No matter if she's on the other side of the world, I don't care. I found out that Yaqui-chan and Michelle-chan haven't even bothered to at least e-mail her or tell her, "Hi." What the fudge? Weren't we all just so fuggin' sad that So-Young was gonna leave and crap? Well, I'm sure as heck still depressed that she isn't with us, so I don't know about these other losers. Here's a part of her e-mail:    nobody writes me from duncanville except of course you  and thank you very much...  This just...made me so sad... What's up with you losers that dare to call yourself "friends"?!? I don't  care  what's going on with you and your life, at  least  try to write to her! Just say hi and that's it. I bet she'd be so happy to hear from any of her D'ville friends. *coughyaquicoughmichellecoughimdyinghelp* Oh my goddess... I know what it feels like to not get mail from your friends, and it sucks, trust me. Crap, I'm so upset. I'm gonna talk to Yaqui-chan and Michelle-chan and ask them what the fug is going on with them. Weren't they almost crying because So-Young was moving? Fuggin' hypocrites.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hard to know, even though Ruto is an ugly naked fish, she has attitude, she knows what she wants and goes for it, also is kind of hilarious how she demands being carried around. -Goddess Din   Last night was  awesome . I haven't had this much fun in years. My brother and I got there at around 3.20 PM or so, and the gates weren't open yet. My dad gave us 20 dollars each, but that wasn't enough to buy something decent. So anyway, at around 3.30 the gates opened, and once we were inside I quickly bought a water of bottle for $4.25. Expensive, yes? I wanted to buy a shirt of Interpol or something, but they were like $30 dollars each, so whatever. I borrowed some money from my brother and we bought the shirt...so kick arse! I love it. The shirt is simple. It's black, has the words "Interpol" written on it in dark gray letters and...that's it. I love it. =P  At 4.20, the gates to the main stage opened. The first group was gonna play at 5 PM, but I didn't know them so who cares. We got to sit in the lawn, but that's alright since you could move freely from the main stage to the back stage. There were a lot of people walking back and forth, and while the first group got ready, we just kept looking at people and how weird they were dressing. We saw two grandmas, and I'm guessing that they just came to see The Cure since they're an 80s group. But anyways, there were a lot of goths, bangers and punks. Some creepy, some weird, and some spiffy. I think I can safely say that I was the only 14-year-old-girl that was at that concert.  The first group was crap. It was just a bunch of loud guitars, loud singers, and more loud guitars. The good thing was that they were only gonna play for 30 minutes. At 5.30 my brother and I went to the backstage to see the second group performing. This one was better, though the singer was acting kind of gay. XD  6 o clock and we had to go back to the main stage to see the next group. I didn't know them either, so blah. Interpol was gonna perform from 7.30 - 8.10, which is not enough for an awesome band like them. Then at 9 PM The Cure was gonna play, and it would last until 11 PM. Once the third group finished, we headed back to the backstage to see the next band. It was kind of weird because the singer looked like Ms. Callaway. XD Hehe. Their group was ok, but we once again went back to the main stage before the first song of this group was over.  After this, Interpol would play. I was so excited! My brother and I were just having a good time, laughing and making jokes. At 7.30, Interpol came up and the crowd cheered loudly. The first song they played was Obstacle 1, and I could hear that all the folks were singing along. They played all of the songs that I wanted to hear, except The New. But it still rocked! When they played Say Hello to the Angels, I wanted to faint. It was so awesome! I was in heaven. I  finally  got to hear one of my favorite bands live. Sooooo happy! Kick me! x_x  Their last song was PDA. Aw...so sad. They made a stop at the middle of the song, and I thought it was the end of it, but then they made a comeback and the crowd just became more loud. Time quickly passed by when Interpol was singing. They played like...three or four songs of their new album (which comes out on September 28), and they were great. So, the songs that I knew of that they played were: Obstacle 1, Stela was a diver, Say Hello to the Angels, PDA, NYC, and there was one more but I can't remember. x_x Whoa, if I got this excited for hearing one of my favorite bands, imagine how crazy I'd get if I'd hear The Cranberries: the best band out there! *faints*  There was gonna be another "great" band playing at the backstage, but my brother and I didn't bother to go there because there was "traffic." So we sat there for 50 minutes, and at 9.10 the lights went out. The people stood up and The Cure started to play.  The Cure was kick arse, but Interpol was even better. They played the Love Song, The End of the World, and some other songs that I don't know the name of but that I knew of. It was fun, and at 10.30 PM we had to get out because my dad was gonna come pick us up. As we were going outside, these girls were giving out some posters, stickers, and pins. One of the pins were of Interpol, so I of course grabbed some. At 11.30 we got home, and I was sooo tired. I tried to stay up late but I couldn't. Pfft, sucks.   Interpol and The Cure pwn.   But apart from that, school tomorrow. Gasp, so fast? I can't believe it. It doesn't feel like school starts tomorrow. I sent an e-mail to Mr. Williams about band and stuff on Friday, but I haven't gotten a reply. Gah, I hope I do so soon. >_ 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Dumb Mike. He lets out a fly and three more fly in. -Mike   Holy crap! This Saturday is going to be a-w-e-s-o-m-e! My brother bought these tickets to go see two of my favorite bands: The Cure and Interpol. *faints* These other bands are coming, but I don't know who they are so who cares. I hope my dad gives us money to at least buy a shirt or something. A shirt of Interpol...holy sw33ts! So the concert starts at 3 PM and it ends at 11 PM... 8 hours of concert-time! =D w00t!  In other news, Setzer has  once again  attacked ZP. You can go here:  urlLink http://zeldapower.com/forums/index.php?s=2ac658725d7ff47aa20744ab1f67ad84&amp;showtopic=9450  to look at the shocking details. What an idiot. I just hope Setzer gets deleted once and for all from ZP. He just keeps ruining it and making it seem like a bad message board. Ack! And so because of him, Rosie and Zix have left. Curse you, Setzer! Well, Zix has not exactly left, but he's not a mod any more and he seemed annoyed by getting modded and demodded over and over again. That's the ZP life for ya. *Ice beams Setzer* Die, garden tool.  Hm nothing much to write today. Probably later on I'll e-mail Mr. W and Ms. Callaway about the crap that's been going on.  _ _;;  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You laugh at me for being different. I laugh at all of you for being the same. -Unknown   Longest entry ever today, so read at your own risk.  So last night I had another dream about band. It was close to the one I had the other night. I had once again returned to marching band. We were in Hardin's Gymnasium, and it was weird because somehow we  all  fit in there. Nice. I was in the woodwind section, and once again I sucked at marching. I was so freakin' lost and didn't know where to march or what to do. It was weird, because somehow I  knew  I had missed three days of practice, and that's freaky because on the other dream I knew that I had missed  two  days of practice. Ugh, so weird. But like last time, someone came to pick me up right in the middle of practice: my brother. He just said we had to leave so we did. _ _;; I kept wondering and saying to myself, "Ugh, just what the heck does this mean?!" Who knew the answer would come to me today at 7 PM?  I was gonna go with Regi-chan and Gaby-chan to watch the band practice, but Gaby couldn't come for some reason which I did not understand. So at 6 PM I went to the Panther stadium to watch my friends march. I was kind of scared because I was afraid that Mr. Williams would talk to me and ask me why I had quit. I was also scared that they would convince my back into the band...but the unexpected happened.  About 20 minutes of my arrival, Mr. Williams came up and talked to me. He told me all this sort of stuff... I'm gonna try and remember what he told me. Erm...well he said that he was surprised when he had heard that I had quit. He told me that I was "band material," and that he didn't want me to miss out on such a great marching band program. Mr. W also said that I was one of the few freshmen (supposedly?) that had gotten a spot on the show. I. Had. Gotten. A. Spot. dany the dot...a spot?! *shock shock* I didn't want to say anything.  So we talked some more about the chances of me going back to band. "I mean, just think about it. If you ever change your mind, then just send me an e-mail. I'm always available. I'm hoping to get a response from you by the end of this week...hopefully." As if I hadn't given enough thought to this situation! I became unsure... again . Why?! I had made my choice, my strong and definate choice... And now Mr. Williams was about to change it?! I love my life.  Indecisive...again. Why...why...why... I didn't know what to think. When Mr. Williams was talking to me, I started to actually like band again. No biggie, it's just Mr. Williams, right?  Wrong.  A few minutes later, Ms. Fedynich comes up, "Hey, what's up with you, girl? Why?" And I told her that I just didn't like band any more. Oh I was so fuggin' nervous! I didn't know what to say... Ms. Fedynich told me almost the same things as Mr. W had told me: that she was surprised when she heard that I had quit and that I couldn't miss out on the show blah blah blah... Why...me...? ;_; I don't know what to think or what to do any more... I just...wish I could be dead right now.  So I started to think about what they had told me... I was still 85% sure that I was staying out of band. They were destroying my decision bits by bits...one by one...director by director... I feel so trapped. I just wish I could talk to someone about how I really feel, but I just can't find the words to express myself. I think my head's about to explode...  When I had arrived, I was sitting down in the Visitors side. When the band took a break, I went to the Home side. I was just sitting there...watching the people march...on all the stuff I had missed. Did I really want to go back? Why wasn't I just sure of myself? What the heck is fuggin' wrong with me?! Lovely. So I just sat there...thinking...watching...not wanting to think or watch. Thank goddess, because not long after that, Regi-chan came. w00tness! Maybe she'll make all of these thoughts to go away and cheer me up...hopefully.  Wrong again.  Once she gets there, I see Ms. Shultz coming towards me. I thought she was going to talk to Regina or something, but heck was I wrong. She said, "Daniela, come here. I need to talk to you for a minute." Crap.  "Uh...do I need to come down there?" "Yeah, just meet me by the stairs and we'll take a walk." Crap again.  --Summary of the conversation--  "*surprised voice* So what's up with you, girl? Why did you quit?"   "Uh...well it's just that I don't know... I didn't like to march any more..."   "Well, you do know that you had a spot in the show, right? You looked so good out there, and that's why the band directors chose you."   "Um well I didn't know that...they just told me that today. Eh, well I mean I  do  like playing the flute, and I like concert bands, but it's just that I  don't  like marching bands."   "Ok lemme tell you something... Summer camp... erm, sucks. I mean, no one likes to stand in the sun getting all sweaty and stuff. But the good thing is that you've already gone through that. Today's the last day of marching camp, and for the rest of the year you're not gonna practice marching for this long..."   "...*nods*"   "I mean, I was so shocked when I found out you quit. Mr. [insert dark dude's name here] came up to me and said, 'Uh well some flute girl just quit.' I was surprised and asked him, 'Well, who was it?' And he said, 'I don't know. Some short girl.' 'Well, you've gotta be more specific than that.' And I started naming all these flute players, but he didn't tell me who. Then I found out that it was you and I'm like, 'Oh no, not her. It can't be her.'"   "Heh, yeah. Mr. Williams and Ms. Fedynich have said the same thing and--"   "Oh so we've all had a grab of you, huh? See, we've talked to you because you're one of the good players out there and we value you. You're a good marcher, so don't quit just because you don't like to march. If you like to play the flute, then stay, and trust me, after today, it will get a lot easier."   "Ok, so let's say that I decide to come back. How will I be able to catch up on all the stuff that the woodwinds have done?"   "Oh I'm sure you'll be able to catch up. All the woodwinds are doing is just 16 steps back, forward, back, forward etc."   "Erm, well I'll talk to my parents about this tonight for sure... I'll e-mail one of the band directors on my final choice..."   "That's great. I mean, I'm still trying to find a replacement for you. Crazy, huh? If you had your flute with you right now, I'd put you right back in. Just think about it, ok? We don't wanna lose a great player like you."  That isn't great. That just means more unsure and more worried.  What to think...what to do...what to think...what to do?!?! I was getting so desperate because I, for a second, had no control over my life whatsoever. Three band directors had talked to me, and all of them were shocked that I had quit. You just have no idea how awesome it felt to have  three , not one, band directors tell you to come back to the band. It felt so beautiful... Now I had only one thing to do: to let them down and go my own way, or go back to my "roots" and make them...happy, I guess.  I didn't want to think of this. Enough worries for just thirty minutes, ok? Regi and I had an  awesome  time. I just couldn't stop laughing...that girl is just hilarious! I had missed her, actually, and I was happy to see her once again. She just kept saying the most stupid, yet funny, stuff I've ever heard. Oh man, it would have been a whole different day if she hadn't been there. It sucked that Gaby-chan couldn't come... ;_;  Regi-chan gave me a note and a bracelet...a fuggin' spiffy bracelet. I'm wearing it right now, actually. ;D So thanx again for the bracelet, Regi! =D *hugs granny* Talking to her made me forget about what Mr. W, Ms. S and Ms. F had said. And I'm glad, too. I didn't want to think about it this moment. Though, as we were talking, Ms. Shults told me to go and move closer to where I could see the woodwinds. I guess she does want me back...doesn't she?  So Regi and I kept talking...and laughing...and, of course, having a good time. I'm telling you, this girl is t3h r0x0rs. At 8.30 I called my mom to come pick me up. As Regi-chan and I were heading towards the front of the high school, we find Ms. Fedynich. Regi was trying to hide from her, but failed miserably.  Me: Hi, Ms. Fedynich! Ms. F: Hey, guys... Regi: *mumbles something* Ms. F: Why are you trying to hide for me? Regi: *mumbles* No I wasn't... Me: *laughs* She's just afraid that you're gonna ask her if she practiced over the summer or not. Ms. F: Oh well you don't have to hide from me. I already talked to your teacher and he said-- Me: *leaves because her ride is here*  When I got home, I talked to my parents. Just when I thought I could  finally  practice the guitar and get my lessons, everything falls over. Why?! Can someone explain to me why?!?!?!  I hate my life.  I don't want other people to control it, I want to make my  own  deicisions. I'm almost never insecure of myself, but now this... Why the he**?!?!  My mom gave me an advice again. If only anyone could know my true feelings right now... _ _;; Ugh, I just wanted to have my guitar lessons! But now that this has come up, I can't. All of my plans ruined. I'm 85% sure that I want to go back to band... Ms. Shultz just made me look at it in a whole different way. Three band directors asked me to come back... Was I gonna...?  Once I had talked to my mom, I was now 93.7% (gotta get the Math going ;D) sure that I wanted to come back. Some things had me worried:  1) How will I be able to catch up on all the marching stuff I have missed? 2) Will Ms. Callaway have a spot for me open for lessons? 3) Will Mr. Shine and/or Mr. Marrel accept me back? 4) Will I have to pass off all the stuff I had done again to get my uniform? 5) Why am I so fuggin' worried and asking so many freakin' questions?  Wouldn't you just  love  to be in my shoes right now?  I decided I was going to e-mail Mr. Williams and tell him I wanted to come back, and ask Ms. Callaway if she could squeeze me in her lessons schedule...tomorrow. But suddenly, I get this e-mail:  From: Michael T To: dany the dot   DANIELA!!! I QUIT BAND!!! YAY!!! I'M FREE!!! WHOO-HOO!!! ::dances around like an idiot:: YAY!!!! ahhh, now...freedom...i am reborn again! from the ashes...of the Duncanville Band Program arise the newly ascended Michael [insert last name here]...future star game programmer!!!! YAY!!!!! I walk along this new path of life as i am led away from the old path...i now start a new life.. YES!!!! I AM FREE...wait.. WE ARE FREEE I LOVE YOU DANY!!! YAYAAYAYAYAYAY! ::hugs and kisses:: bai bai   Someone make my life easier and just shoot me, please?  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         My order for today is: Hunt down and kill Kero!! I have reasons. XP -Goddess Din    Whoa, all this marching stuff is going to my head. I hope it all stops soon. Well, last night I had a dream about band. Great.   I continued marching, and continued to suck. Out of nowhere, my dad appeared and told me we had to leave. I was worried, and I asked him, "Uh...b-but did y-you even ask Mr. Williams that I have to g-go?" Ugh, who cares what Mr. Williams thinks? It's Mr. Shine that gets the final word. But anyways, as we were walking out of the...stadium-kind-of-thing, I saw Mr. Williams. He didn't seem too happy that I was leaving, and then I suddenly found out that he was following me around. He stopped us and asked my dad if he had approved about me quitting band. What the fug? XD And that's where my dream ended. Huzzah! My mom says I look more happy and carefree. And I can't say that isn't true. Band is so stressful, and now that I'm not in it anymore, I can't be any more hyper.  But the good news is that my brother installed Adobe Photoshop 7. At last! My dream has come true! ;_; I really don't know how to use it, and it's really complicated, but hopefully I'll get the hang of it...soon. Maybe I'll read some tutorials and stuff.  The ZP members asked me if I could draw the Mod Squad. I'm currently working on that, but when you don't have a good pencil and a good eraser, it's quite tough. =_=  Still no Twelve Girls Band CD. ;_;  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Wow, a stupid person isn´t stupid enough to know if a stupid person is stupid....probably because they're too stupid. -Regi       When you think you are right and ten other people are telling you that you're wrong, doubt rises. But I gotta stay strong to my decision. Since I didn't show up to the practice yesterday, Sally-chan told me that Mr. Williams was disappointed in me. This is what she said:   Mr. Williams was mad that you quit. He asked me why you quit and I said "I dunno" (I didn't wanna say you hated it!) and he was like WHAT!? SHE CAN'T QUIT! OH MY GOD! so that shows ya Mr. W loves ya! Oh and today was really fun, I wish you would have been there :( Mr. W also said that he's disappointed in you. He asked me where you were, and so did Ms. Shultz, but she didn't say anything except, "She QUIT?!"     I just knew Mr. Williams would be disappointed in me. I remember that when I was passing off my All-Region stuff in eighth grade, he asked me if I was gonna be in marching band next year. I told him, "Yeah..." and he said, "Of course, you must be," and started laughing. Hehe, now look at me. XD   But that didn't really matter...until I read my e-mail this morning. It was from Michael-kun. This is what it said:   hey daniela! everyone was asking me why did you quit, mr williams says hes disappointed and michelle, yaqui and sally told me to talk to you about it...I think I influenced you to quit...I was going to quit today but nobody wanted me to leave, so i talked to Dr. Shine about moving to concert band...he told me that he usually doesnt make those kinds of exceptions, but if I am still very tired...he'll look into it....maybe you can do the same thing...i know that its your decscion to make...but i promised michelle i would talk to you, it doesnt matter to me if you want to come back, ill just tell them I didn't get a hold of you=^^= anyway, come back if you want, stay home if you don't...doesn't matter to me, cause... i'll still love you=^^= ::hugs and kisses:: bai bai     That made so fuggin' upset. I'm tired of all these people who don't respect my freakin' choice. Where's the support? Wait, there isn't any? My friends are just being fuggin' selfish, I thought. They're just thinking of themselves, not me. So I wrote an e-mail to them: Michael-kun, Yaqui-can, Michelle-chan and Sally-chan. This is what I wrote:    Hey, guys...    I just wanna say that Michael-kun  did not  influence me into quitting band. I was already thinking of doing that long before marching camp started. I was planning on  not  quitting band because of my friends, but I decided that I would not let you guys make me do something I  don't  want to do. If you read this, then it'll let you know how I really feel about this situation.  It was not an easy decision to make.  I gave this a lot of thought, so don't you even  dare  telling me that I didn't think of this.    I really don't care who is disappointed in me or who isn't. A lot of people will be disappointed in me throughout my life, and Mr. Williams will not be the first person. I quit band because of my own will, not because of Michael. I don't wanna stay in band just because you guys are in it. If I do that, I won't be enjoying it.  I don't care about the field trips, I don't care about skipping classes because of contests, I don't care about band!  You guys just have no idea  how hard  this decision was to make, and no matter what comes out of it, good or bad,  I'll know I made the right choice . Why? Because I didn't let any of you guys make it for me.     I just wish some of you would respect my choice.  I quit band because I don't like it anymore. Not everything is going to come out the way  you  want it, and this is one of the things. Believe me, this breaks my heart because I won't be in band with you guys any more, but I can't stay in it just because of that. I just wish I could get some support, not only from my parents and Michael, but from my friends. I feel so freakin' lonely once I made this decision. What's this? My friends are upset at me because I quit band?  What kind of friends are you , trying to make me do something I don't wanna do?  So don't try to talk me out of it.  Nothing that you or any band director tells me is gonna change my decision. Just respect it, and leave it. Stop teasing me about it, because this is  not  fun. You guys have no idea how much I'm upset because of this.    I wrote this little...whatever you wanna call it when I was feeling trapped and not knowing what to do: whether quitting band or not. If you wanna read this, then go ahead.  It's my life, not yours.      Support: that's all I'm asking.      Then I wrote the blog entry I had written yesterday. I was so upset at my friends. I was the one disappointed in them: because they wouldn't respect my decision, much less support me. Wait a minute...did I even have friends at that time? Where are your friends when you need them? Where's the  encouragement  when you need it?   Pissed off: that was me at that moment. What were my friends thinking?! The only people supporting me now were my parents, Michael-kun, and Mike. Ah, yes, Mike: the person who always makes me laugh no matter what. I'm starting to think that he's the only one that can really understand me. And heck, that's crazy because I don't know him in real life.  What did my friends want? To stay in band just to make them happy, but then I'd be the one being miserable. They'd be pleased, but I'd be depressed. Was that what they wanted?! For me to be sad and uncomfortable just to make them freakin' happy?  A while later I got a reply from Sally-chan. This is what she said:   De: Sally Enviado el: Martes, 10 de Agosto de 2004 05:32:57 p.m. Para: sikaru64@hotmail.com Asunto: RE: Living with it I read the whole thing, and I am feeling stupid as ever right now. Sure I wanted you to stay in band, but I shouldn't have given you so much grief over it. I didn't know that you were feeling all those things. I can now see that band is just not right for you anymore. You have a lot of courage to quit. When I was saying I wouldn't talk you you anymore, I was kidding. You are awesome, how could we lose our friendship over BAND!? I want to thank you so much for sending me your thoughts, because now I can fully understand why you don't want to stay in marching band, and best of all I  can  support you. So, please forgive me for acting so foolishly!! Let me close by saying you are a great writer! Talk to ya soon, -Sally      I didn't reply to that, but I felt a little more happy now that I had gotten at least one person to support me...to understand me. Not even ten minutes passed and I received a reply from Michael-kun:    De: M.T. Tenchicat Enviado el: Martes, 10 de Agosto de 2004 05:41:20 p.m. Para: Sikaru Urashima   Asunto: support DANY!!! That was very good, i should be following your example. I understand how you feel, I will proabably quit as well, but i'm going to ride the week out. If i don't like it, i'll quit, if something changes...i dont know...but if you need anything at all, I WILL be there for you! Even if you were jumping out of a burning building, I'll be there to catch you. I wish some other people could be more supportive of your choice...my dad even thought you did the right thing=^^= but if it takes me to quit in order for the others to realize why you made your decision, I'll do it...no questions asked...if the rest have a problem with it, fine...its THEIR problem...not yours, not mine, but THEIRs! You do what you have to do...and I'll be right by your side...i dont care if we are the only ones making the same decision, and everybody else is still following everybody else, ill support you and try and help you with your needs as best as I physically, mentally, and emotionally can. =^^= I wish i had a big enough vocabulary to express my feelings toward you, but the words don't come to my head=^^= alright...bai bai luv ya lotzas!     I won't ever let anyone decide for me. This is my life, dang it. Doubt erases, support rises. That's what friends are for, huh?   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Everyone is dropping out like fat kids playing dodgeball! Pretty soon it will just be me and all these super good nerdy people so I will get last chair every time and won't have any friends! -Sally   I wish I could write everything that's going around in my head, but I just can't... I'll try to write everything as much as possible. I think my head's just gonna explode if I don't write this down.  I told myself that I wouldn't quit band until ninth grade is over, but this is just a freakin' hard promise to keep. After being in marching camp for five days, I have decided to throw in the towel. I just don't like band any more. Band used to be fun back in 6th, 7th and 8th grade, but once you start 9th grade, the world of band just becomes so different. It's a lot of hard work, and I'm just not having fun as much as I used to have. I mean, I don't like marching bands, but I enjoy concert bands. If you had a choice between marching band and concert band, then I'd sure as heck choose concert. I just loathe marching, and I'm not good at it. I lose my balance, and I can't play and march at the same time. I also have trouble keeping up with the tempo.  I just want to move on. I've already had the band experience for three long years. It was a very fuggin' nice and awesome experience, but it's time to see new things. I'll make my own decisions, and I won't let my friends influence me into staying in band. Sure, marching band looks like a lot of fun, but not everything is as it seems. In order to have fun in this marching crap, you have to work really, really hard, and when you work that hard, the fun is gone. I sure as heck had a lot of fun in eighth grade, and I enjoyed band back then. I thought marching band was gonna be fun, but then I found out it isn't.  If I let my friends make the choices for me and make me stay in band, I won't enjoy it. I mean, band just doesn't mean anything for me anymore. I hate having to practice the flute, and I can barely play the music these folks have given me. I could surely stay in marching band all the way through senior year, I sure as heck could. But the problem would be that I wouldn't be enjoying it, and I would not practice and hate every moment of it. So that's why I'm not staying in band any more. I'm so fuggin' happy right now.  So I talked to my parents. My mom told me it was the right thing to do, and that she wasn't very happy that I had chosen marching band in the first place. Why? Because of all the pressure and stuff. See, band gives you your P.E. and Fine Arts credits. So to cover for the Fine Arts credits, I'll take Art. P.E. will be a problem. I don't wanna have to take P.E., but if I have to, I will. Another way is that I can choose golf, one of my favorite sports. Though, I don't know what I have to do in order to be able to get in... I really hope I can get inside some golf club or something... I don't wanna have to take P.E. =X  Don't you dare to think that I didn't give any fuggin' thought to this decision. It was really hard to make...honest. I don't wanna quit, but the other part of me tells me I have to. Right now I have people telling me to not quit...saying that I'm a wimp, a loser and stuff like that. They just have no fuggin' clue how scared I am. They're not gonna change my choice. It's about me, not them. I could really care less on whether they want me to quit or not.  As I was talking to Keely-san and Sally-chan (they were the ones telling me not to quit), I became unsure of myself. Did I really want to quit? Was I making the right decision? Are they right and I'm wrong? All those questions started to pop up in my head. Sally-chan showed me pictures of what I was going to miss out...all those band trips, skipping class for going to contests and other endless stuff. They were trying to convince me on staying...and I was sure as heck falling for that.  So I was undecided. That almost never happens to me. Once I make a decision, I know I'm making the right one no matter what. At that moment, no one was supporting me...except Michael-kun. Yes, folks, he's quitting too for the same reason as I am: too much preassure. He, as of then, was the only one that was thinking like me...and of course my parents gave me support. But Keely-san and Sally-chan weren't helping at all... They even said they wouldn't talk to me any longer. That made me feel all alone and without any friends.  Since I was getting kind of upset with those two, I left the conversation. I talked with my mom, feeling so weak because of what Keely and Sally had said. My mom talked to me again, telling me to follow what my mind was saying, not what my friends want me to do. She told me that if I didn't quit now, I'd be dreading band for the rest of the year, and I sure as heck don't want that. My dad also talked to me over the phone, encouraging me to quit if I really wanted to. Once again, I felt better. I was now sure that I was going to quit band once and for all. Not friggin' friend was going to make me unsure again.  I got dressed and wore my musical shirt...just for irony. Since we didn't have morning or afternoon rehearsal, we were gonna have one at 6 PM. My mom was gonna take me there so I could tell Mr. Shine that I wasn't gonna be in band any more. Before I left, though, Ms. Callaway called me about the flute lessons. She asked me if I wanted to have them tomorrow or wait until school starts. I told her neither, because I was gonna quit band and I had already talked to my parents. She just said, "Noooooo, why?!" I told her I didn't like it any more, then she asked me if it was ok to give my spot to another student. I said it was alright. Last, Ms. Callaway told me that if I changed my mind, that I could call her so she could fit me in schedule. Pfft, like that's ever gonna happen.  When I got to the Panther Stadium, Jessica-san [W] came up to me and told me that she didn't want to be here. I said, "Well, I'm just gonna tell a band director that I'm gonna quit band and I'm leaving."  "Oh my gosh, you are soooo lucky! You get to have your life back!" That's right, folks, Jessica-san doesn't like band either. She wants to quit, but her parents don't let her. They tell her that she's going to regret it, and that she'll be mad at herself for having quit band.  "Well, if I regret it then it'll be my fault and I'll blame myself for this... It's my life, not theirs!" Sucks... I wish she could quit. It must blow to be in band when you don't like it. I felt lucky right then.  So I looked around for a band director, and Jessica-san went with me. Soon I saw Mr. Shine walking, and so I told him that I was gonna quit band. He seemed ok with it, and didn't ask me many questions, except my name and what instrument I played. He also said that right now was a good time to quit: right before school started. Once Mr. Shine told me it was alright, I ran to look for Jessica-san, 'cause she had gone to the restroom. When she came out, I told her the good news, and once again reminded me how lucky I was. I was so fuggin' happy that I was jumping around like an idiot.  When Jessica-san and I went back to the stadium, I saw Sally-chan. I exclaimed, "Sally, I told him! I got out of band!" and gave her a two thumbs-up. She just said, "BOOOO!!!" I really don't know how this is gonna affect my friendship with all my band friends... I really hope it doesn't change... I don't want for it to change.  "C'mon, Sally! Give me a hug!" She didn't say anything. I could just see that she was fuggin' upset. The good thing was that Yaqui-chan wasn't there...or Michelle-chan. I wonder how they'll react? They'll probably be mad at me, too, but hopefully this madness will stop soon.  "Ok, Sally! Say good-bye to Daniela!" said Jessica-san. This is the best day of my life. I'm free. I feel careless and so hyper. I said my good-bye's to Jessica-san and Sally-chan, then left the stadium. My life had just started.  I will never regret this choice. My friends can show-off and complain to me about band, but I won't care. Being in band was a great, awesome, and incredible experience. I met a lot of friends because of band, and I owe it one. But it's time to move on and see other things. Band is not life, and life is not band. There's no turning back now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        No beba el agua! -Sally  Since today my brother turns 16...   HAPPY BIRTHDAY, JAVI! =D   Yep, got that right folks. I was gonna give him five dollars, but I found out he "stole" them from me as a joke, so I didn't give them to him. That's what he gets. =P  So today I went to buy some socks, a musical shirt, and some new shoes. It's about time! I really like the musical shirt. It has all these black and white squares that have an eighth note in it, and it's the same on the front and back. It's so spiffy. The shoes that I bought are DC, and they're 7 1/2. Since they don't fit me well and they didn't have size 8, this guy ordered them, so the new shoes should be arriving next week or so. Nice.  My dad says that hopefully I'll get to order the Twelve Girls Band CD. Holy crap, that's just awesome! *-* I can't wait to order it! And best of all, it comes with a DVD! Can my dad get any better?! =P  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I forget what I was gonna say, but who cares, I have a cookie. -Mike   I was supposedly going to pass off the Box Drill today and October, but I couldn't because my flute was broken. The F key wouldn't work. Plus, I figured I wasn't completely ready for the Box Drill. Sigh, I really wanna pass it off, but I think we can't pass off anything on Monday. None of my friends passed the Box Drill, except Sarah-san, and she already has her uniform. Michelle-chan tried doing the Box Drill but she failed it. Hehe, loser. XD All of us were too much of cowards to even try passing it off. Keely-san tried, too, but she failed. Eh?! And she's really good at marching! If she didn't pass it, then I can't pass it. Crap, I seriously need to practice. o_o;;  Marching is becoming more difficult as time passes by. We're starting to march faster and stuff, and well, I lose control and balance. I also think I'm bouncing up and down, and I think I'm marching crooked or something. Ugh, there's no way I'm staying in marching band after ninth grade. I'll just get my P.E. and Fine Arts credits and I'm a goner! Oh I can't wait for that day... I'll finally be able to concentrate on playing the guitar, and that's gonna be so spiffy. I think I'll give my flute to Regi-chan if she still wants it, or maybe I'll just keep it as a memory, but heck I don't wanna remember any of that crap. =P  They let us out a little bit early today. At 3.30 PM I called my mom like 5 times and she wouldn't answer. Two of those times the line was busy, but I kept dialing. I figured it wasn't gonna be a problem if my mom couldn't pick me up, 'cause I could just walk since I have a key to the house. Oh, but wait... I had left the key because I thought my mom was gonna pick me up! Smart move! Since Sally-chan and Mallory-san, (Sally's sister) are so freakin' nice, they gave me a ride home. Mallory-san is the one that gives me rides whenever lunch break is over, which is really nice of her. As soon as she dropped me off near my apartments, my mom arrives. Hehe. =S I won't explain why she didn't answer the phone, 'cause I don't feel like explaining stuff right now. Heck, it's FRIDAY! That means no marching practice for two days, so I'm off to be lazy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Lame advice doesn't necesarilly mean that I'm out of ideas. -Goddess Din   Didn't feel like writing about marching camp before. But anyways, every time my lunch break's over I have to walk to the high school...which is ok, but it's so fuggin' hot outside. For the past three days, every time people see me walking carrying a big thermos of water, looking down at the ground and walking in the sun, they ask me if I need a ride. The first day, which was the second day of marching band camp, two squadleaders stopped and asked me if I need a ride to the highschool. Without even thinking, I said, "Um, nah I'd rather walk... Thanx anyway." They asked me if I was sure, and I told them that I was. So I kept walking. The second day this lady was taking her daughter to the high school, and she asked me if I needed a ride. Of course, I told her that I'd walk, but thanked her anyway. This day a kind old man offered a ride, but yet again I said, "No, thanx." It's not that I'm scared that they're gonna rob me and do something to me or whatever, it's just that I really wanna walk. That might sound crazy but who cares. =P  I'm a bit late, but I forgot to mention this on the first day of marching band... My brother's girlfriend, Vanessa-san, is going to be marching with us because she's a "high-hat" (sp?!). Y'know, it's kinda spiffy... It feels weird, though. XD She's a sophmore, so...yeah. Stephanie-san, Nessa's friend, is also there. I hope I can march with them some time. =P But anyways, I'll start off my crappy day...  Today we learned the X Drill... It's harder than the Box Drill, but hopefully I'll get the hang of it. I kept messing up during the X Drill (but I wasn't the only one...most freshmen had trouble with that) and maybe it's just me but a squadleader laughed at me. I don't know if she was laughing at something else, but when Mr. Williams came up to help me she just started to laugh...not loud, though. Blah, who cares?! I bet they had trouble with this too when they were just starting to march. =P I'm also having trouble marching backwards... I always seem to be a little off from the yard line, and sometimes I think I'm bouncing up and down. Maybe I should try harder.  One hour before we were able to go inside, the band directors held their "annual freshmen marching competition." It was in no form or way a competition: it was a popularity contest. Ok, y'see, all the freshmen were supposed to march and do whatever their band directors told them to, and the squadleaders are supposed to vote for the best marcher. Of course, this was not true at all. First the girls had to march, then the boys. I thought I marched pretty good, and when the squadleaders had to vote, I had no one behind me. All of my g33ky and not-so-popular-friends didn't even make it to the second phase. Vanessa-san got like two votes or something, but anything counts. I didn't care who won, because it wasn't about how good you march, but just how popular you are.  I need to pass off two things before I can get my uniform. I need to play October (the song, not the month) and do the Box Drill while playing the Bb Scale... I figured it can't be so hard, but we'll see. Hopefully I'll pass it off tomorrow, because the uperclassmen are gonna come tomorrow and they're gonna take all the good uniforms. And while we're waiting in line, they have the right to skip freshmen, sophmores and juniors...and some seniors, too. So, yeah...I think all of my friends are gonna get the "bad" uniforms, including me. Pfft, oh well.   Also, since today was squadleader appreciation day, I gave Jennifer-san, a flute squadleader, a dollar. I know it's not much, but anything counts, right? I gave it to her because she "helped" (only Sally-chan and I know what we mean by that ;P) Sally-chan and me pass the 16-marching-forward-steps-with-your-eyes-closed-thingy. She made it soooo easy for us! XD I still don't like this marching band stuff. Bleeeeeeh.  Y'know, it's ironic how I said that I didn't like Sarah-san [B]. Maybe I didn't like her because of how she acted the few times that I'd talk to her...but now that I see her and talk to her a little bit more, I guess she's ok. I mean, after all, I have to pass off stuff with her and all... I should give people some chances. XD Hehe, it was funny because as we were walking, Sarah-san was singing a part of the Freshmore song, which was this, "Help me, I'm weak and lazy. Give me a break before I go crazy." And after she said that, she started doing a weird dance and said, "Well, too late for me, I'm already crazy!" Ha-ha! XD It was hilarious! I couldn't stop laughing...oh boy, retardness.  As we were going outside the band hall to go to our sweet homes, I started a stupid inside-joke...probably the most retarded one. See, Sarah-san was talking in her cellphone, and we were just talking and talking. So, she said, "Hey, you guys! I need to hear what my mom's saying." So.... I started to growl. It was so stupid! Then everyone started growling for no reason, and we continued doing so and so until we got in front of the stadium. See how stupid I am?! But I guess it's ok, since everyone was laughing because everyone was growling. =s People kept staring at us, though. =P Don't you just love inside jokes?  To close this off, I'll say that I'm getting darker. Nooooo!!! I don't want to get dark! I really wanna stay pale. Ugh, look what marching band has done to me. =P 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You're not cool unless you're not the wall of shame! "You're not cool unless you pee your pants!" -Sally   I HATE MARCHING BAND. I HATE IT, HATE IT, HATE IT, HATE IT TO THE MAX! There can't be anything more boring, disgusting and so tiresome. I'll start from the beginning to fill in the details.  Well, I got there like at 7.45 AM and I saw a couple of my friends. I was supposed to get a name tag, and so I did. I also found So-Young's name tag, and knowing that she wasn't gonna come, I took it with me. The name tag, at the bottom, said, "SENIORS '05 RULE!!!" Ha, yeah right. Lamebutts. Just because you're graduating doesn't mean that you're better than everyone else. Burn!  When it was 8 o'clock we had to move to some shade because some guy was gonna talk to us about marching band and crap. Pfft, as soon as I saw Mr. King, I just looked at him with disgust. Ugh, how much I hate him now. Then they started to teach us the basics of marching, like how to stand and crap. They were making us yell some weird stuff, and one of them was "BAND!" At first I though we were yelling "BAM!", but then I found out it was actually "band." A lot of freshmen though the same way, too. Stupid band directors.  We had to stand in the sun doing marching crap from 8.30 - 11 AM. It was crazy. This man (I forget their names) was telling us what to do and stuff, and so were the squad leaders. We only had water breaks of two minutes, and that it isn't enough when the fuggin' sun is just shining right in front of you freakin' face. Seriously, I felt like fainting. One of the flute girls just collapsed to the floor after thirty minutes. She collapsed twice. I was pretty ok with the sun until around 10.50 AM. But I'll go to that later.  All of those marching stuff that they were teaching us made my back and legs hurt like heck. I couldn't stand it. I wanted to die at that moment. And of course, those stupid water breakes (which supposedly were two minutes, but they were like 30 - 40 seconds long... idiots) didn't help at all because I needed more time to rest. I was standing to the left of Sally-chan, and Michelle-chan was further away from me. There were flute squad leaders helping us and stuff (most of them were seniors), and they were trying to make us yell whatever crap they wanted to make us yell. Seriously, I hate it. I hate this marching band crap. If it were for me, I'd instantly quit and go home and not have to worry about anything of this bullcrap.  I felt as if though I was in the army. I had to stand straight, shoulders up, chest out, hips in, legs together, and I couldn't smile or look around at any time. Any time we were in "tension position" we couldn't move at all. We couldn't scratch, sneeze, move our head a little bit... nothing. And what the heck is up with all these positions? I sure as heck am going to forget them tomorrow. I felt so stupid when I was out in the field, but I think that's how all the freshmen felt. 	 At around 10.15 AM Sally-chan felt dizzy and not very well. She just ran out of the field, but I didn't look to where she was going because I knew I'd get in trouble. Later on Casidy-san told me that she went inside the band hall because she was getting dehydrated or something like that. Veronica-san was inside, too. When 10.30 AM came, every time we had a "water break," I would feel dizzy and not be able to keep my eyes open. I saw everything darker than usual, and my feet felt weak, and so did my arms. But I didn't want to run out of the field because I'd feel very stupid. So when it was 10.50, I felt horrible. I wasn't yelling whatever stuff we were yelling, and I couldn't concentrate. The sun was killing me, and it wasn't because I wasn't drinking enough water...it was because the sun was just striking right at my face. I wasn't the only one feeling this, Casidy-san, Sarah-san [B], and Michelle-chan all felt that way. Thank goodness, because at 11 AM we went inside to the band hall, and we were gonna be there for the rest of the morning practice.  As I had expected, the seniors felt all superior to the freshmen, sophmores and juniors. Of course, what can you expect from people that believe they know it all? As we were going to the band hall, I felt so weak and thought I was just going to collapse...but I didn't. Then this freshman, known as Adrian, was holding the door for everyone, which was leading to the band hall. Some idiotic and moronic senior said, "Hey! Good job holding that door, *chuckle* freshman!" Man! I felt like throwing my instrument at his ugly face, then jump him for believing he was superior to all of the people there. What a retard. When I get to be a senior, I won't act as retarded as that stupid moron. Of course, since I won't be in band any longer, then I won't have to smash on freshmen like that. Blasted fools.  We got these sheets, and in one of them there was a Freshmore song. Most. Retarded. Song. Ever. I never thought there could be such a stupid song in the world. In some part it praises the '05 seniors for being the greatest class and crap like that. Pfft, that's not great, that's LAME! The anti-spiff has them. The squad leaders sang it, and I just felt like laughing at how retarded it was. I hadn't smiled or laughed so far, and now it was not the time. Supposedly we have to memorize it, because some idiots might ask us to sing it. Heck, I'll memorize it, but I won't sing it. It's so retarded, and the '05 seniors suck. Burn again!  The morning rehearsal wasn't supposedly gonna be over until 12 PM, but at 11.30 AM they released us. Sally-chan's sister, Mallory, gave me a ride to my apartment. When I got home I found out that my mom wasn't gonna pick me up at 1.15 PM after all. So I just rested for 30 minutes, ate eggs, then went walking from my house to the Panther Stadium. It wasn't so bad, but the sun was still fuggin' strong. 	 I was one of the first people to get there. In fact, I was the only one there. I got there at 1 PM, but we weren't supposed to come back until 1.30 PM.  Then I walked to the high school's cafeteria, because that's where we were supposed to meet after the lunch break.  Ten minutes after my arrival I found Krasynthia-san walking around. I went with her to the band hall and stuff, then when we came back more flutes had arrived. At 2 PM we started working with Ms. Shults (sp?) with the music and crap. I had to share stands with Michelle-chan and Sarah-san [B]. Those losers! They kept making me laugh and I couldn't concentrate on what Ms. S was saying. We were just laughing throughout most of the afternoon rehearsal. My flute was so fuggin' warm, and I was out of tune so bad...but that was ok, since that's how all of the flutes were. Our pieces of music kept blowing away because we were outside. Michelle-chan kept getting mad every time it was about to blow away, so finally, she said, "Ugh! I'm sick of this crap! Here!" Then she takes out this long stick that she found on the ground and puts it under the music so it won't fly away anymore... Oh...my...fuggin'...goddess... The three of us couldn't stop laughing, and we didn't play once because the laughter wouldn't go away. So I hit Michelle-chan for acting so retarded, and I told her to stop. Of course, she didn't, 'cause Sarah-san and I just kept laughing at the most stupid things.  In marching band everything's different. All the squad leaders have first part, and the other people have second part. No matter how good you were in eighth grade, these squad leaders will make you sound bad. They don't say, "Ok, let's hear the first chair players," or, "Let's hear the first row of flutes." Now it's, "Let's hear freshmen now," or, "Now let me hear the sophmores," and stuff like that.  At 3.30 PM we stopped practicing and went inside the band hall to talk about more band crap. Ugh, I DON'T CARE! After more talking and talking, our practice for the day was over. Holy, was I tired or what? I couldn't walk and my feet were aching so bad. They gave us a lot of marching band information sheets, but I didn't bother to look at them. Y'know, I'd quit this instant, but I wanna get my P.E. and art credits before I do. So after this horrible and painful year, I'll be band-less, flute-less, and band director-less. It'll be my happiest day ever. I'm telling you, freshman year is gonna suck so bad...  So I told my mom about everything that happened. She told me to quit. I was glad to hear that, but I didn't tell her anything. When I got home, I ate, then fell asleep for two hours. When I woke up my legs were still hurting. My parents are out right now 'cause they're gonna buy me some vitamins to help me not feel dizzy when I'm out there. I hope that helps... 	 Tomorrow's Crazy Sock Day...or so the band directors want you to believe. First of all, what the fug? This Crazy Sock Day bull is mandatory, but I sure as heck don't have any crazy socks. All I'm gonna wear is some socks that don't match, and if they're not happy with that, then tough. I'm not gonna do all the stupid things that they tell me to do...and why does this have to be mandatory, anyway? What are they gonna do, check everyone's socks? This is just bullcrap. And I'm gonna have to do this band camp for 8 days. I HATE MARCHING BAND. BAND! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Brooms as an enemy? What are they going to do, take over the world by sweeping it squeaky clean? -Atomsmasher   Y'know, I thought the band camp wasn't going to be for a while...but then Sally tells me that it's this Monday at 8 AM... Oh, the horror! I hope I don't forget. It feels like I'm going to school because I have to wake up at 7 AM and get there at 8 AM. Those other 10th and 11th graders are gonna feel so superior to us and try to tell us what to do...probably. But, if they try to embarrase me or make me look more stupid than I already am, then they'll meet the real dany, and the real dany can get pretty mean. So, if they mess with me, I'll mess with them. Crap, how much I hate band. Someone wake me up from this nightmare.  But anyways, Regi-chan told me something that I couldn't believe. It's quite shocking, and it just makes you see what kind of creeps the band directors are. I changed the spelling and grammar a lot. =P   Ok, see...when my brother quit band, he didn´t want to get out of the car to get his stuff, and so instead my mom got down. She was asking for the mouthpiece, but didn't know what the name was. So she asked Mr. King, "Do you know where the thing where you blow through is??" and he replied "Are you stupid?" and some other stuff. I think he was treating her like she was mental or something. Then she came running to the car crying, and couldn't tell my brother the story because she was crying so much. Ha-ha, my aunt said that whenever she comes to Dallas, my brother is going to show him that man so she can cuss him out in Spanish XD! See how mean he was to my mom?!   All I can say is...wow. I never thought any band director could be so mean and disrespectful, especially to a parent. I mean, what the fug? It's not Mrs. Urrutia's fault that she didn't know what the name of it .was. How did he expect her to know what the heck a mouthpiece was if she's not in band? Of course, band directors expect a lot from people, but they're just so fugged up! It didn't even happen to me, and yet I'm so fuggin' upset on what Mr. King did to Mrs. Urrutia. What an idiot. And I thought he was nice... pfft, moron.  Like Regi-chan said, all band directors are mean, and I just noticed that's true. Maybe their band directors from their childhood traumatized them so much, so now they're taking it out on us...or the parents. =s  So... yeah. Band camp's tomorrow and I'm so nervous. 'Tis gonna be be at the Panther Stadium, near the DHS. I'm so nervous...even though I now know what's going on. Hehe, Regi-chan and Kathryn-chan wanna come to the band practices, but Regi-chan can't come until the last rehearsal. It's fine with me, though, 'cause that'd be so embarrasing! I didn't tell either Regi-chan or Kathryn-chan where the band camp was gonna be, but that's alright, too. XD Kathryn said that she was gonna be yelling my name all the time, which would be funny and embarrasing, too. Crap, if I see those two some day at some practice, I'll be so happy! XD  Nothing much to say. I have to go to sleep early (10 PM) for one week and two days. Blaaah, how much I'm gonna miss summer! ;_;  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>