<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There are currently only 4 pitchers to achieve the elite of 4,000 Career strike outs. lets look into the numbers and see who  may  join them on the road to 4,000.....   The 4 players who have reached this platue are as follows :  1. urlLink Nolan Ryan ,  5,714  Career strikeouts in  27 seasons . this took a long time to get this many strikeouts.Nolan got his 4,000th career on July,11th 1985 against  urlLink Danny Heep .You really don't see very many pitchers staying in the majors 27 years.I beleive that  urlLink Nolan Ryan  was not a winning pitcher by anymeans but he powered his opponents with the nasty stuff. Nolan's career was a long one but his record was 324-292,just a smidge above .500.Now he may have over .500 record,but he also had 2,795 career Walks.Lets just say he did not have great control.   2. urlLink Roger Clemens  has  4,200 career  K's in  20 seasons . Roger got number 4,000 on June 13, 2003 against  Edgar Renteria . He also won his 300th career game, wow that must have been euphoric.Roger has retired once already but i hope that he stays in the game for many years to come.  3. urlLink Steve Carlton  has  4,136 career  strikeouts in  22 seasons . Steve got his joyous number 4,000 on August 15, 1986. Steve had a shaky career he could not control his pitches. The team thought that it would be in his best interest to retire in '86 but it was a no-go for Steve. Later in that season he got his 4,000 K, way to go Steve.  4. urlLink Randy Johnson  is our latest to get to 4,000. Randy slid into 4th place on the all time list on June 29, 2004 against the  urlLink San Diego Padres .  urlLink Jeff Cirillo  was randys victim. Randy achieved this in 19 teriffic seasons. Randy will probably strike out over 4,500 by the end of his career,but there are rumors that he will be wearing pinstripes by next season.It is really unfortunate but it is true "MOST" great players will wear yankee pinstripes by the end of their career.Lets hope that Randy is not into all that "hoopla" and he stays with the other pinstripes, purple that is.   There are a few players creeping up on these 4 but probably will not make the cut .    urlLink Greg Maddux    is the next in line with 2,835 in 19 seasons. Greg says that he has a good 4 seasons left in him but by his record this year he may just want to call it quits after this season.   urlLink Curt Schilling   has 2,642 career K's in 17 seasons. Curt is not going to hit the mark. He may have some good stuff but he is not going to last with his body aging and his hemroids raging.I wish the best for him but,4,000 is not in the future.   urlLink John Smoltz   has 2,346 strikeouts in 16 seasons.John is not going to hit the bulls eye. The  urlLink Atlanta Braves  put him in the bull pen,there is no hope johnny boy its not going to happen.If he was to be pulled out of the Pen he still does not have a chance in the world.   urlLink Kevin Brown   with a career 2,312 strikeouts in 18 seasons.The future is not looking too bright for Kevin he is currently on the 15 day DL (strained lower back). If you ask me that means your too damn old. I would have to say that hell would freeze over before he got 4,000.   Looks like 4,000 is alot tougher than everyone thinks. these 4 guys are going to stay at the top for a long time. In order for these guys to rach 4,000 they need to strike out about 400 average a year for 3 1/2 more years.They are "untouchable".    

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm down with the flu for a bit. Jetmech will carry on for me in the meantime. I'll be back soon.  

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						 posted by Todd |  urlLink 3:17 PM 
       |
          0 comments 
         
					  
					   
					   
					  
					    
 					
					   


					

                       
                           Sunday, June 27, 2004 
                       
						 
					   
					     
						 
						
                           
                      	 
                      	 On the Road To 500
	                       
                           
                        
						 
						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was invited to the Blog as the fantasy neophyte, to ask questions. This is my first year playing fantasy Baseball, So that is me indeed. I have to agree with JetMech, that Baseball is "The Great American Pass Time". It's un-American to miss the World Series at the least, and who of us didn't at least play softball as young kid in the first few years of school, if no other sport. So I am one of those nominal Americans getting into this with more seriousness and fervor, and all of your enthusiasm is contagious for sure. So you all have my thanks.  Here is something I hope sparks a little discussion: I have 5 fantasy teams. The first one I was a nervous wreck at the live draft, at the end I thought I had screwed up something wicked and was totally devastated. I noticed looking at the final results of how it went down, that everyone else was very careful to pick up pitchers first. But me in my ignorance drafted players by rank first, not position. The next time I was far better prepared, and drafted based on what I learned from my mistakes. It turns out that my first team is in first place and my second team is in last place. By the time I drafted some of my last teams I decided there might be something to my first instinct, and yes, the teams where I didn't just go after pitchers first are all doing better.  

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    "MOVIN' ON UP"     Marcus Giles (2B, Braves):  If all stays according to plan Giles, who was drafted highly in most leagues, will finally return from a broken collarbone. This is good new for fantasy owners and for Braves fans.  Good second basemans are hard to come by so Giles having a great second half can definitely help your fantasy team.   Magglio Ordonez (OF, White Sox):  Has returned from the DL and should be back in your lineup.  Last year he hit an impressive .317 with 95 runs, 29 homeruns, 99 RBIs, and 9 stolen bases.   Bill Mueller (3B, Red Sox):  Returned from the DL and has been doing his best to make up for lost time going 10 for 25 since his return. He has returned to form and raised his average 12 points already.  Hitting before Nomar and Mr. David Ortiz cant be  so  bad...  Hitting in the middle of the crazed Boston lineup is stat heaven.   Eric Chavez (3B, A’s):  Returned from the DL and will slot right back into the A’s offense.  Not only one of the best defensively, but "Chavvy" is also one of the best hitters in the game today.  Last week, after returning from the DL, he posted 4 runs, 2 RBIs, and is batting .500(6 for 12).   Carlos Delgado (1B, Blue Jays):  Returned from the DL after missing more than a month.  Disappointedly, he was my 1st round pick, but hopefully he'll live up to his status.  Last year he put up remarkable numbers- 117 runs, 42 homeruns, and an ML leading 145 RBI's.   Preston Wilson (OF, Rockies):   He's off to a slow start from coming off the DL, but he's soon to come around.  Last year he had very similar stats to of Carlos Delgado, and hitting in Coors Field can definitely help...   Livan Hernandez (SP, Expos):   The Bad News Bears(Expos) are nowhere near they need to be in the NL East, with a 31-56 record, and 15 games out of first, trade rumors have been hovering over this one time World Series MVP.  One trade rumor says that Hernandez may go to the New York Yankees.  That's a nice lil' jump there...last to first...   AJ Burnett (SP, Marlins): After coming off the DL because of Tommy John surgery, he got tee-ed off having a 5+ ERA, but last month has changed that.  In June, he got 1 win, with a 2.95 ERA, 0.93 WHIP, and 28 K's in 36.2 innings.   Mark Teixeira (1B/3B/OF, Rangers):  Has been slaughtering the ball and has 6 home runs in the last 12 games and has raised his average 22 points in that span. This is more like it and is closer to the real Teixeira than the guy who was hitting just .254 two weeks ago. He’s on pace to flirt with 40 home runs.  Also, hitting behind Soriano, Michael Young, and Hank Blalock will help that RBI total.   Edgar Renteria (SS, Cardinals): Not exactly off to an All Star year, Renteria's luck hasn't came yet.  If you were to watch the ESPN Webgems, you would probably see Renteria the one being robbed of a hit.  The whole year he has been hitting the ball hard, and has been getting solid line-drive hits, but getting robbed.  The second half should be better for him, especially with the possible MVP Scott Rolen and the red hot HR machine Jim Edmonds hitting behind him.   Jose Reyes (SS, Mets): Does anyone remember the second half he had last year? He hit .339 and stole 11 bases.  The Mets hitting has been great the past month and Jose Reyes has been one of the reasons.   Joe Mauer (C, Twins): He was supposed to be a total stud in the majors, but an injury stopped that from happening, well at least for the 1st half of the season.  Fresh legs from the All Star break will benefit this young star.     "Goin' Down Town"     Kevin Youkillis (3B, Red Sox): Has lost the majority of his playing time since Bill Mueller returned from the DL.   Frank Thomas (1B, White Sox): Was placed on the 15 day DL with inflammation of his right ankle - due to bone chips. This might be a lot more serious than noted especially because of the strain that ankle takes just moving the big guy around and surgery which could end his season.   Jose Jimenez (RP, Free Agent): Jimenez was given his release from the Indian organization as a failed stint as closer. He’ll land somewhere but his role as a closer is probably long gone.  Look for Bob Wickman, the possible new closer for the Cleveland Indians.   Josh Beckett (SP, Marlins): Was once again placed on the 15 day DL with blister problems.  In his starts getting a blister, he's gone 5 strong innings, but then the blister occurs.  If Jack McKeon were smart, he'd put Beckett as a RP.  How does a Beckett-Benitez duo sound?   Melvin Mora (3B, Orioles): Has been placed on the 15 day DL with a hamstring injury.  He's not exactly known for his second half performance either.  Last year he barely hit over .200 in the second half.  (TRADE HIM!!!)   Adrian Belte (3B, Dodgers): Despite his first half performance, Beltre probably wont be able to end strong.  Typically, he is a second half hitter, but his ankle injury can counter that.   Ken Griffey JR. (OF, Reds): Not much to say.  He's injured again(Oh, you knew it was going to happen eventually)...      

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There are many positions to fill for fantasy baseball leagues, and not all of them can be expected to be well-known, all-star players. For a competitive team with some under-rated players, here's a list of players that I feel qualify to be on a top team in a league and reasons why.   Batting:   1.  urlLink R. Belliard - Holding a great average, he isn't doing as well as he has been starting off, but he's hitting more HR's, and scoring more runs. He still manages to get on base quite a bit, and 2nd base doesn't have too many promising players.   2.  urlLink B. Wilkerson - This player has been one of the only hot hitting expos, doing it with doubles and HR's lately. Seems to always manage to get an RBI or run during a game. Consistency is key with him.   3.  urlLink E. Byrnes - Although outfield is probably the easiest position to find good players, Byrnes is pretty good himself. He leads the team with SB's, and has been hot as of late June. Pretty good player to hold on to the bench at least.   4.  urlLink T. Wigginton - I wouldn't have said him a month ago, but lately he's been the hot hitter for the Mets. HR's, doubles, and RBI's seem to be racking up for him, and he just seems to be continually improving to try and stay on the Mets team and not get traded. There is purpose behind this 3rd/2nd baseman.   5.  urlLink R. Clayton - Hiding in that Colorado hitting team is a shortstop with great ability to hit, not really Hr's, but more singles. Probably a better back-up SS, he can be a good secret among hitters to get the average up. Pretty good with runs as well as a result, maybe even an RBI here and there.   Pitching:   1.  urlLink V. Zambrano - This pitcher is on what seemed to be the worst team, but Zambrano seemed to move the team in the right direction, leading the team with wins and pitching the most innings, meaning he's a healthy, long-enduring pitcher. Strike-outs have become a main aspect of this pitcher, being a top 5 strike-out pitcher for the AL for 3 months already.   2.  urlLink D. Graves - This one seems obvious by now, but it still holds true; he is helping the reds stay above .500 for now. At 32 saves, he already tied his major-league best, and he still has half a season to go. That division seems to be just getting harder, but they are good contenders themselves. Graves is a guy promising enough to help them stay that way when they have a lead.   3.  urlLink J. Marquis - Just what the Cardinals needed, a great pitcher to emerge and help take them to the top of the NL. At 9-4 at the All-Star break, and quite a few K's, this pitcher will continue to get run support from his team which has many all-stars. Plus he has a good closer behind him.   4.  urlLink V. Santos - Behind Sheets for the Brewers, Santos has been a really big help to the team. They remain over .500 during the All-star break and at 8-3, Santos has chipped in to that occurrence. He hasn't pitched much, but that only leaves room for improvement because his stats are not too bad with the amount of innings he's pitched and the result of having an 8-3 record.   5.  urlLink N. Robertson - This Tiger's pitcher has been hot for the team, with the most wins for Detroit and the lowest ERA for the team at a pretty bad 4.11, he obviously gets much run support from the hot-hitting Tigers. Not only is his winning column impressing, but his strike-outs have been up there near the top of the AL at 94.    

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There are alot of players out there that are considered; "over the hill",but I consider them over achieving.The average age that is considered the peak is 36 for a baseball player.Now to put this into perspective there are few players that fit that bill and may help your fantasy team.The experience and leadership is exactly what a younger team needs to spark their young prospects.I am going to go in depth on why you need one of these seasoned players on your fantasy team.............  To start this discussion off lets start with  urlLink Barry Bonds .Barry is every pitchers nightmare and that story is told by barry's unbelievable walk record.Barry is 39 years old and is one of the hottest hitters in the NL (when he gets pitched to).Barry is hitting .362 with 23HR and 48RBI's.To add to those gigantic numbers he also has 128BB and we are not even at the all star break yet.   urlLink Barry Larkin .I know that yahoo does not rank him well i think that they rank him at 364 overall in ss,well dont always trust yahoo's rank structure.Barry has been red hot in the month of june he had 11RBI 7BB 2K's .429OBP .488SLG .341AVG.Barry is making his 12 apperance to the all-star game and he has deserved every mid season trip.Barry is currently 39 years ripe.   urlLink Randy Johnson  I really dont have to say much about randy he has been all over the headlines.I will just break a tip off his glorious 2004 year. 4,000 career strike out,creeping up on his 300th career win,and of course the trade talks to the Yankees.Randy is 40 years old and still as good if not better than the first day of his career.   urlLink Roger Clemens .Roger is 42 years old this season comming off a retirement.Roger has a .254ERA,113K's, with a 10-2 record.Roger is 2nd in strikeouts this 2004 season to no other than,  urlLink Randy Johnson  and  urlLink Curt Schilling  with 145 K's.   urlLink Kevin Brown  &  urlLink Kenny Rogers  are also a great addition to your fantasy team,both are 39 years of age and have a combined record this season of 19-3 with 114 srikeouts.Kevin is now on the DL but is expected to be back after the all star break.Both of these pitchers hang out in the bull pen and talk to all the young pitchers to help them with their confidence.   urlLink Steve Finley .I am a huge fan of Steve and think that if you have not picked him up in your league you are sadly mistaken.Steve is having a career year with 21HR 45RBI's and a .291BA at 39 years old. Steve would have more RBI's but unfortunatly he is playing with a bunch of double and tripple A teamates that cannot get on base for the life of them.Steve will hit another 20 some homeruns by the end of the year and end up with a career high of 40+ homeruns.  Now i Know that alot of fantasy managers are scared to pick up alot of the players with age and knowlege,but if you ask me i think that they only get better and smarter with age.Lets hope that these players can keep up their career years and stay playing Major League Baseball&reg;.If anyone feels that i have left anyone out of the picture please add a comment. 

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I should have a post or two up in the next few days, so in the mean time, lets get focused on baseball and not on the Troll. With the all star game just around the corner, what has got to be the biggest injustice in your opinion? Beltran losing a spot due to switching leagues? Perhaps a deserving player not making the squad? Let us know what you think, and I’m sure all of us on the board will be giving ours... 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello all to those that frequent this board, The BP junkie is on board as a contributor. A quick background breifing goes as I grew up living, eating and shitting baseball,and have currently come back to my first love. I have the low down on the minors, upcoming stars, and can even give my own little spin on the majors and general baseball knowledge, and of course, the old fantasy 2 cents(and the fantasy advice all boils down to how your leagues scoring is set up, so the info is use it or lose it at your own risk). Anyhow, I hope to be the more colorful and passionate of the correspondents, and hope you all look forward to my posts and get something from them, because the best is yet to come, always...                                                                     Signed,                                                                   The BP junkie   Torture - standing outside the gate, hearing the crack of the bat, and seeing schmucks get balls you know you could out hustle...  

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here are a couple of pitchers to keep an eye on. Cleveland reliever, and now interim starter  urlLink Kazuhito Tadano  has been over-powering in his last thirteen innings with 19 K’s a 2.08 ERA, and a .85 WHIP, (8 hits and only three walks). Right now Tadano is filling in for a sore shouldered C.C. Sabathia, but racking up strikeouts at this clip with a nice array of pitches dominated by a nice 90-MPH fastball, makes Tadano someone to keep in mind. Tadano utilizes a throwing motion that makes it tough for hitters to pick-up on what’s coming. At least in the interim, this will be to Kaz’s advantage.   Milwaukee left-hander  urlLink Chris Capuano  is just coming back this June from the DL due to shoulder issues. Right now his control on his fast ball is tenuous, but this has allowed him to further develop his off-speed stuff. His last start came in Colorado where he allowed one run through six with six strikeouts. Capuano has really yet to be touched up this season, never giving up more then three earned runs in a game. This Duke product has proved to be a really smart pitcher, who has illustrated the capacity to evolve his repertoire as need be. Capuano has another start tomorrow against Pittsburgh, so if you’re like me and your gamble on Duan Brazelton doesn’t pay-off after today’s start, picking of Capuano may just save your week and pay dividends for the entire second-half of the season.     

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey todd great to see that you made a quick recovery,keep on keepin on. 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   In the world of fantasy baseball everyone always needs a pitcher and everyone always needs a source for stolen bases. The Tampa Bay Devil Rays are playing some good ball right now, and they also happen to have two rookies who have a broad window to make an impression.   urlLink Dewan Brazelton  (6-4, 214, R)  Dewan is 2-0 with a 2.05 ERA and a 1.41WHIP. In his first decision versus the Marlins; Dewan took a "no-no" into the 8th. Yesterday Braz notched his second win in as many starts against the Jays. This kid is still very rough around the edges, and he's going to make some bad mistakes, but his upside is huge. Braz needs to learn how to "pitch" and not "throw". Kind of like the difference between a "boxer and a "fighter", Braz is just a fighter right now. Dewan still walks way to many hitters, and unless he gets his control issues together, he's going to get rocked one of these days or a few of these days.   I still like the kid, and I picked him up off waivers, so that's really all you need to know about how I feel about him. Braz is just so close to becoming nasty and dominant, sometimes you just gotta take a chance.   urlLink Joey Gathright  (5-10, 170, L)  The fastest man in baseball cleats is filling in for injuries to Rocco Baldelli and Tino Martinez. The 1-2 combo of Carl Crawford and Joey G. at the top of the D-Rays lineup gives this Yankee fan cold sweats, OK not really, but it does remind me of the Marlins 1-2 of Pierre and Castillo.   So far Joey G. is batting .333 in 18 at-bats with 6 Runs, 3 SB, and an OBP of .429. That BA is going to go down, and if it goes down too far Joey's going back down too. In the meantime, if you need some cheap steals, pick him up and watch for another D-Ray's speedster, BJ Upton to eventually get the call up to that big, teal gutted shopping mall they call a ballpark in Tampa.   You’ve been served.  

						
</post>


</Blog>