<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A church member asked me last week if I had heard of Blogging. My answer was evident by the look on my face, no. They told me about the process, and I thought it would be an interesting adventure. I am sure that there will be things that I write that will ruffle some feathers. I am sure there are things that I will read that will ruffle my feathers. I think all that is good.  I make no bones about who and what I am. I a country preacher who was saved by the overwhelming love of Jesus, and hold fast to a Biblical world view. I choose to live my life in an attempt to please Him. There are times I blow it royally, and there are moments I get close to accomplishing it. I hate religion, but I love the relationship I have with my savior. He has grace and mercy even for the folks I don't like. All religion has, is guilt, and pressure. Don't get me wrong I know what sin is, and do not think much of it, but Jesus always loved sinners while despising sin. I want to get to the point of loving people into the Kingdom of God. Again I do not want to be misunderstood. There is only one way into relationship with God. Jesus period. I can not work my way in, I can not earn my way in by being good enough, or by trying to rid the world of those who do not think like me. God's grace through Jesus my Lord that's it period. Oh yea I tried a bunch of the other stuff, it just left me blah.  My faith is not the only thing I am passionate about, but my faith shapes my other passions. Take my wife and kids for example. They are my life. I have the greatest wife in the world! She puts me in my place when needed, and she picks me up when I am low. She loves her career, She is a Middle School Math teacher. She has the "smarts" to earn a PHD in mathematics, and teach on the college level. Yet, what gives her a charge is instilling the love of math into the lives of kids. I have seen her make algebra exciting to 13 year olds. To me that is a miracle. I love her for her passion for her career, and her students. She is also teaching our daughters how to be strong independent, thinking women. She is instilling in them a modesty, that I fear is very lacking in teens of the day. At the same time she is helping them find the beauty they each posses. Each of them are finding their niche, their place, and that is really cool to see. I love her for this as well. I get a charge out of the new discoveries they make about life, and how they apply those discoveries in their lives. I am amazed at how perceptive they are, I do not recall being that sharp as a teen, I know I thought I was, but I was lacking much of what they have. I can honestly say I am proud of my wife, and kids. I am a blessed man.  Well thanks for reading, and BE BLESSED TODAY. GOD LOVES YOU EVEN IF YOU DON'T LIKE HIM    

						
</post>


</Blog>