<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The other day I was thinking about what an interesting world, or society rather, we live in. That is, a society that has made incredible leaps and bounds in terms of medical advancements, especially with regard to DNA and genetics. (I find the study of genetics fascinating. Having said that, I also believe that the current corporate-driven uses of biotechnology are potentially harmful and irreversibly damaging to our current ecosystem. Much to my surprise, I've met people who can't seem to understand how I can be pro-genetic research while being against putting insufficiently tested genetically modified organisms into the food supply without labeling, purely for corporate gain. Only a dull mind could conceive of a contradiction there. The long and short of it is, if a consumer has the right to buy and eat genetically modified products, surely I, as a consumer, have the right to  not  buy and eat genetically modified products. In any case, I've long ago tired of debating the issue with people who are, in my opinion, susceptible to corporate-sponsored marketing. To those enlightened consumers who are interested in the daily goings on with our agriculture, I recommend signing up to the  urlLink Organic Consumers Association's Organic Bytes Newsletter . It's an email newsletter that comes once or twice a month with all the latest news.)   So anyways, here we are, with the ability to look right into a person's DNA, which is quite small, and see things like who was at the crime scene, or what type of physical/personality traits a new baby may have, etc. And this high powered technology is used for things like.......like making it possible for Maury Pauvich to help one of his female guests determine which of the twelve men is the father of her baby. Thus the title of this blog entry, for which I must thank the incomparable Luke Carter. It's like advanced scientific discovery meets "food goes in here (while pointing at one's mouth)" citizen.   I've been keeping a glancing eye on the  urlLink 2004 Democratic National Convention  and it seems to be going well for them. The  urlLink 9-11 Report  has been published and apparently is flying off the bookshelves, making it one of the most popular books right now.   Movie reviews: The Bourne Supremacy was excellent. I gave it 4.5 amnesiatic killer spies of of 5.   I, Robot was much better than I thought it would be. It earned a respectable 3 buggy robots of the killing kind out of 5.      

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Apparently,  urlLink Linda Ronstadt was kicked out of a Las Vegas casino  for dedicating a song to Michael Moore and his documentary Fahrenheit 9/11.  Of   all   the things that go on in Las Vegas, this 'incident' is cause for a strong response. Gee whiz...    urlLink Moveon.org  has come out with  urlLink a great commercial  promoting the film 'Outfoxed'.   But enough about that.  Come on everybody! It's a good ol' fashioned   urlLink    John Kerry - Dubya Bush sing-a-long! 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Samstock was this past Saturday, and all went well. The band played half decent, the food was good and it was fun.  urlLink Paul Remole  was there too. The only downer was that I hurt my back lifting up one of the pieces of equipment soon after getting there. It's still sore today, three days later, but getting better. I'm taking it as a sign of how much pain people can be in as I embark on my new career direction of healing and wellness. Pain sucks.   Supersize Me is a great little documentary. I think I'm getting addicted to these 'thinking person' movies and have lost much of my interest in the usual Hollywood fare. The next documentary I want to see is  urlLink Control Room , which seeks an answer to the question, 'Is America stabilizing or radicalizing the Arab world?'.   Books I currently have on the go are  urlLink Your Money or Your Life ,  urlLink Toxic Sludge Is Good For You , and  urlLink Gandhi's Autobiography . All non-fiction, of course. &nbsp; :)   Click the image below to see my friend, Les Smith's latest movie...    urlLink   
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This post is being brought to you by the BlogThis! feature.  It's a system whereby I add a link to the Links toolbar in my browser.  When I want to post, I click it and it opens a posting window.  Beats going to the blogger site to add messages, I guess.  I'm applying to the Canadian College of Massage and Hydrotherapy today.  It's a two year course and so I'll graduate as a Registered Massage Therapist in 2007, at the ripe old age of 36.  The course is offered right here in KW, so I won't have to move or anything like that.  There are some prepatory courses I need to take before then which I'll get started on post haste.  I've learned how to make a great chutney.  4 dates, 2 cups of cilantro leaves, lime juice and olive oil (or ghee) in a food processor. Now if I only had a food processor!!  :)     

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I decided that I needed a blog. I've spent the last little while setting my new blog up and it's pretty easy to do.  I believe the nice folks at Google power this particular blog app, and they've done a nice job.  This Thursday I'm going to see  urlLink Supersize Me , so I'll have a review of that on Friday.  Other documentaries I've seen lately are  urlLink Fahrenheit 9/11  which I highly recommend, and  urlLink The Corporation  which is also fantastic.  In terms of Hollywood films I've seen King Arthur and Spiderman 2 which were neither great nor horrible, so I won't bother dignifying them with a link.    urlLink   
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I registered the domain name  urlLink onebigeye.org .  I'd like to eventually use this domain as a portal for alternative health care practitioners, or possibly even start my own church to see what that's like. Right now I just have a  urlLink splash page  set up there.  If you check it out, turn on your speakers for a couple of small sound effects.    :)  Not too much else going on, other than my back is feeling quite a bit better!  I made the following graphic for fun over the weekend as well.  Enjoy!   Transformation  (Click image for larger view)    urlLink   
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I went to Sauble Beach and spent a day or so with Rosie and Brad. Brad's parents have a great cottage up there and it was nice to sit around in the water for a while. We went cycling for a bit and my back got quite sore. The ride home practically killed me. Fortunately, it wasn't reinjured, and it's been improving considerably every day since. While up there, we went to see The Village. It was quite good. I think I liked Six Sense and Signs better, but it is nonetheless a worthy addition to that director's list of movies.  I had my first Reiki session with Shirley Martin, Pablo's Reiki instructor. I wasn't sure what to expect but it was awesome, to put it mildly. Shirley is very gifted and I'll definitely be seeing her again.  I'm looking forward to having the next four days off as well. I am sooooooo due for a long weekend.... :)    The Monsanto New Product of the Week     
</post>


</Blog>