<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Seth's claim to fame is this story that made national news back in 2000.&nbsp; Hopefully his soccer playing will give him some more fame in the future.   urlLink http://www.soccertimes.com/mls/2000/may12.htm     
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Congratulations today go to this man, Seth Trembly, my former high school teammate and current Colorado Rapids substitute.  In today's 3-1 away loss to the San Jose Quakes, Seth was the first guy off the bench and made quite an impression...scoring the Rapids only goal of the game...and the first goal for the team in a little over three games, I believe.  And it was a sweet goal...stepped up to win the ball, beat a man to the left, and ripped a strike to Pat Onstad's right...taking away his shutout.  I always watch for Seth when the Rapids are playing, and this is just the moment I was hoping to see.  (It was on ESPN2 today.)  Rob Stone, the play by play guy...was like, "I like this Seth Trembly!"  It was Seth's first goal of the year.  I'm glad I saw it.  By the way, we were teammates my senior year on the varsity team.  He was only a sophomore at the time (in fact, he played varsity his freshman year while I was still on JV, how sad--well, I guess he is a professional player now so that kind of doesn't make me feel as bad).  He started playing for the Rapids while he was still a senior at Arapahoe HS.  Way to go, man.  Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       After getting about four hours of sleep Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday nights...and having people over to mine and Matt's place last night--then going out dancing till 2:30am--and then staying up for another beer and some coversation with our neighbor.....I did the unthinkable.&nbsp; I slept.&nbsp; I woke up at 3 in the afternoon today, without waking up once-- not once --during the night/morning/early afternoon. &nbsp; What probably made my extended slumber possible was the fact that Bear was not in my room...but left out in the living room all night...and therefore left us a little present under the dining table.&nbsp; He was let outside by Matt, and I was left to sleep. &nbsp; Now we're debating on what to do for an encore tonight.&nbsp; Maybe go back out to the beer garden/dance club.&nbsp; Who knows.&nbsp; I think Matt and I are off to see I,ROBOT in a little over an hour.&nbsp; I hope it's good but I'm expecting a so-so movie.&nbsp; Bridget Moynahan is hot...I can tell you that. :)  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         For starters.   Thursdays...for me...are a toss up.&nbsp; I can't decide whether I look forward to them or dread them.&nbsp; They are long first of all.&nbsp; And they involve lots of brain-numbing work...creativity and all that...and then, after I spend one hell of a long day in a newsroom and editing bay, I get to run home, change clothes, and drive out to play some softball.&nbsp; It's fun.&nbsp; It's just exhausting.&nbsp; I think it's one of those things that I do dread for most of the week, but once I get into the story and all I have a good time...and am glad I'm putting my storytelling skills to use (what skills I purport to having, mind you.)&nbsp; And the softball is fun.&nbsp;  &nbsp;   Bloop and a blast.   Played a good game tonight.&nbsp; Led off and went 3 for 3.&nbsp; Nothing fancy of course.&nbsp; I have the power to hit singles.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; But the team we played sucked.&nbsp; Had our first "win by mercy rule" victory...and my team is maybe a game over .500.&nbsp; Maybe.&nbsp; And it's a church league.&nbsp; We--I'm serious about this--have to say a prayer before the game.&nbsp; It's the home team's responsibility.&nbsp; It's the visiting team's responsibility to find any and all gay players and ban them from the league for life--and any child-in-sin they may be responsible for.&nbsp; After the game...we all dance around a giant bonfire which burns permanently in right-center...chanting in jubilant anticipation of the re-election of The Lord's President, Mr. George W. Bush.&nbsp; Then...once we leave the field of our open and proud Christian lives...we go home and secretly masturbate to a bootlegged DVD of anal sex.&nbsp; Ahhhhhhh...I'm glad I'm living where I'm living.&nbsp; If I lived elsewhere--you know, everywhere else permeated with sin--I'd be dipping myself into a giant fondue pot of hell.&nbsp; We people here have things figured out.&nbsp; Good Lord willin'. &nbsp; How in the world did my post veer in this direction?!&nbsp; It must be, once again, nearly four hours past my recommended bedtime. &nbsp; Goodnight.&nbsp; Don't let the concert-fuckers bite.   &nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Okay....outdoor music festival in Norway...such headliners include Alicia Keys (who I think is HOT)...and everybody is having a good time and I'm getting a bit of a scandanavian sunburn when--HOLD THE PRESS--IS THAT WHAT I THINK IT IS?!?!?!  According to the Norway media...these two naked fornicators decided to have sex on stage in order to raise awareness for the environment--specifically, the shrinking rainforests of the world.  Those two little fuckers also run a porn site on the web...which gives a portion of its profits to environmental groups.  Oh...it gets better.  The band playing at the time?  The Cumshots.   Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is me in two minutes.  Problem is...it should have been me about four hours ago.  Even a bigger problem...it happens to me nightly.  GOODNIGHT.........no, I'm serious.  Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    http://sports.espn.go.com/ncf/columns/story?columnist=maisel_ivan&id=1839834                  Apparently this is the future of college football, until the next time BCS sparks some sort of controversy.  Seriously, why can't we have both the bowl games and a playoff?  Take the top four or eight teams.  The big playoff games can still be the typical bcs bowl games--rose, sugar, etc...  Then the other bowl games can continue as they are now--completely inconsequential but still fun for hardcore football fans and fans of the teams playing.  I think a college football playoff system is like gay marriage becoming legal--it's eventually gonna happen.  Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, put this picture in your mind.  I'm sitting here in my newsroom...waiting for my roommate to get back to the station so we can work out across the street.  But I forgot the stuff to take off my makeup--which he's bringing.  So I'm waiting in my gold mizzou basketball shorts and a white t-shirt--and makeup caked all over my face.  How's that for handsome.  But I'm actually loving working out.  This might be the first time I've looked forward to lifting weights.  I go three days a week, and I think that it may be a pattern that continues for quite a long time.  I'm hoping so.  I haven't had muscle my whole life.  And it just makes me feel better...like when my room is clean.  (it's never clean, but if it was, i'd feel better)  I don't, however--like working out in makeup--so that special Clinique Foaming Facial Cleanser needs to arrive pronto. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I'm sitting here at work--just finished my on-air work for the morning.  The highlight of the local cut-ins (every half hour for the two hour "The Early Show") was me promoting the last half-hour of the show, saying it would include a performance by Clay Aiken.  How I ache for him.  Many of you heard about my earlier comments about the young pop star on the air...and the resulting public outcry.  Clay and I are now dating, thank you very much.  But now I'm putting off the part of the work-week that I hate the most--the part where I have to open up the phone book which sits below me and to the right...select a name at random...and call that person up and tell them I want to do a story on them.  Of course, most people aren't home...so most of the stories I do involve retired folks or people who work on their own business out of their home.  If I have to do another "I quit my job and went to work for myself...ahhh the freedom" story I think I'll just throw myself in the dry creek bed on the outskirts of town.    It's tough to drown around these parts.    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Read from earlier today.  What time did I want to get to bed?  7:30?    What time is it now?  9:45.   Knights of Columbus  that's sad. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think it was brilliant and hilarious throughout--but I think it's almost too selective for everybody to enjoy.  I don't mean it's selective in the sense that you have to be in news to get the jokes, because you surely don't.  It's mostly an absurd comedy set inside a newsroom.  There are some inside things but they're minor.  I just mean that, well, comedy is like porn--some stuff does it for you while other stuff simply doesn't.  This comedy was so out there--people just didn't get it as Ferrell, McKay and all the others intended.  I've actually heard some people say that the movie wasn't funny at all.  I think it's incredibly funny, but it just wasn't the kind of funny people were expecting.  It's dry, it's random, and they are jokes with no punchlines.    My prediction:  I think the movie has a great chance of doing what Austin Powers did (maybe not to that degree).  A.P. did rather poorly in the theaters--I remember being not-too-impressed after leaving the theater for the first time.  But when it hit video...it's quotability and all that out-there, random humor began clicking for people and the sequels have been insanely huge.  My two cents.  Almost time for bed.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The greatest news team...ever.  I mean, this news team would even beat a news team led by the masters of conversational delivery themselves--Onstot and Cosgrove--a sports reporter named Crow--a columnist who goes by O'Connell--and with Vitale doing it's sales and LaPlaca making us all look good in the land of PR.    Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Prost!  Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ahhh, Will Ferrell.  How I long to be you.  Whether he's the one musing about Hansel, male model of the year, or declaring "San Diego" to actually be a German translation of "whale's vagina," you really can't doubt his genious.  --Doesn't San Diego mean Saint Diego? -- No.  I'm afraid not.  --No...I'm sure of it.  It means Saint Diego! -- I guess we'll just have to agree to disagree.   Well...enough of those shinanigans.  I'm tired.  I want to nap, but if I nap I won't be able to go to bed tonight at a decent hour...and considering the fact that I've only been getting about five hours tops recently...a decent hour tonight means by 7:30pm.  Good thing it's dark by then.  Oh wait.  I'll have to wait 2 1/2 hours until it's dark--son of a bitch.  I came home today from the Olive Garden (more on that later) hoping my roommate would be up for seeing Spidey 2 with me--he hasn't seen it; I have, loved it, and want to see it again.  But not only was he not up for seeing Spiderman, but he wasn't even up.  He stole my nap idea, the bastard!  So...what else to do but start a new blog.  And digest three meat ravioli.  So tasty...yet so bad for me.   But lunch was very nice; with one of my favorite people, a friend and co-worker of mine.  She's a prime example of the bittersweet nature of working in a television newsroom.  Sweet girl, very nice, very fun, and very attractive.  It's horrible.  I'm her friend, and more than happy to be just her friend, but the little crush thing is always there, and may always be there.  Which is fine.  I just wish it went away.  She's currently dealing with a mutual friend of ours that couldn't let similar (yet stronger) feelings go away, and they ended up taking control of him...and now he just acts so idiot with anything related to her.  I never want that to happen to me, and don't think it will.  But yeah, there's tons of this sort of thing.  The vast majority of the girls in my newsroom are very good looking, and most are pretty nice, and all are  completely off limits --for a variety of reasons...the one constant being the fact  we're co-workers .  The problem compounds with the fact that these are the only people I hang out with...co-workers of mine.  I don't meet many other new people.  And I suck at meeting women at bars and shit, and asking for phone numbers.  I think it's awkward and degrading and sleazy--but these are all just excuses because I'm a pansy.  I wouldn't find it any of those things if I had the balls to be confident and go for it.    I went to a wedding this past weekend, and actually did meet a very cool girl and got her phone number...but she lives in Midland.  For those of you unfamiliar with West Texas (and for everybody's sakes I hope you all are) anything that is not in Lubbock is  way too far .  Might as well call though.  Like I said, she was cool.  But here's the thing.  I whine and bitch--but I don't know if I even want to get into anything while I'm here in Lubbock, because within a year I'm just going to be looking to move and I don't want to have that shit to go through again.  It's too fucking painful.    I'm glad that my first blog entry could be full of self-doubt and pouting.  Off to what I hope will be a very interesting experience for both me as the writer/gettin-shit-off-my-back-guy-because-i-woke-up-at-3:15am person...and you as the reader/passing-time-because-i'm-bored-as-hell person. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sometimes...I feel like I'm working during the weekend.&nbsp; There is something to be said about staying active on your days off, but I think I've taken that overboard the last few weekends.&nbsp; I've been going out like crazy, partying pretty hard...and just waking up and doing it all over again the next day.&nbsp; Last night was fun and pretty wild.&nbsp; Drinking and darts over at Erin's place...then some bowling (smoke-free bowling now the city non-smoking ordinance has kicked in)...and then out to the bar/club for some more drinking and dancing.&nbsp; It was a great time, even though the night ended kinda bad with not one girl (aside from my friends) wanting to dance with me.&nbsp; Stuck up I tell ya.&nbsp; I'm not a bad guy to dance with, but they want the sleazy, scary looking guy instead...ya know, the guy that just comes up from behind and grabs them and suddenly I guess their dancing.&nbsp; I don't want to be that guy.&nbsp; I just think I'm going to stop trying to dance with other people.&nbsp; I wish I didn't like to dance, or that I was just plain bad at it.&nbsp; It would make that decision a lot easier.  Well, I'm off again now...a co-worker of mine is moving to Albequerqe for a reporting job (her home town actually, it's a great move for her) and we just finished a pool party at her apartment complex in her honor.&nbsp; The one day we spend time in the pool, it's overcast and not one degree above 76.&nbsp; Oh well...it was fun.&nbsp; Now I'm gonna jump in the shower before running out to watch the Lonestars, our indoor football league team.&nbsp; They're fun games to watch.&nbsp; Then, it's back out to the bars, then maybe to a club....then definitely to bed.&nbsp; After all, I have a soccer game to play in tomorrow.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     An interesting column out of the International Herald Tribune...you can read it  urlLink HERE .&nbsp;&nbsp;It was written by a&nbsp;guy&nbsp;who works&nbsp;for the New York Times, and may have originally been published in the NYT.&nbsp; Who knows.&nbsp; Who&nbsp;cares.&nbsp; But the column comments on the manner in which the Republican Party consistently wheels out the Fear Machine whenever the Democrats have some big news to talk about--basically, oh yoo hoo!&nbsp; Over here please!&nbsp;&nbsp;We're not through yet!&nbsp; Not that--if the roles were reversed--the Democrats wouldn't do the exact same thing, because I think they could...and would.&nbsp; But the article is really a&nbsp;movie column, and he says that the new Manchurian Candidate is more&nbsp;partisan than Fahrenheit 9/11.&nbsp; I don't know how that's possible; in fact, I&nbsp;never even knew this&nbsp;was a left-leaning movie!&nbsp; Anyways, interesting article.&nbsp;&nbsp;I really suggest you give it a good read-through.  Posted by  urlLink Hello    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     I just got home from a softball game after working fourteen hours straight.&nbsp; I'm way too tired for extended pleasantries.&nbsp; But Bear--always on the lookout--wishes you a happy goodnight, and a sleep full of puppy dreams.   "Ruff! Rrrr Ruff!"  "What?! You know I don't speak Spanish!"  That's how I roll.&nbsp; Night.  Posted by  urlLink Hello    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink        I'm pretty sure  this is a man competing in the fast-paced and extremely popular olympic sport of Women's International Handball. If not...she must be an East German and this picture is from the '70s. Or she's Marian Jones' cousin...Marta.  Honestly, don't you just love the Olympics?&nbsp; Random sports that would shame a man to watch the other three years and eleven months...but for that magic time, that pommel horse is the coolest.&nbsp; Not to mention synchronized swimming.&nbsp; And that new thing, the one with the jumping and the ribbons.   This year's Olympics ,&nbsp;in the country that supposedly came up with the idea of the games 1.3 million years ago, and then  modernizing  them 29 years ago...should be the greatest.&nbsp; I mean, they are still finishing the stadium in Greece where they'll have the opening ceremonies...and people are saying it might not be completed by that time!&nbsp; I guess that's okay when you're Invesco Field at Mile High and a Jimmy Buffet concert is the first event to be held there...but didn't they build that stadium in Athens for this purpose above any other?&nbsp; Just three weeks ago they had just finished digging out the pool--THE OLYMPIC POOL.&nbsp; Jesus...is the construction company being run by Nia Vardalos' family?&nbsp; Are they sealing the new buildings' joints with Windex?   Then there's the  terrorism.&nbsp; The constant "terrorist threat" we are under.&nbsp; U.S. Special Forces are on their way to Greece; it was announced this morning.&nbsp; I'm telling you what's going to happen here.&nbsp; Everybody is going to be so concerned with the facilities and the terrorists running around and the drug scandals that we're going to forget that people are playing in such fine spectator sports as&nbsp;the one&nbsp;illustrated above.&nbsp; And you know something is going to go wrong.&nbsp; And I hope it doesn't.&nbsp; But if it does, this is how it's going to go down:   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   The Windex adhesive will finally give way, spilling scores of people out of a high grandstand and plunging them to their doom.&nbsp; Of course...the rushed construction and&nbsp; Windex won't be blamed--it'll be al Qaida--which of course means Iran in the eyes of our nation's leaders.&nbsp; U.S. Special Forces leave Greece, and head to the Middle East...where our undersized army(already&nbsp;split in two) now splits itself into three.&nbsp;&nbsp;Weapons of Mass Destruction aren't found--but mass graves from the early&nbsp;'90s are...and war is&nbsp;justified (despite the&nbsp;"Olympic Commission"&nbsp;publishing reports&nbsp;the 2004 catastrophe was in fact the fault of Windex and that Iran had nothing to do with the tragic events.)&nbsp; Al Franken writes a book called  I hate you&nbsp;Glass Cleaner. ..Rush Limbaugh responds on the radio&nbsp;by saying that Franken sniffs glass cleaner, and that he should be locked up for life because of it...all while chokin' down a couple more pain killers.&nbsp; Disney keeps Rush Limbaugh on the air on the numerous stations they own...but pulls&nbsp;financing from the latest Michael Moore movie about gay marriage because it's way too politically polarizing.&nbsp;&nbsp;Of course, during all of this Sean Hannity and Bill O'Reilly are just pointing and yelling...at who and about what really doesn't matter.  
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           My life is rated NC-17.   urlLink What is your life rated?   I just blame it on the unending drugs, alcohol and countless sexual partners...many of this--mind you--occuring&nbsp;at the same time in a vat of honey-mustard.   If you want to know what your life is rated...click on the question above.&nbsp; It's ten questions...so, it's gonna take you seven hours.&nbsp; (each question is a six point essay)    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Are people taking  this "girlie men" thing too far? Is it really offensive to women and homophobic? Maybe...I don't know. I'm just sick of every little thing getting blown out of proportion just for politics. All these democrats are crying foul in California right now--saying Arnold is homophobic, sexist (same ol' shite)--but how many of them do you actually think care that he called them that? I mean, are actually offended? I'd say hardly any. One, maybe two. But it's all about politics. Somebody says something remotely offensive and the other guys just run with it as if you just said we should kill all blacks and Jews. Remember when all that mess was being made about Kerry making anti-war speeches at the end of Vietnam? Since when is being against Vietnam something a person should be ashamed of?! That man was in the middle of hell--killing poor people and saving his friends--and now he's the one with the bad war record,&nbsp;while Bush--who actually HAS a horribly shady military "record"--is considered the one who's better suited to handle the military!&nbsp; (You know my politics, but I'd rather have somebody who knows the horrors of war--the true horrors of war--making decisions as to when to use the military).&nbsp; Anyways, back to the attack on Kerry for protesting Vietnam: It's the same thing as Arnold. Opponents take something you say and just run with it, using it as proof of some extreme that isn't justified. I don't know...but even though I do think AHNOLD may be sexist in someways, and most probably homophobic, people should also realize the phrase "girlie men" was used to satirize him on SNL, and reusing it during the non-stop game of calling out political enemies isn't the end of the world...or inherently wrong.  Posted by  urlLink Hello    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'm not always  down with Drudge...but I make a couple daily stops at the drudgereport.com. Well, this morning I was horrified to find  urlLink this .   I don't even know what to say about that, other than "geez, I'm sorry mister," and "that guy should be shot." I would think even crazy people would know to stay away from doing &nbsp;that .  &nbsp;   Looks like Lance  is going to run away with it--again--in France this year.&nbsp; Six straight, a feat never achieved in the Tour de France.&nbsp; Isn't it incredible?&nbsp; I've been following him on the OLN channel, and he's just a machine.&nbsp; A pure machine; he never shows emotion, pain, anything.&nbsp; He just gets this granite look on his face and keeps it there.&nbsp; I think about the pain he must be in while climbing&nbsp;the Alps for hours and hours, and it makes any type of sacrifice I've ever made--any kind of&nbsp;discomfort--seem like nothing.&nbsp; Then again, there's a reason he's won six straight.&nbsp; (and I sure pray it isn't doping!)&nbsp;  &nbsp;   Today's noon show  was one of the worst shows I've been a part of here in Texas.&nbsp; Everything was wrong.&nbsp; It just looked sloppy.&nbsp; We start off with me reading the three "headlines" to video--kinda&nbsp;a preview of some stories to come--and then I say about the last headline "that's our big story today at noon."&nbsp; At that point our "open" plays (voice guy: "you're watching KLBK-13 News at Noon, blah blah blah").&nbsp; At least, it's supposed to play.&nbsp; Today it was replaced by a commercial of some sort that played for about six seconds before HELLO, now I'm on air and trying to play it off like I'm smooth as butter.&nbsp; For some reason I did perform rather smooth.&nbsp; Oh, but then there was the teleprompter.&nbsp; The fucking guy--pardon my french--sucks ass at moving the teleprompter along as I read.&nbsp; I know for a fact he's just not paying attention and talking to his friends in the Master Control booth.&nbsp; It's so frustrating, and if you've ever seen an anchor without a prompter having to go off scripts, you know it just looks like shite.&nbsp; Then we killed a story in advance--my director told me in my ear this one story wasn't running--so I read ahead (from my scripts of course, not the prompter) to the next story.&nbsp; Apparently, noone told the tape guy we were cutting a story because he was lost--so we played one wrong tape...then had no video for the rest of the first news block.&nbsp; It was special.&nbsp; After that...the prompter continued to suck but I've gotten used to it.&nbsp; Mornings: good prompter.&nbsp; Most noon shows:&nbsp;I think a team of&nbsp;babboons must be running the prompter.&nbsp; Everything else went back to normal though...and we finished the newscast as well as we could.&nbsp; Had a good interview with a couple great youngsters who are doing a lot for their community--helping to organize a free sports camp for low-income kids.&nbsp; Oh, but then I start to read the "closing video" at the end of the show--you know, the funny video of the baby pandas or whatever.&nbsp; Well I start to read it, when my producer is yelling in my ear--NO NO NO.&nbsp; So I say, "well okay, I guess we don't have time&nbsp;for that."&nbsp; And we say goodbye.&nbsp; Awkwardly.&nbsp; It was horrible--we looked like frickin amateurs.&nbsp; That, and our competition had a live shot for the&nbsp;top story (the same top story that&nbsp;we had a basic soundbyte and no prompter for).&nbsp; We had&nbsp;our asses handed to us, and I don't like it.&nbsp;&nbsp;The one thing that keeps my shoe out of this computer monitor is knowing that we're better than them 85% of the time.&nbsp; Fuck their ratings and their boring on-air talent.&nbsp; And fuck whoevers fucking up my prompter.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;      
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey...had a good game tonight.&nbsp; We played this team that we tend to beat up on, but we still enjoy the fight--because it seems to always come close to somebody coming to blows.&nbsp; Our soccer team, Quien Sabe, won 8-1 or something like that.&nbsp; It was such a blowout, I even got a couple goals and should have had a third.&nbsp; I really enjoy playing soccer though with these guys--ditto the softball I play on Thursday nights.&nbsp; It's just nice to get out and get those competitive juices going again; not to mention my out of shape ass. &nbsp; These guys are cool though; most of them are a bit older and have families with kids.&nbsp; I hope (and expect) to be doing the same thing when I have a family someday...staying active with other guys playing soccer.&nbsp; After the games we "circle the wagons"...back our cars in (mostly pickup trucks around here) facing each other and sit on the tailgates drinking a couple beers.&nbsp; Actually, I hate driving a wagon for the obvious reasons...but the back acts as a nice seat in these circumstances.&nbsp; Useful thing after all. :) &nbsp; I'm off to bed.&nbsp;&nbsp;Colin might get less sleep than me tonight.&nbsp; He's got his last two finals in Germany tomorrow...and is waking up early to continue studying.&nbsp; I love that guy.&nbsp; He's the best.&nbsp; I can't imagine having a cooler brother;&nbsp;somebody I could be more proud of.&nbsp; He's really had a nice time out there in Germany and been productive...travelled and all that.&nbsp; But it'll be nice to have him back in the states.&nbsp; I'm hoping to get him down to Lubbock before&nbsp;his fall semester starts at CU.&nbsp; I believe it's his senior year, if you can believe that.&nbsp; We're closer in age than I ever realized...I think as the two of us get older it'll become more and more obvious. &nbsp; Okay, really...off to bed before I actually&nbsp;get  less &nbsp;sleep than Colin.&nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I gotta tell ya guys...being single sucks.&nbsp; My friends and I go out to the bar/club--which is the worst place ever to go if you're feeling alone and wishing you had some "female companionship."&nbsp; Girls here in Lubbock are really good looking...but I think they make themselves up more than girls in other places (which I don't really care about) and many of them have lots of family money.&nbsp; W's tax cut done their daddies well...yessum.&nbsp; Nice clothes, nice cars, fake breasts--you name it...there's lots of it here.&nbsp; But they're also not as nice as girls elsewhere, I think.&nbsp; Really snobbing, stuck up.&nbsp; More into being chased than actually having fun, having a chat, dancing, whatever.&nbsp; And then, when you think things are going decent...you're quickly reminded that you ain't shit.&nbsp; Last night had a good example of that.&nbsp; Finally got up some courage and started dancing with a girl...and shit she got going with me on the dance floor.&nbsp; Really attractive girl, too...in just about every physical way.&nbsp; Mind you, I hadn't talked to her...yet.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; But we danced for a few songs and then the DJ pulled out some shit beat, so we stopped.&nbsp; My buddy Justin was planning on having people over to his place afterwards for drinks, and I asked the girl if she and her couple friends wanted to join us.&nbsp; She said she was game, but was from out of town and needed to ask her friend.&nbsp; Well, I asked her friend...she was like, yeah that's sounds cool. &nbsp; Twenty seconds later the three girls leave the dance floor...fake like their going to the bathroom...and get the hell out of Dodge. &nbsp; Now...I'm certainly no Cassanova...and I know I'm not the hottest guy in the world--but I'm not bad either...and neither were some of the friends I was with.&nbsp; It's just this typical shit where girls will play games just to play them.&nbsp; All they had to do was say no, sorry...and I wouldn't have blamed them.&nbsp; They didn't know me.&nbsp; They didn't know my friends.&nbsp; But just so blatantly walking off...as they say on the way to Chicago:  BIAH, BIAAHHH !!!!! &nbsp;     &nbsp; It's now the following afternoon...I just got done losing some money in online poker--just a couple bucks...I don't play for much at all.&nbsp; And I've got this foggy head from last night and this general distate for my plight with "the ladies."&nbsp; Add to this:&nbsp; there's a really cool girl that I met at a wedding last week...25 years old, pretty, nice, funny...and we had a good time after the wedding going out with our friends and dancing.&nbsp; But she lives in Midland, about an hour and a half away.&nbsp; She gave me her number though and said to call her.&nbsp; That was last weekend.&nbsp; She was leaving the next day at some point.&nbsp; Rob was coming into town, and I called her that next day around noon to see--since she was heading out of town and who knows if I'd ever see her again--if I could by her lunch before she left.&nbsp; I got her answering machine and left a message...explaining why I broke the "don't call for  X  number of days"&nbsp;rule.&nbsp; Anyways...I left my number but said I'd be calling her sometime&nbsp;in&nbsp;the next week, yada yada.&nbsp; Well,&nbsp;my week was crazy...and I didn't want to call before Thursday since I'd called her Sunday.&nbsp; But Thursday is the most insane day ever (see earlier posts) and Friday was crazy also&nbsp;(after work...I went&nbsp;to be a "celebrity judge" at a homemade ice cream contest).&nbsp; So I called her yesterday and&nbsp;I got her machine again.&nbsp; I'm like, shit, do I leave a message?&nbsp; I do...saying I'll call back today...hope you're having a good weekend, etc. etc.&nbsp; But I'll call today and if I get her voice mail again (this is&nbsp;her cell phone, mind you) I'll just leave my number again and put the ball in her court.&nbsp; No need to keep calling and become&nbsp;"the weirdo."&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; I sound like a loser.&nbsp; Blah.&nbsp; I need to go see Anchorman today...that'll make me feel good.&nbsp; Ya know...some "afternoon delight."  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I, ROBOT.  Saw it last night.  I'd give it a C+/B-.  The first half of the movie was quite awful actually.  Will Smith was annoying me with the same old schtick he's done in his old movies--but I usually like his schtick!.  Even worse was Bridget Moynahan, who looked good but her character was just an abomination!  (again, first half of the movie...of course everything changes.)  The point of her character (aside from being pretty and eventually helping Will Smith fight the good fight) was to be more robotic than the robots--she literally speaks dialogue like a machine.  It was disgusting...I was thinking, "yeah...I get it.  They can be more real than us, okay.  Now stop annoying me!"  But the jokes were failing and the movie was creeping along.  Then things picked up--some very nice action sequences and cool CG.  The science was never that good, and constantly I was thinking "that would never happen--they would react differently" but all those things were able to be pushed to the side once the gettin' jiggy wit' it got underway.  Ends better than it starts.  See it if you must.  I'd rather have seen Spiderman 2 for the second time.  Now THAT is a summer movie.  Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I would never challenge this man to a thumb war.&nbsp; I would surely lose.&nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just watched John Edwards speak at the DNC.&nbsp; That guy is sharp; he's got a good future ahead of him in the Democratic Party, especially if he and Kerry can win the election.&nbsp; (we'll see about that.)&nbsp; I appreciated the fact he got into some specifics when talking about his and Kerry's domestic economic platform.&nbsp; Basically, they want to resume certain government-funded programs for the youth and under-priveledged that were closed by the current administration (such as the 3 million inner-city kids who lost after-school programs.)&nbsp;&nbsp;They will&nbsp;also give certain tax breaks/credits to different types of families in different situations.&nbsp; All this, plus making good health care affordable to just about everybody.&nbsp; The best part is how they will fund all of this, since...thanks to the current&nbsp;President (I want my cake and I want to eat it too)...our country is broke.&nbsp; Remember Bush's tax cut?&nbsp; The one where&nbsp;almost half the total money&nbsp;cut went to the richest two percent?&nbsp; Well...Kerry and Edwards are going to keep the tax cut--that is, they're going to let the bottom 98%&nbsp;keep their tax cut--and they'll roll back the cut given to that highest&nbsp;two percent.&nbsp;&nbsp;(I don't have the number...but it's a lot of money.)&nbsp; That's the main thing--there&nbsp;are some other measures like closing government loophole spending, and less money to the HMO's...and&nbsp;all that jib-jab I can pretend to understand but really do not.&nbsp; I also like the&nbsp;fact&nbsp;Kerry and Edwards will stop giving tax breaks to companies that take their jobs overseas...and will&nbsp;instead give those tax breaks to companies who keep their jobs here in America.&nbsp; I don't think outsourcing will be entirely all that bad&nbsp;in the long run for the international and domestic economy here in the U.S., but I certainly think&nbsp;jobs were outsourced faster&nbsp;and in greater number than they should have been...and millions of Americans have paid dearly for it.&nbsp; The new tax breaks should go a long ways to finding a proper balance.&nbsp;&nbsp;  Edwards did the standard "John Kerry: War Hero"&nbsp;bit tonight, which shouldn't surprise anyone.&nbsp; As John Stewart told Katie Couric on this morning's Today Show...he thinks Vietnam has been mentioned more in the past week than&nbsp;at Woodstock.&nbsp; (That's why he gets paid the big bucks.)&nbsp;&nbsp;But I&nbsp;certainly know why&nbsp;the Democrats are pushing the whole Kerry-volunteered-for-war-and-saved-lives thing.&nbsp;&nbsp;The majority of people polled say they think Bush is stronger on military-related issues...including Iraq and the&nbsp;war on terror.&nbsp; Considering&nbsp;al Qaida is as strong today as were before 9/11...and we went into Iraq prematurely for what turned&nbsp;out to be false reasons, I'd say Bush has a lower&nbsp;career batting average than any&nbsp;National&nbsp;League pitcher.&nbsp; Since Kerry hasn't been Commander-in-Chief before, I'd say it's kinda tough to say what kind of war president he'd be.&nbsp; But--especially after the current administration seemed so damn trigger happy--I do agree with&nbsp;the following&nbsp;point:&nbsp; John Kerry has been to war...he's been shot at, injured, and has probably killed another human.&nbsp; He's seen all the horrors that war provides, and&nbsp;knows that war can often&nbsp;end with little resolution...little gained.&nbsp; Therefore,&nbsp;he wouldn't be hesitant, but would be more likely to show proper&nbsp;restraint when facing a possible conflict.&nbsp; That's all I ask for...but I do ask for it.&nbsp; I know President Bush&nbsp;does what he thinks is right--but I think&nbsp;his view of the world is a bit too simplistic.&nbsp;&nbsp;Difficult problems, easy solutions.&nbsp; Not so.&nbsp; Kerry is so often viewed as a confused and two-sided&nbsp;flip-flopper.&nbsp; My first point would be this--if you look at any career politicians' (such as Kerry's) voting records over the decades, some things might come off looking contradictory.&nbsp; Some probably while others aren't.&nbsp; My other point--which really responds to the whole "I voted for the war before I voted against it" fiasco--is that his critics are trying to simplify this&nbsp;once again.&nbsp; I would hate to be a politician, because anything I did could be made to look a certain&nbsp;unflattering way.&nbsp; Kerry was going to vote to support the funding of the war...but on the condition that funds would come from a certain area (again, I think he wanted to use the rich's money but I'm not sure of the specific details).&nbsp; When it came out that the funds would come out of the general pocketbook of America...Kerry&nbsp;backed out like he said he would.&nbsp; But&nbsp;Kerry, who is very smart, gets himself into trouble by not making it simple.&nbsp; He needs to understand that he's running in a&nbsp;soundbite&nbsp;era--where they are going to take ten seconds and that's it.&nbsp;&nbsp;If he says "I voted for it before I voted against it" and then goes on in his speech to explain himself...well, tough.&nbsp; The networks (and&nbsp;the Republicans) are only going to acknowledge the soundbite...and Kerry needs to realize that.&nbsp; Now, he's the "policy-juggling fool who doesn't support our troops."&nbsp; I'm just rambling here...trying to&nbsp;get my own thoughts down so I can make better sense of all of this.&nbsp; Hopefully&nbsp;my writing hasn't been too confusing.&nbsp;   What's funny is I wasn't even going to mention&nbsp;Edwards (and, in turn, Kerry) that much tonight.&nbsp; I wanted to post about an article I read about blogging and bloggers&nbsp;on the ABC News website.&nbsp; It's really cool--you can&nbsp;skim through it  urlLink here .&nbsp;&nbsp;   I'm off to bed.&nbsp; Tomorrow is my typically tyranical Thursday.&nbsp; I'm actually going to interview John Edwards in the morning (no, I'm not kidding)...and putting the story together should take me&nbsp;well into&nbsp;late-afternoon/early-evening.&nbsp; Then it's off to softball, where I hope to play a bit better out in left field than I did last week (I didn't play bad--didn't make any errors--but I thought I should have gotten to a couple of balls I was a half-step away from).  As always, I wish you the best.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'll tell ya what.&nbsp; I give this place a lot of trouble sometimes, but I can see why a lot of families love living here in Lubbock...prefer raising kids here...etc.  This is a total "Evan moment" from people who know me.&nbsp; I couldn't find my wallet Tuesday morning on my way out the door to work.&nbsp; I was running behind (as I often am at 4:30am) so I didn't have the time to look through everything.&nbsp; But I was concerned.&nbsp; Later that day I give&nbsp;my place&nbsp;a good look-through again and couldn't find my wallet.&nbsp; For some reason, I didn't turn my room upside down as I should have.&nbsp; I've misplaced my wallet before though, and I just figured it would turn up.&nbsp; This morning, when I still couldn't find my wallet, I started to worry--but I thought back to Monday night...I had gone to see the Bourne Supremacy, and was wearing my adidas warm up pants that can lose things.&nbsp; Maybe I dropped it there.&nbsp; So I called them up this morning.&nbsp; They had my wallet in lost and found.&nbsp; And everything--EVERYTHING--was still in it.  I'm one lucky guy.  I wonder what the statistical chances are&nbsp;of getting back a wallet left in a theater with everything still inside.&nbsp; They can't be that good, can they?&nbsp; I had cash in there--not much but still--a VISA and my debit card from Wells Fargo.&nbsp; Maybe they are better than what we'd think.&nbsp; If I found a wallet with money and credit cards and an ID inside, I'd return it to Lost and Found.&nbsp; Would you?&nbsp; I'm betting just about everybody I know would do the right thing...plus there's something to be said for karma.&nbsp; I dunno...that'd make an interesting story for the news.&nbsp; Lose a bunch of shit and track it.&nbsp; See how many people do the right thing when they find it.&nbsp; Oh, wait...I'm on the news.&nbsp; Maybe I could bring that up sometime to Russ, my news director.&nbsp;   Anyways, the whole point is...I tip my hat to you Lubbock.&nbsp; There are good people here.&nbsp; I don't always see eye to eye with many of them regarding things bigger than probably any of us can fully understand...but these are people who are raised in Christian homes with Christian values.&nbsp; Good people.&nbsp; I'm not a Christian but I believe in most of those values, and&nbsp;when you act a fool and you're helped out...you're thankful.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Here is Woody Allen as sperm in "Everything You've Always Wanted to Know About Sex..."   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Smile...you're about to be embarrassed.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Once more.&nbsp; Sperm boy.&nbsp; For good measure.&nbsp;   For the real story about his NASA visit...and how Democrats aren't too happy about these pictures being "leaked," click  urlLink here .    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     It's the battle of giants. About to air in&nbsp;five minutes on FOX News (the only time they'll get my business).   Thanks to the beauty of the internet, and&nbsp;the fact that this is a taped&nbsp;exchange, I already have the&nbsp; urlLink transcript &nbsp;to read, thanks to the Drudge Report.&nbsp;   Here's the problem...everybody is working with different definitions.&nbsp; My position is this--Bush worked off bad intelligence; whether or not he knew it was bad is up for debate (although I am confident he was selective about which intelligence to make public when making his case for war.)&nbsp; I got in a really big argument with my roommate Matt about the following:&nbsp;he said that Bush is a good war president (and definitely better than Kerry) because he had to make the call, and ended up making a mistake (yet made the right call because he was protecting our oil interests...yada yada yada--I still can't believe Matt said the war was justified for oil).&nbsp; But I said even if he believed the intelligence, that Saddam Hussein had weapons of mass destruction, then he still is in the wrong because the most important thing for me was imminence.&nbsp; Was Saddam going to kill our babies at any time?&nbsp; Bush sure had a lot of Americans thinking he would (since, most Americans though Saddam partnered with Osama on 9/11).&nbsp; The truth is...Saddam was contained and had been contained for nearly a decade.&nbsp; The humanitarian reasoning for going to war is not good enough for me.&nbsp; Most of the ethnic genocide took place years ago.&nbsp; Besides, if we were to save all the peoples of the world from tyrannical and unfair rule, we'd be warring with a lot more countries in a lot poorer continents.&nbsp; But Bush wanted Iraq from the beginning--from the day he took office (people inside his cabinet have confirmed that)--and the post-9/11 climate was a perfect opportunity to make it happen.&nbsp; But we weren't in danger from Iraq.&nbsp; We were in danger from a group of people we had not yet caught in Afhanistan, and Pakistan.&nbsp; But that didn't matter to Bush, or his neo-cons.&nbsp; And now Americans are other people around the worl d are dying in Iraq, stuck in a pile of shit so deep we don't exactly know how to get out of it.  That's not the kind of war president I want.&nbsp; I want somebody who will show patience...and can weigh every factor and all intelligence before making a decision which will costs Americans (and the world) thousands of lives.&nbsp; It disgusts me that Bush's deeds haven't disgusted more Americans.  Okay...I'm gonna watch now.  Posted by  urlLink Hello    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here's another great link.  Apparently...Canadien visa officials must ensure foreign strippers are "quality" enough before being granted a work permit.&nbsp; The story  urlLink here .  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wasn't this a song?  Seriously, you have to read  urlLink THIS .  Sorry...but this thing had to be posted.&nbsp; Thanks to my buddy Geoff for the link.&nbsp; Now that's how you debate.   urlLink  &nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink       You obviously know  where I stand on the slippery slope of politics...but I have to say this--The Clintons rocked the house tonight at the Democratic National Convention.    Hillary was okay ; not as natural in her delivery (and Cosgrove has taught me a thing or two about conversational delivery) but still was saying some great things.    Former President Clinton  was unbelievable.&nbsp; With the stumbling and bumbling you see from politicians as of late...it's easy to forget just how powerful the man can be at the podium.&nbsp; His speech was brilliant, and I'm not overstating myself.&nbsp; Clinton worked the line between positive praise for Kerry and the Democratic Party and tough words for conservatives very well.&nbsp; Of course, his delivery was money throughout.&nbsp; I thought his best choice was to present the choices to the viewers--he'd say what Bush's policy is...and then say, hey if this is what you believe in then vote to re-elect...if not, then take a look at John Kerry.&nbsp; Said that similar sort of thing for a number of issues...and he was making a killing on it.&nbsp; Also had a powerful line about the type of brave, military leader Kerry is: (not verbatim)   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  "You know, during Vietnam many&nbsp;young men&nbsp;from well off, wealthy families could get out of going to Vietnam.&nbsp; Our current president&nbsp;chose to&nbsp;stay out of Vietnam...and so&nbsp;did I.&nbsp; John Kerry came from a priviledged background.&nbsp; If he wanted to...he could have stayed out of the war.&nbsp; But he said,&nbsp;"No.&nbsp; Send me."     It was skilled .&nbsp; Clinton is a genius, and a rock star.&nbsp; His speech was so good--I wish I would have never doubted him.&nbsp; (see prior post)&nbsp; Independents had to have been moved.&nbsp; Even Bear the Dog was moved.&nbsp; Moved to fall asleep on my bed (my pillow actually).&nbsp; Ewwww.&nbsp;   Posted by  urlLink Hello     
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink       Common sense prevailed  today at USA Today.&nbsp; I'm not one for censorship...but if you want to write for a publication like USA Today...your writing has to at least have some taste, and should stray from psychobabble as often as possible.   Check out the story  urlLink HERE.       Posted by  urlLink Hello      
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Blogging is getting some cred at the DNC!    Maybe there's a future in this!&nbsp; :)       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink       I won't give  the plot away in this post.&nbsp; I saw   The Bourne Supremacy   for the second time this evening.&nbsp; If I had to use one word to describe the fim, it would be "cool."&nbsp; Pretty much, if you liked the first one you'll really like this one.&nbsp; I'm just so sick of spy movies turning into these CGI cheese-fests (I'm talking about you, 007.)&nbsp; I agree that Pierce Brosnan has played a great James Bond...probably the best one aside from Mr. Connery.&nbsp; But the movies have gotten painful.&nbsp; Matt Damon is fantastic again in this episode as Jason Bourne.&nbsp; Seriously, this guy is good.&nbsp; Damon is one of those guys I would classify being a "man-crush."&nbsp; In other words...a guy that I know I would really want if I was a woman, or gay.&nbsp; Probably shouldn't have said that.&nbsp; But I&nbsp;seriously think this could be the signature role of Damon's career.&nbsp; He gets the character--the isolation, the emptiness, and yet his physical and intellectual dominance over every adversary is completely believable.&nbsp; I don't think many actors could pull it off like Damon does.    Kudos go to  new director Paul Greengrass ("Identity" director Doug Liman produced).&nbsp; Greengrass grew up on documentaries, and is best known (and admired) for 2002's Bloody Sunday--a docu-drama about the massacre U2 sang about.&nbsp; The action is streamlined, and cut quick--a few times too quick I'd say.&nbsp; He loves to use the hand-held camera (which I think was used to perfection in Michael Mann's The Insider, but that was a drama).&nbsp; Here, the action is frenetic, and the handheld quick-cut style adds&nbsp;attitude and pace, but can lead to some confusion in certain action sequences...especially ones dealing with hand to hand combat.&nbsp; Still...I'd take this exciting style of cinema over Chris Columbus' bland technique used in the first two Harry Potters.&nbsp; But even though, thanks to the quick editing, there are probably twice as many shots than in other thrillers of the same genre...I would argue that Greengrass does not waste one frame of film.&nbsp; Every shot means something.&nbsp;    If I had  to pick a favorite between Identity and Supremacy...I would probably go with Identity at this point.&nbsp; But it's tight...and could change in time.&nbsp; Both movies have great action sequences as well as some terrific exchanges in dialogue.&nbsp; Joan Allen is especially good in Supremacy--her scene on the cell phone with Bourne...all while he has her in his sniper rifle's sights...is fantastic.&nbsp; And thank god they finally did something with Julia Stiles.&nbsp; After the first one I wasn't just wondering why they cast her--I was wondering why her character was even in the film.&nbsp; It was that pointless to the plot.&nbsp; In Supremacy, she has a small but interesting part...and does quite well with it.&nbsp;    Pretty much everyone  knows these movies are based on a trilogy of novels.&nbsp; If Universal doesn't make a trilogy on film they're insane, and don't worry they will make the third one.&nbsp; But these movies haven't been sticking to books anyways...and now I'm wondering what dilemma will spark the third film's plot.&nbsp; I mean, how many times does Bourne have to run away from everybody for them to just leave him alone!&nbsp; That said...it looked like he did a good enough job after the first one...and this movie's storyline for bringing him back in was a good one; and quite clever.    Regardless of these  concerns...I'm definitely interested to see where Damon's Bourne character goes from here.    Posted by  urlLink Hello      
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Anyways...here's to  an exciting convention. And when I say exciting...I mean exciting some times, and painfull at other times. Because, as Ahnold would point out, this is nothing but a convention of Girly Men.  Posted by  urlLink Hello    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      It didn't work  then. Here's hoping it will work this year. I never know if having Clinton front and center is a good thing in regards to public opinion. To me, it's great. But people just can't get past that Lewinsky mess. I don't know...I tend to look at our nation's progress. When I do, he doesn't look too bad to me. Not at all.  Posted by  urlLink Hello    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink       Here's the title --fanboys, start the drumroll. Star Wars: Episode III-- Revenge of the Sith . I personally like the title; I think it works. Unfortunately, the movies (the newer trilogy) always are better in my mind than they are on the screen. I would definitely say Episode II improved over the crap that was The Phantom Menace...but really, we're still talking about movies that will never live up to the wonder of the original trilogy. There was a sense of magic in those movies that no amount of CGI can install in the newer additions. It had to do with the characters, and the stories. Lucas has lost whatever he once had. He can't write, and he sure can't direct. Most people don't know that he didn't direct Empire Strikes Back and Return of the Jedi. I wish he would have handed over the reigns on the prequel...handed over the actual teleplay...and just was there as a hands-on executive producer and story man. But hey, it's his baby; he should have the right to do as he please with it.   Now...if I sound like a nerd with all this talk (and I'm sure I do) then I want you to check out a link to some talkback from Aintitcoolnews.com.  urlLink CLICK HERE TO READ MUSINGS FROM MEN WITH WAY TOO MUCH TIME ON THEIR HANDS.    Check out the uber-dorks. While reading it, I was expecting Triumph the Insult Comic Dog to pop up out of nowhere. It would have been better with him there.   Posted by  urlLink Hello         
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      We had some  big news hit last night/this morning, making for a very interesting and hectic morning show. If you're curious, check em out at my station's website:  urlLink KLBK13.TV .   The bad thing  about the news business is this--our most exciting days are the same days other people are suffering. It can make you step back at times. But it's my job to tell the story...and interesting, hard-hitting stories like these are what journalists like myself look forward to covering.   The first paragraph  online for the robbery/murder story was written by me for the noon show...just before I tossed it out to a reporter going live from the 7-11 where the clerk was killed. (shot through the neck).   Off the record : just last week we did a story on the insane amount of armed robberies we have been seeing here in town, and the police told our reporter it was non-story and they didn't have time to talk to us about something so inconsequential. They sound pretty stupid now. It was only a matter of time before one of these robberies ended badly.   And hey, check  out the motorcycle death story. Yesterday, we thought this guy simply crashed his bike and died. Turns out, the autopsy says he was shot in the chest, and that's why he crashed his bike. This world is crazy. Even in Lubbock, Texas.    That link again  to the stories  urlLink here . (Note...this is the website's home news page--might have to search if you are going to the link a good while after I've posted this.)  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ya know...I rant and rave so much on here about politics. I realize that I spend most my time spreading the good gospel of the democrats. Well, this evening I thought I'd give someone else a shot. Here's the latest column from Ann Coulter. Read on, and learn the ways of the right.    The traditional greeting at the Democratic National Convention is, "Where do you teach?" On rare occasions, the greeting is modified to, "Where does your husband teach?" or "Where does your gay lover teach?" (Democrats could save a lot of money by holding the Democratic National Convention and the National Education Association Convention at the same time.)The Democrats keep loudly proclaiming that Republicans represent only extremely white rich people, while the Democrats represent all Americans. (Bar bet: Among the four major candidates for president and vice president this year, who has the smallest net worth? Answer: George Bush.)If the Democrats are a fair cross-section of America, then I guess we can stop worrying about class size. As a friend of mine points out, if the Democratic delegates represent America, then the teacher-student ratio in this country is, at worst, one teacher for every three students. And since the teachers unions don't include private or parochial school teachers, we're looking at a teacher-student ratio of about one teacher for every one student.  Democrats are representative of the nation only if the nation we're talking about is Brazil. For Democrats, there is only the maid and millionaires. There are no Americans in the middle. To the extent Democrats are forced to recognize working-class white men, they call them "fascists."To thunderous applause here in the American Taliban, billionaire Teresa Heinz Kerry said she looks forward to a day when "women who have earned the right to be opinionated will be called smart and informed -- just as men are." It's no wonder Democrats weren't interested in liberating Afghanistan and Iraq from woman-hating Islamicist fanatics: They think real oppression of women consists of people calling Teresa "opinionated" right here in the USA.How did Teresa "earn" the right to be opinionated again? By marrying inherited wealth? She also boasted that the Heinz family charity, John Kerry, "earned his medals the old-fashioned way." A couple of sponges on another man's wealth might want to steer clear of using the word "earn" so much. Democrats don't believe in capitalism and don't worry about taxes on earned income because they can't imagine there is any way to "earn" money other than the Teresa Heinz-John Kerry way.          Despite colossal efforts by the Democrats to fake out Americans and pretend the Democrats are normal Americans who love their country, every once in a while they make a mistake and give us a "tell." The Democrats have carefully studied Americans, observed their habits and expressions, so you would think for five days the Democrats could pull off a passable impression. Special-effects artists are working overtime. Gore was prohibited from screeching about Republicans being Nazis, and Clinton was told not to show up in a toga. Democrats unable to conceal their America-hating pacifism were relieved of their anti-war signs and escorted to the free-speech veal pens a few blocks from the convention center.Convention organizers even forced the delegates to choke their way through the Pledge of Allegiance -- something the teachers' students are not allowed to say. The delegates play along, pretending they know the words and making the occasional random reference to "God," trying not to sound ironic. But, inevitably, they stumble, dogs start growling, and you realize these people are androids.          In a prepared speech carefully reviewed by the Democrats' Americanization team, Jimmy Carter said: "After 9/11, America stood proud." Proud? I believe "proud" was the last emotion most Americans were feeling after 9/11, coming in considerably behind, for example, "fighting mad," "incensed," "enraged," "humiliated" and "vengeful." It didn't occur to any of the Democrats vetting Carter's speech to cut that line? "What's the matter, Prince? Why are you growling? That's just a moderate Democrat."          Even as Democrats ape Republicans -- producing a platform that lyingly claims Democrats support war with Iraq, the Patriot Act and the defense of America -- the fundamental difference between Republicans and Democrats can't help slipping out: Democrats are not angry about 9/11. Sad, maybe -- sad that it didn't happen on Clinton's watch so his legacy would be more than a semen stain. But they're not angry. Indeed, the belle of the ball at the convention is noted patriot Michael Moore, who apparently thinks Americans who voted for George Bush deserved to be killed on 9/11. The day of the attack, Moore wrote this on his Web page: "Many families have been devastated tonight. This is just not right. They did not deserve to die. If someone did this to get back at Bush, then they did so by killing thousands of people who DID NOT VOTE for him! Boston, New York, D.C. and the planes' destination of California -- these were places that voted AGAINST Bush!" Perhaps Moore could provide the terrorists with a map of the red states before the next attack.          This week, Moore was boasting about how well-received he was by the Democrats in Boston -- evidenced by his yukking it up in a sky box with former president Jimmy Carter. He has been hugged by DNC chairman Terry McAuliffe and praised by impeached former president Bill Clinton.Moore's only concession to the Democrats' role-playing is to deny that he is a Democrat, hoping enough Americans were taught by public school teachers that no one will know how to look up Moore's voter registration card. ("Democrat.")          Moore says Bush must be defeated because Bush lied about the war in Iraq. Ninety-three percent of the delegates agree with him, saying they oppose the war in Iraq, according to a New York Times/CBS News poll.But the Democrats' candidates for president and vice president both voted for war with Iraq. Their party platform supports the war with Iraq. (Let's just hope wherever the delegates teach, they're not teaching logic.)          The only "issues" Democrats dare discuss publicly are the things everyone can agree on: They are for "jobs," a good economy and the middle class. None of their blather ever touches on any issue on which Democrats and Republicans could possibly disagree.The issues on which the parties differ are: pre-emptive attacks on terror-producing nations, gay marriage, gun control, partial-birth abortion, taxes, letting non-citizens and felons vote. But the Democrats won't talk about those issues. This is the Democrats' week to make-believe they are Republicans for the folks watching at home on TV. In the lingo of the delegates, this is "story time."        I won't even get into with her tonight. I'm tired. You should feel lucky.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Believe it or  not...I went on a date tonight with a 26-year-old high school English teacher. It was pretty much a blind date--the girl is a good friend of a co-worker of mine...and said I had to meet her. So I did. Went to Chili's, then for some drinks. It was a really nice time.   Who knows if  this will lead anywhere. To be honest, I don't know if she's that interested in me. But I'm not worried; it was nice to get out on a date. It's been a long, long time.   Anywho...I try  not to write to much about my love life (or lack thereof)...because someday I'm going to start dating somebody...and that person is going to want to read my blog...and I'll have some comments on there about her I wouldn't want her to see. So, sorry about being so vague, but I think it's a necessity.   What I will  say. I'm headed to Oregon this Thursday morning for the entire weekend, but I'm looking forward to hanging out with her again next week.   And I think  the fact she's a teacher is kind of hot. Wouldn't you?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I am stupid.   It's pretty much as clear as that.  I consider myself to be a successful person, but time and time again I'm reminded that it's all blind luck.  Yeah...that's it.   I am lucky.   I just left my wallet at a public place for the second time in less than two weeks.  You remember my praising of the people of Lubbock (Lubbockites?  Lubbockians?  Lubbeeks?) after my wallet was turned into the movie theater with everything intact.  Last night...with three beers in my belly and apparently existing three sheets to the wind (I drank with the guys after the soccer game)...I stopped at Walmart to get what else but laundry hampers and bathroom cleaning products.  (It's a typical stop for 10:30 at night.)  I was still in my t-shirt and soccer shorts, so I had no pockets and kept my keys and my wallet in the tray of the shopping cart.  When I unloaded the shopping cart into my car in the parking lot--I failed to remove my wallet...and replaced the cart (like a good citizen) into the cart replacement thingy with the wallet still there.  I realize my folly this morning before work...but ALAS, the Walmart parking lot attendant...the cart boy...found my wallet and returned it to lost and found with everything.  still. inside.  Wonders never cease.  How can I be so careless, stupid--and yet so lucky all at the same time.  And again, West Texas has surprised me.  I tip my glass to you, Lubbock.  And then I throw the contents of the glass in my own face for being a fucking idiot.   Off to bed .  I hope you enjoy laughing at my expense.  I deserve it.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Saw the movie  last night in a packed theater. This isn't an easy one to discuss for two reasons. The first, because it's difficult to talk about the film without talking about its plot (something you probably don't know much about because of the secrecy surrounding it). I'll do my best to write in generalities; no spoilers here. But The Village is also difficult to discuss because I don't really know how I feel about it. The most basic thing I can say about Shyamalan's latest is that I'm dissapointed in it. But how dissapointed...now that's the tricky part.   I want to  love this movie. I consider The Sixth Sense and Signs to be two of the better examples of movie storytelling in the past ten years. I like the fact that M. Night takes him time with his plot, and doesn't feel the need to give you all the details. He crafts his stories slowly, patiently, and I think it makes for smart filmaking. This time around, however, I think he went too far with the slow, deliberate pace. The movie feels held up from the slow, emotionless dialogue. The cast speaks in this proper Elizabethan dialect, and it's fine...but I never was sure it was entirely convincing. And I'll make this point--when the dialogue seems hollow, and the characters therefore passive--then the trademark "frights" are somewhat lessened.   It is scary  at times...and Shyamalan, who has always been a master at creating a "gives-me-the-whilies" scene, pulls off some pretty creepy shit. The "creatures" are certainly effective, and the use of sound and camera work add to the mood. There are a couple scenes in particular that produced some good screams from the audience. Still...I wasn't as consistently frightened this first time around in the theater as I was watching The Sixth Sense and Signs. Both those movies had me terrified pretty much throughout. Yeah, I know. I'm a wuss. Maybe one of the reasons it wasn't as scary is because people were wondering if they were even real from the beginning. I mean, this is a Shyamalan movie, and the audience is pretty much waiting for a twist. Figment of the imagination? An actual alien race living in the woods? Something else? I won't give anything away. But in The Sixth Sense and Signs, the scary baddies were ghosts and aliens, respectively, and those are both things that people are familiar with, maybe had bad dreams about, and can--in turn--be pretty frightening. Unknown creatures are scary, but I tend to be more scared about things I've always been scared of.   There are some  great scenes, and some great performances. I love Joaquin Phoenix; he was fantastic in Signs and is quite good here, as well. I really believed in his character, as a young man who pretty much doesn't know what fear is. The standout was a newcomer...Ron Howard's daughter, Bryce Dallas Howard. She didn't even have to audition for her role (Ivy, a young blind woman with a can-do attitude). Shyamalan saw her in a play on Broadway and offered it to her right after that. She's awesome in the movie. Awesome. I didn't like Adrien Brody's character, but I understand he's key to the plot. He plays this mentally challenged young man who's in love with Ivy--problem is, Joaquin's character, Lucius, is quietly in love with her too. I thought Brody's character was distracting, especially in the frightening scenes. Here everybody is...quiet, petrified, wimpering...waiting for the creatures to approach their houses--and here's Brody, clapping and laughing. "They're coming! They're coming!" A tad distracting.   When all is  said and done...I thought the movie improved as it went along. It started off slow, and I didn't feel completely into it until the first "invasion" scene (which was scary). The movie says a lot about people--as usual, Shyamalan is not simply out for screams, he wants to say something in his movie. Everybody has secrets...that's the thing you know from the beginning, but don't get to figure out what it is until later. It's tense, it's moody...but some might say it's a bit boring.   But as the  final word, I will say this: nobody I saw it with saw the twist coming. And that's pretty impressive...since everybody is waiting for the twist to come. In fact, it pretty much turns the movie from a C to a B-minus. Not bad, but definitely somewhat of a dissapointment considering Shyamalan's past work.  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        So many benefits  to an extended weekend. A just ended a fantastic four days in the Oregon countryside, where I attended my uncle's first wedding and spent some quality time with family. It was, in fact, the first time my immediate family (mom, dad, brother and myself) were all together since we made a trip to Ireland more than a year ago. Not just that--it was  eight  years since I last saw my uncle and others from my father's side of the family. The last time, I was in Oregon for my Grandmother's memorial service. I was fifteen. I think back to then, and the changes I've undergone since, and it's tough to even gauge them without becoming bewildered to some point. I barely recognized some of these people--and I'm sure some of them barely recognized me. But they're family, and in almost no time we were all comfortable around each other once again, as if we'd always kept in touch. That's a great thing about family, and old friends. It might be awkward to re-start a relationship, but it certainly is possible...and rewarding. Now, I have invites to stay at homes in Seattle (I'd love to) and southern Iowa (well...if I'm passing by). Of course, I extended the offer of a warm futon or couch in the South Plains of West Texas...but unless one of my relatives is making a drug run through Lubbock south to Mexico (not  completely  unrealistic), I think it'll have to be an Oregon reunion or nothing at all.   It was great  to hang out with Colin. We get along so easily; our personalities are slight extensions of one another's...and our senses of humor are pretty much identical. I don't think it'll ever get old to recite quotes from movies from our childhood. That is, I can listen to him do his Ah-nold impression for a lifetime and it would never get old. (That, and the Mama Fratelli from The Goonies....) Anyways, Colin and I spent the majority of Friday and Saturday in the Roaring River behind the homes of our relatives, trout fishing. It was a damn good time. It's a small river, but with some nice holes to hit if you can get your lure into them. I love fishing streams because it's a challenge. There is a purpose to every cast. You just aren't chucking it out into a lake with bait and a bobber. You find what hole you want to hit...cast just upstream of that spot...let the current take the lure past it...then slowly bring the spinner back through the hole, hopefully where a hungry fish awaits. I had a great Friday...caught ten fish. Best outing in years, actually. Naturally, the biggest was maybe nine inches--and in comparison to the others--she was a whopper! But, you catch em and you let em go. Hopefully they'll grow up to be bigger fish for future brothers to find on a sunny Oregon summer day.   Colin took tons  of digital pictures of fishing, the wedding, and general highjinks...but he won't be able to get them to me until he moves up to Boulder in a couple weeks. When I see them, the blog will see them. I look forward to sharing them with whoevers interested.   In the meantime ...I'm trying to figure out why my computer won't let me save pictures online in J-Peg format. I can't post them on my blog (to my knowledge) unless they are in that specific format. Bitmaps not allowed. When I figure it out, I'll jazz the blog back up with some visual delights. :)   The downside to  the extended weekend? I missed opening night of Collateral--my must-see movie of the summer. If you read  urlLink Derek's blog , you might have already read what he thought of the movie. Sounds like a real winner. And, yeah, I'm telling everybody right now...Michael Mann is possibly the most skilled filmmaker I know of (I'm talking both technically and in how he tells a story through characters). If you've seen Heat, The Insider, Manhunter, The Last of the Mohicans and others you know what I'm talking about. I'll see the movie tomorrow, and will post my thoughts. The other movies I want to see, after Collateral (now showing here in Lubbock):  1. Napoleon Dynamite 2. The Clearing 3. I'm Not Scared 4. The Manchurian Candidate 5. De-Lovely 6. Harold &amp; Kumar Go to White Castle 7. Anchorman (for the 4th time) 8. Anchorman (5th time) 9. Anchorman (6th time) --seriously, the thing gets better with each viewing. the first half is comedy genius. Then...we have a whole new batch of movies coming out--including the surely-bad yet oh-so-nerd-appealing Alien vs. Predator. We'll see.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Don't get me  wrong. I love me some Krispy Kreme. Few things are better than a glazed donut from the Double-K when it's fresh out of the oven. But what I don't like, are little bastards dressing up as Krispy Kreme workers in a sad attempt to be interviewed on the noon show.   These two kids ...probably 19 tops...come in this morning as I'm about to leave on a mid-morning break. They show up in the newsroom and say they're going to be interviewed on the noon show because it's the first day of public school around here, and they were passing out donuts to kids in celebration or whatever. But when they told my bosses all this--it sounded more like gibberish and less like the English language. So they call me back in, tell me two young men are in the newsroom...and were nervous and didn't know what questions I was going to ask in the interview and therefore came in early. Way early.   I'm thinking, okay , shit, fine, I'll be right there--I hadn't even gotten out of the parking lot yet. So I come in, tell them I didn't have them down in my calendar for an interview today (Monday and Wednesday afternoons are reserved for the Animal Shelter to bring in stray cats and dogs) and ask them who they talked to. More gibberish--"I think it started with an 'S'," genius number one says. "I didn't write anything down." You little idiots. So I think that maybe they got confused, and were supposed to be on our competition's show on NBC. So, for the first time ever, I call over there and ask. Nope, was the unenthusiastic answer. Okay, so what gives with these guys. So my bosses are in my news directors office, and call me in and we shut the door. He says to tell them to get lost, that we can set something up some other time. Then we say, hey, let's call Krispy Kreme. The manager there doesn't seem to know about any young employees telling a tv news show about how they handed out free donuts to kids. So I go back out, tell the kids hey sorry but we can't put you on. But before you leave, what's your guys' names and your boss' name. I write it down...and as they're walking out I call up Krispy Kreme again. The guy says nobody by the three names I got even works there (and it's the only one in town). I hang up and run outside--alas, they had fled.   Damn little bastards . Don't fuck with KLBK-13. We'll eat your children.  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink        Well isn't this  nice.  I just wrote a long post, explaining why in the world I have a picture of girls getting off a spaceship with this guy in a tin-foil suit helping them on my blog.  And it didn't go through or something.  So here I am, pouting and refusing to re-write it.  But here's the gist.   I'm going to  kill myself because I've just added to my already insane schedule.  I get up at 3:30am, try to get to bed between 8 and 9pm...and now I have joined the cast of a musical called "Pageant" (a scene from another theater's production of the show pictured above)--which should be fun and great and rewarding but will require three hours a night (7-10pm) for the next month or so.  Then, it'll be performances on the weekends for the next six weeks.  It's a great show, and my part--a cheesy emcee of a second-rate beauty pageant--is fantastic (not to mention not much of a stretch for me to play.  Should be a good time.   But the schedule  I have created for myself is crazy.  I need to be sleeping right now, and not poorly re-writing posts I've already done.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink        This could be  the movie of the summer for us young ones. It's getting good reviews across the board--check out rottentomatoes.com if you don't believe me, you untrusting jerk. Zach Braff--that dude from Scrubs who wrote, directed, produced and starred in this movie--said noone has made  the  movie about what it's like to be a twenty-something these days...when you realize that growing up and independent is inevitable (or something like that). Apparently, this movie addresses some of those themes, and is pretty funny and touching in the process. I look forward to its arrival in The Hub City.  Oh, and if you want to read a really cool, funny blog--check out the one Zach Braff's been doing for the past couple months while promoting his first movie.  It's really cool.   urlLink Click here and bookmark it!    Sorry about not  posting for awhile. Things have gotten crazy for me. I'll post why shortly. Right now I'm at work, delaying...working. shit, phone call. be right back. Wow...okay, that was cool. This guy just called me up, saying I interviewed his wife for a local museum on our noon show--and she was really nervous but I calmed her down and treated her well...yada yada. (what do these people expect? that I'll eat their first born?) But he said he had a tip for me, that at 7:05am tomorrow morning the International Space Station will go from one horizon to the other horizon in exactly ten minutes and 10 seconds...and will be visible for 9 minutes, 59 seconds. Those people at NASA are exact! So...cool, I can mention that at the end of our broadcast tomorrow (it ends at 7am.) Perfect.   Oh, about the  title and the "movie lull." There are some great movies out right now in theaters--Garden State is not here in Lubbock quite yet. But Napoleon Dynamite and some others (I listed a few I want to see in a prior post) look pretty good. But for some reason I haven't gone to see them. Haven't felt motivated--it's weird. I do want to see Collateral again as well. I never got around to writing a review--but I'll say this: Michael Mann is a master. Great performances from Tom and Jamie. Damn fine movie. I'd certainly say that Collateral is Mann's most accesible movie to a wide audience since The Last of the Mohicans...meaning I think just about everybody could like it. It's not as slow and brooding (art-housey) as The Insider or Ali. Obviously...there's a lot more action in this than those previous two films. Okay...it's time to work. 54 minutes exactly until I'm on air for the noon show. Wish me luck. I have some good posts to make later in the day.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>