<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I landed another one today :). They are so hard. And I was doing some tight boardslides. I can't wait until I get a camcorder. At GameStop at the mall today, I found a PS2 controller that plugs into a PC's USB port that I wanted to get... to play my GTA and THPS games with. I'm broke, so I have to wait until I get my allowance on Thursday. Well, that's it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Weird News   urlLink 1337   Damn it, I stayed up late again, I'm out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just remembered something. Kevin only called  once  all day! I wonder if he's alright? Usually I get 5-10 calls a day from him  at least ! I'm going to his house tomorrow to see if he's ok. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wish I could do a kickflip and catch it high in the air every time. I can kickflip most of the time, if I'm going slow, and I don't catch it until it hits the ground. I need to practice and hopefully I'll get better. Once I am an expert at kickflips, I'm moving on to backside flips (which I can rarely do, but fakie, which is easier). Damn skating is hard work.  I just got done playing Counter-Strike. I pwned so many noobs on it (go to  urlLink Pwned.nl  if you think I'm a retard)! Actually, I'm the one that got killed the most—95% of the people that play have no life outside of CS, so they are  experts . It pisses me off. Even when I join a "newbie" server, I get tons of pros waiting to shoot me in the head once I turn a corner. Oh well, I quit. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Skatepark again today... yay. I tried to rock-to-fakie in the medium bowl at the skatepark (4 feet maybe) and I fell on my right hip—the same one I have been falling on for the past month! Damn it hurt like hell. I could barely walk, but I was still trying tricks in the bowls and grinding ledges. Luckily, I didn't fall on it again lol. I probably would have broken my hip. I was happy today because Kevin didn't come with us to the skatepark, just Me, Scott, and Alec. Kevin likes to brag a little too much.  Before I went to the skatepark I went to the Dollar Store with Scott, Alec, and Kevin to buy some candles to use as curb wax. We waxed up a curb at Schweitzer Elementary and tried to grind it. We could all grind it except Kevin—he weighs too much. If he went on a diet he would be able to grind better. After the wax wasn't working very good, we brought a metal bar from Alec's house and set it on the curb and we just grinded on that. It worked a  lot  better. We called it a curb condom. I can't wait to use Alec's condom again tomorrow - lol. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Finally I escaped from my boredom :). Here's how:  Ok, yesterday I  was  bored. I skated all day again and ended up spending the night at Matt's house. It wasn't so boring once I got to his house—we watched Along Came Polly and 50 First Dates. That second was was actually kind of sad, but they were both funny and good.  Today I went to the book store on the way to the doctor (for my Dad) and bought a copy of PC World, which I forgot to subscribe to many times before. Then I went to the skatepark ( yay ). I learn something new every time I go there. I can't wait until I get a good job and I live alone—then my parents won't bitch about how I always want to go places. I could just drive myself and some friends up to the skatepark everyday, bitch-free! Oh well, that's probably gonna be at least six years away.  Well, it's about time to go play Counter-Strike and kill some team members! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         This is just a quiz I took and I thought I would post it here. Go ahead and take it if you want.   &nbsp;  I took the  urlLink Blogging Personality Quiz  at  urlLink About Web logs  and I am...    The Daily Grinder    I love blogging because it's like therapy. I can write about anything and everything that happens to me - from the food I ate to what I was doing when I heard the latest 'breaking news'. Being able to communicate with my friends (online and/or real life) through my blog is important to me.   
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       WARNING: Do not read this or you will become a victim of boredom!! Ok read it if you want, whatever.   Today... hmm... Oh yeah, first thing in the morning, I woke up and Scott (my brother) and Scott Belt (my brother's friend down the street) were swimming in my pool. I  hate  swimming. I don't know why, it just sucks. My parents think I'm weird because of that. My parents also say I'm lazy when I sit on my ass all day on my computer, when that's all they do every day. Ok, back to my day. When I saw them swimming I decided to go to Kevin's house to skate. That was pretty boring. We raised one end of his rail to make it really high. I left his house after I was bored to death and went home. I sat down and read my TransWorld Skateboarding magazine and after a while I ate dinner. Then I went to the school to skate with Alec. There's nothing to skate at the school, so that's another thing that sucked. Then I went home and here I am. I'm gonna play THUG later, I'm starting to get back into it.  Saturday I want to go to the skatepark. One of my friends that I haven't seen in a while is gonna be there. Damn it, I wish I owned a skatepark! That would kick more ass than anything else! I could skate it for free and invite friends, and I could make money by charging other people to use it. I'll probably just get one put in my backyard when I have my own house, if I ever have the money (not sure how much it would cost).  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       All I did today was eat and sleep. Nobody was home, except Matt, and he's not very fun to skate with cuz he kinda sucks at it. I was going to go to the skatepark, but I couldn't because my parents cooked chicken and rice, and I  had  to stay home to eat that! Damn it was good, lol. So Matt came over and I tried to get him to boardslide, but he couldn't and I don't even think he really tried.  Scott and Kevin got into another fight today. Scott won ten dollars in a bet with Kevin and Kevin said he wouldn't give it to Scott. Then Scott started making fun of Kevin for being fat and Kevin made fun of Scott for being gay (which he isn't). That's all they do to each other when they're mad, and I always laugh at them, lol. So when Kevin invited me to the skatepark, he didn't want Scott to come, just to make him even madder.  I really want to go back to the skatepark - I think I'm obsessed. Next time I go there, I'm gonna ask how old I have to be to work there and if they will hire me. It would  kick ass  to work there! You get to skate there for free and you get paid for it! The only thing you have to do is watch other people and make sure they paid to get in, and you have to get help if someone gets hurt. That's basically no work, because people rarely get hurt there. If I can't get a job there, I'm gonna try to get one at Pac Sun at the mall or Gamestop with Alec, but I think you have to be 16 to work at those places. I'll have to wait two years since I'm only 14 but oh well.  I guess that's all I have to say for now. Wow, I wrote a lot compared to my other tiny posts! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been thinking about playing THUG again, after my 6 month break, but I'm too lazy to go turn on my PS2. According to GameFAQs.com, THUG 2 is released on October 5, and I can't wait! Right now I'm at the Hall of Fame at Lineage ( urlLink click here ), and there are some sweet vids there. It makes me wanna go play and make my own video. I just don't wanna get up... Screw it! I'm gonna play!  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yep, all I did today was skateboard. I went to the skatepark for the first session (12:00-4:30), came home and ate, went to Matt's house to skate, and finally came home and skated some more. At the skatepark I learned to air out of the quarter pipe and I ollied a table (about 6-7 decks high) off a ramp. It surprised my brother and Kevin cuz I was getting so damn high. Yeah, it was fun but now my feet hurt. I'm gonna go rest. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Haha I'm goin to the skatepark tomorrow! Wait, no it's today cuz I stayed up past midnight. Shit, I need to sleep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Me, Scott, and Kevin rode our bikes to 7-11 to get some slurpees, and since Kevin is so fat and he loves food, he bought two taquitos. We got home and started skating my rail and Kevin got bored. Scott and Kevin started making fun of each other and finally Kevin left. Only 10 minutes later, Kevin called back asking if Scott wanted to skate with him, proving that he doesn't have any other friends besides me and Scott. What a loser. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yep, I just got home from the skatepark a few hours ago. I went with Alec and Kevin. As usual, Kevin lied about some tricks he could do. Here is a list of things he said he did but he lied about:&nbsp;     Spine transfer from the big bowl to the medium one (there is a small, medium, and big one)  Ollie into the small bowl  Rock to Fakie in the medium bowl  Tail stall in the medium bowl  Ollie a cone (about 4-5 decks high) off a ramp   Yep, he's full of shit alright. He just lies about stuff so he doesn't sound like he sucks (which he does, really bad).  When I was at the skatepark, I saw one of my friends from school (name is Jordan). He was at someone's graduation but he got bored and came into the skatepark to skate with me and it was pretty fun. I'm going up there with him again next Saturday. Well that's about all&nbsp;I have to say now. I just drank a cup of cappucino so I'll be staying up late tonight.    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here are some funny websites I have found. I'm posting them here to share them and so I don't forget about them. Leave a comment if you have some you want me to add. &nbsp;  urlLink AlbinoBlackSheep.com   urlLink EbaumsWorld.com   urlLink Entensity.net   urlLink FunnyJunk.com   urlLink HappyTreeFriends.com   urlLink HomestarRunner.com   urlLink JoeCartoon.com   urlLink Pwned.nl   urlLink SomethingAwful.com   urlLink Stickdeath.com   urlLink UrbanDictionary.com   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here's a pretty weird game I found a while ago. I haven't played it but it sounds really dumb.  urlLink Boboboubo Boubobo - Game Info - GameFAQs  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was so awesome at Cedar Point! My best friend Matt couldn't go because he got grounded for getting his dad's cell phone stolen and broken :(. But instead I went with my brother Scott and Matt's brother Kyle. We went on almost every ride. I wanted to ride the Dragster (400 feet tall) but it was closed down because it broke and injured 4 people. lol. I don't care, though, if it was open I would still ride it. So now the only two rides I haven't been on at Cedar Point are the Dragster and the Power Tower. My favorite is the Millenium Force cuz you go so fast and it's so smooth. It's  really  fun but the line is  always  at least an hour long, which sucks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was going to one of my "friend"s houses with my brother to go skate. His name is Kevin and he's dumb. The only reason I wanted to go over there is to grind his rail and jump his ramp. When we got there, we rang the doorbell over 10 times before he finally answered. Then he said he couldn't do anything because his mom wasn't home, and he walked into his neighbor's house (probably to play video games). I guess he just didn't want to play with us. Just for that, when I get back I'm gonna tell him how much fun I had at Cedar Point without him. :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My parents overreact every time we go on vacation. When we leave the house, it has to be  spotless . All day today and most of yesterday they had me cleaning so we can go to Cedar Point. About a month ago before I went to Florida, we cleaned the house for almost a week straight. Oh well, it will be worth it once we get there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is another test using the button on the Google Toolbar. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just started this whole thing, so I'm just testing it out now. I'm going to Cedar Point tomorrow so I'll write when I get back. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Mozilla Firefox  beats any other browser out there. I just got it today and it is great.  Also, the Google desktop search is awesome. You have a search box on your taskbar and you can do a Google search without even opening your browser.  urlLink Click here  to get it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Haha I just made an avatar to go with my sig, yay! Here is both the sig and avatar next to each other:       Doesn't it look sexy? I got the skater from this screenshot (forgot the website):     
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I decided that I would put my Photoshop CS to use and make a signature that I can use at forums (thpsforums.com mainly). It is my first one ever, and personally I think it kicks ass. Anyways, here it is:     Hope you like it! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Entensity.net - hmmm...   Go there, it's a great site! I go there every day, he posts funny and weird stuff (not appropriate for kids). He usually posts every weekday, but he has been working on a new layout, so sometimes he doesn't have time. Anyways, just thought I would let you know. GO THERE! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finally found out what the VIS and RAD thingies do, and now I have to figure out where to put all my lights and stuff like that. Before I was compiling without VIS and RAD and the lighting was the same everywhere, and I wondered why my lights didn't affect anything, lol. Ok, so it's late, I'll work out the whole lighting thing tomorrow and finally (maybe) I'll be 100% finished on my first map. Okie Dokie cya bye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is the first time I went to the skatepark without Scott. It made me happy :). Actually I didn't care. He has to go to a gay hockey school tomorrow, which wastes his life a lot. Anyways, Scott went with Matt up to Wayne High, and I went to the skatepark with Kevin. This time Kevin only made up  one lie ! I should congratulate him for that! Well, I'm getting a lot better at my 180s. Yep, I'm getting better and better at everything every time I go there. I did a fakie noseslide on accident lol. I was trying to fakie boardslide but messed up. Oh well I'm gonna play Counter-Strike y'all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, Matt came over at about 1:00 and we skated for 3 hours and then we went to 7-11. He came home with me and came in my house and played Counter-Strike with us. He never played it before and he said it was fun so he's prolly gonna buy it. Then we skated even longer at the school until about 7:30. So Matt followed me everywhere all day, which got pretty annoying and boring. I told him he should leave when my parents left for the airport (Mom's goin to Las Vegas) but dumbass Scott said it was alright for him to stay, RUINING MY PLAN!! Dumbass. Oh well, it was still kinda fun.  I also finished my hoverboard_wars map for CS, but I might need to add a few more things later. And I don't have anywhere to upload it, so I can't share it with anybody. That was the only map I worked on today. I played another fun map, cs_bikini. It's a beach with a tennis court, pool, and a house. It's really good and someone must have spent about a month on it.  Fuck it, I'm tired, see ya. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, the past few days I have been playing a lot of Counter-Strike, so I thought, why not make my own maps? So I downloaded Valve Hammer and Wally (for making textures) and I started two maps. It is a lot easier than I thought it would be, and it's a lot of fun. I am making a space station map and a hoverboard wars map. When I am done, I will upload them if I can find some web space. So yeah, I'll be working on those for a long time. I played CS a lot with Alec, but he went on vacation two days ago and won't be back until next Monday. I told him I would have a good map done by the time he gets home.  Also, I downloaded two maps, de_wallmart, and de_desktop from  urlLink RedSquall , and they are  very  good. De_wallmart is an exact replica of a Wallmart store, including the parking lot and bathrooms and everything else that is in the real store. De_desktop is the dude's computer desktop. You can climb into his computer or around the books and boxes and climb wires... all kinds of shit. Very good maps. He has a lot more at his site, I'll check them out later today when it's not before 3:00 AM. lol.  Another thing...  urlLink NewGrounds.com . It's a good site that I just recently signed up for that shows Flash movies and games. There are a few CS movies that I saw today,  urlLink here is the latest and best one . You can click on the guy's profile to see the rest. His first video was made when he was 12! And it didn't suck. He is 15 now and he has made the best Flash videos I have seen in my life. I hope he makes more!  Oh, and one last thing. Matt's party is in like 4 or 5 days! They already tore down both neighbors' fences so they can use those yards during the party. It's gonna be a  huge ass  party! His parents invited about 100 people, his sister invited about 300 and Matt invited around 20, lol. Anyways, it's gonna be fun as hell and I can't wait.  And finally,  one last thing . I'm goin' to sleep cuz I'm about to pass out. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>