<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a Taylor Lithium 7000 at WalMart for $21.  It's digital, which is nice.  It seems kind of weird, to not watch the hand spin around on the dial.  But it's nice to have no guesswork.         
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so far today, i've got 2352 steps.  not too shabby, really.    I'll go down later and walk around the plaza or something.  And after work, I'm going to have to go somewhere to get milk & coffee.  I haven't decided if it'll be Wal*Mart (more walking, shop for scale!) or just a regular grocery store (more expensive, less annoying).  Then I really should go for a real walk, outside, in my neighborhood.  It's nice weather these days, there are constantly people out doing fitness type things in my neighborhood, and really - I should just do it.  Be Nike and stuff.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .5 liter bottles  II  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      chef salad with honey mustard dressing (this is from the cafeteria - it's a smallish-medium salad)  fruit salad cup (also smallish-medium)  water    I feel so much better for having this, instead of some bready sandwich or something.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seriously.  I think that might be how I gained 3lbs overnight.  I used to know a girl who claimed that she'd get the mighty bloat from eating too many carbs.  And yesterday was sure full of carbs.      I think that one of the key things that I need to do in this quest is limit my carb intake.  I know that sounds like so much trendy bullshit, but I'm not talking about going on some sort of atkins crusade.  I'm talking about not having carbs as my main food source anymore.  Yesterday I had carbs at every meal, and then more later on that night just because I was still hungry.  At dinner I had three potatoes.  (Granted, one was medium and the other two were small, so it was the equivalent of 2 potatoes.  But that is still a lot.)    It's simple, really, and I know this to be true.  I feel better when I eat veggies instead of potatoes or rice or whatever.  I end the meal feeling good, not full and lethargic.      Sometimes those potatoes are so fuckin good tho.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1 english muffin  cashew butter  apricot spread  coffee, usual ingredients    1 vitamin tab  3 fiber tabs  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      scale still sucks.    I'm feeling really sucky over the waffles last night.  I think I should be stronger or something.      Well.  I need to stop haranguing myself over it and just get more active.  The problem here is only partially what I eat.  The bigger problem is that I'm not active enough.      Eat less, move more.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had waffles.  For dessert, I guess.      This type of thing is why I weigh 242#.  I know this, but I tell you now those waffles were fucking good.      Before the waffles I was hungry.  After the waffles I was not.        So at least it wasn't some  oh, woe is me, i'm so fucking fat i'll just eat a big pile of cheetos  thing.    It wasn't a binge.  I was just still hungry.  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dinner is a heap o home fries (i know.) and 2 emeril chicken & apple sausages. I know that it's not exactly diet food, but I'm starving, it's already owned and these might just be the best damn home fries I've ever made. (I seasoned them with Lawry's, black pepper (from the tin) and salt-free fajita seasoning, then fried them in a little bit of peanut oil.)    well, fuckdiddly.  i'm still hungry.      erf.  I don't know what's going on this week - I'm not about to start my period or anything.  FEH! 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      big scoop steamed rice  tiny egg roll (spring roll?)  apx 1.5 c. thai cashew chicken (cabbage, carrots, sprouts, some other veggies, lean chicken, cashews)  drink: water  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .5 liter bottles  IIII    I'm thirsty today, for some reason. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My pedometer readings are going to be off kilter today. When I got to the office, I checked it and it said 77 steps. This is close to 90% lower than the usual reading for this time of day.     ah, well.      Final reading: 4700 steps.  Add in the steps that didn't get counted today, and it looks like I've done about my avearage.  Which I need to double to lose any weight.   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1 english muffin, toasted  1 morningstar farms veggie breakfast pattie  1 slice colby jack, from the block  smear apricot whole fruit spread    ~6 oz orange juice  coffee (irish creme flavored beans)  2 tsp sugar  prob. 1/2 c. 2% milk    vitamin!  fiber tabs!    (can't forget again.)  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really hate my scale.  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2 emeril's chicken & apple sausages  1/2 - 1 cup shells &amp; cheese  1/2 cup mustard greens      (cooking time snack: 6 black olives, 2 slices colby jack from block)    dessert:   handful frozen blueberries  1/2 c. fat free french vanilla yogurt  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      4 fresh veggie spring rolls (uncooked wonton wrapper, lettuce, bean sprouts, carrots, cilantro, mint)  ~1 tbsp peanut dipping sauce  bizarre but delicious Thai dessert - sweetened rice milk, honeydew, cantaloupe, mango (papaya?), fresh sweet corn, water chestnuts  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      shameful.  3 slices domino's pizza.      aka, flavored bread.    I hate domino's.  I forgot my lunch, tho, and I'm flat broke.  This was from the Journal Club luncheon, so it was free to me.      also, water.  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      once again, measured in .5 litter increments  IIII 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got my pedometer clipped to my panties again. It's this skirt - it just won't hold it up because the waist is too big on me.     So far, I've got 1151 steps.  Not too bad, I guess.      final count: 5011      i'll get busy bumping that up on a day that is not monday. 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1 small pig in a blanket (I wanted a ham & cheese croissant, but the donut shop was out of them.  I would like to note that I did not fall prey to the siren call of the apple fritters.  They looked damn good too.)    coffee - usual ingredients    I keep forgetting my fiber & vitamin tablets.  I'm not quite sure what to do about that yet.  : 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the weekend wasn't as damaging as I thought it'd be.&nbsp; That's way cool.&nbsp; I really wasn't all that bad, in retrospect.&nbsp; No alcohol, one partial soda, lots of steak with mac & cheese and that's about it.&nbsp; The rest of it was pretty much in line with what I've been eating during the week.  onward & upward!&nbsp;   er, downward... 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not weighing on the weekends.  I'm taking the weekend off.  hee.      John's coming over, and he said he'd bring me shipley's donuts.  This is a rare treat - there are no Shipley's around here, and I'm a Shipley's girl.      I'm kind of hoping that we can head over to the Caribbean place for lunch.  I'm pretty sure that they have all you can eat Friday & Saturday lunch.  At the very least, they've got cheap jerk chicken.    So far today, I've had two cups of coffee.  I slept in, so that was nice.   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Around 3:30 or so, I had a loaded baked potato at Anderson's. It had cheese, margarine, sour cream, green onions, yellow onions, bacon bits and it was absolutely delicious. Decadent, but delicious.    I'm hungry now, and what I really want is nachos. That is not overly diet-friendly. I'm going to grill a chicken breast on the foreman the top it with a bit of colby jack and some tomato. Maybe some salsa. Maybe some black olives. Then I'll put some chips on the side. This is still not the most balanced meal - I need more veggies - but it's better than the craving I've got, and I think it'll be a reasonable facsimile of nachos.    (I usually do a pile of chips, a pile of chicken, black olives, TONS of cheese, guac, sour cream, tomato and maybe lettuce.)    Diets tend to fall apart on me during the weekend anyway. I'll try to do right, but I'm not going to stress myself out about it either. It'll still work, in the long run. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so far (12:20pm) I've taken 1759 steps, according to my new pedometer.      This does not include the walk from my apartment to the car, which was typically 75 steps or so with the bitch pedometer.      This is making me wonder if the stupid bitch pedometer has been resetting itself all along and I just didn't know it. I tended to put that thing on in the morning and then pretty much leave it alone for the greater part of the day. Maybe check in once or twice with it. Not eagle-eye or anything.     Because, see, the only thing that I've done here that is differen than any other day is take the stairs instead of the elevator. But I've got drastically more steps than I used to. Maybe two flights of stairs really does make all the difference, but it seems unreasonable.     Ok.  I just got home from work, it's 7:09 pm, and I am not walking any more today.  I took 6437 steps today, and I stood out in the Dallas heat for over 2 hours handing out tickets for a bbq sandwich and a glass of iced tea.  Then we moved inside and stood just inside the door for another hour.  My feet hurt, my back hurts, and I am tired tired tired.  And sort of regretting turning down the offer to take an extra sammich home. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My whole eating schedule today is going to be kind of screwy, due to the Semi-Monthly TGIF BBQ Extravaganza the grad school is hosting.  Our office is co-sponsoring it, so I need to go over to hand out food & drink tickets and make nice with everyone.  Everyone's meeting over there around 3 - we'll eat first then get set up for the (cough*ahem*cough) nerd brigade.  (shhh.  don't tell them i said that...)    So, I'm having a salad now to tide me over till 3pm, when I'll actually eat.  This is really a pretty good thing, because I forgot to pack a lunch today.  (der.)    So, anyway.  Right now, I'm having a small Caesar salad.  Only, instead of Caesar dressing, I'm using honey mustard.  It's got a little less fat, and I love it.  Later on, about 3pm, I'll have either a bbq sandwich or a loaded baked potato.  I'm leaning towards potato at this point, but we'll see.   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      again, measured in .5 liter bottles  III    I get a new bottle every day, and then fill it up from the big Ozarka cooler in our office. I'm not throwing out all of these bottles... unless I actually put my mouth on them. I drink from a coffee mug, so I'm only using the bottle for measurement purposes. This way I don't get any mouth-germs on the Ozarka cooler.     that would be grody. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1 english muffin  1 morningstar farms veggie breakfast patty  1 slice colby jack, from the block  smear of apricot all-fruit spread  coffee (with chicory!)   ~2tsp sugar  ~apx 1/2 c. milk (2%)      
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This seems to be going rather quickly.  I did take a water pill yesterday, because my feet were swollen (again) but still.  I'm sure it's water weight, but it kind of freaks me out and thrills me at the same time that I've lost 4 pounds this week.  Not even this week, per se, but just since Tuesday.      Of course, I was still drinking sodas then, and salty snacks were not out of the question.  (Hello, Cheetos, my old friend...)    I'm just going to keep doing what I'm doing, and counting my steps and see how it all pans out.    Today I'm trying my new pedometer.  When I first put it on, I had 3 steps almost immediately, before I even finished getting dressed.  When I got to my car, I had 4 steps.  This could be a problem.  I think that the problem was that I didn't have it on my pants right, and it had flopped over so that it was sitting horizontally.  It really needs to be vertical to actually count anything, so I reset it and we'll see how it goes.      So far, I've got 826, so I guess it's going ok.  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2199 + 1278 + 3736 = 7213  Is it really possible that I've walked more than twice as far today as I did yesterday?&nbsp;   Yeah, maybe...  I'm kinda tired.&nbsp; And I did take the stairs a lot today.&nbsp; And I went to Wal*Mart again.&nbsp;   So...&nbsp; maybe.  Then again, with that bitch pedometer, who the hell knows. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a new pedometer!   Wal*Mart had the $4 one in stock, and it's the one that does steps & distance but not calories.&nbsp; YAY!&nbsp;   I will report back tomorrow with news of suckage.&nbsp; (or lack thereof.)   Oh, and it's a really ugly putty gray.&nbsp; The $8 one is transparent blue, which is kind of cool.&nbsp; It does distance, steps and calories.&nbsp; The $12 one talks.&nbsp; So, the stuff that I remembered from last night (and posted about at length below) was pretty much all wrong.&nbsp; heh.  The one that I got does not flip open, which was a bit of a deterrent to me.&nbsp; I didn't want the reset button to be exposed.&nbsp; But then again, the one that is a bitch flips open, so the reset button is presumably protected.&nbsp; So hopefully this will be ok. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      has reset again.  Now I'm at 213.      2199 after lunch  1278 after walking around D building  213 now    2199 + 1278 + 213 = 3690.  Not too shabby, really.     I'm so buying the new one tonight.      Stupid.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. I am going to buy a new pedometer tonight.  Screw that waiting till payday bullshit.  This bitch has reset itself for the last time.      2. Yeah, I get that I just totally tempted the Pedometer Furies or whatever with #1, but really.  I have a hammer.  This can all be resolved.    3. I'm abandoning this cockamamie one post per day bs too.  It's confusing and annoying.  Plus, I realized that blogger puts the date at the top as a header then puts all the posts for that day under it.  That's a hell of a lot better than my way, I tell you now.    4. What the fuck was I thinking with that cinnamon roll?  Now I've got goddamn indigestion.      shit.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      they are calling my name.      crap.    i'm going to eat 1/2 a cinnamon roll.  they're small.  it'll all still be ok.    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The pedometer already says 903 steps.  I don't know how this is possible, as at this time yesterday I only had 533.  I did take the stairs down from the parking garage (3 floors), and I've been downstairs once today to use the restroom.  But still.  I'm not going to argue with it or anything, I'll take the steps it gives me & all.  I'm definitely buying a more reliable pedometer, tho.  I just don't trust this thing anymore.    To that end, I've checked REI (online), Wal*Mart,  Target and ebay.  Ebay seems the worst idea - I tend to use it as a tool to get an idea of what brands are available.  It's senseless to pay $5 shipping on something like this - I want to do my research online then go buy in person.      Both Wal*Mart and Target sell Sportline pedometers.  They are packaged as Sportline at Wal*Mart and as ProSpirit at Target.  (Flip it over, and it says ProSpirit made for Target by Sportline or some such. )  The same models are selling for about $4 more at Target, so they're out.  I'll go to Wal*Mart and get the same thing for less.  (Between the pedometer and the coffee maker, I'll save about $10-20 by going to Wal*Mart.  I'll brave the teeming hordes for that much money on two items.)  Plus, I'd rather have it say Sportline than stupid target brand ProSpirit.  It's a brand prejudice - I've always thought of ProSpirit as cheap & crappy.  Nevermind that I'd never heard of Sportline before yesterday.      The cheapest model that Wal*Mart sells is $4.83, and it was (of course) sold out.  I have no idea what sort of features it has or anything.  The next step up is the Sportline 330.  ($8 at WM, $12 at Target)  It looks pretty simple - it claims to be perfect for 10,000 step/day programs, which is essentially what I'm doing.    Then comes the Sportline 345 or 349 (I really should have taken notes.) ($12 at WM, $16 or $18 at Target.)  It has more features, calorie counter, etc.  Calorie counting sort of discourages me.  It seems like it takes way WAY too long to burn them so I wind up giving up on the whole thing.  It's a perverse psychological thing with me, so I'll probably be best not knowing this type of info.    Target has a light-up pedometer for either $16 or $18 (it was on two racks, and they seemed to have the same description on the price hangers.)  Light-up is neat and all, but I can't imagine where/when I'll be walking in total darkness and still AB!SO!LUTELY! need to know how many steps I've taken right then.  I mean, sometimes I like to open it up, just to see, but really.  I'll have to stew on this a little more, but I really don't think that a nifty light is worth an extra $10 or so.    The talking pedometers are too obnoxious for me.  I don't want some thing that hangs on my belly and talks.  The clicking is bad enough.  I try to draw attention *away* from that area, not  to  it.    REI sells a Freestyle Tracer pedometer that was (according to their site) recently rated the #1 pedometer by the Wall Street Journal.  It's $25 and if I can find it cheaper somewhere else, I might consider it.  It does have a calorie counter, though, and I'm not thrilled with that.      You know, at this point, I'll probably be better off with one of the Sportlines from Wal*Mart.  If I decide that I want to upgrade to a fancier pedometer that has distance, calories, etc then I can do that later.      The irony of all of this is that I'll likely do all this research then pick my pedometer based on the color available at the store when I'm ready to buy.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that I should add a better scale to next month's shopping list too.   Breakfast:  2 eggo waffles  2 pats butter  2 tbsp eggo lite syrup  apx 1/4 c. raw slivered almonds coffee, usual ingredients   lunch:  Commerce Street (Roast beef, cream cheese, lettuce, tomato, sweet onion, horse radish mayo, wheat bread)  1 bag Zapp's Sour Cream & Creole Onion chips (12g fat, 220 calories)  water  (At least i did not succumb to the unholy love of the Street's Club. It's huge. Also, my cookie was not only chocolate chip, it was crispy. So I tossed it.)   snack:  one whole small cinnamon roll. thank the sweet zombie jebus, the rest of them are gone.   dinner:  3 soft chicken tacos, made at home  ~3 flour tortillas (small)  ~1 chicken breast (seasoned with garlic salt &amp; salt-free fajita seasoning)  ~sprinkling of shredded colby jack (on each taco)  ~1 whole avocado (divided between the three tacos)  ~2 tomatoes (also divided)  This really would have tasted better with corn tortillas, but I wanted flour this time, for whatever reason.&nbsp; Next time I'll do corn.   water (.5 liters again):   IIII  II   activity:  walking, again. maybe pushups  as of 1:44 pm, I've taken 2129 steps today. This includes many trips down the stairs rather than using the elevator. I'm less disciplined regarding taking the stairs *up*, however.  In penance for the cinnamon roll, I decided to take a walk. I checked the pedometer (219?) and took the stairs down to one (I'm on 5) only to discover that I was locked in (thank god the building is not on fire). I then went back up the stairs to 2 and used the restroom. While in the restroom, I double-checked my pedometer. The bitch said 490. V. frustrating. Then, I rode the elevator down to one. Picked up some checks and walked up to the D building and made the big circuit around all the lecture halls and past the cafeteria. I then rode the elevator up to my floor, partially because I don't want to be sweaty and partially because you can't get into the stairwell from one, which is BOUND to violate some fire code somewhere. Now the pedometer says 1278, the stupid bitch.   I'm buying a new pedometer tonight, dammit.     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I know I said I was going to weigh once a week.  I don't wanna.    I'm going to edit this throughout the day; I want to do one entry per day - it seems cleaner that way.    I don't know if I want to attribute the 2 pounds to my crappy scale or the fact that I was up at least 3-4 times last night to take a massive leak.     I'm going to call it water weight.  That's better than scale anomaly.   Breakfast:  english muffin, toasted  2 slices ham (40 calories)  1 slice colby jack, from the block (110 calories/ounce - I have no idea how much this weighed)  coffee  ~1.5 tsp sugar  ~1/2 cup milk   Lunch:  leftover beef with string beans & fried rice (there's probably about 1.5 - 2 cups of this)  the other half of the blueberries & yogurt from last night (1/2 cup)   Snack:  1 golden delicious apple  2 oz cashew butter   Dinner  2 Emeril chicken & apple sausages cooked in water then browned &amp; served with mustard  a small serving of green beans with about 1/2 a pat of butter.   water, tracked via .5 liter bottles  IIII  Other than the coffee this morning, I had water all day.   Today I'm wearing my McDonald's stepometer.  I'm going to try to do this every day.  I think it'll help me walk more.  The catch is to actually remember to put it on.  I think that when I take it off, from now on I'll put it directly in my purse, so that I'll have it with me the next morning without actually having to remember it.  So far, I've gone 533 steps.  That is not much.   DOOD!  I just checked my stepometer while I was in the bathroom, and it showed that I've taken 63 steps.  I don't know how it got reset - you have to open it to do that, and the button's even kind of hard to press.  This is very frustrating.  And it had to be reset - there's no way that I've run it back to zero - the thing's got five digits!    I'm probably going to look into getting a new pedometer.  Never trust anything from McDonald's.   ok.  After work, I went to walmart and target to look at coffee makers and pedometers (walmart won, but I'm going to just add it to next month's shopping list.) so that's my activity for the night.  It's like discount-style mallwalking.    The pedometer says 1915, so I'm going to assume that the goofy thing only reset once and just add the two counts together to get my daily step count.  I dunno what else to do at this point.  SO.  1915 + 533 = 2448 steps.   According to the stepometer owner's guide, 10,000 steps equals about 5 miles.  So I've walked about 1.25 miles today.  Not great, but better than I thought it'd be.     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      goddamn.  &nbsp;  I've gained 4 lbs since I weighed last.&nbsp; That was several months ago....&nbsp; probably March or April.&nbsp; In fact, it was April.&nbsp; It was when I went to the doctor and found out I had IBS.&nbsp; Just after John's birthday extravaganza at Hooter's.&nbsp; (Hooter's is no longer my friend, btw.)  &nbsp;  Can we call this breakup weight?&nbsp; Or, vacation + breakup weight?  &nbsp;  Anyway.  &nbsp;  This really has to change.&nbsp; I'm reaching the range where I'm eligible for thumbstomach.  &nbsp;  I think that what I'll do here is list my weight weekly, and list my food &amp; activity daily.&nbsp; Or something like that.&nbsp;&nbsp; So....  &nbsp;  Breakfast:  2 eggo waffles  real butter  eggo lite syrup  coffee w/1.5 tsp sugar and 2% milk that I didn't measure.  &nbsp;  Lunch:  veal piccata with a side of spaghetti &amp; marinara  greek salad with tomato vinaigrette  2 incredibly decadent garlic butter rolls  (it was free!)  water  &nbsp;  Dinner:  ramen soup (I appreciate the irony here.) to which I added:  green beans  edamame  baby brussel sprouts  brocolli florets  1 smallish chicken breast  some soy sauce (to get this much stuff in there, it takes a lot of water, which makes it really bland.)  sriracha   and, um, gas-x for dessert.&nbsp; heh.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp; ok, dessert was actually a handful of frozen blueberries topped with fat free stonyfield farms yogurt in french&nbsp;vanilla.&nbsp; it was super yum.&nbsp; and healthy!&nbsp; yay! &nbsp;  Activity:  hm.&nbsp; I did some extra walking today due to WIPS lunch, and I took the stairs up to my car after work.&nbsp; When I got home, I did 10 girly pushups.&nbsp; This made my knees and elbows hurt, and it proved to me that it really is past time I vacuum.  &nbsp;  I also went to the library and picked up five more books, which will not really up the not-sitting-on-my-ass quotient.&nbsp;     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Just maybe. &nbsp; We'll see how far I get on this thing.&nbsp; While I fully want to be thin again, I know myself well enough to realize that this is an uphill battle, in a big way.&nbsp;  &nbsp; My, how the puns just roll out of me. &nbsp; All I know is that the image of me that lives in my head is not compatible with the image of me that I see in pictures and mirrors.&nbsp;  &nbsp; This will not do. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Breakfast: 1 english muffin 1 oz cream cheese apricot spread on both sides (unmeasured) 2 cups coffee, usual ingredients  1 vitamin 2 fiber tabs 1 antibiotic (evil, i tell you.  evil.) lots of water  Lunch will be tuna salad on crackers.  Dinner will probably be leftover meatloaf.  I hope it does not suck.  heh. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      breakfast was kind of meh.   1/2 english muffin ~.5oz peanut butter smear apricot spread coffee, 1.5 tsp sugar + whole milk (I had to buy milk at the gas station, and the 2% was expiring soon)  also 1 vitamin 2 fiber tabs 1 clindamycin water  and once i got to the office, 2 tylenol and more water.  oi.  lunch today will probably be bbq - i'm broke and i've got a coupon for 2 free lunches.  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had a boatload of water today.  .5 liter bottles  IIII  II  yesterday's water, that i forgot to post about: 24 oz bottles IIII 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY!!!  I didn't go for a walk as planned.  I was all set to, but when I got home there was a flyer on my door saying that the apartment complex was having Renewal Day.  So I went up there to sign my new lease (and popped a balloon and got a free water bill!  yay!)  Then I went to the library and got more books, and found out that they have EXTENDED the summer reading club through the 20th!  I'm not too late to turn it in after all!  More YAY!   It was a pretty good night.  :)  Also, when I got home from all that, I made meatloaf and a baked potato.  The meatloaf had poblano instead of bell pepper, and it rocked.  (It could have used a little more ketchup tho.)  Now, I'm just waiting for my antibiotic to time out (can't lay down for 30 minutes after taking it) so that I can go to bed.    Good day. 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weather is beautiful today - which is bizarre for August in Texas.  I went downstairs and took a walk and it was just lovely.  20 minutes, ~2900 steps and I feel so much better for it.  I went across the plaza, past the student union and police station, by the physical plant building, down to the student garage, past the bird sanctuary (yick) then through the staff garage, the faculty garage and back across the plaza to my office.  I'll need to take another walk tonight, in order to make my >7500 step goal.  The forecasted low is 65*.  God, I love a cool front. :) 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to get better about writing down *everything* that I eat.   late morning snack: handful of pretzels.  I really should have counted these before I ate them.  I bought them yesterday at the student store - 3.5 oz bag of rolled gold classic style thins - 110 calories per 1oz serving, 3.5 servings per bag.  I ate some yesterday, some just now, and I can probably get another couple snacks out of this bag.  This was probably close to an ounce, I dunno.  Either way, not too much of a diet buster or anything.  (It's the sodium that'll get me.)  For my afternoon snack, I brought an apple with ~2oz almond butter.  yumtastic. 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Joy.   Breakfast: just over 1c cereal (frosted flakes with 1/3 less sugar) 1.25c 2% 1 banana coffee, usual ingredients (i could only drink 1/2 of it tho)  1 vitamin 2 fiber tabs 1 zyrtec 1 clindomycin lotta water  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More than any other day since I've started this.  And a fair number of them were stairs.  YAY!  I didn't go for a formal walk tonight.  I did go to walmart, though.  Rotisserie chicken for dinner (with the leftovers made into a fabulous chicken salad for tomorrow's lunch) (I also had some salad, which was sub-par) and I got the stuff to make meatloaf tomorrow night.  I just could not bear the thought of walmart and cooking dinner all in one night.  I love to cook - that is not it at all - I just would have wound up eating at 9 or 9:30, and that is too late for me.  My new goal is to get into the 230s during the month of August.  I'm flirting with it - 241.5 a couple days ago is nearly there!  But I want to get firmly into the 230s with no more forays >240.  I can do it.  My plan to make this happen mostly includes walking more.  I'm so out of shape (one of my doctors called it deconditioned) that this is about all I really want to attempt at this point.  If I try to get all radical, and make myself hurt, I'll stop doing anythng.  I know this from past experience.  Anyway - I'm going to shoot for >7500 steps/day.   I can do this! 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided that I had to get out of my office for a while, and a cool front came through town earlier.  So, I went downstairs and did a 15 minute walk.  I'm a little sweaty now, but I feel much better.  I got about 1900 steps in, so that is good news.   It's a beautiful day.  And I got a compliment on my skirt.  :) 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ate lunch at about 11 today.  I was really hungry really early, for some reason.  But because of this, it now seems like it should be about two hours later than it really is.    I have a twix on my desk.  It's been here so long that the contest on the package has expired.  Which is to say, maybe three weeks.  Ok, maybe four.  Still.  I'm finally eating it today.    I'd really like to have meatloaf for dinner.  Freaky, huh?  I don't have the stuff, though, so I'll have to figure something else out.  Or go to the store.  hm.  This time, instead of bell peppers (indigestion issues) I'm going to try it with fresh poblano peppers instead.  They don't hurt me.  I'm super sleepy.  Lethargic.  Maybe it's due to the giant infection that I've had from that whole root canal thing.  Probably.  I sure could use a nap.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yet another day of holding steady, I guess.  Of course, I oversalted last night's dinner so badly that I could be holding on to 5 pounds of water weight, but whatever.   Breakfast today: 1 english muffin 1 morningstar farms breakfast pattie 1 slice tillamook mild cheddar (love this cheese) smear apricot all fruit coffee, usual ingredients  also - 1 vitamin, 2 fiber tabls, 1 zyrtec, 1 clindamycin, a whole lotta water.  oof.  Lunch will be a generous portion of leftover cashew chicken.  Dinner is undecided.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday when I got back from the dentist I was at 242.5, so that is good news.  Today I forgot to weigh until after I'd eaten breakfast & had my coffee.  (Not that a ham & cheese on toast and a cup of coffee makes a huge difference, but still.  It wasn't my normal naked just after the morning potty break weigh-in.)  Today is not the best food day, it is turning out.  BBQ for lunch, with mashed potatoes (the most evilly delicious mashed potatoes ever - way garlicky and topped with obscene amounts of cheddar) and friggin peach cobbler as sides.  Co-Irker ordered it for our weekly lunch.   When I'm ordering lunch from the bbq place, I can avoid the cobbler.  I can avoid the mashed potatoes too.  They're just words on a menu.  Abstract.  No real temptation there...  But when I'm presented with the fragrantly steaming wonder of both garlic mashed potatoes and spicy delicious peachy goodness?  No resisting that, my friends.  Particularly when every sack lunch has potatoes and peaches in it.  It's not like there was a choice.  (Other than spend my last $4 on mediocre cafeteria food instead.  And what sort of choice is that?)  And now I'm afraid that I'm going to have to go downstairs to the pseudo starbucks to get an over priced, over roasted cup of coffee, because I'm about to pass out.  I don't know if this is from carb crash or just the lethargy that comes with making my first foray into the world after a week of dental chaos and midday naps.  
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dunno.  I haven't eaten very much lately.  It not only hurts, but my tum's upset.  Dunno if it's from the vicoden, the antibiotics or the ibs.    i also think that one of the reasons that i dropped so drastically from yesterday is that i hadn't pooped in 2 days or so, and it all decided that it wanted OUT! NOW! this morning.  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ham & cheese croissant (small croissant, 1 serving ham, 1 serving cheese) coffee - usual ingredients  1 antibiotic 4 tylenol 1 vitamin 3 fiber tabs  that's a meal in itself.  bah. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oi.  the first time i weighed, it was 247.5.  then i realized that i was wearing my robe, and i'm usually wearing (um) nothing.  so i tried again.  which is a relief.  holding steady is infinitely better than creeping up.   altho, i was prepared to blame the extra weight on the swelling on the left side of my face.  goddamn root canal. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      chile relleno (cheese) tiny serving rice tiny serving refried beans salsa handful of chips  I thought that the chips wouldn't cause too much trouble.  They're pretty brittle chips; super fresh and not tough; if I bit into them with the right side of my mouth or broke them into smaller bite size pieces, then it shoudln't make my left side ache too much more.   This was very wrong.   I can't blame it all on the chips, though.  Just chewing and letting my top & bottom teeth touch at all really hurts.   This well and truly sucks. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got my stupid pedometer clipped to my panties again.  Yesterday, it did not count all my steps.  I tell you now, it did NOT.  At the end of the day I had 3100 or so, and I did all of my regular walking plus a trip to one of the D bldg lecture halls *and* a trip to walmart.  That's a 7000 step day if there ever was one, and I was in a hurry for most of it.   But, whatever.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      II
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      coffee, usual ingredients irish oatmeal - prob. 1cup cooked (1/2c. uncooked) with brown sugar, 1 pat butter, 2% milk  today will be filled with food that i do not have to bite into. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was 243.5.  I guess that things aren't going as well on this diet thing as I'd once hoped.  It was kind of a fucked up weekend, though, and yesterday just continued the trend.   In short, fried chicken is no longer my friend, fornevermore.  Also, toothaches suck. 
    
</post>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ugh.   i hate being sick.  so why did i think it would be ok to have fried chicken for dinner last night?   dumbass.  ugh.  i wish john was around.  i'd send him for ginger ale.  feh.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I miss John.  Not just having My Boyfriend.  I miss  John .  This kinda sucks.  Good things from today: I got my Biology textbook! It was $86 at the bookstore, but I also found it for $45 on ebay. If I can get the ebay one pretty cheap, I'll take this one back to the bookstore. I'm all for the college bookstore, really, but dude. That is like half price. Even after shipping.  I also got a new backpack! I could keep using my Timberland one, but it's not a good fit for my giant books, and basically it annoys me. Plus, it matches my luggage and I don't want to wear it out. This one is an Eastpak, and the color is Sweet Blue (perfect). I got it at Ross for $14.99 - I can deal with that.  I can also justify anything.  When I got home I sewed my Specials patch (that John gave me) on the front.  le sigh.  I'm not great with the sewing of patches, apparently. It's a bit puckered. Of course, it was a little awkward, because this is on the front pocket and it was kind of hard to get in there.  I also got cable tv today! That is super yay. And I returned all of my Netflix movies, so they should get there in time to not cause me any fees.  I've been watching A&amp;E (one of John's favorite channels) and now I'm watching the 100 most shocking moments in rock on VH1.  The cat is leaning against my leg. She's been so clingy lately. I think she misses John too. Seriously - he spoiled her in a big way. He took her for walks, and let her on the balcony all the time and he'd lay in the floor an play with her until *she* walked away. Plus, when she does the dangerous cat acrobatics and got stuck over on the window sill, his arms are long enough that he can reach her and just scoop her up. She prefers that method over the kitty elevator (aka laundry basket).  I wish this would pass.  This missing is my weakest time.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       when I said I wished it would rain.      It's been raining all night.  It's still pouring.  It's a deluge.  There is a shelter open in Lancaster, because over 200 houses have flooded.      I've got to get to Fort Worth, too.  Tyler's surgery is today, and I want to be there for Jennifer.  In fact, they're scheduled to begin right now.    One truck driver's family is on the news.  Their dog was tied to a tree out in the yard, and everything happened so fast they didn't get a chance to go out and get it.  So it drowned.   Fuckers.  I hate it when people tie dogs to trees.  (the news guy said family pet, not dog.  but really.  who ties a cat?)    Thankfully, the regular weather guy is back on channel four.  I like him.  I think that he was on vacation last week, and the vapid weather whore was on in his place.      Jesus.  The Trinity River is flooding.  That's about a block from here.  The Elm Fork, anyway.      It's supposed to rain pretty much all day, with a break around noon.  I'm just gonna have to go.  There's no sense in trying to wait this out.   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Not me; John. Poor guy. It sucks to be in his industry right here, right now. (IT, Dallas.) Well. Probably right now, anywhere. But that's kind of beside the point. His last day of work is Friday, but he'll get paid through August 18. Plus, they're giving a fairly generous (for the times) bonus for working past May 1 when he knew the layoff was coming. So that is good news.     There's no telling what this will do to his house-hunting. Hopefully he can find something soon, job-wise so that the whole mortgage approval thing doesn't get derailed. He's got an interview tomorrow, so that's something I guess.     I still think that the best thing for him to do would be to go to Houston and try to start over there. His dad just moved there, and he's offered to let John bunk up for a while. It would be good for him to get a change of scene. Of course, that will have to come after he's completed his work detail for the DWI thing, but that's another issue.     And he and his dad will feed each other beer for hours on end.  Then turn to each other in complete befuddlement -  where'd the beer go?!?!     Maybe I should let him figure out his solutions on his own.  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's overcast again.  They're saying it'll rain, which you know, I kind of wish it would - I love the rain.      There's something scratchy stuck in the back of my throat.  It's been there since breakfast.  V. annoying.    I still don't know if I'm going to the hospital with Jennifer tomorrow.  I'll have to call her tonight.      It's such a relief to know that I'm not moving in September.  I would have had to start packing like, this weekend.  >whew   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Pretentious much?    heh.    OK, so.  I finally talked to Mom's mortgage lady.  She didn't call me back earlier because things were so slow last week.  (Funny thing that - she didn't call John back quickly because things were so busy.  Damned coming & going, I guess.)  My mid-score is 524, which I believe is the average of my score from the three major (are there any minors?) credit houses.  It needs to be at about 580 for her company to help me, so there's that.  (I can probably get approved somewhere - but at a higher interest rate.)  I can qualify for about $70k, which is about $20k more than I thought.  Scary and exhilirating.      I'll really be better off waiting a while and getting the credit built up.  I'm in no financial position to buy right now, IMO, and I'd just as soon wait.  Plus, the thought of packing up all my shit once again just wears me out.  I'm in my 4th apartment in 5 years - that is an awful lot of moving.  It's hard on me, the cat and the furniture.  I'd just as soon wait a bit, if it's all the same to you.      So now, I need to really buckle down and get serious about bumping that score back up.  And with a 12-month goal in place (well.  actually.  more like 13 or maybe 14, depending on the deal that the apartments give me when my lease is up in september...) it won't seem so far off.  So, when it comes down to battling the purse lust, I can say oh, just a few more months and I'll be set!      or something like that.   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It has occured to me recently that this phrase is horridly overused.      annoying.   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       so frustrating.    I just spent 9 minutes on hold only to be told that they haven't even started my paperwork yet.  When I turned it in on the 12th, the guy that I gave it to said that it'd be about a week.  The woman I talked to today said to maybe try back again on Friday.      feh.     
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that I'm going to call off the house-hunt for a year.  I'll stay put in my apartment, pay down/off my credit cards, get my credit back in order and then try again.  Maybe I'll even be able to put aside some savings, so that I'll have a non-debt cushion in place before I haul off and buy a place and become responsible for all repairs.      Then again, if I find the right condo, my payments will be the same as they are now (give or take) and I can do all the same stuff while building equity.      The hitch with that little dream is that I've got no money for inspection fees, earnest money, closing costs, down payment, movers, etc. etc. forevermore.      I'm really better off just waiting a while.  That was my original plan anyway.      The only way this could change is if I got a generous student loan and was able to use the money towards these costs...  I'm not sure that's even possible, though.  And it seems sort of addictive or something.  At the least, it's poor financial planning.  Or something.  I don't know exactly why, but it feels wrong.      If I can devote $200-250/mo towards paying off debt, I can be debt free (excluding car payment) in a year.  That is piddly.  Measly.  I'm currently making minimum payments, which is about $100/mo.  So this will be double.  If I lay off new purses and shoes, I can do this.  Granted, the purses and shoes that I'm buying are usually $5 - $20 a pop, but that adds up.  I can use Paul Mitchell hair products to save money.  They're cheaper than TIGI, and still acceptable.  Stop with the frivolous impulse buys, no books (I'll just get to the library more often)  no  but it's for my house  buys.    I will still buy a new scale, though.  I hate my scale.  And a washing machine, even if used.  I do need that.    Of course, if my apartment complex raises my rent to market rate at the end of my lease (in September), I'll have to rethink this.  I've currently got concessions equaling about $200/mo off, so if they bump me back up to market rent, I'll have to move anyway.  I hate the thought of moving only to go to another apartment, so that will require a re-think definitely.  I don't imagine they'll really do that tho.  I think they'll continue my concessions.    I hope they will, anyway.  Moving is hard.   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My allergies are kickin my ass today.  I've already taken a Zyrtec, and if my nose will stop running long enough, I'll take some Nasocort.  erf.    I've also taken a pepcid; apparently low-acid orange juice is just as bad an idea as regular orange juice.  It sure did taste yummy at the time, though.      So, that means that it's not even 10 am and I've already taken 6 pills (1 vitamin, 3 fiber tabs, 1 zyrtec, 1 pepcid) and I'm contemplating a nasal spray.  If the sinus/allergy chaos keeps up, I'm gonna need a couple Tylenol for the headache that's brewing.  This seems like an awful lot of pills, in all honesty.  I'm not geriatric.      God, I might need a Rolaids, too.  Damn that tasty orange juice!    le sigh.    Last night during Clinton's speech at the DNC, they showed a shot of Michael Moore looking miserable and disgruntled.  I really don't like that guy.  I understand that a lot of people think he's the bees knees, but he seems like such a malcontent to me.      Yes, yes, great voice for our time, necessary agitator for much needed political change, blah blah.  He just looks unhappy is all I'm saying.    The bulletin board in the hutch area of my desk keeps falling down.  I'm not entirely sure how to fix this.    I'm having a severe cast of anti-work funk this week.  I just don't want to be here.     
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       that man can speak!     and  um  he's lookin pretty hot tonight.     and his tie is a little crooked.  it's so endearing!     
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's 10 minutes in (on cbs - i have no idea how long this has been going on irl.) and the level of absurdity is just amazing.      holy moly    I'm voting for Kerry because I hate Bush.      The End.     Oh, fuck - I missed Gore's speech!  damn.  I was wondering why they led off with Glenn Close of all fucking people.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Why did I eat the Domino's?  WHY?  It would have been better to write a hot stupid check than to eat that krep.  Good lord.      I've taken a pepcid.  I wish they didn't take so long to kick in.      The Thai Guy is coming over to pick up his check.  Maybe he'll bring me some of that yummy rice dessert.  With mango.      That would be nice.      eta: I've hit the Thai Guy jackpot!  He brought me 4 fresh veggie spring rolls and a rice milk dessert thing that has honeydew, cantaloupe, what might be mango (or possibly papaya), fresh corn sliced from the cob and quartered water chestnuts.  Bizarre, but delicious.  YAY!!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that Courtney Love has new lips and cheekbones.  Or something.  She's looking fundamentally different these days, to me.    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       oh my god oh my god oh my GOD!    Stargate and Stargate Atlantis are ALL! NEW! THIS! FRI!DAY!  Starting at 8pm!      If the cable guy is late I might have kittens.   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just cancelled my netflix subscription.    This should not cause emotional distress.  Why is this causing me emotional distress?    Probably that magnificent rental queue that I'd built up.  It was at about 233 or so.  Ridiculous, but still.    Now my cable bill will only result in an approximate $8 increase to my monthly budget, though.  So that is good.    I wonder if I can print out the rental queue???    hm.  It appears that I really should have thought of that before cancellation.      oh, well.  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was able to get my appointment changed to Friday.  So that is cool.  It actually works into my plans better - the cable guy is going to be there in the afternoon, and the college bookstore is only open in the morning.      I also upgraded from basic (local channels + wgb, tbs & discovery - $10/mo) to standard, which includes the sci-fi channel.  It's $41/mo.  I'm getting $10/mo off my cable internet, so it's really only costing me an extra $31.      Now I for sure need to cancel my Netflix.  heh.   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've got Thursday & Friday off this week.  That's a nice thing to remember on a Monday morning.      Thursday I've got the cable guy scheduled for between 2-5pm.  Hello clear picture, goodbye rabbit ears.  Friday I want to go to the college bookstore.  This is the extent of my plans.      But then I talked to my cousin over the weekend.  She's just broken up with her boyfriend and also her son is having surgery on his hips.  On Thursday morning.  He's got kidney failure, and consequently rickets - it's some sort of genetic or congenital problem; I'm not sure which.  His paternal grandmother died young of kidney disease, so I'm leaning towards genetic.  Poor guy.  They're going to do something to straighten out his hips and then he'll be in a full-body cast for several weeks.  He's six, I think.    God, her life is hard.  I realize that much of it is her own doing, but damn.  Damn.      And now I feel like I should go to the hospital to be with her on Thursday.  I'm not sure that anyone else will.  I'm going to try to reschedule the cable installation.  Maybe I can move it up and get it done one night early this week or something.   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is a man that parks in my garage, at work.  Actually, there are many men that park in my parking garage, and many women too.  And a couple of people that I'm not too sure about.  But this particular man used to flirt with me in the biggest way.  He sent out strong  I want you  vibes every time I saw him.  He's not too hard on the eyes, despite the Magnum PI moustache, but really.  I had no interest in him.  Because he's  married.   And I was with John, which was the next best thing to being married.      Plus, that moustache.  That type of thing is ok from a distance - whatever you want to put on your face, fella...  But it's nothing I can get personal with.      Suddenly, one day, he stopped all vibeage.  Completely and utterly lost all interest in me.  Which was weird - I've not encountered too many men that could flip the switch like that.  But hey, maybe things got better at home or whatever.      Oh, how naive I can be.      He has found himself a red headed whore to diddle!  They are in the parking garage every single day.  They hang out after work every day, sometimes for hours, sitting in one truck or the other like lovestruck teenagers.  They park together, always one or two spaces apart.  Sometimes, they'll park in the middle row so that they can face each other.  When she gets there first, she sits in her little red toyota truck and fusses with her hair and makeup, and twists around in her seat, waiting and watching for him to pull in.  (heh)  When he gets there first, he goes through the papers in his briefcase or sits, listening to the radio and trying to look busy.      One day, there was a note taped to her windshield, face down.  It was obviously in a woman's handwriting - you could see the printing through the paper.  I nearly pulled it off of there, to see what it said.  I was afraid that he'd get there just as I was sticking it back down or something, so I left it alone.   I guess he got there too late for her that day or something.    When I leave in the afternoons, they'll see me coming and we all pretend we don't see each other.  In the mornings, it's more of the same.      I guess I could park elsewhere.  But at the time that I come in, shady spots are at a premium, and I'm not going to let my car bake in the sun just to avoid these two cheaters.      I could get my ass out of bed a little earlier, and try to get here before they do.  That still wouldn't solve the problem of leaving.  I don't know what time the two of them leave work, but when I get out there, they're either still sitting there or they're just leaving.  (She stares back at him longingly as she drives away.  It's really amazing.)  Last Friday, after the BBQ Extravaganza, they were still up there when I left here at about 6:45pm.  There was a puddle of condensation underneath the exhaust on his truck.  They must have been there for a while for that to happen.    They've both got american flags glued to their back windows.  I don't really know why, but this bothers me.      I could start a record.  Take pictures of their cars, parked together like they are.  A chronicle of the parking patterns of Cheater Cheater Pumpkin Eater and the Redheaded Floozy.  hee.      (I have my own prejudices against redheaded whores, thanks to John and the Infamous Bennigan's Incident.  We shall speak no more of that, however.)    (dirty whore.)    I dunno.  I guess it's none of my business, and I shouldn't even worry about what they do.  But I feel like I've been unwillingly (well.  sort of unwillingly.) drawn in to the conspiracy or something.  I don't even know their names, but I know that they're cheaters.      What am I going to do about it, though?  Other than frown and judge and make that 'hmmmmm' noise that Marge Simpson makes?     
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'll admit it - I'm a weather nerd.  ;)    A cold front came through last night.  I've had the a/c off all day.  It's so nice.  All of the windows are open, and the fan is blowing right on me.  Today's high was in the upper 70s.  That is just amazing for here, now.  I'm taking advantage of it for as long as I can.  Which is probably tonight, and that's it.  heh.  I think that tomorrow it's going to be close to normal temps again.  Which is going to call for a/c, definitely.   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Our house hunting trip yesterday was quite discouraging. The *one* house that I liked turned out to be totally misrepresented - the listing agent included a picture of the house next door instead of the shack-type place that they're actually trying to sell. (The house next door is appraised at $125k; the shack type place is appraised at $7k. GOD.)  And the listing agent is *related* to the seller - this is no innocent mistake, in my outraged opinion.    John found next to nothing. Several of the houses that he'd printed out were so far out away from the city as to be completely too far away to even go look at. There was one that was in far east Dallas that was not too bad, but there were people looking at it when we drove by. So, we went up to McDonald's around the corner to use the restroom. This house was the last on our list, so we'd been in the car for a while and desperately needed the facilities. We went in, used the restroom, went back out and BAM! The truck wouldn't start. Oh, holy shit. John tried several times to start it, checked all the fuses & relays, looked under the hood and did everything he knew to do. Bless his heart, if it was a pc he could have diagnosed it blindfolded, but the whole internal combustion thing is not really his bit. Finally I just called for help. TMobile offers roadside assistance for $2.99/mo, added to my cellular bill. It is so totally worth it. They were there in about an hour, to give us a jump. The guy that came to help us was so very nice. (There was a bit of awkwardness when it came time to explain that John couldn't try to start it yet because he was waiting for the breathalyzer to kick in.) Anyway - I'm glad that I have the service. And I'm glad that I was with him - he would have been so stranded. We were way the fuck out away from everybody we know, I think. I guess. I don't really know where all of his friends live.     It was like a sauna in that truck.  I guess that we could have gone into McDonald's to wait, but we both despise McD's.  Sweat is good, sometimes.  I guess.  It sure wore me out, tho.    We got back to my place, dropped his truck off here and got the battery info out of it, then I took him up to walmart to get a new battery. This seems to have fixed the problem, so that is good news. Once he got the battery installed, we started dinner. He was using old charcoal, so it took a little while longer to get it going. The steaks turned out really well, though, so that was good news. The only hitch is that by the time that we got done eating, it was after 10. John's occupational license allows him to drive 4 hours per day (heh - we were out for like 6 hours yesterday, but dude. It was practically an act of god. The God Of Batteries.) and he can't drive between the hours of 10pm and 5am.     So, I just asked him to stay the night. It's totally not worth the risk just to get out of here, you know? He crashed on the couch and I cooked him breakfast this morning. It was weird to be together like that and not touch each other. When he left today, he gave me a hug. I probably held on longer than I should have, but damn. This was one of those times that it was hard to remember why we broke up in the first place.     In other news, Baja Fresh really really sucks. We had lunch there yesterday, and they have the absolute WORST salsa that either of us have ever tried to eat. They are off our Acceptable Places To Eat List. bleck-ptooey.    The cat has made the death-defying leap from the balcony to the window sill twice this weekend. She did it yesterday while we were cooking dinner, and again today. Little shit. When John's here, he can reach her, but I have to get the laundry basket out. (It becomes the kitty elevator.) Today I nearly dropped her - I just had the basket in a weird position. It was kinda scary. And I halfway jammed my finger. So she's grounded from the balcony for a while. Which is going to be rough on both of us. She gets just beside herself with wanting to go out there. Last week, she wanted to go out so bad that she stood up on her back legs by the back door and hopped up and down. I wish I had a video camera. It was priceless. And loud - she yells the whole time she does that, until I let her out.    I'm watching Murder On The Orient Express on CBS. I'm having continuity issues. Earlier, just after the train became stranded due to a landslide in the mountains, a prissy frenchman (??) could not get a signal on his cellular phone. Now, Hercule Poirot has borrowed a laptop from a suspect in order to do an internet search. I realize that cellular service is not exactly well known for reliability in rough terrain, but seriously. Wireless internet? If it's not internet, then the laptop  just happened  to have  all  of the information that Msr. Poirot needed for his exposition.      I call bullshit, but it's still somewhat entertaining.   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In my office.  So I adjusted the thermostat.  This will probably make it comfortable about the time I leave, the way that the a/c is rigged up here.  It's really weird - to me, anyway.  The thing blows a mixture of heated & cooled air, and the thermostat regulates the ratio.  It never shuts off, though.  So it's not like the a/c at home, which will run pure cold for a while then shut off once the desired temp is reached.      Maybe it's this way in every big glass building, I don't know.     
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       that I were wearing different pants.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that if I get a house in a rougher part of town, I might get a dog.  I don't want a big scary guard dog, just a dog with a deep meaningful bark.  Then again, I feel kind of guilty for even considering using an animal in this fashion.  Which is probably a bit warped in and of itself.      Of course, I'll have to take Johnny with me to pick the dog.  I can't have something he'll be afraid of.  So, shar-peis are out.  And probably boxers too, judging from the number of them on pet finder that say 'no kids' in the profile.      This is all too early to even worry about, because getting a dog while I'm living alone and going to school part time is just not going to work.  I need to be home more to care for a dog; it'd be cruel to leave it alone for that much time.  Cats are pretty much ok with it, but even still I feel guilty.  And Polly is pouncing my feet again, so something's up with her anyway.      sigh.    John just sent me an email titled 'it has to get better.'    this does not bode well.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hoooray!!!    I feel much better today.  Still kind of tired, like I could stand to sleep in or something.  But, tomorrow is Saturday and I will attempt to do just that.  (Which means that I'll likely be up around my usual time anyway, but at least it will be of my own accord and not due to the alarm clock.)    I'm wearing my khaki capris today.  These have been hanging in my closet, unworn, for probably close to a year.  I thought they'd gotten too tight.  They're still a little tight around the calves, but I'm wearing them anyway.  It's more a sign of desperation than anything - I need more clothes.  I also refuse to buy new clothes at this size.  (I will, however, replace what wears out.  I'll just not *add*; it's more of a treading water thing.)    I don't see any reason to look like a ragamuffin just because I want to lose some weight.      Still, I've got my size 12 columbia khaki shorts hanging on my bedroom door, just for a daily reminder of the goal.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yay!&nbsp;   FINALLY!&nbsp;   It's a bit lumpy, but at least there isn't a gaping hole in there anymore.&nbsp;   Brendan Frasier was on Scrubs tonight, and he looked a little chubby.&nbsp; I still would like to lick him.&nbsp; hee.&nbsp;   It seems like there was something else I was going to write about, but I'm tired.&nbsp; I don't remember.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I realize it.  I'm not quite willing to embrace it.  I don't enjoy it.      I shouldn't have creepout over little people.      I can't even really say midget anymore without feeling like a horrid bigot.  When I say it, I cringe at myself.      The credit for this sea change goes largely to the girl on The Amazing Race.  Seriously.  She's fucking awesome, and she's WINNING.  (well.  they're in second place.  which is way ahead of nearly everybody else.)      Everybody loves a winner.      Except the loser, but whatever.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is a midget in a wheelchair parked in the hallway outside my office.      I suppose that he's there waiting for the meeting in the conference room to let out, or something.  Maybe he has a presentation to make.      I'm going to be very quiet and hope that he does not feel like chatting.      Because, you know, I'm a sorry enough human being to be creeped out by things like this.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've decided that I do need a coffee pot after all.  When my previous coffee pot finally died I decided that I would just switch to a french press and a kettle.  The kettle is good to have, no matter what.  And I love the french press.  Truly I do.  The problem is that my coffee with chicory really doesn't get along well with the french press at all.  It's too finely ground or something.  Instantly strong enough to cause whiplash.  Then, Mom & Jeff brought me drip-grind flavored coffees, as souvenirs from their trip to Hawaii.      Drip grind and the press aren't friends, really.    Finally, I came to the realization that there are some mornings that I want to dump some grinds in the filter basket and walk away while the coffee is made for me.     I think that, for now, I'm going to just get a Mr. Coffee 4-cup coffee maker.  It's cheap (at WM, $13 for the switch style, $18 for the one with a programmable digital timer) and it looks nice.  Then, when money is less of an issue and I have a little more storage, I can then invest in the Melitta percolator that Target has for $39.  It's pretty, and makes great coffee, I'm sure.      It's not wrong for a single girl to have three coffee makers.  It's just not.    Today's air pollution level is at Orange again.  It was Orange yesterday too.  I think that they missed it, though, because today is much much clearer than yesterday was.  The sky is blue again, I can see the clouds, and the buildings that are off to the north of here are visible in detail again - not just vague outlines.      My chest still feels a little heavy, though.  So maybe it's some form of non-hazy air pollution that we've got today.      Either way, the sky sure is pretty.  It's good to see blue again.   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night I dreamed that I had a bunch of kittens in my yard, and they kept trying to get in to come live with me.  One of them, the one that I wanted to keep, was white with black spots and it was gentle and sweet and it would let me look at its little feet.  It needed its claws trimmed, and somebody had put a flea collar thing on its little wrist, like a bracelet.  This worried me, because I thought that if I kept it I'd be swiping somebody's pet.      But if they put a flea collar where the cat could chew on it, they don't deserve a cat anyway.  Those things are full of evil chemicals.      John and I talked for a long time last night.  We talked about his legal stuff, Bob and Dawn (bless her heart, that girl is just pure dumb), us, houses, the breakup, his recent sex dream about me (hee!) and my dream about him and the commune.    He says that he understands that this isn't going to go anywhere - that hanging out together isn't going to result in us getting back together.  I'm just going to have to take him at his word on that, and steel myself to make it true.  He said that there were things that I was not happy with, and there were things that he was not happy with, and I ended things amicably enough, civilly enough, that he feels it's ok for us to still be buds.  Or something like that.      He said that in six or eight months, I could meet someone and then he'd know that it was time to bow out.  It'd be too weird to have an ex-boyfriend hanging around.  Or, he could meet someone.  Same thing.      Am I ready for that kind of thought?  I don't even know.  It's that whole head vs. heart thing again.    At the end of the call, the thanked me for being a 'buddy'.      I just laughed.  What other response would be appropriate for that?  It's weird, and sweet and I can't decide what I really think about being his buddy.    And I can't figure out what he could have been unhappy about.  Either he's saying that to save face or I'm completely clueless.  I'm not naive enough, or egotistical enough (really) to think that I was the perfect girlfriend.  Still, I'm stumped.      Of course, it could be the same differences that I felt were so catastrophic.  Or something similar.    If I really want to know, I'm going to just have to ask him.      The question is, do I really want to know?   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I still haven't heard anything from John about his court thing.&nbsp; Maybe he's still there.&nbsp;   This shouldn't even be&nbsp;any of my concern.&nbsp; hmph.   ok, I emailed him.&nbsp;   Whatever.&nbsp;   He's got work detail for every Sunday at 7:30 am for 22 weeks, $1000 in fines & court costs to pay and his license is gone for 2 years.&nbsp; He's got an occupational license for that time, and he's got to keep that breathalyzer thing on his truck until he gets his real license back.&nbsp;   So, it's bad but it could have been much worse.  I still think he's going to get hit with that $2500/year surcharge eventually, but he thinks he'll get out of it.&nbsp;   Which, again, whatever.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I'm wearing: black liz claiborne capsleeve t, with black on black embroidery around the v-neck and a deodorant stain on the right side.&nbsp; oi. (xl) overdyed indigo levi's movin on surplus skirt (18W) birkenstock oahu platforms in magazine pop red (40wide) matching VS second skin satin panties & bra; the panties have seen better days & should probably be thrown out.&nbsp; but then the bra would be matchless.&nbsp; (xl, 38b) stepometer  This skirt is fitting a little bigger than it did last time I wore it.&nbsp; I shudder to think.&nbsp; The waist is always big on me, because everything seems to be made for tube-shaped people these days.&nbsp; I've been blessed with a waist and hips.&nbsp; I'd call it hourglass, but at this point, I think I'm more of a day-glass.&nbsp; heh.&nbsp; Anyway.&nbsp; Because the waist is loose, the stepometer keeps falling over.&nbsp; I'm thinking of clipping it to my panties.&nbsp; I thought about the pocket, but it has to be upright in the front, and the pocket would be more to the side and not upright.&nbsp;   Are you happy to see me, or is that a stepometer in your pants?  &nbsp; John's in court today.&nbsp; It's for the DWI he got in February.&nbsp; He's going to plead no contest (I think) and get his sentencing and occupational license today.&nbsp; Or something like that.&nbsp;&nbsp; I hope it goes well for him.  I need to call Comcast and see about getting cable tv.&nbsp; I think that I can get basic for $10/mo, which will also give me a $10/mo discount on my cable internet.&nbsp; Why John didn't do this in the first place is beyond me, but he makes&nbsp;weird decisions all the time.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night I dreamt that John and I were still together, and living behind a storefront.&nbsp; Lots of artists and creative types lived there, and there were sculptures and weavings and arty things everywhere.&nbsp; It was also dirty, with dirt floors and trailers and children running about in white shifts and tunics.&nbsp; The&nbsp;storefront was very folksy, and&nbsp;the artwork was sold to tourist types at what could have been a tidy profit if everyone in the commune (there's no other word for it) had stuff worth selling.&nbsp; As it was, the few carried the many and everyone wound up looking like dirty hippies that could use a bath and a job.  We had a couple of stalls to ourselves; they faced each other and the space in between was open at each end, so we had no privacy.&nbsp; I guess they were more like sheds, really.&nbsp; There were just curtains to hide our stuff in the sheds, and I hung woven art at the end, on the outside of the walls, to mark them as ours and pretty it up a bit.&nbsp;   He'd been out to eat with his friend Mark, and I had dropped him off and was late to pick him up.&nbsp; I'd been to see family or some such, and I had a couple of my&nbsp;friends in the car.&nbsp;&nbsp;When we got back to the restaurant, they bailed and took off.&nbsp; It was planned that way - our friends didn't mix.&nbsp; He and Mark were sitting out in front of the restaurant, on the curb of the valet island.&nbsp; I couldn't get all the way up there because there were cars blocking my way (both of them classic mustangs;&nbsp;maybe this&nbsp;means something?) but John & Mark saw me anyway.&nbsp; Mark took off to his own car, which was there in the parking lot, and John made his way through the parked cars to me.&nbsp; He got in the car and immediately started in about how wrong it was of me to be late, how I made him feel unimportant and wasn't it just dandy how I had better things to do than come get him like I said I would.&nbsp; He railed on me and I railed back all the way home.&nbsp; I parked my car (my existing car, the mustang) out in the dirty old-west style street and made my way to the store.&nbsp; I just wanted to go home.&nbsp; John went somewhere else, I assumed to a bar.&nbsp;   I went into the storefront, and Christopher Masterson (of all people???) was there, wearing a black suit with a white shirt, waiting for sales and purposefully not looking at me.&nbsp; He lived in the commune too, and he was running the store that evening.&nbsp; The store was cluttered, and as I crabwalked my way through it, I moved something on one of the tables with my butt, then something else on a different table with my belly.&nbsp;&nbsp; I got through the store, and went through the back door to the living area.&nbsp; I walked down the dirt roadway, past the trailers, dodging kids&nbsp;until I got to our sheds.&nbsp; I went in and discovered Polly curled up asleep on a shelf, in a space in the middle where the curtains wouldn't&nbsp;reach.&nbsp; I was so mad that he'd brought her here; she was supposed to stay with family until we got out of there.&nbsp; There was no way to keep her inside - she'd wander off and get lost or taken and I was pissed that&nbsp;he had done exactly what I asked him not to do.&nbsp; I cursed and looked to the side, where two little girls in dirty white shifts with wild hair and bare feet were watching me from the makeshift&nbsp;wooden deck attached to the side of an ancient yellow and tan travel trailer.&nbsp;   I turned back to my shed, and the cat was yawning and watching me.&nbsp; I went to the end of the shed, to hang up a new bamboo wall hanging that I'd brought home.&nbsp; It started to sound like rain, so I went back to the middle area of our shed and pulled back one of the curtains to start putting stuff away, out of the rain.&nbsp; My niece, Whitney, was  in  there!&nbsp; What the hell?&nbsp; She was wearing a purple nightgown, and lavender panties, and she was laying on top of all this stuff that wasn't a bed.&nbsp; She was crying and trying to pull her top down to cover her panties.&nbsp;   I looked up just then, and the roof of our building was smooth and transclucent, and I could see the clouds scudding across the sky.&nbsp; They looked like schools of fish.&nbsp; It was beautiful.&nbsp; And I thought,  well at least I have that.    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I love love LOVE this show!&nbsp; It's the only reality show I'll watch.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Just before everything blew up on the boards, I started a thread about it.&nbsp; That's about the only reason that I'd go back to the stupid board - to check on that thread.&nbsp;  &nbsp; The Military Dad &amp; Daughter are in last place.&nbsp; Dammit.&nbsp; I like them.&nbsp;  &nbsp; There is another team (and I'm not sure which one) where the guy calls the girl Baby, incessantly.&nbsp; This annoys me.&nbsp; John used to call me that occasionally, usually it was Babe, but Baby all the time annoys me. &nbsp; Oh, she just called him Baby.&nbsp; I would have to limit my time with them, if I really knew them. &nbsp; Oh, Mirna just hit the car behind her!&nbsp; Oh, and one of the brothers just called her bitch as he drove by!&nbsp; Now that is Klassy. &nbsp; God, I love this show.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There's an article about Jim Morrison's last days in this month's Rolling Stone.&nbsp; God.&nbsp; He was so tortured.&nbsp; And so young.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I read that article at the library tonight, where I also got five more books to read.&nbsp; The Summer Reading Program ends July 31.&nbsp; If I finish the book I'm on, plus 5 more, I'll get 3 free hardcovers.&nbsp; I think it's worth the effort.&nbsp; Probably.&nbsp; I maybe shoulda checked out the free book selection before committing myself to this....  &nbsp;  The thing is, I know that I'm going to be super busy once school starts again.&nbsp; So, I want to cram in as much recreational entertainment as possible before it gets all crazy.  &nbsp;  The new blog for the diet/lifestyle overhaul is up and going.&nbsp; oi.  &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Catwoman looks good for video.&nbsp;     
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think that I might make a new, separate blog for my die(t) progress.&nbsp; Or, lack thereof.&nbsp; heh.&nbsp; I'm afraid that if I start talking about it here, it'll be all I talk about.&nbsp; And I don't want that to happen.&nbsp; That's ultimately defeating; I get tired of hearing myself go on about it and wind up giving the whole thing up. &nbsp; The sad truth of the matter is that I need to do  something  - so maybe if I put it in the public forum (so to speak; I have no idea if anyone actually reads this...) then maybe - just maybe - I'll actually finally make it happen.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Of course, there's no real telling if this strategem will actually work.&nbsp; I've tried it before - with Weight Watchers or just going to the gym.&nbsp; Those are fairly public as well,  and  they cost money.&nbsp; I'm usually good for 3-4 months or 20 pounds, whichever comes first.&nbsp; Then, a few years later, when the pounds have crept back and brought unwelcome friends, I'll start over.&nbsp; Lose another 20 pounds.&nbsp; If I'd kept off all of the 20 pounds that I've lost over the years, I'd be thin.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Or, something like it.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Has been rather slow.&nbsp; Which is good, in a way.&nbsp; After work I'm going to have to swing by school and pay my tuition, then I can go home and do whatever....&nbsp; I think I'll stop by the library and at the very least drop off the books I've finished reading.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I just caught a glimpse of my arm - that flabby place on the inside - the one that has always been towards the back?&nbsp; It's not so much towards the back anymore - it's&nbsp;spread to&nbsp;the side.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Maybe I won't get more books to read.&nbsp; Maybe I'll figure something else to do that does not involve me sitting on my ass.  &nbsp;  fargle.    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just couldn't take the green today.&nbsp; I'm feeling a little under the weather, digestively speaking, and the green was not making me comfy.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Luckily, I'm wearing a green shirt.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Joy. &nbsp; Hopefully the afternoon will pass quickly.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       That's our air pollution level today.&nbsp;  &nbsp; ugh.&nbsp;  &nbsp; My chest feels heavy, and I'm kind of short of breath.&nbsp; My office is on the 5th floor, and the 1st floor of my building is actually below street level.&nbsp; So, basically, my office windows&nbsp;give me the equivalent to a 4th floor view in any other building.&nbsp; Within about 1/2 a mile, things start getting hazy.&nbsp; There are some large-ish buildings about&nbsp;5-7 miles north of here, and I can barely see their outline.&nbsp; The trees outside my office are barely moving - there's no real breeze to speak of.&nbsp;  &nbsp; The planes taking off from Love Field (less than 2 miles away) are hazy as soon as I can see them, while they're still in steep ascent.&nbsp;  &nbsp; This can't be good for anyone.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got a&nbsp;conditional approval from a lender on LendingTree.&nbsp; yeek!&nbsp; I have no idea what&nbsp;is conditional about it, tho.&nbsp; It doesn't say.&nbsp; I haven't called them yet, and I'm not sure that I will.&nbsp; I did, however, call my mom's finance lady.&nbsp; She's got a good line on grant and first time buyer programs, and since Mom already has a relationship with her, I feel that she won't steer me wrong. &nbsp; I didn't call her first, because if I got a resounding NO then it seemed like it would be less humiliating if it were from some random internet site than from someone that my mom works with all the time. &nbsp; Right now, I'm just trying to keep from getting my hopes up too much.&nbsp; If this doesn't work out, it will all still be ok.&nbsp; I can just stay in my apartment for another year, clean up the credit and then try again.&nbsp; Or something. &nbsp; I have found a really cute house, tho.&nbsp; At least, cute in the pictures on the internet.&nbsp; I need to drive by it.&nbsp; John's coming over on Saturday so that we can do that.&nbsp; (The neighborhood has a great potential to be very scary, which is inherent in my price range, and I don't want to go alone.)&nbsp; He's also bringing steaks and the grill.&nbsp; It's going to be supremely ironic if we wind up buying houses in the same neighborhood. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Somebody closed the blinds in my office last night.&nbsp; I didn't leave here until after 6 pee em.&nbsp; Who could have done that?&nbsp; And why?&nbsp; It's really annoying because they're really long and heavy, and a complete pain in the ass to get back the way I want them.&nbsp;   Rude.   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       those THANK YOU! commercials.&nbsp;  &nbsp; They're just stupid.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Thank you wouldn't get you out of those situations.&nbsp; It's just a bizarre word salad thing to say.&nbsp;  &nbsp; &nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just found out that the textbooks for fall term won't be available for purchase at my college bookstore until after July 30.&nbsp; Which sucks, because I've taken the 29th &amp; 30th off, with the intent to go to the stupid bookstore on one of those days for the express purpose of BUYING A GODDAMN BOOK. &nbsp; They won't give out the ISBN number over the phone or the web, so I can't find the damn book on the web at all.&nbsp; I don't think they even give out the full title.&nbsp; They've got it listed as "Biology: Concepts Etc", but I can't find anything Etc by this author.&nbsp; I can find "Biology: Concepts and Connections", but I don't know for sure that's it.&nbsp; I  think  that's it...&nbsp;&nbsp;but I need to know for sure before I&nbsp;sink ~$100 into it.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Stupid bookstore.&nbsp; This wouldn't even be worth bitching about except that they're only open from 7:45am - 5:00 pm M-F, and I'm *supposed* to work 8:30 - 5:30, M-F.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I am tempted to go over there and get a printout from them next week, when I'm off, then go to amazon and get the book on the cheap.&nbsp; But I've been skittish about online ordering since last semester's month-long Algebra book shipping time.&nbsp; I can't afford to have that sort of setback in biology.&nbsp; I need to hit the ground running with it. &nbsp; Maybe they'll let me go ahead and get it on Friday.&nbsp; Maybe I can smooth talk my way into getting out of there with what I need.&nbsp;  &nbsp; If not, I can always take a stupid long lunch and battle downtown....&nbsp;long lunches are not the worst thing, after all. &nbsp; &nbsp; In other news, coke is no substitute for coffee.&nbsp; What was I thinking? &nbsp; Also, I forgot to bring a knife to work, for my apple.&nbsp; So I had to attempt to chop my apple into little tuna-salad bits using a plastic knife.&nbsp; About halfway through, I decided to wash a new razor blade for my box cutter, and use that.&nbsp; That was simultaneously the best and worst idea I've had in a long time.&nbsp; I didn't injure myself, which is slightly remarkable.&nbsp; I stopped using it after about 1/3 of the apple was chopped.&nbsp; That's&nbsp;when I realized that not only was it smelling very metallic, but this was the first time in my life that I've used a razor blade to chop  anything  and I am just too goody goody for words.&nbsp; I went back to the plastic knife.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Just came by to see me!&nbsp; YAY!!!&nbsp; He's going to Seattle next week to do two away rotations, and he said that he'd stop back by to see me again before he leaves town.&nbsp; It sounds like he's doing really well.&nbsp; Which is so good to hear - I was a little worried for him when he dropped the program.&nbsp; He's got a lot going on right now.&nbsp; Still, though, he's doing well.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  It's always so nice when he comes by.&nbsp; He's a sweet boy.&nbsp; :)  &nbsp;  (that would be funny to hear if you knew him, probably.&nbsp; heh.)  &nbsp;  He is proud of me.&nbsp;&nbsp; And, you know, I'm proud of him too.&nbsp;  &nbsp; We're cool.&nbsp; hee. &nbsp;  :)    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just won a cat stocking on ebay.&nbsp; I had forgotten that I even bid on it.&nbsp; Luckily, it's only $2.99, even with shipping.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Definitely one of those 'oh, FUCK!&nbsp; I won?!?!' moments. &nbsp; But at least now Polly has a stocking.&nbsp; oi. &nbsp; (i'll add a picture of it later.&nbsp; i don't want to install hello on the work pc.)  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Guess who!&nbsp; Guess who doesn't have enough money in the bank account to write a stupid check to go get a latte!&nbsp;  &nbsp; Did you guess me? &nbsp; If you did, then you get an imaginary (and free, 'cause i'm broke, bitch.) cookie.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I am sofa king glad that I actually&nbsp;managed to remember to bring my stupid lunch today.&nbsp; god. &nbsp; Maybe I'll have a coke and a smile.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       because that's how I feel on the inside.&nbsp;  &nbsp; ugh. &nbsp; It's monday alright.&nbsp; I was supposed to be here early, because we've got an applicant in town.&nbsp; I totally spaced on that and got here late.&nbsp; I'm out of cash, I didn't have coffee.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I've got a weird pain deep inside my left hip, and it just won't let up.&nbsp; Last night the ache went all the way down to my knee.&nbsp; I vacillate between toomah and oh, I just need to exersize and work it out; it's nooothing.&nbsp; Really.&nbsp; Just a little muscle ache from laying around being depressed for&nbsp;two weeks.&nbsp; Get out and take a walk - I'll feel better!&nbsp;  &nbsp;   but maybe it's a toomah.   &nbsp; sigh. &nbsp; I really should just stop talking to John.&nbsp; Really.&nbsp; I'm sitting here waiting for him to email me.&nbsp; That's fucked.&nbsp; I need to move on.&nbsp; Not to somebody else, exactly; just to the phase of the breakup where I stop thinking about him all the damn time.&nbsp; When he was over yesterday, we smiled and laughed and talked about things we both knew without saying, then we&nbsp;became awkward.&nbsp; This is how everything will be, if we keep this up.&nbsp; We'll be in this awkward limbo until we either get back together  one more time  or have a blowup and sever all contact.  &nbsp; I don't know which I want, anymore, and that is not good.&nbsp; And I don't know if he even thinks about these things.&nbsp; I suspect not, because he is a boy in all senses of the word, and I think that such depths of navel-gazing are unknown to him.&nbsp; But, he could.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Or not. &nbsp; &nbsp; I think that I'm going to have to go downstairs and get a latte.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       is so weird.&nbsp; I guess probably because I'm so American.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Why is the sound always so bad?&nbsp;  &nbsp; I still like it, tho.&nbsp; When I'm in a British tv mood.&nbsp;   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       John didn't come over today.&nbsp; Well.&nbsp; He didn't stay.&nbsp; Just picked up his mail and made some small talk.&nbsp; Bob had called and wanted him to go fishing, so he did that instead of cooking with me.&nbsp; It's just as well&nbsp;- he said that he's not trying to work his way back in or whatever... (it was one of our inarticulate body language style conversations;&nbsp;those are&nbsp;always fun to try to explain.)&nbsp; It's possible that he's just looking for company, nothing more.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Anything is possible. &nbsp; I can be ok with having dinner with him.&nbsp; In my head.&nbsp; I'm not sure about my heart.&nbsp; Not&nbsp;yet.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Earlier today I felt good.&nbsp; I was on top of the breakup wave.&nbsp; I could see for miles.&nbsp; New house, new career, new everything.&nbsp; It was good.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Now I feel a little sad again.&nbsp; It's so weird to think of us being done, forever.&nbsp; He's not my&nbsp;boyfriend anymore; I'm not his girl.&nbsp; Just a bud.&nbsp; Someone to hang out with sometimes, if nothing better is going on. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; I bought some perfume today.&nbsp; Hang Ten.&nbsp; hee!&nbsp; I got it at Ulta for ten bucks.&nbsp; Not too shabby.&nbsp; I like it.&nbsp; I also got some new OPI polish for $0.56 - if I'd known it was that cheap, I might've got two.&nbsp; I love their 50% off clearance sales.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Someday my posts will not start with his name.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    like, totally&nbsp; urlLink    &nbsp; I just watched Valley Girl on DVD.&nbsp; I had no idea that I had a Valley Girl hair cut back then.&nbsp; I don't remember calling it that...&nbsp; but dude&nbsp; I was so rockin and I didn't even know it. &nbsp; I thought the accents were worse than they are too.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Nic Cage was so Bert in this thing, but yum. &nbsp; I so like want this soundtrack, dude.&nbsp;  Totally.   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       From Slate:   Our relationship with celebrities also depends on our assumption that we can know what they're "really like"  (the quote is from  urlLink this article , but the article has little to do with&nbsp;this train of thought...) &nbsp; This pretty much sums up my Austin pitfall.&nbsp; I thought I *knew* the Crazy Girl from Austin.&nbsp; She was very much like a celebrity to me.&nbsp; She owned a cool site, collaborated on another cool entertainment/recipe site, and I really thought because of these things, that I knew her.&nbsp; But really, she'd only update her column every few weeks - that doesn't let me know her.&nbsp; It's a one-sided conversation, and I'm not the active side.&nbsp; She'd drop onto the boards every few months and post a handful of times.&nbsp; That doesn't let me know her.&nbsp; It's a snapshot, at best.&nbsp; Sometimes a blurry one.&nbsp;  &nbsp; When I&nbsp;realized that all of the things that I thought were ironic exaggeration were actually terrifying understatement,&nbsp;my illusion&nbsp;just fell apart.&nbsp;  &nbsp; The other thing that whacked me upside the head (again) is my tendency to think well of things that are prettily packaged.&nbsp; This girl is a very gifted writer, and we all (on the board) have/had an image of her as witty, fierce, fun and all around fucking awesome.&nbsp; I think that everyone that wasn't in Austin still has that image.&nbsp; Apparently, Jen is trying to convince herself that she still wants that image to be true, and the rest of us that backed out of the BBQ from hell are just insane.&nbsp; Which is fine, I guess.&nbsp; I just wish that she were a good enough person to be able to do that without slamming everyone else involved.&nbsp;  &nbsp; And I still don't see what my weight had to do with the situation, but that is a rant for another day. &nbsp; I have a tendency to take things at face value and be lulled into contentment with pretty words and neat pictures.&nbsp; That's why I'll do stupid shit like download recipes for grilled lamb chops with fennel butter and spend an hour searching google results for importable absinthe. &nbsp; I hate licorice.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I still haven't heard anything from LendingTree.&nbsp; This shouldn't bug me; expecting an instant answer is a bit unrealistic.&nbsp; But still.&nbsp; I hate waiting. &nbsp; John emailed me today, and I was inordinately pleased about it.&nbsp; Foolish, but still comforting to know that he misses me too.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I'm still pissed that the chubby girl called me homely.&nbsp; Well.&nbsp; Annoyed.&nbsp; The hurt is subsiding, due to the absurdity of it all. &nbsp; Work has become hectic in the past few days.&nbsp; It turns out that Robin is now my legitimate supervisor.&nbsp; I don't know what to think of this.&nbsp; It's at least somewhat comforting to have some structure about the whole thing.&nbsp; Before it was just a bullshit ad-hoc crapshoot.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Yesterday I went to tour the Westin, to choose a hotel for next year's conference.&nbsp; I had to take Linda, from the graduate school.&nbsp; For some reason, she felt that appropriate lunchtime conversation should involve a discussion of a colleague's  brain injury  and subsequent erratic behavior.&nbsp; God.&nbsp; I tried to steer the conversation back away from that as quickly as possible, but she was apparently needing to get some stuff off her chest.&nbsp; It went on far, far too long.&nbsp;  &nbsp; This place wears me down so bad sometimes.  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I applied for a home loan through lending tree tonight.&nbsp; oi.&nbsp; I'm nervous.&nbsp; But, what can it hurt?&nbsp; John got approved, Corey got approved, maybe I can get approved too.&nbsp; John used texaslending, maybe I'll go there if this lending tree thing doesn't pan out. &nbsp; I saw John tonight.&nbsp; Since Mom was meeting him in Irving to show him a house, I just went over there too.&nbsp; She's loaning me the money to pay my tuition until the student loan kicks in, and this was really the best time to see her since they're going out of town next week, which is just&nbsp;before it's due.&nbsp; Anyway.&nbsp; I wanted to get out of there before he got there, and I wanted to stay until he showed up.&nbsp; Just as I was about to back out of the driveway, he pulled in &amp; blocked my way.&nbsp;  &nbsp; It was one of those bittersweet things.&nbsp; He's gotten a haircut.&nbsp; But I knew that&nbsp;- he gets his hair cut every two or three weeks anyway, and he was going to do that when he left here last weekend.&nbsp; There were little hairs along the nape of his neck that the stylist missed.&nbsp;  &nbsp; He mentioned bringing the grill when he comes to get his mail next weekend.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I wanted to go to him tonight.&nbsp; Put my head on his shoulder and let him wrap his long arms around me. &nbsp; But, what will have really changed?&nbsp; It's always like this when we break up, and it always goes back to the same old cycle.&nbsp; I can't fall into this same old trap, no matter how comforting it might be right now. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; I just found a house that has stained waferboard instead of paneling in the kitchen.&nbsp; Holy God.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Welcome to my price range.  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've got that song stuck in my head.  I heard it on the way in to work today, and I'd totally forgotten how much I love it.  Funny how that happens, really.  Songs will just drop off of playlists and out of mind.  Which is totally unfortunate [insert pretentious rant about music industry "ideas" about what constitutes punk rock, good vocalists, innovative ideas and the tragedy of derivative homogenization here] but there's a new radio station in town that plays older music.  It's called Sunny97.1, which almost made me vomit and run, but it turns out that I really like it.  Where else can I hear The Commodores, The Beach Boys, Elvis, Journey and The Bee Gees all in a row?  It's newer than the oldies station and more character-driven than the other station in town that plays stuff from the 80s.    I love that disco is back on the air.   urlLink Check it out.   I even like their goofy little sun logo.    It's a Clear Channel station, which makes me feel a little dirty inside.  But whatever.  ooh, the beach boys are on.  yay! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    polly in the sun&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       thinking about it. That level of meanness is just fucked.    Almost all of the people that I thought were my friends have completely shunned me since this whole stupid thing went down. One girl has contacted me since I left the boards. (Which was so cool - I like her a lot; she seems like a good person.)   I'm going to be so much better off without this crap in my life. There was some good there, I thought, but apparently it was all fool's gold anyway.   I told John about the army comment, and he said all the right things, of course. He's good at that, particularly during attempted reconciliations. The thing that makes me feel so pathetic is that this is what finally made me cry. John and I broke up after 4 1/2 years of trying, I lost nearly all of my online friends in one fell swoop, I'm broker than broke due to spending so much money on the fucking Austin trip (talk about wanting a do-over) and I'm crying over some chubby 34 year old drug addled freakass calling me a sullen homely fat girl.   I really do know that it's not just that. That was just the last thing - the thing that pushed me from stressed and annoyed to actively hurting. And I sincerely believe that I'm not the problem here. That level of mean (particularly in a grown woman) is just not of my doing. It's pathological.   I'm going to paint my toes now.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just discovered that I've been labeled one of "the founding members of the sullen homely fat girl army" due to the Austin fiasco. Apparently, the board folks are happy to be rid of me. Some of them, at any rate.   I can't say that I'm happy to know this, but it sure does clear up any lingering doubts about whether I should go back and see if anyone misses me.   This wasn't something I sought out; the other "founding member" tipped me off to it. And the comment was made here**, on LJ, which is kind of making me want to find some other place to keep my thoughts. Not like moving my stuff will protect me in any way; I just want distance is all.   I just don't understand that level of mean. Why on earth would you want to be that way?  And I'm not fucking homely. Or particularly sullen. (Now would not be the best time to prove that last one, tho.)  oh, and my period finally started. yay.   Now I'm going to go get busy running my army.   [**this was all originally on live journal.  i moved it because this shit just freaked me out and i wanted to get further away from the badness.] 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       John called last night to get my mom's number (again). While we were on the phone, he asked me to dinner. Well, not *to* dinner... He said that if I were feeling lonely over the weekend, he's got some steaks in the freezer and he'd be happy to bring the grill over so we could cook out. This is his normal routine for attempted reconciliations. In the past it's always worked on me, but really. We've tried to make this relationship work four times now, and we keep smacking up against the same old problems at around a year or a year and a half into it. Do I really want to invest another year with a man that talks at me and yet still won't take me to the movies? (Or even just go to the movies with me - I'll gladly pay, just go and don't bitch & whine about them not serving beer at the theater.)  I can't have dinner with him. Even if I thought it was worthwhile and not leading him on in some way, I'm legitimately busy - I've got a work picnic to go to, and I need to go see my mom at some point.   And I really wish I'd start my friggin period already. I haven't had sex since sometime in May, I think, but I just get so much comfort from that monthly reminder that I'm really not pregnant.  Also, lunch was fucking terrible. Do not eat the chicken salad from Great American Hero ever! again!  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I scored TWO purses on clearance tonight! yay! One is a super cute Roxy denim with white fur trim, and the other is a sun 'n' sand with a seashell print on it. It was only $3, and it's waterproofed canvas. The perfect size for sunscreen, shades and my cell phone for a trip to the beach! (Never mind that the nearest beach is 5 hours away - that makes no differnece, really.) It seems to be made pretty well, and it turns out that it was manufactured in Grand Prairie! Super cool, in that hometown way. And it has a shrinky dink tag. hee.   Now, I need to herd the cat off the balcony and take my tired ass to bed. oof.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink holy crap!   I guess Ronald didn't go over too well in Norway.  hee!  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       John called last night to talk real estate. He has no idea what he's doing, and it's both endearing and frustrating to talk to him about it. We talked about it all for over an hour. I don't know what to think about it all, really. The longer he looks for a house, the more he agrees with my ideas about what type of house and where to buy. Sometimes I just want to say to him 'okay... How about we just save ourselves some time and cut out the part where you don't believe me and have to find out on your own?'  But then, that would be a tad arrogant.  I turned in my loan paperwork at school last night. I have no idea what I'm doing. And I don't know what sort of insane troll logic the federal government uses to determine the Estimated Family Contribution, but mine is over 40% of my take home pay. Can that be right? Do they really expect me to spend more on tuition than I do on rent? Seriously?   I think that I'm going to use some of the loan money to buy a washing machine. I could make a damn good case for the usefulness of Maytag towards my studies. hee.  Lunch was a fancy ass BLT, and now I could use a nap.  Happy: my chocolate chip cookie only had one chip  Frustrated: parking has gone up to $200/year for my garage. I could park down the hill in the lot that is alway full and hope/pray that someone had to go home unexpectedly and only pay $80/year. But it's 1/4 mile away, and that is not so far. Except in August.  Expected: I have purse lust again. Nothing about any of my already owned purses is satisfying me. I'm making a trip to Ross tonight. Maybe I'll find something fabulous on clearance. I need girly, not utilitarian.   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It seems that, in the past two to three weeks, I've lost about 75% of my social network.   John and I got into a huge fight in early June - wait... fight? Not so much a fight. I told him that I had some concerns about the relationship and he freaked right the fuck out and had a giant hissy fit and I asked him to leave. Granted, he had just got off the phone with his good friend Mark, talking about how he was thinking that we might get MARRIED, so it was not great timing, I guess, but when *is* a good time? It was just stupid, and of course, he was drinking. I can't live the life of a beer widow. After the initial shitfest, it's at least been amicable. That's something I guess. I'm sad about it. We were together longer than any other relationship I've had. I felt more committed to him/us than anybody else, but it just got to where the painful parts were too much and I couldn't live with watching to see if he was going to be the happy cuddly drunk tonight or the sullen stomping angry drunk. One more beer or one off-hand comment made all the difference, and I am too goddamn fabulous for such misery. (And who isn't?)  I talked to him the weekend of July 4th, and he was going to a friend's house for a barbecue. He said that he thought he might drag his mom along, so that she could drive and he could drink. (Since he's got the breathalyzer on his truck & all.)  god.  The proof that I'm so very ok with the end of us is that while I'm sad, I'm not distraught. It sucks, but I'm ok with it.  Then, at the end of June I went to Austin to meet some fabulous ladies that I've known for years on a message board. Only, not all of them turned out to be so fabulous. Don't get me wrong - I had a great time, for the most part. I got to see an awesome punk show (MC5, baby. oh, yeah) and ate some great food and got to visit with some lovely people. There was also shopping. But, the woman that owns the message board turned out to be a total fucking loon. She'd invited us over to her house for a barbecue, but between the casual off-hand comments about the rats (big enough to steal baking potatoes), the roaches, the exploding can of peaches in the pantry, the sea of boxes in the house ("I'll clear a path to the bathroom, back door and kitchen!" "I put some boxes behind the couch, so the couch is a little closer to the shelves that are in the middle of the floor, but it really doesn't look bad at all!" [this on saturday night, ~2am. or, 13 hours before the bbq was to start.]) and the somewhat suicidal *funny* comments ("Do you ever worry about freak accidents?" [and my favorite, while on a gigantic overpass:] "sometimes I worry that I'm going to lose control and drive off the side of one of these things.") AND the torrential rains (did I mention that the bbq was to be outdoors?) (and not to mention the nasty, scary, i bet people get raped here bars that she took us to saturday night), I just couldn't make myself go.   One of the other ladies (that I thought I was fairly close to) had already decided that she wasn't going either, due to the extreme crazy and the overwhelming stench of dog & rotting fruit in the board-owner's car. There were four of us that were supposed to go, so instead of making four individual phone calls with varying degrees of lame guilt-ridden excuses, I asked my friend to call & cancel for us all. This was apparently the worst thing that I could have ever done, because it was perceived as a Grand Conspiracy by the crazy girl. (Maybe if I were crazy too, I would have foreseen such an outcome.) Crazy Girl then went to the board (that she owns; I'm not trying to make some sort of false claim to ownership or rightful place or whatever) before the rest of us had even left the hotel to bitch about what horrible human beings we all are. And, apparently, nearly everyone agrees with her. We should have been there, no matter fucking what, because we made a *committment* to be there and you do not SNUB people that way. And they'll all eat her brisket, anyday, and would have never treated her in such a horrible fashion.  ok, wtfever.  I'm not putting myself through such bullshit in the name of social conform, especially not on my fucking vacation. But maybe I really am just a bitch.  And then, the icing on the shitcake:  The four of us that were involved in The Big Snub had agreed to keep our reasons secret. There's no need to spread the love, in my opinion. Just because my fantasy has been shattered (I really, seriously, thought that the Crazy Girl was super cool and crazy in that fun way) is no need to go around ruining her image with everyone else. And she has a really high position with everyone on the boards - it's like she's been placed on 400 pedestals. So, I kept it to myself. I weathered the storm on the boards: the calls for explanation and apology and "make it right!". I apologized for hurting her feelings and said that I wished that I'd handled it in a better way. There was no conspiracy, I'm sorry you thought that, blah blah. None of that was good enough.  And in addition to THAT, it looks like one of the four of us has a complete lack of discretion. This fucking bullshit saga has made it on to Tomato Fucking Nation, and *then* it got posted back to the boards. Oh, sunshine and light. This resulted in another round of condemnation from my "friends", and a "full disclosure" of the "facts" from my 'friend', which soundly put the blame on me and one other girl. (How the fourth girl has gotten out of this largely blame free is kind of mysterious to me. She's super sweet, though, and was depending on the rest of us for rides, so maybe that's it.) Despite the fact that my 'friend' (oh, fuck it. Jen.) was the first one to declare that she was NOT GOING - on FRIDAY night, before any of us that were involved even knew about the filthy nasty car - now Jen says that she made a bad call based on information about the filthy nasty car from the rest of us. That she thought she 'knew' us, but she really should have never listened to us at all.   Which, again, wtfever.  btw - Crazy Girl says that rats, roaches and rotting fruit are FUNNY! She can't see how I can't see the FUNNY in that!   point proven, imo.  So, after over 2 1/2 years, 8000+ posts and being appointed to moderator, I'm done. I've been stripped of moderator duties (do me a favor, mate. gah.) and possibly banned from the boards completely. (I haven't been back to check on that.) And, really, good riddance. If they don't know me well enough to know that it had to be fucking BAD for me to skip out on something like this, then the hell with it.  I guess I'll try using this thing for a while, to get my net-venting fix. I couldn't keep it up before; there's only so much talking about myself that I can do, and I had the boards to use. School's starting up in a month or so, and I've got a bitch of a schedule, really. 4 nights a week and two campuses. Biology, no less. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I can't think of a witty title just now. When I first started this blog, I was overflowing with witty (wittier?) titles. Now, it's just  oh, fuck. Title. hm .  I have not devised a plan to get back to the BBQ place as of yet. Since I've got $7 to last the next 2 weeks, and I'm out of freebie coupons, I think that I might be out of luck until payday. Of course, all of this frenzied scheming (heh) might be for naught, if he was just making conversation with someone he recognized, instead of actually flirting. But he asked me what I was doing that weekend! That sounds flirtatious to me. Of course, I had to ask for clarification from Annette, as I am sometimes dim to these things. She felt it was flirtation as well. ("Well, he doesn't talk to  me  that way!" squeee!)  The level of giddiness that I have sustained due to this maybe-flirtation is somewhat astounding. But fun! hee.  And he is, of course, very cute. And he has a dreamy voice, with a beautiful Texas drawl.  I want to hear him growl my name. In the dark. Or maybe with the lights on.   squeee!    ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  ^^much needed dividing line.   ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  ^^just for safe measure  I got into an argument with John yesterday on the way to my grandparents house. Isn't that stupid? He started off talking about the canoe he's buying from his friend Jordan. This progressed to band talk, and the fact that Jordan refuses to play for Dawn (Bob's trash-ho new girlfriend.) to which I expressed a bit of surprise followed immediately by understanding.  No shit? Well, I can see his point.  John did not understand what I meant at all. (surprised? me neither.) He thinks that she really is interested in Bob. In it for the long haul. Sure, she is. Right now. I have no faith that it will last. She is one of those people whose pathology is to jump from thing to thing. Since February, she's held 5 jobs. None of them lasted more than a month, most of them were measured in days or weeks. And she (reportedly) works her ass off at all of them, only to be lied to, misled or just plain screwed over. She met Bob when she moved in with her boyfriend, Bob's loser pothead filthy pig roommate. She supported him, then got to know Bob, then broke up with LPFPR, moved out, lived wherever for about 2 weeks, moved back in -this time with Bob- had their first date, started planning the wedding, and there ya go.  I'm sure it will all work out fine, though. Never mind that he wants nothing to do with kids and she's always wanted a daughter most of all.  More than anything.   That is a minor detail to be worked out after the gala celebration of love in Cancun.  Anyway. We got in the fight because John thinks that they're both very serious about this thing due to the fact that they've both introduced the other to their families already. He does not introduce anyone to the family until he is very serious about them. It took me a year to meet his mom. Over three to meet his dad. He still won't do anything with my family. He skipped both thanksgiving and christmas last year. The year before that he went to Thanksgiving but not Christmas. He thinks that this sort of attitude towards family is normal, and when I told him that I did not think it was normal things just went downhill. He's got such wierd boundaries, and he just doesn't see it. Or, he knows it and doesn't want to admit it and gets defensive about it.  Or, maybe I'm just a judgemental bitch. Either way, it's an issue.     And Mike flirted with me!        In other news, I had a great time at my grandparent's house yesterday. I gave Johnny his WCC notepads, and talked politics with my grandfather for hours. It was lovely. Then, my grandmother regaled me with tales of her recent trip to Farmersville to visit my great-grandmother. All in all, it was a really nice visit. I haven't been over there in a few months.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Mike Anderson flirted with me at lunch today!  eeee!  He is super cute.  And successful.  And cute.   I could date a restaurateur.  Oh, yeah.  hee      
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I started reading  urlLink this book  last night.   I think that I'm going to have to buy it.  I'm just a little ways in, and there are so many parallels that it's both comforting and horrifying.  I don't want to know that his behaviors are something every alcoholic does.  I don't want to know that my behaviors are something everyone who loves an alcoholic does.  But at the same time, I'm hungry to know that somebody else understands this, has put themselves through this for love or obsession or codependency or whatever you'd prefer to call it.   I will say that I've never masturbated against his body after he passed out.  But, the only time he'd spoon with me was if he was too drunk to fuck and passed out mid-attempt.  And I'd lay there, with his limp hand on my hip and his warm fuzzy belly against the small of my back, listening to his soft beer-scented snores.  I would pick his limp hand up, hug it between my breasts, kiss it and them move it back to my hip, grateful for this short time of affection with no expectations.    After I knew, I wanted one thing in life: I wanted Jay to love me more than he loved booze.  I wanted him to look at his bottle of gin and say something like, "Oh, this bugs you?  It's gone."  Then toss it over his shoulder like a handful of salt.   Substitute  John  for  Jay  and  beer  for  gin , and there you have it.  That is all of my angst and tears and hopes about John boiled down to three sentences.   Right after John got his second DWI, back in February, he swore that he was done drinking forever.  He poured out all the beer he had left in the house and declared himself a former drinker.  (He's NOT an alcoholic, okay?)  About a week later, I decided that I'd like to have a ginger ale with dinner.  No vodka, no whiskey, just Canada Dry and a little ice.  And, I hesitated.  I didn't want to open the can, afraid that the mere sound of the can popping open would be enough to send him tumbling off the wagon.  I stood in front of the fridge, door open, can in hand, torn about what to do.  Finally I decided that it was just stupid to even think this.  If this was all it took to send him running back to beer like a cat to a can opener then it was really not my responsibility and I was having my damn ginger ale.   He was sitting about 10 feet from me when I opened the can.  His head whipped around so fast that I momentarily thought he was going to fall out of his chair.  His jaw dropped.  It took him a few seconds to get ahold of himself.  I watched all of this with sinking heart and quiet resignation.   Sure, babe.  You're not an alcoholic at all.   That weekend he bought a six pack.   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I hate my period.  I really do.  And now that I'm not having sex anymore, it's even worse.  Before, it was a glorious confirmation that I didn't need to cry and shake and make an appointment and lay awake at night meditating on potential lost and what might've been.  Now it's just pain and blood.   At least I don't have to have endless debate about the intricacies of modern birth control with John.  Or convince him that no, there really is  no point  in trying to assign blame because it was never 100% guaranteed.  (Wearing a condom would make it closer to 100%, you know.  And yes, I do know that you can't feel a damn thing with that on.)  And no, we really  can't  wait and make this appointment in a few weeks and there's no reason that me wanting to get this done  now  should make you suspicious.  If anything, I would think that me wanting to wait would make you suspicious, but I guess that's another matter.  Anyway.  Maybe I'll check out seasonale.   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been tired and achey the past two days.  I think this is because I just had a root canal and I'm also about to start my period.  Like, any minute now.  My neck and shoulders are just aching, though.  This sucks.   I just took my scary antibiotic so I can't lay down for another 30 minutes.  Believe me, I'm counting down.  oi.  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Literally.  I don't know if it's from my poor tooth or from the frightening antibiotic I'm taking.   The side effects for this damn thing are horrendous.  In fact, one of the websites says that because of its side effects, it's only used to treat serious infections.  Dreamy.   My two favorite side effects: diarrhea (sometimes fatal) and an unpleasant or metallic taste in the mouth.  Another good one is jaundice.  Pretty!  (I don't have that.)  I'm feeling lucky that I've got the metallic nastiness rather than the other.  In other news, it is raining!  This is the most bizarre and wonderful summer ever!  The rain has left the air so much cleaner - it's pretty out now.  :)  (Of course, all that funk that was in the air is now in the ground & water, but let's concentrate on the positive, ok?)  I watched an episode of Family Guy last night.  I must say that I don't really see the greatness.  Sure, I laughed a couple of times, but seriously.  I was offended or grossed out more times than I laughed.  Maybe this is another example of me just not getting the creepy factor.  Or whatever.  Or maybe I just don't think that fat jokes are funny.  Particularly when they're told four times in a row.   A lot of people talk about pushing the envelope or getting people out of their comfort zone.  Or some other trendy cliche regarding making people think in new and different ways.  I don't see why anyone needs to be pushed out of their comfort zone in such a manner.  A crucifix in a vat of urine doesn't make me think anything other than  ew, sick freak .   What's so bad about a comfort zone anyway?  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The pseudo barrista at the pseudo starbucks offered to give me Verona, which was brewing at that very moment.  He can pour and brew at the same time.  I have no idea what Verona is supposed to taste like, but I figured that fresh is better than whatever might be sitting in the thermoses around the other side of the counter and went for it.   Apparently,  Verona  stands for  remarkably bitter .  I put 9 (yes, NINE) packets of sugar in my medium coffee, and all of the fat free milk they had, plus a good amount of half and half.  Still, it's dark and has a bitter burnt aftertaste.  And, foretaste....  or whatever you call it when the tip of your tongue recoils in terror from the acrid bitterness of the coffee that you're forcing past it.   So, I went to the Starbucks website and did a search on  Verona .  Here's what it turned up:  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~    Caff Verona    Originally we blended this for a Seattle restaurant as the ideal after-dinner coffee. The crisp acidity of the medium-bodied Latin American coffees is grounded with the earthy flavor of the Indonesian coffees. A sweetness gilds the coffee's slight smokiness -creating a deep, rich dessert coffee.   ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~   Medium my ass.  Bold would probably give me whiplash.  I hate starbucks.  I really do.   And why the fuck does caffe have 2 Fs?   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My face is a normal size again.  (Well.  Except for a slight puffiness in my left eye, which I think was caused by a cat hair.  Not dental related.)  I'm exhausted.  My tooth has been re-reamed, and I'm going back next Tuesday for the filling and a cleaning.  This doesn't really make me happy, although I'm glad to know that it's halfway done.   My portion of the root canal charge was $152.  Which means that the whole thing cost something like $760.  I had to borrow $150 from John.  I'm more determined than ever to pay off my credit cards and build up a small savings.  This type of thing is only life.  It happens all the time.  (Not with my teeth, thank god.  But small crises abound.)  I need to be more prepared.  I need a cushion, so that I can bounce back from all these little  things  that come up.   The apartment complex finally sent out the renewal offer for my lease.  It's going up $15/mo starting in October, but they'll give me $100 off October's rent if I sign for longer than 10 months.  Not too shabby.  This will make my rent $526/mo, which is still very very cheap.  I can still enact my debt-reduction plan very easily at that rate.  (After, of course, I get out of the hole that I created for myself with the Austin debacle.)  Oh, crap I need some coffee.  I'm super tired.   The hole in the back of my tooth is driving me batshit.  It's got a temporary filling, but I can still feel the hole.  yeeck.  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i still feel poopy and i'm out of cereal.  feh.  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I do not feel well, and I look worse.  My face is huge.  On the left side anyway.  Luckily, my boss understands this.  And Robin said htat I could just stay out until I get the root canal, so that is good news.   I'm going to go lay down again.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       goddamn.  i look like half a chipmunk.  this kept waking me up last night.  i  so  should have asked for narcotics.   i feel like shit.  muzzy and painful.  last night, when i was able to sleep, i dreamt of a big bloody mess clamped between two panes of glass, like a vise.  it was part of me.   narcotics.  i should have asked for narcotics.  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       John offered to loan me the money to pay for the evaluation.  I started crying.   I'm going to call my insurance company tomorrow, and see if this is a normal thing.  I don't understand why the endodontist wants me to pay for the evaluation up front.  And the woman said something about filing the insurance for me, and then if I *wanted* to be reimbursed I would be.  wtf?  You think I'd rather you be paid twice?  YES I want to be reimbursed.  der.   I'm not even sure I heard her right.   Anyway.   This just seems weird, but I need to call the insurance company to check on the night guard anyway, so I'll just ask about this at the same time.  I'll need to know how soon they'll reimburse me anyway.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       fuckdiddly.  I have to have another root canal in the same tooth.  And I have to go to an endodontist to get this done, because the canal is so long.  Apparently, most dentists refer root canal re-dos to endodontists.  Most dentists refer canine tooth root canals to endodontists in the first place, because these teeth have long canals naturally.  I'm rather disgruntled over my previous dentist not doing this.   The reason that most dentists refer to specialists for this is because it takes  really really big files .  General practice dentists don't have files big enough to do this.  This terrifies me.  I also need to check into whether or not my dental insurance will cover a nighttime bite guard.  And I'm going back to the regular dentist on the 17th for a cleaning.   And the final insult: the endodontist wants me to pay the $90 evaluation fee up front, and then they'll file my insurance for me.  This is fanfuckingtastic, as I've got $88 to last the rest of the month.  I've already mailed off all my bills, all my credit cards are full, and I really don't want to hit my mom up for another loan.  I also can't let my goddamn canine tooth rot out.  All of this because of that goddamn wreck when I was 16.  Wear your seat belts, friends & neighbors.  (Also, do not blow out a tire, overcorrect and slam into a telephone pole 2 days after getting your drivers license.  But that probably goes without saying.)  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm about to leave work.  i'm going to stop by my apartment first, so i can brush my teeth, then i'm heading over to the dentist.  really.  i would just rather not.  i want this to magically go away.  ugh.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's not letting up.  I am a little freaked.  I don't want a root canal.   argle bargle.  I'm going to the dentist today, at 2:45.  Luckily, the dentist is on the corner of my street.  That's the nice thing about where I live.  I can get everything on the corner.  There's a dentist, a health club, a gas station, a public library,  a walgreens and a nice taco place.  All right there.  I usually drive, because it's about 5 or 6 blocks down, but I could walk.  If I was motivated enough.  Which I won't be today, because every step I take sends pain from my tooth up into my left nostril.  Sexy, innit?  I just went through my cell directory and deleted all the phone numbers from my ex-board friends.  That was rather satisfying.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I overslept, mostly due to my bizarre ass dreams and also due to the two ultracet that I took last night at 11 pee em to combat the ache in my tooth.  At about 7:45 I realized that I had to be at work at 8:30 today for a meeting, and laying naked in bed was really not going to help me accomplish that goal.    oh, fuck.   ^^ how so many of my mondays start off.   This ache in my tooth is kind of worrying me.  It's the tooth that I had to have a root canal on several years ago.  I hope that some new form of badness has not settled in here - it's one of my canines.  I like my canines.  They are large and nicely shaped.  (Just like me!)  I do not want any badness to happen to them.  Occasionally I'll get this type of ache back near a molar, and it usually turns out to be some blackberry seed or popcorn husk or some such that's worked its way up into my gum and set up malicious residence.  I'm hoping that's all this is.   I've flossed, but didn't see anything come out of there.   Yes, I really should floss more often.  I know this.  But it makes me gag and occassionaly puke for real, so I put it off.   It could also be that my teeth have shifted slightly and the tooth next to the canine is now touching the bottom teeth.   I don't really know why it's happening - I just know I wish it would stop.  It sucks.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>