<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        TAYLOR N FUNK PULL UP ON A SCOOTER W/A WAGON BEHIND W/PINK FLAMINGO STUFF ALL OVER IT!!!      &nbsp;  Taylor n Funk~HEY JENNA!!!! WANT A SNOW CONE?!?!?   JENNA~SURE!!!!!   TAYLOR N FUNK~GOT SOME ICE N A PLUG?!?!   LMAO!!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Omg today was great!! Lauren had her snowcone thingy at the pool so we were selling them out the girls bathroom window!!!Man i dont know what im going to do next year w/out my girl Lauren by my side!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well me n my so called "Friends" still are not talking n i still think they have a club n hate me but then i stoped n thought about it n there was somebody that always made me laugh and always made my day better when i talked to him!! And we are getting a lot closer now that i dont really talk to my other "friends" but that really doesnt matter when im w/him bc i dont think about my other friends!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       LAUREN FUNK OMG YOUR PARTY WAS THE BEST!!!!!!!!!! It was a F-ing (insider) BLAST!!!! Frrom Ding-Dong-Ditching like every one on you&nbsp;road and the other roads to SPOONING AND FORKING ppls houses in x~mas colors!!!! To putting that stuff all over the cars!!!! That junk in ur sisters mouth!! Chips in the freezer!! We got sooooo FREEKING SOAKED!!!!&nbsp; Out in the pouring rain for an hour and a half!!! When that man came out and was yelling at us!!!! HAHAHA great times with Hil Meg Manda Stehp&nbsp;Kris Lauren Jenna!!!!!! Got to do it again some time soon!!!    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Dont you Hate it when you friends plan things and they dont invite you to come along too But you find out about it anyway! Well I do and my friends are! So im sitting here all by my self typing this bc i have nothing else better to do!! Some Times I think all my friends have a club n they all hate me!!!     
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well Today my mom made me go n run at K.R for my Cross Country stuff!! The times got changed so it was me n 2 other girls we ran for like 15 mins n then lifted!!! But i got to see my Good Friend DUSTIN.F!!! lol &nbsp;What Fun!!! BUT I DID FIND A DOLLAR!!!!!! lol    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well we had yet another swim meet tonight!!! WE ONLY LOST BY AROUND 100!!!!! lol thats good for us bc we never win!!! I DID MY I.M(all four Fly,Back,Brest,Free) AND DIDNT DIE!!!!! AND I GOT 2 place!!!!!!! LOL  GO MITCHELL HILLS OOBOOS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well we had this swim team funraiser thingy and It sarted out really good!!!! I was talking to one of my guy friends and Jordann was hanging aound me n then one of her "Friends" come and she like just left me to hang w/her! Then she was hanging all over these guys that were a tid bit too young for her and hanging all over them and every one was like Taylor go tell her to stop flirting she has a b/f so being the good friend I am i went n told her and she got all pissed off and went off on me!! LOTS OF BAD WORDS WERE SAID THAT NIGHT!!!  THEN SHE WAS TRYING TO TALK SHIT BOUT ME TO THE GUYS SHE WAS HANGING W/AND THEY WERE ALL LIKE I DONT KNOW WHAT UR TALKING BOUT TAYLORS HOT!! LMAO!!  And then she though i took her danm bag n i went off on her and her mom was standing right next to me!! N now we are not talking!!   BUT JENNA ME LAUREN N AMANDA WERE IN THE VAN MAKING THE ALAMR GO OFF!!! SOME FUNNY SHIT RIGHT THERE!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       MY SISTER HAD HER BABY TODAY!!!!   Baby n Mom are doing great n my   sister n new baby are comming   home on Friday when she gets   ou  t of the hos. TO COME N SEE ME!!!!!!! lol Baby was 7lbs and 12 oz and is 21 inchs long!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well today when I went to Cross Country I didnt have all my papers so some   really kool Junior gave me a ride back to my house so I could get some papers   filled out and I was like I dont really know u but sure you can take me home!!   hahaha Cheat 2 wish u were there!! ALL MY 8TH GRADE C.C RUNNERS GIVE   THE NEW 7TH GRADERS HELL FOR ME!!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Omg I  got back on line today and all my 7th grade C.C Buddies imed me and were all like OMG TAYLOR WE MISSED YOU TODAY AT CROSS COUNTRY!!!   And It just made my day and almost made me cry!! I luv ya guys and have a blast this year even tho im not running w/ya!! But I will be at some of ur meets   so run up and give my a hug if ya see me!!! OMG No one knows how much I miss ya guys!!! And It was great to hear from ya!! Man Im missing the old days   when my friends from my grade cared about me n talked to me!!! Because Now A Days some of my good friends are not really talking to me and like never tell   me anything and I miss the days when they did tell me stuff and did talk to me like every day!! But Im SUPER glad im making my NEW UPPER CLASS MAN   FRIEDNS!!!! gots to love My New Cross Country Buddies!! But No one will ever replace the old memories of my good old Running Buddies!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well Cross Country started for real today but i didnt go bc i had to go to the doc. to get my physical!! But I heard that it was kinda hard but they only ran 3   miles so its not like im behind bc i ran that today when i got home!! Cant believe school starts in like 2 n a half weeks!!! Whoo Hoo get to see all my   friends again!! But going to miss all the good friends and all the good time i have/ha w/all my 8th grade friends!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I feel like I don't even know one of my friends anymore! I feel like they don't care what im doin or if they even talk to me..and its really sad cuz like two months ago I couldn't go a day w/o talking to them! Things have changed completely.. im sooo bummed!!! I mean they are off doing god knows what and going out w/god knows who and man "it" has just completely changed!!!   BUT IM SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO GLAD I HAVE MY OTHER FRIENDS THAT ARE MAKING ME LAUGH AND MAKING MY SUMMER JUST THE BEST!!! LIKE Lauren~ Girl dont know what id do this summer w/out ya!! I luv yas n im going to miss ya this year!!!   Brent~ Man u make me laugh!! From just iming me to say Hi or calling my cell for no reason!!   and Justin thanks for everything ya do to make my summer fun!!   Rach~Fun times on the scooters man!! Yours is broke all the time!! Ur handle Bars!! NO X~MAN FOR U N KELLY!! LMAO insider!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        ToP 10 ReAsOnS tO dAtE a ~SwImMeR~ 1. They like it wet. 2. They dive right in . 3. Love going fast. 4. Are use to wearing next to nothing in front a group of people. 5. Brestroke is favorite to many. 6. Others like it on their back. 7. They are experts at putting on rubber and can do it fast. 8. They know how to push it and work under HARD conditions. 9. They are firm believers that practice will make you better and will at any time day or night. 10. Are use to doing things again and again till you can't go on any longer."      ~!~!*~People dont swim because its fun. Ask any swimmer, most of them hate it, but they couldnt imagine their life with out it. Its part of them, its something they live for. They live for the 5 a.m practices, pasta partys, cheers, long bus rides, invitationals, countless swim caps, chlorine, and coaches you hate but appreciate later. They live for the way it feels when you beat the person next to you by a tenth of a second and you know those 2 extra laps you did in practice were worth it. You live for the way you jump every time you hear a buzzer, or the way you scream whenever you hear the gun on the 500 even though you hear it every time. You live for the way you celebrate when you get to do a set with fins. You live for the way you become a family with your team, and noone understands what happens within that pool or locker room but you. You live for the countless songs you sing in your head when your swimming those laps. You live for the people who scream at you while your swimming even though all you hear is BLAH BLAH BLAH. You live for the competition, you live for the friends, you live for the practice, you live for the pain, its a part of you. Your a swimmer    ~!~!Dont be discouraged by other swimmers because deep down their just as afraid as you are!!      ~!~!you know you're a swimmer when you can leave the wall in the middle of a sentence, come back to the wall, and pick up the conversation right where you left off.    ~!~!dedication is putting on a swim suit 4 sizes too small    ~!~!Coming to school in the morning with cholorine- wet hair is the trademark of a true athlete    ~!~!only a swimmer can describe to you the feeling of diving into a pool at 5 am, slamming into the touchpad at a meet, the stench of moldy, chlorinated swimsuits, the agony of hitting your head on the wall in a backstroke race, the thrill of success and the heartbreak of one hundreth of a second"       ~!~!You know you are a real swimmer when you feel more comfortable in a suit then real clothing!~    ~!~!You know you are a swimmer when you live on gatorade, swedish fish and gold fish    ~!~!to truly understand a swimmer and their life, you gotta expericence the pain of lossing a race by a hand touch, the despair of missing a state cut off by .01 seconds, the feeling of diving into a pool at 6 in the morning, how wonderful it feels when you are in the water, the feeling you get when you look up at everyone around you and see how proud they are of you, and knowing what it is like to be doing something you truly love    ~!~!I've Been Told Swimming Is A Wimp Sport But I Don't See It...We Don't Get Time Outs In The Middle Of A Race...We Cant Stop And Catch Our Breath...We Cant Ask For A Substitution...We Cant Roll Over And Just Lie There...Still Think Its A Wimp Sport    ~!~!It is better to have swam and lost, than to have ever been a cheerleader    ~!~!true athletes dont wear shoes but were caps and goggle      ~!~!$$*~Friend: Can i see ur house?Swimmer: Sure come this way!Friend: U live in a swim pool??Swimmer:Yup! I spend more time her then i do at my so called "house"! Its the best place in teh world and i wouldnt trade it for anything!    ~*You say your "Born 2 cheer" i say thats too bad Because i say im "Born 2 swim" and thats something to be Proud of!       ~!~!*A friend asked me to skip a swim practice to shop at the mall. i said no way! Then she offered to buy me a pack of power bars and gatorade. i had to consider that. but nope, not goin    ~!~!*~Our BOyfreinds know better not to tell us to choice between Swimmin and them b-c it would be good-bye guys.Hello Swimmin.      10 REASON WHY IM A BACKSTROKER 1)I can breathe better doing backstroke then any other stroke 2)I can see my team mates cheering for me 3)When im doing my start i dont feel like im going to fall 4)In a race Im forced to remember things like:how many strokes to finish and to turn 5)I'm not only one type of swimmer but three! a sprinter -50bk ,a mid-distance-100bk, and a distance swimmer -200bk 6)Backstroke is the only stroke you do on your back 7)I have an original start 8)In a race I can look up and see my splits on the clock/timer 9) backstrokers are known for their finish's 10)the chances of my goggles leaking Or falling off are slimmer, swimming backstroke then any other stroke! Backstroke is KICK ASS!"      ToP 10 ReAsOnS tO dAtE a ~SwImMeR~ 1. They like it wet. 2. They dive right in . 3. Love going fast. 4. Are use to wearing next to nothing in front a group of people. 5. Brestroke is favorite to many. 6. Others like it on their back. 7. They are experts at putting on rubber and can do it fast. 8. They know how to push it and work under HARD conditions. 9. They are firm believers that practice will make you better and will at any time day or night. 10. Are use to doing things again and again till you can't go on any longer."      You know you're a swimmer when... 1. You're always away on weekends 2. You have no social life!! 3. You have your own separate droor for all of your swim shirts! 4. Your hair turns green 5. You dont have time for other sports 6. Your homework gets wet from being in your swim bag! 7. You have enough goggles and caps for the whole swim team! 8. It's normal when you wear more than 1 suit! 9. You cant wait for school to end because you want to see all of your swim buds at practice!!! 10. Your walls are covered in swimming stuff 11. Guys in tight suits are ok! (only in this sport) 12. Half your wardrobe is SWIMMING related 13. You get to travel to some of the coolest cities... but for swimming 14. It's normal going to school smelling like chlorine 15. Your main diet is pasta, gatorade, and power bars. 16. You cant tell you're sweating (which is ok!) 17. You have a million psyche CD's for swimming 18. The worst thing to hear someone say is, "this set will be FUN!" 19. You're dedicated for the sport you love!!!!        ~!~!after all the hard practices we would stand in the team room and say how we couldn't wait for the season to be over. well.. it's over now and i couldn't miss it more    ~!~!You know your a swimmer when ...You see nothing wrong in saying, "I'll show you my breast, if you will show me your fly.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well now that Swim Team   is   over ='( I didnt have to get up at 9!! But My   mom made me get up n go run for Cross Country!!!   My Girly Lauren is out of town in penn. n wont be back till wed!!   lol man now i have to find some one to do all the stupid shit Funk n I do every day!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well on Friday I went   running at K.R and   we ran 4 miles and   only had to walk   like 20 steps!!!   lol yea for Taylor!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well we had the big city meet thingy today!! O what fun!! I had to get up at 6:30 n I was at the YMCA for like 8   LONG   HOURS!! But it was fun!! I had an   ok meet nothing to bad!! 9th over all in my back!!! lol who would have though me 9th out of all them damn girls!! lol AND MY TEAM WON PER.CAPATIA!!!  or how ever u spell it!! Its when you take the number of swimmers your team has(we only had 16!!) and times it by the number of points you built up thought    out the whole meet!!! I GOT JK TO SIGN SOME HEAT   SHEET THINGY!!!! lol just incase u dont know him he went to the  trils for the 2004 OLYMPICS !!!! YEA FOR ME!!! I came home and framed it!!! lmao!! and he   signed some blow up pink flamingo we call our mascot!!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>